{
  "name": "JPDB 80K",
  "cards": [
    {
      "question": "鉄道橋",
      "answer": "てつどうきょう",
      "meaning": "railroad bridge"
    },
    {
      "question": "給水車",
      "answer": "きゅうすいしゃ",
      "meaning": "water wagon, water tender"
    },
    {
      "question": "紀元節",
      "answer": "きげんせつ",
      "meaning": "Empire Day (February 11th; national holiday held from 1872 to 1948)"
    },
    {
      "question": "尊貴",
      "answer": "そんき",
      "meaning": "noble (person)"
    },
    {
      "question": "高弾性",
      "answer": "こうだんせい",
      "meaning": "high elasticity"
    },
    {
      "question": "出来物",
      "answer": "できもの,できぶつ,でけもの",
      "meaning": "tumour, tumor, growth, boil, ulcer, abscess, rash, pimple, able man, fine man"
    },
    {
      "question": "渥美半島",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "親疎",
      "answer": "しんそ",
      "meaning": "degree of intimacy"
    },
    {
      "question": "潜水夫",
      "answer": "せんすいふ",
      "meaning": "diver"
    },
    {
      "question": "恋いる",
      "answer": "こいる",
      "meaning": "to love"
    },
    {
      "question": "有職故実",
      "answer": "ゆうそくこじつ",
      "meaning": "studies in usages and practices of the ancient court and military households"
    },
    {
      "question": "視差",
      "answer": "しさ",
      "meaning": "parallax"
    },
    {
      "question": "仙翁",
      "answer": "せんのう",
      "meaning": "lychnis (Lychnis senno)"
    },
    {
      "question": "水生昆虫",
      "answer": "すいせいこんちゅう",
      "meaning": "aquatic insect"
    },
    {
      "question": "讒訴",
      "answer": "ざんそ",
      "meaning": "false charges, slander"
    },
    {
      "question": "帳票",
      "answer": "ちょうひょう",
      "meaning": "report, form"
    },
    {
      "question": "陸中",
      "answer": "りくちゅう",
      "meaning": "Rikuchū (former province located in present-day Iwate Prefecture and parts of Akita Prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "白靴",
      "answer": "しろぐつ",
      "meaning": "white shoes (for use during the summer)"
    },
    {
      "question": "電圧計",
      "answer": "でんあつけい",
      "meaning": "voltmeter"
    },
    {
      "question": "俟つ",
      "answer": "まつ",
      "meaning": "to await, to look forward to, to anticipate, to depend on, to need"
    },
    {
      "question": "現在価値",
      "answer": "げんざいかち",
      "meaning": "present value"
    },
    {
      "question": "理学療法",
      "answer": "りがくりょうほう",
      "meaning": "physiotherapy, physical therapy"
    },
    {
      "question": "約分",
      "answer": "やくぶん",
      "meaning": "reduction of a fraction (to lowest terms)"
    },
    {
      "question": "故事来歴",
      "answer": "こじらいれき",
      "meaning": "origin and history, particulars"
    },
    {
      "question": "裄",
      "answer": "ゆき",
      "meaning": "distance from the seam in the back of a kimono to the end of the sleeve"
    },
    {
      "question": "零落れる",
      "answer": "おちぶれる",
      "meaning": "to be ruined (reduced to poverty), to fall low, to go under, to come to ruin"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉋屑",
      "answer": "かんなくず",
      "meaning": "wood shavings"
    },
    {
      "question": "俠気",
      "answer": "おとこぎ,きょうき",
      "meaning": "chivalrous spirit, chivalry"
    },
    {
      "question": "旧正月",
      "answer": "きゅうしょうがつ",
      "meaning": "lunar New Year (esp. the Chinese New Year)"
    },
    {
      "question": "米櫃",
      "answer": "こめびつ",
      "meaning": "rice bin, breadwinner"
    },
    {
      "question": "酒太り",
      "answer": "さけぶとり",
      "meaning": "beer belly"
    },
    {
      "question": "縄文土器",
      "answer": "じょうもんどき",
      "meaning": "straw rope-patterned ancient Japanese pottery"
    },
    {
      "question": "ペン皿",
      "answer": "ペンざら",
      "meaning": "pen tray"
    },
    {
      "question": "趣意",
      "answer": "しゅい",
      "meaning": "main meaning, opinion, idea, aim, motive, gist, meaning"
    },
    {
      "question": "漏刻",
      "answer": "ろうこく",
      "meaning": "water clock"
    },
    {
      "question": "引っ攫う",
      "answer": "ひっさらう",
      "meaning": "to kidnap, to abduct, to snatch, to carry people away, to take by force"
    },
    {
      "question": "第一審",
      "answer": "だいいっしん",
      "meaning": "first hearing"
    },
    {
      "question": "郵貯",
      "answer": "ゆうちょ",
      "meaning": "postal (post-office) savings (deposit)"
    },
    {
      "question": "火取蛾",
      "answer": "ひとりが",
      "meaning": "garden tiger moth (Arctia caja)"
    },
    {
      "question": "作出",
      "answer": "さくしゅつ",
      "meaning": "new creation, new invention, new production, new breed"
    },
    {
      "question": "下肥",
      "answer": "しもごえ",
      "meaning": "manure, night soil"
    },
    {
      "question": "希塩酸",
      "answer": "きえんさん",
      "meaning": "dilute hydrochloric acid"
    },
    {
      "question": "雲集",
      "answer": "うんしゅう",
      "meaning": "swarm, throng"
    },
    {
      "question": "然々",
      "answer": "しかじか,ささ",
      "meaning": "such and such"
    },
    {
      "question": "気胞",
      "answer": "きほう",
      "meaning": "bladder, vesicle"
    },
    {
      "question": "着船",
      "answer": "ちゃくせん",
      "meaning": "arrival of a ship, ship which has arrived"
    },
    {
      "question": "半ドア",
      "answer": "はんドア",
      "meaning": "half-opened door (car door, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "地権者",
      "answer": "ちけんしゃ",
      "meaning": "land owner, leaseholder"
    },
    {
      "question": "後屈",
      "answer": "こうくつ",
      "meaning": "retroflexion"
    },
    {
      "question": "青焼き",
      "answer": "あおやき",
      "meaning": "blueprint, cyanotype"
    },
    {
      "question": "遼遠",
      "answer": "りょうえん",
      "meaning": "remote, far off"
    },
    {
      "question": "搗き立て",
      "answer": "つきたて",
      "meaning": "freshly pounded (rice cake)"
    },
    {
      "question": "鮠",
      "answer": "はや,はえ,はい",
      "meaning": "minnow, shinner"
    },
    {
      "question": "希硫酸",
      "answer": "きりゅうさん",
      "meaning": "dilute sulfuric acid, dilute sulphuric acid"
    },
    {
      "question": "石灰化",
      "answer": "せっかいか",
      "meaning": "calcification"
    },
    {
      "question": "遊歴",
      "answer": "ゆうれき",
      "meaning": "tour"
    },
    {
      "question": "神楽月",
      "answer": "かぐらづき",
      "meaning": "eleventh lunar month"
    },
    {
      "question": "石抱き",
      "answer": "いしだき",
      "meaning": "form of torture in which the victim kneels on triangular wedges and stone slabs are placed on their"
    },
    {
      "question": "討っ手",
      "answer": "うって",
      "meaning": "pursue and attack (a criminal)"
    },
    {
      "question": "液化ガス",
      "answer": "えきかガス",
      "meaning": "liquefied gas, liquid gas"
    },
    {
      "question": "回り灯籠",
      "answer": "まわりどうろう",
      "meaning": "revolving lantern"
    },
    {
      "question": "駅手",
      "answer": "えきしゅ",
      "meaning": "station worker"
    },
    {
      "question": "撰する",
      "answer": "せんする,ぜんする",
      "meaning": "to write (prose, etc.), to compile (an anthology)"
    },
    {
      "question": "雨止み",
      "answer": "あまやみ",
      "meaning": "break in the rain, waiting for a break in the rain"
    },
    {
      "question": "石墨",
      "answer": "せきぼく",
      "meaning": "graphite, black lead"
    },
    {
      "question": "受難曲",
      "answer": "じゅなんきょく",
      "meaning": "Passion music"
    },
    {
      "question": "平和憲法",
      "answer": "へいわけんぽう",
      "meaning": "pacifist constitution (often applied to the Japanese constitution), constitution which outlaws use o"
    },
    {
      "question": "機屋",
      "answer": "はたや",
      "meaning": "weaver"
    },
    {
      "question": "押花",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "単発機",
      "answer": "たんぱつき",
      "meaning": "single-engine plane"
    },
    {
      "question": "御史台",
      "answer": "ぎょしだい",
      "meaning": "Censorate (Later Han and Song-dynasty surveillance agency)"
    },
    {
      "question": "入れ札",
      "answer": "いれふだ",
      "meaning": "bid, tender"
    },
    {
      "question": "後来",
      "answer": "こうらい",
      "meaning": "after this, from now on, henceforth, henceforward, coming late, someone coming late"
    },
    {
      "question": "明徳",
      "answer": "めいとく",
      "meaning": "virtue, Meitoku era (of the Northern Court) (1390.3.26-1392.10.5), Meitoku era (of reunified Japan)"
    },
    {
      "question": "万万歳",
      "answer": "ばんばんざい",
      "meaning": "matter for great congratulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "定本",
      "answer": "ていほん",
      "meaning": "revised edition (of a book or manuscript), authoritative edition, standard edition, edition incorpor"
    },
    {
      "question": "分国法",
      "answer": "ぶんこくほう",
      "meaning": "laws established by daimyo applicable only in their own domain (during the Warring States period)"
    },
    {
      "question": "寓居",
      "answer": "ぐうきょ",
      "meaning": "temporary abode, staying on a temporary basis"
    },
    {
      "question": "発問",
      "answer": "はつもん",
      "meaning": "asking or putting a question, questioning"
    },
    {
      "question": "印僑",
      "answer": "いんきょう",
      "meaning": "Indian working abroad, overseas Indian"
    },
    {
      "question": "同夜",
      "answer": "どうや",
      "meaning": "the same night, that night"
    },
    {
      "question": "甲矢",
      "answer": "はや",
      "meaning": "arrow with feathers that curve to the left (the first of two arrows to be fired)"
    },
    {
      "question": "地方分権",
      "answer": "ちほうぶんけん",
      "meaning": "decentralization of power, decentralisation of power"
    },
    {
      "question": "消息通",
      "answer": "しょうそくつう",
      "meaning": "well-informed person, insider"
    },
    {
      "question": "腰付き",
      "answer": "こしつき",
      "meaning": "gait, posture"
    },
    {
      "question": "遊蕩児",
      "answer": "ゆうとうじ",
      "meaning": "debauched person"
    },
    {
      "question": "漸進的",
      "answer": "ぜんしんてき",
      "meaning": "gradual"
    },
    {
      "question": "新字",
      "answer": "しんじ",
      "meaning": "newly created character, newly introduced (kanji) character (in a textbook)"
    },
    {
      "question": "元結",
      "answer": "もとゆい,もとい,もっとい",
      "meaning": "(paper) cord for tying the hair"
    },
    {
      "question": "蜂雀",
      "answer": "はちすずめ",
      "meaning": "hummingbird (Trochilidae family)"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒闇天",
      "answer": "こくあんてん",
      "meaning": "Kalaratri (Deva)"
    },
    {
      "question": "本品",
      "answer": "ほんぴん",
      "meaning": "this product, this item, this article"
    },
    {
      "question": "分骨",
      "answer": "ぶんこつ",
      "meaning": "part of a person's ashes"
    },
    {
      "question": "織り模様",
      "answer": "おりもよう",
      "meaning": "woven pattern or design"
    },
    {
      "question": "免疫不全",
      "answer": "めんえきふぜん",
      "meaning": "immunodeficiency"
    },
    {
      "question": "凝脂",
      "answer": "ぎょうし",
      "meaning": "solidified oil"
    },
    {
      "question": "葉影",
      "answer": "はかげ",
      "meaning": "shadow of a leaf or tree"
    },
    {
      "question": "休らう",
      "answer": "やすらう",
      "meaning": "to rest, to relax"
    },
    {
      "question": "生殖腺",
      "answer": "せいしょくせん",
      "meaning": "gonad"
    },
    {
      "question": "詩才",
      "answer": "しさい",
      "meaning": "talent for poetry, poetic genius"
    },
    {
      "question": "歌口",
      "answer": "うたぐち",
      "meaning": "flute mouthpiece, poetic style"
    },
    {
      "question": "絞り滓",
      "answer": "しぼりかす",
      "meaning": "strained lees (e.g. sake, tofu), draff"
    },
    {
      "question": "怠業",
      "answer": "たいぎょう",
      "meaning": "sabotage, slow-down tactics"
    },
    {
      "question": "三三五五",
      "answer": "さんさんごご",
      "meaning": "in groups of twos and threes, in small groups"
    },
    {
      "question": "硬骨漢",
      "answer": "こうこつかん",
      "meaning": "man of principle"
    },
    {
      "question": "本アカ",
      "answer": "ほんアカ",
      "meaning": "main account (on social media, etc.), principal account, real-name account"
    },
    {
      "question": "男顔",
      "answer": "おとこがお",
      "meaning": "masculine face (on a woman)"
    },
    {
      "question": "袴着",
      "answer": "はかまぎ",
      "meaning": "ceremony fitting child with a hakama"
    },
    {
      "question": "同盟条約",
      "answer": "どうめいじょうやく",
      "meaning": "treaty of alliance"
    },
    {
      "question": "春雷",
      "answer": "しゅんらい",
      "meaning": "spring thunder"
    },
    {
      "question": "忠君",
      "answer": "ちゅうくん",
      "meaning": "loyalty to one's ruler"
    },
    {
      "question": "馬陸",
      "answer": "やすで",
      "meaning": "millipede"
    },
    {
      "question": "含水",
      "answer": "がんすい",
      "meaning": "hydrated, hydrous"
    },
    {
      "question": "上程",
      "answer": "じょうてい",
      "meaning": "introducing (a bill), presentation, departure on a journey"
    },
    {
      "question": "公衆道徳",
      "answer": "こうしゅうどうとく",
      "meaning": "public morals"
    },
    {
      "question": "不入り",
      "answer": "ふいり",
      "meaning": "small attendance, poor house"
    },
    {
      "question": "初穂料",
      "answer": "はつほりょう",
      "meaning": "ceremony fee, money dedicated to the gods when participating in a ceremony"
    },
    {
      "question": "酸度",
      "answer": "さんど",
      "meaning": "acidity"
    },
    {
      "question": "森林帯",
      "answer": "しんりんたい",
      "meaning": "forest zone"
    },
    {
      "question": "措置入院",
      "answer": "そちにゅういん",
      "meaning": "involuntary admission (commitment) (to a mental hospital)"
    },
    {
      "question": "寛正",
      "answer": "かんしょう",
      "meaning": "Kanshō era (1460.12.21-1466.2.28)"
    },
    {
      "question": "縞馬",
      "answer": "しまうま",
      "meaning": "zebra"
    },
    {
      "question": "映画人",
      "answer": "えいがじん",
      "meaning": "cineast, someone who works in the movie industry"
    },
    {
      "question": "未然形",
      "answer": "みぜんけい",
      "meaning": "nai stem (of a Japanese verb), irrealis form, imperfective form"
    },
    {
      "question": "対子",
      "answer": "トイツ",
      "meaning": "pair, eyes"
    },
    {
      "question": "必着",
      "answer": "ひっちゃく",
      "meaning": "must arrive, must be received"
    },
    {
      "question": "鼠花火",
      "answer": "ねずみはなび",
      "meaning": "Catherine wheel (firework), pinwheel"
    },
    {
      "question": "四苦",
      "answer": "しく",
      "meaning": "the four kinds of suffering (birth, old age, disease, death)"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤花",
      "answer": "あかばな",
      "meaning": "willowherb (Epilobium pyrricholophum), safflower red, kimono color combination (crimson outside, blu"
    },
    {
      "question": "副審",
      "answer": "ふくしん",
      "meaning": "assistant umpire, assistant referee"
    },
    {
      "question": "当籤",
      "answer": "とうせん",
      "meaning": "winning (in a lottery, raffle, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "強剛",
      "answer": "きょうごう",
      "meaning": "overwhelming strength, extremely strong person, powerhouse, very strong player, very strong team"
    },
    {
      "question": "特殊詐欺",
      "answer": "とくしゅさぎ",
      "meaning": "variant of bank-transfer fraud"
    },
    {
      "question": "胴中",
      "answer": "どうなか",
      "meaning": "trunk, torso, second player (out of three), player that goes after the dealer"
    },
    {
      "question": "下期",
      "answer": "しもき",
      "meaning": "second half of the (fiscal) year"
    },
    {
      "question": "錦旗",
      "answer": "きんき",
      "meaning": "pennant, gold-brocade flag"
    },
    {
      "question": "風俗営業",
      "answer": "ふうぞくえいぎょう",
      "meaning": "businesses offering food and entertainment, cabaret, club, gambling and restaurant businesses, sex i"
    },
    {
      "question": "素絹",
      "answer": "そけん",
      "meaning": "coarse silk"
    },
    {
      "question": "素戔嗚尊",
      "answer": "すさのおのみこと",
      "meaning": "Susanoo-no-Mikoto (deity, younger brother to Amaterasu)"
    },
    {
      "question": "聴取者",
      "answer": "ちょうしゅしゃ",
      "meaning": "radio listener"
    },
    {
      "question": "入牢",
      "answer": "にゅうろう",
      "meaning": "imprisonment"
    },
    {
      "question": "財閥解体",
      "answer": "ざいばつかいたい",
      "meaning": "dissolution of zaibatsu"
    },
    {
      "question": "分置",
      "answer": "ぶんち",
      "meaning": "division (of an organization), branch"
    },
    {
      "question": "明暦",
      "answer": "めいれき",
      "meaning": "Meireki era (1655.4.13-1658.7.23)"
    },
    {
      "question": "千鳥格子",
      "answer": "ちどりごうし",
      "meaning": "hound's-tooth check"
    },
    {
      "question": "忘年",
      "answer": "ぼうねん",
      "meaning": "forgetting the hardships of the old year, forgetting one another's age difference"
    },
    {
      "question": "八万四千",
      "answer": "はちまんよんせん,はちまんしせん",
      "meaning": "84,000, many"
    },
    {
      "question": "築造",
      "answer": "ちくぞう",
      "meaning": "construction, building"
    },
    {
      "question": "言葉付き",
      "answer": "ことばつき",
      "meaning": "speech, expression, wording, language"
    },
    {
      "question": "触法",
      "answer": "しょくほう",
      "meaning": "infringement of the law"
    },
    {
      "question": "杉板",
      "answer": "すぎいた",
      "meaning": "cedar board"
    },
    {
      "question": "筑波大学",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "突立",
      "answer": "とったつ",
      "meaning": "stand straight up"
    },
    {
      "question": "篤信",
      "answer": "とくしん",
      "meaning": "devoutness, devotion"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛石",
      "answer": "とびいし",
      "meaning": "stepping stones, stone skipping, ducks and drakes"
    },
    {
      "question": "朔望",
      "answer": "さくぼう",
      "meaning": "first and fifteenth days of the lunar month (corresponding to new moon and full moon)"
    },
    {
      "question": "分遣",
      "answer": "ぶんけん",
      "meaning": "detachment, detail"
    },
    {
      "question": "御酌",
      "answer": "おしゃく",
      "meaning": "pouring alcohol, person pouring alcohol for guests or customers (typically a woman), (apprentice) ge"
    },
    {
      "question": "躁病",
      "answer": "そうびょう",
      "meaning": "mania"
    },
    {
      "question": "住する",
      "answer": "じゅうする",
      "meaning": "to live, to reside, to inhabit"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉱水",
      "answer": "こうすい",
      "meaning": "mineral water"
    },
    {
      "question": "鮨屋",
      "answer": "すしや",
      "meaning": "sushi shop, sushi restaurant, sushi bar"
    },
    {
      "question": "体落とし",
      "answer": "たいおとし",
      "meaning": "body drop (judo), body throw"
    },
    {
      "question": "堕獄",
      "answer": "だごく",
      "meaning": "going to hell, falling into hell"
    },
    {
      "question": "標準価格",
      "answer": "ひょうじゅんかかく",
      "meaning": "standard price"
    },
    {
      "question": "下げ札",
      "answer": "さげふだ",
      "meaning": "tag, label"
    },
    {
      "question": "ラ音",
      "answer": "ラおん",
      "meaning": "rale, rales"
    },
    {
      "question": "急伸",
      "answer": "きゅうしん",
      "meaning": "sudden rise (esp. of stock prices), jump"
    },
    {
      "question": "墨書き",
      "answer": "すみがき",
      "meaning": "inking the outlines of a picture"
    },
    {
      "question": "極熱",
      "answer": "ごくねつ,ごくねち,ごくあつ",
      "meaning": "extreme heat, extremely hot (esp. of sake)"
    },
    {
      "question": "井底",
      "answer": "せいてい",
      "meaning": "well bottom, narrow place"
    },
    {
      "question": "文安",
      "answer": "ぶんあん,ぶんなん",
      "meaning": "Bun'an era (1444.2.5-1449.7.28), Bunnan era"
    },
    {
      "question": "筋腫",
      "answer": "きんしゅ",
      "meaning": "myoma"
    },
    {
      "question": "下半",
      "answer": "かはん",
      "meaning": "lower half"
    },
    {
      "question": "戯れ歌",
      "answer": "ざれうた",
      "meaning": "funny song, comic song, limerick"
    },
    {
      "question": "角力",
      "answer": "すもう,すまい,かくりょく",
      "meaning": "sumo wrestling, wrestler, rikishi, comparison of strength, contest of strength, sumo"
    },
    {
      "question": "山桃",
      "answer": "やまもも",
      "meaning": "wax myrtle (Myrica rubra), asian bog myrtle"
    },
    {
      "question": "鳩舎",
      "answer": "きゅうしゃ",
      "meaning": "pigeon house"
    },
    {
      "question": "親藩",
      "answer": "しんぱん",
      "meaning": "feudal domain owned by a Tokugawa family branch"
    },
    {
      "question": "小見出し",
      "answer": "こみだし",
      "meaning": "subheading, subtitle"
    },
    {
      "question": "空包",
      "answer": "くうほう",
      "meaning": "blank ammunition, blank cartridge"
    },
    {
      "question": "千言",
      "answer": "せんげん",
      "meaning": "lots of words"
    },
    {
      "question": "夙",
      "answer": "しゅく,まだき",
      "meaning": "outcasts common around the Kyoto region from the Kamakura period to the Edo period, a very short whi"
    },
    {
      "question": "擬古",
      "answer": "ぎこ",
      "meaning": "imitation of classical styles"
    },
    {
      "question": "穀粉",
      "answer": "こくふん",
      "meaning": "grain (rice) flour"
    },
    {
      "question": "先後",
      "answer": "せんご,せんこう",
      "meaning": "before and after, earlier and later, order, sequence, occurring almost simultaneously, inversion (of"
    },
    {
      "question": "差金",
      "answer": "さきん,さしがね",
      "meaning": "difference, margin, carpenter's square, instigation, suggestion"
    },
    {
      "question": "角立てる",
      "answer": "かどだてる",
      "meaning": "to be sharp, to be pointed"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜寒",
      "answer": "よさむ",
      "meaning": "night cold, chill of night, cold night"
    },
    {
      "question": "火食",
      "answer": "かしょく",
      "meaning": "eating cooked food"
    },
    {
      "question": "成長曲線",
      "answer": "せいちょうきょくせん",
      "meaning": "logistic curve, growth curve"
    },
    {
      "question": "注解",
      "answer": "ちゅうかい",
      "meaning": "gloss, explanatory notes, annotation"
    },
    {
      "question": "葉状",
      "answer": "ようじょう",
      "meaning": "leaflike"
    },
    {
      "question": "法曼荼羅",
      "answer": "ほうまんだら",
      "meaning": "dharma mandala (in Shingon), mandala were each deity is represented by its seed syllable in Sanskrit"
    },
    {
      "question": "末子相続",
      "answer": "まっしそうぞく,ばっしそうぞく",
      "meaning": "ultimogeniture, postremogeniture"
    },
    {
      "question": "御料地",
      "answer": "ごりょうち",
      "meaning": "imperial estate"
    },
    {
      "question": "空夢",
      "answer": "そらゆめ",
      "meaning": "fabricated dream"
    },
    {
      "question": "秋の七草",
      "answer": "あきのななくさ",
      "meaning": "seven autumnal flowers (bush clover, Chinese silvergrass, kudzu, fringed pink, golden lace, thorough"
    },
    {
      "question": "回転計",
      "answer": "かいてんけい",
      "meaning": "tachometer, revolution counter"
    },
    {
      "question": "作例",
      "answer": "さくれい",
      "meaning": "model of writing, example of writing, example sentence (in a dictionary), illustrative sentence"
    },
    {
      "question": "何の様",
      "answer": "どのよう",
      "meaning": "what sort, what kind"
    },
    {
      "question": "病理的",
      "answer": "びょうりてき",
      "meaning": "pathologic, pathological"
    },
    {
      "question": "手離れ",
      "answer": "てばなれ",
      "meaning": "(child) no longer requiring constant monitoring, completing a job"
    },
    {
      "question": "均等割",
      "answer": "きんとうわり",
      "meaning": "per capita basis, per capita rate, equal apportionment"
    },
    {
      "question": "賢母",
      "answer": "けんぼ",
      "meaning": "wise mother"
    },
    {
      "question": "春節",
      "answer": "しゅんせつ",
      "meaning": "Lunar New Year, Chinese New Year, Spring Festival"
    },
    {
      "question": "瓜実顔",
      "answer": "うりざねがお",
      "meaning": "oval face (e.g. of a beautiful woman)"
    },
    {
      "question": "犬馬の労",
      "answer": "けんばのろう",
      "meaning": "rendering what little service one can"
    },
    {
      "question": "虎頭",
      "answer": "とらがしら",
      "meaning": "kanji 'tiger' radical"
    },
    {
      "question": "仙薬",
      "answer": "せんやく",
      "meaning": "panacea, elixir (of life)"
    },
    {
      "question": "歯音",
      "answer": "しおん",
      "meaning": "dental, dental consonant, dental sound"
    },
    {
      "question": "小板",
      "answer": "こいた",
      "meaning": "small plank, piece of wood"
    },
    {
      "question": "封止",
      "answer": "ふうし",
      "meaning": "sealing, seal"
    },
    {
      "question": "凱風",
      "answer": "がいふう",
      "meaning": "southerly wind"
    },
    {
      "question": "証印",
      "answer": "しょういん",
      "meaning": "a seal affixed to a document"
    },
    {
      "question": "疵付ける",
      "answer": "きずつける",
      "meaning": "to wound, to injure, to hurt someone's feelings (pride, etc.), to damage, to chip, to scratch"
    },
    {
      "question": "乳鋲",
      "answer": "ちびょう",
      "meaning": "metal ornament in shape of a woman's breast"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪道",
      "answer": "あくどう",
      "meaning": "wrong course, evil course"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦闘帽",
      "answer": "せんとうぼう",
      "meaning": "field cap (used by Japanese troops in WW II)"
    },
    {
      "question": "孕み女",
      "answer": "はらみおんな",
      "meaning": "pregnant woman"
    },
    {
      "question": "六韜三略",
      "answer": "りくとうさんりゃく",
      "meaning": "two books on the art of war in ancient China, the secrets (essence) of the art of war, secrets of su"
    },
    {
      "question": "頸筋",
      "answer": "くびすじ",
      "meaning": "nape of the neck, back of the neck, scruff of the neck"
    },
    {
      "question": "対露",
      "answer": "たいろ",
      "meaning": "towards Russia (relations, policy, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "弱酸",
      "answer": "じゃくさん",
      "meaning": "weak acid"
    },
    {
      "question": "幽愁",
      "answer": "ゆうしゅう",
      "meaning": "deep contemplation, melancholy, gloom"
    },
    {
      "question": "色模様",
      "answer": "いろもよう",
      "meaning": "colored pattern, coloured pattern, love scene"
    },
    {
      "question": "搦む",
      "answer": "からむ",
      "meaning": "to entangle, to entwine, to pick a quarrel, to find fault, to be involved with, to be influenced by,"
    },
    {
      "question": "妊娠線",
      "answer": "にんしんせん",
      "meaning": "pregnancy stretch mark, striae gravidarum"
    },
    {
      "question": "流し打ち",
      "answer": "ながしうち",
      "meaning": "hitting to the opposite field"
    },
    {
      "question": "代書",
      "answer": "だいしょ",
      "meaning": "amanuensis, scribe"
    },
    {
      "question": "御用新聞",
      "answer": "ごようしんぶん",
      "meaning": "pro-government newspaper, newspaper that curries favour with the government"
    },
    {
      "question": "自噴",
      "answer": "じふん",
      "meaning": "gushing forth (e.g. oil well), natural emergence (e.g. spring water)"
    },
    {
      "question": "稀覯",
      "answer": "きこう",
      "meaning": "rare"
    },
    {
      "question": "雲形定規",
      "answer": "くもがたじょうぎ,うんけいじょうぎ",
      "meaning": "French curve"
    },
    {
      "question": "環節",
      "answer": "かんせつ",
      "meaning": "segment (of worm)"
    },
    {
      "question": "実線",
      "answer": "じっせん",
      "meaning": "solid line"
    },
    {
      "question": "言言",
      "answer": "げんげん",
      "meaning": "every word"
    },
    {
      "question": "守戦",
      "answer": "しゅせん",
      "meaning": "war of defense, war of defence, defensive fight, defensive warfare"
    },
    {
      "question": "突っ慳貪",
      "answer": "つっけんどん",
      "meaning": "blunt, curt, brusque"
    },
    {
      "question": "農奴解放",
      "answer": "のうどかいほう",
      "meaning": "emancipation of serfs"
    },
    {
      "question": "禅堂",
      "answer": "ぜんどう",
      "meaning": "zendo (Zen meditation hall)"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤樫",
      "answer": "あかがし",
      "meaning": "Japanese evergreen oak (Quercus acuta)"
    },
    {
      "question": "礼典",
      "answer": "れいてん",
      "meaning": "etiquette, ritual"
    },
    {
      "question": "諾否",
      "answer": "だくひ",
      "meaning": "consent or refusal, yes or no, decision to accept or decline, up or down (vote), assent or dissent,"
    },
    {
      "question": "溢血",
      "answer": "いっけつ",
      "meaning": "hemorrhage, haemorrhage"
    },
    {
      "question": "胸算用",
      "answer": "むなざんよう,むねざんよう",
      "meaning": "making a rough estimate in one's head, expectation, anticipation"
    },
    {
      "question": "ミリ波",
      "answer": "ミリは",
      "meaning": "milli-wave"
    },
    {
      "question": "古史",
      "answer": "こし",
      "meaning": "ancient history"
    },
    {
      "question": "時習",
      "answer": "じしゅう",
      "meaning": "periodic reviewing"
    },
    {
      "question": "北家",
      "answer": "ペーチャ",
      "meaning": "north player"
    },
    {
      "question": "言交わす",
      "answer": "いいかわす",
      "meaning": "to have a chat with, to exchange words or promises, to promise, to get engaged"
    },
    {
      "question": "壁塗り",
      "answer": "かべぬり",
      "meaning": "plastering"
    },
    {
      "question": "涎掛け",
      "answer": "よだれかけ",
      "meaning": "bib, drool bib"
    },
    {
      "question": "同値",
      "answer": "どうち",
      "meaning": "(logical) equivalence"
    },
    {
      "question": "私産",
      "answer": "しさん",
      "meaning": "private property"
    },
    {
      "question": "複合材料",
      "answer": "ふくごうざいりょう",
      "meaning": "composite material"
    },
    {
      "question": "放学",
      "answer": "ほうがく",
      "meaning": "expulsion from school, dismissal of class (at the end of the day)"
    },
    {
      "question": "引き釣り",
      "answer": "ひきづり",
      "meaning": "trolling (fishing)"
    },
    {
      "question": "中京",
      "answer": "ちゅうきょう",
      "meaning": "Nagoya"
    },
    {
      "question": "地牢",
      "answer": "じろう",
      "meaning": "dungeon, underground prison"
    },
    {
      "question": "防湿",
      "answer": "ぼうしつ",
      "meaning": "damp proofing, moisture proofing"
    },
    {
      "question": "周辺装置",
      "answer": "しゅうへんそうち",
      "meaning": "peripheral equipment, peripheral device"
    },
    {
      "question": "速習",
      "answer": "そくしゅう",
      "meaning": "speed learning, intensive learning"
    },
    {
      "question": "飼い鳥",
      "answer": "かいどり",
      "meaning": "pet bird, cage bird"
    },
    {
      "question": "空拳",
      "answer": "くうけん",
      "meaning": "with bare hands, with or from nothing"
    },
    {
      "question": "庶人",
      "answer": "しょじん,しょにん",
      "meaning": "commoner, common people"
    },
    {
      "question": "売り声",
      "answer": "うりごえ",
      "meaning": "hawker's or vendor's cry"
    },
    {
      "question": "ゴム印",
      "answer": "ゴムいん",
      "meaning": "rubber stamp"
    },
    {
      "question": "大河小説",
      "answer": "たいがしょうせつ",
      "meaning": "roman-fleuve, long novel, epic novel"
    },
    {
      "question": "平ったい",
      "answer": "ひらったい",
      "meaning": "flat, even, level, smooth, plain (speech, etc.), simple"
    },
    {
      "question": "佳麗",
      "answer": "かれい",
      "meaning": "beauty"
    },
    {
      "question": "十万億土",
      "answer": "じゅうまんおくど",
      "meaning": "eternity, paradise"
    },
    {
      "question": "食品ロス",
      "answer": "しょくひんロス",
      "meaning": "food waste"
    },
    {
      "question": "風姿",
      "answer": "ふうし",
      "meaning": "appearance, demeanor, demeanour"
    },
    {
      "question": "天が下",
      "answer": "あまがした,あめがした",
      "meaning": "the whole country, the public, the world, the ruling power, having one's own way"
    },
    {
      "question": "中子",
      "answer": "なかご",
      "meaning": "core, tang (of a sword, etc.), middle of a nest of boxes"
    },
    {
      "question": "殯宮",
      "answer": "ひんきゅう",
      "meaning": "temporary imperial mortuary"
    },
    {
      "question": "継投",
      "answer": "けいとう",
      "meaning": "relieving the (starting) pitcher"
    },
    {
      "question": "格外",
      "answer": "かくがい",
      "meaning": "nonstandard, extraordinary, special"
    },
    {
      "question": "空風",
      "answer": "からかぜ",
      "meaning": "dry wind"
    },
    {
      "question": "天文時計",
      "answer": "てんもんどけい",
      "meaning": "astronomical clock"
    },
    {
      "question": "回教徒",
      "answer": "かいきょうと",
      "meaning": "Muslim"
    },
    {
      "question": "奄美大島",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "悪報",
      "answer": "あくほう",
      "meaning": "karmic retribution"
    },
    {
      "question": "舌骨",
      "answer": "ぜっこつ",
      "meaning": "hyoid bone (of the skull)"
    },
    {
      "question": "企業戦略",
      "answer": "きぎょうせんりゃく",
      "meaning": "corporate strategy"
    },
    {
      "question": "地球局",
      "answer": "ちきゅうきょく",
      "meaning": "earth station (for a satellite)"
    },
    {
      "question": "連体詞",
      "answer": "れんたいし",
      "meaning": "pre-noun adjectival, adnominal adjective"
    },
    {
      "question": "楽天地",
      "answer": "らくてんち",
      "meaning": "paradise"
    },
    {
      "question": "名園",
      "answer": "めいえん",
      "meaning": "famous garden, fine garden"
    },
    {
      "question": "塔中",
      "answer": "たっちゅう",
      "meaning": "small Zen temple built to commemorate the death of a high priest, minor temple in the grounds of a h"
    },
    {
      "question": "待命",
      "answer": "たいめい",
      "meaning": "waiting for orders"
    },
    {
      "question": "面喰い",
      "answer": "めんくい",
      "meaning": "being attracted by physical looks only, person who puts much store by good looks"
    },
    {
      "question": "白雨",
      "answer": "はくう",
      "meaning": "rain shower"
    },
    {
      "question": "車海老",
      "answer": "くるまえび",
      "meaning": "kuruma prawn (Marsupenaeus japonicus), kuruma shrimp, Japanese tiger prawn"
    },
    {
      "question": "仰のける",
      "answer": "あおのける",
      "meaning": "to turn up (one's face or a card)"
    },
    {
      "question": "一分一厘",
      "answer": "いちぶいちりん",
      "meaning": "(not even) a bit of, (not even) a hint of, (not) an iota of"
    },
    {
      "question": "都大路",
      "answer": "みやこおおじ",
      "meaning": "avenue in the capital, busy main street of the capital, main thoroughfare"
    },
    {
      "question": "大本山",
      "answer": "だいほんざん",
      "meaning": "head temple of a Buddhist sect"
    },
    {
      "question": "物損",
      "answer": "ぶっそん",
      "meaning": "property damage (i.e. as from an accident)"
    },
    {
      "question": "釈尊",
      "answer": "しゃくそん",
      "meaning": "Sakyamuni (sage of the Sakyas)"
    },
    {
      "question": "腹掛け",
      "answer": "はらがけ",
      "meaning": "workman's apron, bib"
    },
    {
      "question": "出生届け",
      "answer": "しゅっしょうとどけ,しゅっせいとどけ",
      "meaning": "birth registration"
    },
    {
      "question": "疳高い",
      "answer": "かんだかい",
      "meaning": "high-pitched, shrill"
    },
    {
      "question": "確答",
      "answer": "かくとう",
      "meaning": "definite answer"
    },
    {
      "question": "煤色",
      "answer": "すすいろ",
      "meaning": "color of soot (colour)"
    },
    {
      "question": "沈魚落雁",
      "answer": "ちんぎょらくがん",
      "meaning": "charms of a uniquely beautiful woman, (so beautiful that) fish stay on the bottom of water and flyin"
    },
    {
      "question": "纏繞",
      "answer": "てんじょう",
      "meaning": "twining around, entangling"
    },
    {
      "question": "竈馬",
      "answer": "かまどうま",
      "meaning": "camel cricket (Diestrammena apicalis), camelback cricket, cave cricket, spider cricket"
    },
    {
      "question": "霽れる",
      "answer": "はれる",
      "meaning": "to clear up, to clear away, to be sunny, to stop raining, to refresh (e.g. spirits), to be cleared ("
    },
    {
      "question": "楔を刺す",
      "answer": "くさびをさす",
      "meaning": "to make sure of"
    },
    {
      "question": "公定歩合",
      "answer": "こうていぶあい",
      "meaning": "official discount (bank) rate"
    },
    {
      "question": "股がる",
      "answer": "またがる",
      "meaning": "to straddle, to sit astride, to mount, to extend over, to spread over, to span, to extend into"
    },
    {
      "question": "顕揚",
      "answer": "けんよう",
      "meaning": "extolling, exalting"
    },
    {
      "question": "追出し",
      "answer": "おいだし",
      "meaning": "expulsion, dismissal, ejection, eviction, drum beat at the end of a day's performance (in the theatr"
    },
    {
      "question": "二部作",
      "answer": "にぶさく",
      "meaning": "two-part work"
    },
    {
      "question": "遺風",
      "answer": "いふう",
      "meaning": "hereditary custom, surviving tradition, teachings passed down from previous generations"
    },
    {
      "question": "観梅",
      "answer": "かんばい",
      "meaning": "plum blossom viewing"
    },
    {
      "question": "煙害",
      "answer": "えんがい",
      "meaning": "smoke pollution"
    },
    {
      "question": "神典",
      "answer": "しんてん",
      "meaning": "writings about the gods, Shinto scripture (e.g. the Kojiki)"
    },
    {
      "question": "煮返す",
      "answer": "にかえす",
      "meaning": "to warm over"
    },
    {
      "question": "兇徒",
      "answer": "きょうと",
      "meaning": "outlaw, rebel, rioter"
    },
    {
      "question": "瀝青炭",
      "answer": "れきせいたん",
      "meaning": "bituminous coal"
    },
    {
      "question": "基調講演",
      "answer": "きちょうこうえん",
      "meaning": "keynote speech"
    },
    {
      "question": "留具",
      "answer": "とめぐ",
      "meaning": "latch, clasp, catch, check, fastener"
    },
    {
      "question": "捻くる",
      "answer": "ひねくる",
      "meaning": "to twirl, to spin, to fiddle with, to change (e.g. wording)"
    },
    {
      "question": "乳様突起",
      "answer": "にゅうようとっき",
      "meaning": "mastoid"
    },
    {
      "question": "粒銀",
      "answer": "つぶぎん",
      "meaning": "small silver coin of the Edo period"
    },
    {
      "question": "成る可く",
      "answer": "なるべく",
      "meaning": "as (much) as possible, as (much) as one can, wherever practicable, if possible"
    },
    {
      "question": "紅衛兵",
      "answer": "こうえいへい",
      "meaning": "(Chinese) Red Guards"
    },
    {
      "question": "音声合成",
      "answer": "おんせいごうせい",
      "meaning": "speech synthesis, voice synthesis"
    },
    {
      "question": "激語",
      "answer": "げきご",
      "meaning": "harsh language"
    },
    {
      "question": "金剛手",
      "answer": "こんごうしゅ",
      "meaning": "Vajrapani, wielder of the vajra"
    },
    {
      "question": "痛惜",
      "answer": "つうせき",
      "meaning": "deep regret"
    },
    {
      "question": "断筆",
      "answer": "だんぴつ",
      "meaning": "ceasing to write, putting down one's pen"
    },
    {
      "question": "戯作",
      "answer": "げさく,ぎさく",
      "meaning": "cheap literature, writing for amusement, light literature popular in the late Edo period"
    },
    {
      "question": "樹陰",
      "answer": "こかげ,じゅいん",
      "meaning": "shade of tree, bower"
    },
    {
      "question": "船方",
      "answer": "ふなかた",
      "meaning": "boatman"
    },
    {
      "question": "表徴",
      "answer": "ひょうちょう",
      "meaning": "appearing on the surface, symbol, sign, distinguishing mark, diagnostic character"
    },
    {
      "question": "五爵",
      "answer": "ごしゃく",
      "meaning": "five ranks of nobility (in Japan, 1868-1946)"
    },
    {
      "question": "九輪",
      "answer": "くりん",
      "meaning": "kurin, nine vertically stacked rings on a pagoda finial"
    },
    {
      "question": "護国神社",
      "answer": "ごこくじんじゃ",
      "meaning": "shrine honoring war dead, shrine honouring war dead"
    },
    {
      "question": "秋の暮れ",
      "answer": "あきのくれ",
      "meaning": "autumn dusk, the end of autumn"
    },
    {
      "question": "徒ならぬ",
      "answer": "ただならぬ",
      "meaning": "unusual, uncommon, extraordinary, out of the ordinary, incomparable, serious, alarming"
    },
    {
      "question": "小札",
      "answer": "こざね",
      "meaning": "armor platelet"
    },
    {
      "question": "蘇鉄",
      "answer": "そてつ",
      "meaning": "sago cycad (Cycas revoluta), king sago palm, sago palm, Japanese sago palm"
    },
    {
      "question": "弘徽殿",
      "answer": "こきでん,こうきでん",
      "meaning": "ladies' pavilion (of the inner Heian Palace)"
    },
    {
      "question": "真空包装",
      "answer": "しんくうほうそう",
      "meaning": "vacuum packaging"
    },
    {
      "question": "一親等",
      "answer": "いっしんとう",
      "meaning": "first degree of kinship"
    },
    {
      "question": "不行状",
      "answer": "ふぎょうじょう",
      "meaning": "misconduct, misbehaviour, impropriety, profligacy"
    },
    {
      "question": "市庭",
      "answer": "いちば",
      "meaning": "(town) market, (street) market, marketplace"
    },
    {
      "question": "地蛍",
      "answer": "つちぼたる",
      "meaning": "glowworm"
    },
    {
      "question": "引き技",
      "answer": "ひきわざ",
      "meaning": "pulling techniques"
    },
    {
      "question": "組替える",
      "answer": "くみかえる",
      "meaning": "to rearrange (classes), to recompose, to reset, to recombine (genes)"
    },
    {
      "question": "相続財産",
      "answer": "そうぞくざいさん",
      "meaning": "inheritance, inherited property, heritage"
    },
    {
      "question": "伴性遺伝",
      "answer": "はんせいいでん",
      "meaning": "sex-linked inheritance"
    },
    {
      "question": "在郷",
      "answer": "ざいごう,ざいきょう",
      "meaning": "hometown, rural districts"
    },
    {
      "question": "催促状",
      "answer": "さいそくじょう",
      "meaning": "dun, letter requesting money, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "神徳",
      "answer": "しんとく",
      "meaning": "divine virtues"
    },
    {
      "question": "絡げる",
      "answer": "からげる",
      "meaning": "to tie up, to bind, to tuck up (clothes, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "寂滅為楽",
      "answer": "じゃくめついらく",
      "meaning": "freedom from one's desires (entry into Nirvana) is true bliss"
    },
    {
      "question": "日本馬",
      "answer": "にほんうま",
      "meaning": "native Japanese horse"
    },
    {
      "question": "糊化",
      "answer": "こか",
      "meaning": "gelatinization"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭書",
      "answer": "とうしょ,かしらがき",
      "meaning": "headnote, heading, superscription, recitals, above-mentioned, referred to above"
    },
    {
      "question": "黄体",
      "answer": "おうたい",
      "meaning": "corpus luteum"
    },
    {
      "question": "撰ぶ",
      "answer": "えらぶ",
      "meaning": "to choose, to select"
    },
    {
      "question": "純毛",
      "answer": "じゅんもう",
      "meaning": "all-wool"
    },
    {
      "question": "養毛剤",
      "answer": "ようもうざい",
      "meaning": "hair tonic"
    },
    {
      "question": "国語学",
      "answer": "こくごがく",
      "meaning": "Japanese philology, Japanese linguistics"
    },
    {
      "question": "禁猟期",
      "answer": "きんりょうき",
      "meaning": "closed season for fishing or hunting"
    },
    {
      "question": "恬として",
      "answer": "てんとして",
      "meaning": "coolly, indifferently, nonchalantly, calmly"
    },
    {
      "question": "暖房装置",
      "answer": "だんぼうそうち",
      "meaning": "heater, heating apparatus, heating arrangement, heating equipment, heating system, room heater"
    },
    {
      "question": "利かぬ気",
      "answer": "きかぬき",
      "meaning": "unyielding"
    },
    {
      "question": "骰子",
      "answer": "さいころ,シャイツ",
      "meaning": "dice, die, dice (esp. in mahjong)"
    },
    {
      "question": "風待ち",
      "answer": "かざまち,かぜまち",
      "meaning": "waiting for favorable wind, waiting for favourable wind"
    },
    {
      "question": "六欲天",
      "answer": "ろくよくてん",
      "meaning": "the six domains of the desire realm, the six heavens of the desire realm"
    },
    {
      "question": "朝見",
      "answer": "ちょうけん",
      "meaning": "audience with the Emperor, imperial audience"
    },
    {
      "question": "木太刀",
      "answer": "きだち",
      "meaning": "wooden sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "花卉",
      "answer": "かき",
      "meaning": "flowering plant, flower, ornamental plant"
    },
    {
      "question": "漸増",
      "answer": "ぜんぞう",
      "meaning": "gradual increase"
    },
    {
      "question": "小器",
      "answer": "しょうき",
      "meaning": "small container, person of small capacities"
    },
    {
      "question": "備州",
      "answer": "びしゅう",
      "meaning": "Bishū (the three former provinces of Bizen, Bitchū and Bingo)"
    },
    {
      "question": "別事",
      "answer": "べつじ",
      "meaning": "another affair, mishap"
    },
    {
      "question": "測度",
      "answer": "そくど",
      "meaning": "measure"
    },
    {
      "question": "召し取る",
      "answer": "めしとる",
      "meaning": "to arrest, to apprehend, to call, to summon"
    },
    {
      "question": "彩なす",
      "answer": "あやなす",
      "meaning": "to decorate with many bright colours (colors), to create a beautiful variegated pattern, to manipula"
    },
    {
      "question": "論弁",
      "answer": "ろんべん",
      "meaning": "argument"
    },
    {
      "question": "己等",
      "answer": "おれら,おいら,うぬら",
      "meaning": "we, us, I, me, ye, you"
    },
    {
      "question": "賢夫人",
      "answer": "けんぷじん",
      "meaning": "wise wife"
    },
    {
      "question": "花穂",
      "answer": "かすい,かほ",
      "meaning": "spike"
    },
    {
      "question": "潜性",
      "answer": "せんせい",
      "meaning": "recessiveness"
    },
    {
      "question": "浮び出る",
      "answer": "うかびでる",
      "meaning": "to surface"
    },
    {
      "question": "衣手",
      "answer": "ころもで",
      "meaning": "sleeve"
    },
    {
      "question": "多動",
      "answer": "たどう",
      "meaning": "hyperactivity (of a child)"
    },
    {
      "question": "日本狼",
      "answer": "にほんおおかみ",
      "meaning": "Japanese wolf (Canis lupus hodophilax; extinct)"
    },
    {
      "question": "定収入",
      "answer": "ていしゅうにゅう",
      "meaning": "fixed income"
    },
    {
      "question": "勅使門",
      "answer": "ちょくしもん",
      "meaning": "imperial envoy gate, temple gate used by imperial envoy"
    },
    {
      "question": "甘味噌",
      "answer": "あまみそ",
      "meaning": "low-salt miso, sweet miso"
    },
    {
      "question": "訓誡",
      "answer": "くんかい",
      "meaning": "warning, admonition, lesson or a phrase that teaches you not to do something"
    },
    {
      "question": "樹枝",
      "answer": "じゅし",
      "meaning": "branch (of a tree)"
    },
    {
      "question": "半跏趺坐",
      "answer": "はんかふざ",
      "meaning": "half lotus position (meditation posture), sitting with one foot placed on the opposite thigh"
    },
    {
      "question": "男狂い",
      "answer": "おとこぐるい",
      "meaning": "wantonness, man-crazy"
    },
    {
      "question": "共同購入",
      "answer": "きょうどうこうにゅう",
      "meaning": "cooperative buying, group buying, joint purchase"
    },
    {
      "question": "化学結合",
      "answer": "かがくけつごう",
      "meaning": "chemical bond"
    },
    {
      "question": "副木",
      "answer": "ふくぼく",
      "meaning": "splint, brace"
    },
    {
      "question": "島陰",
      "answer": "しまかげ",
      "meaning": "lee of an island, area hidden by an island"
    },
    {
      "question": "協同組合",
      "answer": "きょうどうくみあい",
      "meaning": "cooperative, association, partnership"
    },
    {
      "question": "評言",
      "answer": "ひょうげん",
      "meaning": "comment, critical remark"
    },
    {
      "question": "兵仗",
      "answer": "ひょうじょう,へいじょう",
      "meaning": "arms, armed soldier"
    },
    {
      "question": "弟嫁",
      "answer": "おとうとよめ,おとよめ",
      "meaning": "younger brother's wife"
    },
    {
      "question": "内意",
      "answer": "ないい",
      "meaning": "intention, personal opinion"
    },
    {
      "question": "補記",
      "answer": "ほき",
      "meaning": "addition (to a text), additional entry (e.g. to a database)"
    },
    {
      "question": "音写",
      "answer": "おんしゃ",
      "meaning": "transliteration, transcription"
    },
    {
      "question": "導出",
      "answer": "どうしゅつ",
      "meaning": "derivation (e.g. in math, logic), drawing (conclusion, summary etc.), leading (e.g. to a conclusion,"
    },
    {
      "question": "細字",
      "answer": "さいじ,ほそじ",
      "meaning": "small type or handwriting"
    },
    {
      "question": "改ページ",
      "answer": "かいページ",
      "meaning": "repagination, new page, form feed, page break"
    },
    {
      "question": "回転体",
      "answer": "かいてんたい",
      "meaning": "solid of revolution"
    },
    {
      "question": "適中",
      "answer": "てきちゅう",
      "meaning": "proving to be right, coming true, being on the mark"
    },
    {
      "question": "御言",
      "answer": "みこと",
      "meaning": "the spoken words of the emperor or a noble"
    },
    {
      "question": "闇相場",
      "answer": "やみそうば",
      "meaning": "black-market price"
    },
    {
      "question": "古生物",
      "answer": "こせいぶつ",
      "meaning": "extinct plants and animals"
    },
    {
      "question": "奇乳",
      "answer": "きにゅう",
      "meaning": "witch's milk (milk secreted by some neonates)"
    },
    {
      "question": "癋見",
      "answer": "べしみ",
      "meaning": "beshimi, noh mask with a slanted mouth, bulging eyes and large nostrils"
    },
    {
      "question": "早替わり",
      "answer": "はやがわり",
      "meaning": "quick change, quick transformation, metamorphosis, turning suddenly into"
    },
    {
      "question": "内裏様",
      "answer": "だいりさま",
      "meaning": "imperial palace, person living in the imperial palace (esp. the emperor), festival dolls representin"
    },
    {
      "question": "湖北",
      "answer": "こほく",
      "meaning": "north of a lake, north of Lake Biwa"
    },
    {
      "question": "吸口",
      "answer": "すいくち",
      "meaning": "mouthpiece, cigarette holder, cigarette filter (tip), fragrant garnish (for soup)"
    },
    {
      "question": "頻用",
      "answer": "ひんよう",
      "meaning": "frequent use"
    },
    {
      "question": "仮定形",
      "answer": "かていけい",
      "meaning": "hypothetical form (of verbs and adjectives in modern Japanese)"
    },
    {
      "question": "乳量",
      "answer": "にゅうりょう",
      "meaning": "milk yield (of a cow)"
    },
    {
      "question": "此れ式",
      "answer": "これしき",
      "meaning": "trifle, insignificant thing, (only) this much"
    },
    {
      "question": "間色",
      "answer": "かんしょく",
      "meaning": "compound color, compound colour"
    },
    {
      "question": "愚蒙",
      "answer": "ぐもう",
      "meaning": "stupid, foolish"
    },
    {
      "question": "女方",
      "answer": "おんながた",
      "meaning": "onnagata, male actor in female kabuki roles, female partner (in a relationship)"
    },
    {
      "question": "祈雨",
      "answer": "きう",
      "meaning": "praying for rain"
    },
    {
      "question": "緊張病",
      "answer": "きんちょうびょう",
      "meaning": "catatonia"
    },
    {
      "question": "針を含む",
      "answer": "はりをふくむ",
      "meaning": "to hurt someone's feelings"
    },
    {
      "question": "免震",
      "answer": "めんしん",
      "meaning": "base isolation, seismic base isolation, base isolating, vibration damping at the base of a building"
    },
    {
      "question": "寒気立つ",
      "answer": "さむけだつ",
      "meaning": "to feel cold, to have a chill"
    },
    {
      "question": "修好条約",
      "answer": "しゅうこうじょうやく",
      "meaning": "amity treaty"
    },
    {
      "question": "勇猛心",
      "answer": "ゆうもうしん",
      "meaning": "intrepid spirit"
    },
    {
      "question": "楮",
      "answer": "こうぞ,かぞ,かじ",
      "meaning": "hybrid mulberry tree used to make Japanese paper (Broussonetia kazinoki x papyrifera), paper mulberr"
    },
    {
      "question": "必達",
      "answer": "ひったつ",
      "meaning": "certain fulfilment"
    },
    {
      "question": "内法",
      "answer": "うちのり",
      "meaning": "inside measure"
    },
    {
      "question": "芳潤",
      "answer": "ほうじゅん",
      "meaning": "mellow (flavor or fragrance, esp. alcohol), rich, full-bodied, superior"
    },
    {
      "question": "立ち勝る",
      "answer": "たちまさる",
      "meaning": "to be superior, to surpass"
    },
    {
      "question": "耳標",
      "answer": "じひょう",
      "meaning": "earmark (on cattle, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "頌する",
      "answer": "しょうする",
      "meaning": "to celebrate someone's achievements"
    },
    {
      "question": "人作り",
      "answer": "ひとづくり,ひとつくり",
      "meaning": "personnel training, human resources development, character building"
    },
    {
      "question": "論理積",
      "answer": "ろんりせき",
      "meaning": "logical product, AND operation, conjunction, intersection"
    },
    {
      "question": "茲",
      "answer": "ここ",
      "meaning": "here, this place, this point, now, these past ... (e.g. three years), these last ..., the next ... ("
    },
    {
      "question": "金鉄",
      "answer": "きんてつ",
      "meaning": "gold and iron, firmness, adamancy"
    },
    {
      "question": "訥訥",
      "answer": "とつとつ",
      "meaning": "halting (speech), faltering, stammering"
    },
    {
      "question": "落葉松",
      "answer": "からまつ,らくようしょう",
      "meaning": "(Japanese) larch (Larix leptolepis, Larix kaempferi)"
    },
    {
      "question": "極軌道",
      "answer": "きょくきどう",
      "meaning": "polar orbit"
    },
    {
      "question": "幻怪",
      "answer": "げんかい",
      "meaning": "strange or mysterious and troubling"
    },
    {
      "question": "無帽",
      "answer": "むぼう",
      "meaning": "bare-headed, uncovered"
    },
    {
      "question": "強磁性",
      "answer": "きょうじせい",
      "meaning": "ferromagnetism"
    },
    {
      "question": "鯒",
      "answer": "こち",
      "meaning": "flathead (esp. the bartailed flathead, Platycephalus indicus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "他山",
      "answer": "たざん",
      "meaning": "another mountain, another temple"
    },
    {
      "question": "おぼこ娘",
      "answer": "おぼこむすめ",
      "meaning": "innocent girl, naive girl, virgin"
    },
    {
      "question": "本手",
      "answer": "ほんて",
      "meaning": "ace up one's sleeve, trump card, basic melody (esp. on koto and shamisen), proper move (in go, shogi"
    },
    {
      "question": "秀歌",
      "answer": "しゅうか",
      "meaning": "splendid tanka, splendid waka"
    },
    {
      "question": "下り口",
      "answer": "おりぐち,おりくち",
      "meaning": "top (of a flight of stairs), exit involving a descent (e.g. from a bus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "飯台",
      "answer": "はんだい",
      "meaning": "(Japanese-style) dining table"
    },
    {
      "question": "跡目相続",
      "answer": "あとめそうぞく",
      "meaning": "successorship"
    },
    {
      "question": "為替市場",
      "answer": "かわせしじょう",
      "meaning": "exchange market"
    },
    {
      "question": "草刈場",
      "answer": "くさかりば",
      "meaning": "hay-meadow commons, place (or organization, etc.) from which numerous people hope to benefit"
    },
    {
      "question": "耳小骨",
      "answer": "じしょうこつ",
      "meaning": "auditory ossicles"
    },
    {
      "question": "物価高",
      "answer": "ぶっかだか",
      "meaning": "high prices of commodities"
    },
    {
      "question": "力帯",
      "answer": "ちからおび",
      "meaning": "abdominal-support belt"
    },
    {
      "question": "遠鳴り",
      "answer": "とおなり",
      "meaning": "distant peals (thunder), distant roar (sea)"
    },
    {
      "question": "尽忠報国",
      "answer": "じんちゅうほうこく",
      "meaning": "loyalty and patriotism"
    },
    {
      "question": "油菜",
      "answer": "あぶらな",
      "meaning": "rape (seed oil plant, Brassica campestris)"
    },
    {
      "question": "屈葬",
      "answer": "くっそう",
      "meaning": "crouched burial"
    },
    {
      "question": "為所",
      "answer": "しどころ",
      "meaning": "appropriate time to do (something), occasion when (something) must be done"
    },
    {
      "question": "唯唯",
      "answer": "ただただ,いい",
      "meaning": "absolutely, only, obedient, submissive, tame, slavish"
    },
    {
      "question": "唐織",
      "answer": "からおり",
      "meaning": "karaori, Chinese weave, cloth decorated with birds and flowers in silk, noh theater costume made wit"
    },
    {
      "question": "多能",
      "answer": "たのう",
      "meaning": "versatility"
    },
    {
      "question": "活き造り",
      "answer": "いきづくり",
      "meaning": "sashimi prepared from live fish, arranged in its original shape"
    },
    {
      "question": "目差す",
      "answer": "めざす",
      "meaning": "to aim at, to have an eye on, to go toward, to head for"
    },
    {
      "question": "非能率",
      "answer": "ひのうりつ",
      "meaning": "inefficiency"
    },
    {
      "question": "道州制",
      "answer": "どうしゅうせい",
      "meaning": "administrative reform proposal, involving integration of prefectures into 7 or 9 states"
    },
    {
      "question": "神祇官",
      "answer": "じんぎかん,かみづかさ,かんづかさ",
      "meaning": "Department of Divinities (1868-1871), Department of Worship (under the ritsuryo system)"
    },
    {
      "question": "聖餐式",
      "answer": "せいさんしき",
      "meaning": "Holy Communion, the Eucharist, the Lord's Supper"
    },
    {
      "question": "軟玉",
      "answer": "なんぎょく",
      "meaning": "nephrite"
    },
    {
      "question": "健胃",
      "answer": "けんい",
      "meaning": "strengthening the stomach, strong stomach"
    },
    {
      "question": "極楽蜻蛉",
      "answer": "ごくらくとんぼ",
      "meaning": "happy-go-lucky fellow, an easygoing and indifferent person, a pococurante"
    },
    {
      "question": "宿運",
      "answer": "しゅくうん",
      "meaning": "fate, destiny"
    },
    {
      "question": "技術援助",
      "answer": "ぎじゅつえんじょ",
      "meaning": "technological assistance"
    },
    {
      "question": "金権",
      "answer": "きんけん",
      "meaning": "power of money, financial influence"
    },
    {
      "question": "胛",
      "answer": "かいがね",
      "meaning": "shoulder blade, scapula"
    },
    {
      "question": "代変わり",
      "answer": "だいがわり",
      "meaning": "taking over (e.g. store or family's headship), subrogation, substitution of one person for another ("
    },
    {
      "question": "耐酸",
      "answer": "たいさん",
      "meaning": "acid-resistant"
    },
    {
      "question": "震駭",
      "answer": "しんがい",
      "meaning": "terror, shock"
    },
    {
      "question": "過褒",
      "answer": "かほう",
      "meaning": "excessive praise, overpraise"
    },
    {
      "question": "学齢",
      "answer": "がくれい",
      "meaning": "school age"
    },
    {
      "question": "猫草",
      "answer": "ねこくさ",
      "meaning": "cat grass (often Avena sativa), catgrass"
    },
    {
      "question": "袖下",
      "answer": "そでした",
      "meaning": "bottom of the sleeve, height of the sleeve (of traditional Japanese clothing), secret, secret bribe"
    },
    {
      "question": "優勢勝ち",
      "answer": "ゆうせいがち",
      "meaning": "winning by judges' decision (in judo)"
    },
    {
      "question": "奉幣使",
      "answer": "ほうへいし",
      "meaning": "imperial messenger to a shrine, envoy returning courtesies"
    },
    {
      "question": "檜皮",
      "answer": "ひわだ,ひはだ",
      "meaning": "cypress bark"
    },
    {
      "question": "本場物",
      "answer": "ほんばもの",
      "meaning": "genuine article"
    },
    {
      "question": "早版",
      "answer": "はやばん",
      "meaning": "early edition (of a newspaper)"
    },
    {
      "question": "犬張り子",
      "answer": "いぬはりこ",
      "meaning": "papier-mâché dog"
    },
    {
      "question": "都銀",
      "answer": "とぎん",
      "meaning": "city bank, metropolitan bank"
    },
    {
      "question": "御強",
      "answer": "おこわ",
      "meaning": "glutinous rice steamed with red beans or some other ingredient, trickery, deception"
    },
    {
      "question": "厚恩",
      "answer": "こうおん",
      "meaning": "great favor, great favour, obligation"
    },
    {
      "question": "弾み車",
      "answer": "はずみぐるま",
      "meaning": "flywheel"
    },
    {
      "question": "即興的",
      "answer": "そっきょうてき",
      "meaning": "improvised, impromptu, extemporaneous, off-the-cuff, ad-lib"
    },
    {
      "question": "親王家",
      "answer": "しんのうけ",
      "meaning": "imperial prince's family, family of a prince of royal blood"
    },
    {
      "question": "有平糖",
      "answer": "あるへいとう",
      "meaning": "toffee"
    },
    {
      "question": "画筆",
      "answer": "がひつ",
      "meaning": "artist's brush"
    },
    {
      "question": "杙",
      "answer": "くい,くいぜ,くいせ",
      "meaning": "stake, post, pile, picket, stump"
    },
    {
      "question": "歌合",
      "answer": "うたあわせ",
      "meaning": "poetry contest"
    },
    {
      "question": "継娘",
      "answer": "ままむすめ",
      "meaning": "stepdaughter"
    },
    {
      "question": "派生語",
      "answer": "はせいご",
      "meaning": "derivative (word)"
    },
    {
      "question": "微視的",
      "answer": "びしてき",
      "meaning": "microscopic"
    },
    {
      "question": "誕辰",
      "answer": "たんしん",
      "meaning": "birthday"
    },
    {
      "question": "権柄",
      "answer": "けんぺい",
      "meaning": "power, authority"
    },
    {
      "question": "海栗",
      "answer": "うに",
      "meaning": "sea urchin, seasoned sea urchin eggs"
    },
    {
      "question": "弁当代",
      "answer": "べんとうだい",
      "meaning": "lunch money"
    },
    {
      "question": "灰土",
      "answer": "かいど,はいつち",
      "meaning": "ashes and earth, poor volcanic soil"
    },
    {
      "question": "等外",
      "answer": "とうがい",
      "meaning": "also-ran, non-winner"
    },
    {
      "question": "回流",
      "answer": "かいりゅう",
      "meaning": "circulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "雑駁",
      "answer": "ざっぱく",
      "meaning": "confusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "快刀",
      "answer": "かいとう",
      "meaning": "sharp sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "側聞",
      "answer": "そくぶん",
      "meaning": "hearing casually, hearing by chance, learning by hearsay"
    },
    {
      "question": "破防法",
      "answer": "はぼうほう",
      "meaning": "(Japanese) Anti-Subversive Activities Act"
    },
    {
      "question": "頑是",
      "answer": "がんぜ",
      "meaning": "distinction between right and wrong"
    },
    {
      "question": "昭和の日",
      "answer": "しょうわのひ",
      "meaning": "Shōwa Day (national holiday; April 29), Showa Day"
    },
    {
      "question": "夏椿",
      "answer": "なつつばき",
      "meaning": "Japanese stewartia (Stewartia pseudocamellia)"
    },
    {
      "question": "油槽船",
      "answer": "ゆそうせん",
      "meaning": "an oil tanker"
    },
    {
      "question": "蕗の薹",
      "answer": "ふきのとう",
      "meaning": "edible flower bud of the fuki (Petasites japonicus) plant, an early spring delicacy"
    },
    {
      "question": "字一色",
      "answer": "ツーイーソー",
      "meaning": "all honors, winning hand consisting only of honor tiles"
    },
    {
      "question": "院本",
      "answer": "いんぽん",
      "meaning": "drama, playbook"
    },
    {
      "question": "痴鈍",
      "answer": "ちどん",
      "meaning": "dull-witted"
    },
    {
      "question": "本有",
      "answer": "ほんぬ,ほんう,ほんゆう",
      "meaning": "state (or period) of life, innateness, innate feature (or character, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "仲裁人",
      "answer": "ちゅうさいにん",
      "meaning": "arbitrator, mediator"
    },
    {
      "question": "亡魂",
      "answer": "ぼうこん",
      "meaning": "departed soul, spirit"
    },
    {
      "question": "板付き",
      "answer": "いたつき",
      "meaning": "being on stage when the curtain opens, wooden floor, wooden-floored room, thinly-sliced food grilled"
    },
    {
      "question": "科名",
      "answer": "かめい",
      "meaning": "family name"
    },
    {
      "question": "大邦",
      "answer": "たいほう",
      "meaning": "large country, great nation, major power, great power"
    },
    {
      "question": "盥回し",
      "answer": "たらいまわし",
      "meaning": "acrobatic barrel-rolling (performed using the feet while lying on the back), handing something aroun"
    },
    {
      "question": "贐",
      "answer": "はなむけ",
      "meaning": "farewell gift, parting gift, viaticum"
    },
    {
      "question": "聚落",
      "answer": "しゅうらく,じゅらく",
      "meaning": "settlement, village, community, town, (bacterial) colony"
    },
    {
      "question": "胃下垂",
      "answer": "いかすい",
      "meaning": "gastroptosis"
    },
    {
      "question": "呼吸中枢",
      "answer": "こきゅうちゅうすう",
      "meaning": "respiratory center, respiratory centre"
    },
    {
      "question": "目色",
      "answer": "めいろ",
      "meaning": "facial expression"
    },
    {
      "question": "草本",
      "answer": "そうほん",
      "meaning": "herbaceous plant, herb"
    },
    {
      "question": "迂路",
      "answer": "うろ",
      "meaning": "detour, diversion"
    },
    {
      "question": "通分",
      "answer": "つうぶん",
      "meaning": "reduce"
    },
    {
      "question": "憬れる",
      "answer": "あこがれる",
      "meaning": "to long for, to yearn after, to admire, to be attracted by"
    },
    {
      "question": "月内",
      "answer": "げつない",
      "meaning": "by the end of this month"
    },
    {
      "question": "自修",
      "answer": "じしゅう",
      "meaning": "self-study, teaching oneself"
    },
    {
      "question": "天心",
      "answer": "てんしん",
      "meaning": "zenith, divine will, providence"
    },
    {
      "question": "チゲ鍋",
      "answer": "チゲなべ",
      "meaning": "Korean stew, Korean hot pot"
    },
    {
      "question": "ソーダ灰",
      "answer": "ソーダばい",
      "meaning": "soda ash"
    },
    {
      "question": "薬名",
      "answer": "やくめい",
      "meaning": "name of a drug or medicine"
    },
    {
      "question": "沸騰点",
      "answer": "ふっとうてん",
      "meaning": "boiling point"
    },
    {
      "question": "実証主義",
      "answer": "じっしょうしゅぎ",
      "meaning": "positivism"
    },
    {
      "question": "付け鼻",
      "answer": "つけばな",
      "meaning": "false nose, artificial nose"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪晴れ",
      "answer": "ゆきばれ",
      "meaning": "clear weather after snowfall"
    },
    {
      "question": "廉恥",
      "answer": "れんち",
      "meaning": "sense of honour (honor)"
    },
    {
      "question": "奥書",
      "answer": "おくがき",
      "meaning": "postscript (to a book), verification, publication (in a book)"
    },
    {
      "question": "兇猛",
      "answer": "きょうもう",
      "meaning": "fierce"
    },
    {
      "question": "経皮感染",
      "answer": "けいひかんせん",
      "meaning": "percutaneous infection"
    },
    {
      "question": "雲形",
      "answer": "うんけい,くもがた",
      "meaning": "cloud formation, cloud-shaped"
    },
    {
      "question": "青金",
      "answer": "あおきん,あおがね",
      "meaning": "green gold, lead"
    },
    {
      "question": "高下",
      "answer": "こうげ",
      "meaning": "rise and fall (e.g. prices), fluctuation, difference (rank, grade, quality, etc.), variation"
    },
    {
      "question": "腸骨",
      "answer": "ちょうこつ",
      "meaning": "ilium (part of pelvis)"
    },
    {
      "question": "媾合",
      "answer": "こうごう",
      "meaning": "sexual union, congress"
    },
    {
      "question": "南郊",
      "answer": "なんこう",
      "meaning": "southern suburbs"
    },
    {
      "question": "山焼き",
      "answer": "やまやき",
      "meaning": "burning a mountain (by design)"
    },
    {
      "question": "弾性体",
      "answer": "だんせいたい",
      "meaning": "elastic body"
    },
    {
      "question": "生害",
      "answer": "しょうがい",
      "meaning": "commit suicide"
    },
    {
      "question": "糸球体",
      "answer": "しきゅうたい",
      "meaning": "glomerulus"
    },
    {
      "question": "全篇",
      "answer": "ぜんぺん",
      "meaning": "whole book (volume), complete episode"
    },
    {
      "question": "卜する",
      "answer": "ぼくする",
      "meaning": "to tell (a person's) fortune, to divine, to fix, to choose"
    },
    {
      "question": "鹹い",
      "answer": "しおからい,からい",
      "meaning": "salty (taste), briny"
    },
    {
      "question": "茶汲み",
      "answer": "ちゃくみ",
      "meaning": "serving tea, tea server"
    },
    {
      "question": "楽日",
      "answer": "らくじつ,らくび",
      "meaning": "last day of a tournament, closing day of a show"
    },
    {
      "question": "神鏡",
      "answer": "しんきょう",
      "meaning": "divine mirror, sacred mirror (one of the three sacred treasures)"
    },
    {
      "question": "口唇期",
      "answer": "こうしんき",
      "meaning": "oral phase, oral stage"
    },
    {
      "question": "相勤める",
      "answer": "あいつとめる",
      "meaning": "to work (for), to be employed (at), to serve (in)"
    },
    {
      "question": "開け閉て",
      "answer": "あけたて",
      "meaning": "opening and shutting"
    },
    {
      "question": "比売神",
      "answer": "ひめがみ,ひめかみ",
      "meaning": "goddess"
    },
    {
      "question": "大永",
      "answer": "たいえい",
      "meaning": "Taiei era (1521.8.23-1528.8.20)"
    },
    {
      "question": "陶枕",
      "answer": "とうちん",
      "meaning": "porcelain pillow (used in summer)"
    },
    {
      "question": "投合",
      "answer": "とうごう",
      "meaning": "agreement, coincidence, congeniality"
    },
    {
      "question": "譜代大名",
      "answer": "ふだいだいみょう",
      "meaning": "hereditary daimyo (whose ancestors supported Tokugawa Ieyasu prior to the battle of Sekigahara)"
    },
    {
      "question": "抜去",
      "answer": "ばっきょう",
      "meaning": "extraction, withdrawal, evulsion, avulsion"
    },
    {
      "question": "罪障",
      "answer": "ざいしょう",
      "meaning": "sins (which prevent entry into bliss)"
    },
    {
      "question": "大衆薬",
      "answer": "たいしゅうやく",
      "meaning": "over-the-counter drug"
    },
    {
      "question": "月中",
      "answer": "げつちゅう,がつちゅう,つきなか",
      "meaning": "(for the) whole month, middle of the month, mid-month"
    },
    {
      "question": "提示部",
      "answer": "ていじぶ",
      "meaning": "(musical) exposition"
    },
    {
      "question": "気が若い",
      "answer": "きがわかい",
      "meaning": "young at heart"
    },
    {
      "question": "勇断",
      "answer": "ゆうだん",
      "meaning": "resolute decision"
    },
    {
      "question": "反射炉",
      "answer": "はんしゃろ",
      "meaning": "reverberatory furnace"
    },
    {
      "question": "別珍",
      "answer": "べっちん",
      "meaning": "velveteen"
    },
    {
      "question": "用談",
      "answer": "ようだん",
      "meaning": "business conversation"
    },
    {
      "question": "木所",
      "answer": "きどころ",
      "meaning": "classification of fragrant woods used as incense"
    },
    {
      "question": "粗製濫造",
      "answer": "そせいらんぞう",
      "meaning": "mass production of inferior goods"
    },
    {
      "question": "語原",
      "answer": "ごげん",
      "meaning": "origin of a word, derivation of a word, etymology"
    },
    {
      "question": "公職追放",
      "answer": "こうしょくついほう",
      "meaning": "purge of public officials"
    },
    {
      "question": "同前",
      "answer": "どうぜん",
      "meaning": "same as above, ditto, ibid."
    },
    {
      "question": "口固い",
      "answer": "くちがたい",
      "meaning": "discreet, tight-lipped"
    },
    {
      "question": "序詞",
      "answer": "じょし,じょことば",
      "meaning": "foreword, preface, introduction, prefatory modifying statement (of a waka, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "下回り",
      "answer": "したまわり",
      "meaning": "subordinate part, menial service, subordinate, utility man"
    },
    {
      "question": "電子手帳",
      "answer": "でんしてちょう",
      "meaning": "electronic organizer"
    },
    {
      "question": "友禅染",
      "answer": "ゆうぜんぞめ",
      "meaning": "type of dyeing method or pattern, silk printed by the Yuzen process"
    },
    {
      "question": "男名",
      "answer": "おとこな",
      "meaning": "male name, adult name"
    },
    {
      "question": "流連",
      "answer": "りゅうれん",
      "meaning": "stay on"
    },
    {
      "question": "弁護士法",
      "answer": "べんごしほう",
      "meaning": "Attorneys-at-Law Act, Lawyer Act"
    },
    {
      "question": "連銭葦毛",
      "answer": "れんぜんあしげ",
      "meaning": "dapple gray (horse coat color), dapple grey"
    },
    {
      "question": "畑焼き",
      "answer": "はたやき",
      "meaning": "burning stubble and dry grass"
    },
    {
      "question": "八十八夜",
      "answer": "はちじゅうはちや",
      "meaning": "eighty-eighth day from the beginning of spring"
    },
    {
      "question": "下僚",
      "answer": "かりょう",
      "meaning": "subordinates, petty officials"
    },
    {
      "question": "餅肌",
      "answer": "もちはだ",
      "meaning": "soft skin, smooth skin"
    },
    {
      "question": "現金問屋",
      "answer": "げんきんどんや",
      "meaning": "cash-basis wholesaler"
    },
    {
      "question": "社会運動",
      "answer": "しゃかいうんどう",
      "meaning": "social movement"
    },
    {
      "question": "神札",
      "answer": "しんさつ",
      "meaning": "type of amulet sold at Shinto shrines"
    },
    {
      "question": "分光",
      "answer": "ぶんこう",
      "meaning": "spectrum"
    },
    {
      "question": "唐紙",
      "answer": "からかみ,とうし",
      "meaning": "thick printed paper (for covering sliding doors), paper sliding-door, sliding door covered with thic"
    },
    {
      "question": "寄留",
      "answer": "きりゅう",
      "meaning": "temporary residence, sojourn"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕向け",
      "answer": "しむけ",
      "meaning": "delivery, sending, treatment"
    },
    {
      "question": "精美",
      "answer": "せいび",
      "meaning": "supreme beauty, exquisiteness"
    },
    {
      "question": "相似る",
      "answer": "あいにる",
      "meaning": "to resemble each other, to resemble one another"
    },
    {
      "question": "掛り切り",
      "answer": "かかりきり",
      "meaning": "being devoted, spending all one's time and energy on"
    },
    {
      "question": "蒼蠅",
      "answer": "あおばえ,そうよう",
      "meaning": "bluebottle fly, little pest"
    },
    {
      "question": "関係会社",
      "answer": "かんけいがいしゃ",
      "meaning": "affiliated company"
    },
    {
      "question": "瞬ぐ",
      "answer": "まじろぐ",
      "meaning": "to wink, to blink, to twinkle, to flicker"
    },
    {
      "question": "漢名",
      "answer": "かんめい",
      "meaning": "Chinese name (often of plants and animals)"
    },
    {
      "question": "国語科",
      "answer": "こくごか",
      "meaning": "Japanese language (as a school subject in Japan)"
    },
    {
      "question": "観相学",
      "answer": "かんそうがく",
      "meaning": "phrenology, physiognomy"
    },
    {
      "question": "鑞",
      "answer": "ろう",
      "meaning": "solder"
    },
    {
      "question": "建築面積",
      "answer": "けんちくめんせき",
      "meaning": "building area"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝タバコ",
      "answer": "ねタバコ",
      "meaning": "smoking in bed"
    },
    {
      "question": "博労",
      "answer": "ばくろう",
      "meaning": "cattle or horse trader, good judge of horses or cattle"
    },
    {
      "question": "宇宙中継",
      "answer": "うちゅうちゅうけい",
      "meaning": "satellite relay"
    },
    {
      "question": "罰俸",
      "answer": "ばっぽう",
      "meaning": "punitive wage cut"
    },
    {
      "question": "鬼胡桃",
      "answer": "おにぐるみ",
      "meaning": "Manchurian walnut (Juglans mandshurica)"
    },
    {
      "question": "合目的的",
      "answer": "ごうもくてきてき",
      "meaning": "pertinent, appropriate, congruent, apt, fitting"
    },
    {
      "question": "貰い火",
      "answer": "もらいび",
      "meaning": "catching fire (from a neighbouring house on fire)"
    },
    {
      "question": "非人情",
      "answer": "ひにんじょう",
      "meaning": "heartless, inhuman, unfeeling"
    },
    {
      "question": "人馬宮",
      "answer": "じんばきゅう",
      "meaning": "Sagittarius (9th zodiacal sign), the Archer"
    },
    {
      "question": "踏み迷う",
      "answer": "ふみまよう",
      "meaning": "to lose one's way, to go astray"
    },
    {
      "question": "佩用",
      "answer": "はいよう",
      "meaning": "wearing (an insignia, sword, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "忌明け",
      "answer": "いみあけ,きあけ",
      "meaning": "end of mourning"
    },
    {
      "question": "紅軍",
      "answer": "こうぐん",
      "meaning": "Red Army, Chinese Workers' and Peasants' Red Army"
    },
    {
      "question": "公空",
      "answer": "こうくう",
      "meaning": "international airspace, international space"
    },
    {
      "question": "完全変態",
      "answer": "かんぜんへんたい",
      "meaning": "complete metamorphosis, holometabolism"
    },
    {
      "question": "唱名",
      "answer": "しょうみょう",
      "meaning": "intoning the name of the Buddha, chanting the name of the Buddha"
    },
    {
      "question": "原寸",
      "answer": "げんすん",
      "meaning": "actual size, full size"
    },
    {
      "question": "人間の鎖",
      "answer": "にんげんのくさり",
      "meaning": "human chain (chain of people holding hands, usually in protest)"
    },
    {
      "question": "岩垣",
      "answer": "いわかき,いわがき",
      "meaning": "stone wall, natural stone wall"
    },
    {
      "question": "機械翻訳",
      "answer": "きかいほんやく",
      "meaning": "machine translation, mechanical translation, automatic translation"
    },
    {
      "question": "打消し",
      "answer": "うちけし",
      "meaning": "negation, denial, negative"
    },
    {
      "question": "生日",
      "answer": "せいじつ,うまれび,いくひ",
      "meaning": "birthday, lucky day, day of celebration"
    },
    {
      "question": "外港",
      "answer": "がいこう",
      "meaning": "outer port for large city"
    },
    {
      "question": "調性",
      "answer": "ちょうせい",
      "meaning": "tonality"
    },
    {
      "question": "眺め遣る",
      "answer": "ながめやる",
      "meaning": "to gaze out at, to look out over"
    },
    {
      "question": "自動詞",
      "answer": "じどうし",
      "meaning": "intransitive verb"
    },
    {
      "question": "砂糖漬",
      "answer": "さとうづけ",
      "meaning": "preserving in sugar, food preserved in sugar"
    },
    {
      "question": "御宝",
      "answer": "おたから",
      "meaning": "treasure, picture of a treasure ship, money, cash"
    },
    {
      "question": "百方",
      "answer": "ひゃっぽう",
      "meaning": "in every way"
    },
    {
      "question": "院内感染",
      "answer": "いんないかんせん",
      "meaning": "hospital-acquired infection, healthcare-associated infection, HCAI, nosocomial infection"
    },
    {
      "question": "悲歎",
      "answer": "ひたん",
      "meaning": "grief, sorrow, anguish, lamentation"
    },
    {
      "question": "舅姑",
      "answer": "きゅうこ",
      "meaning": "parents-in-law"
    },
    {
      "question": "雄偉",
      "answer": "ゆうい",
      "meaning": "magnificent"
    },
    {
      "question": "乳汁",
      "answer": "にゅうじゅう,ちしる,ちちしる",
      "meaning": "milk (of a mammal), latex (milky fluid found in plants)"
    },
    {
      "question": "老熟",
      "answer": "ろうじゅく",
      "meaning": "maturity"
    },
    {
      "question": "初年",
      "answer": "しょねん",
      "meaning": "first year, early years (of a reign or era)"
    },
    {
      "question": "万寿菊",
      "answer": "まんじゅぎく",
      "meaning": "French marigold (Tagetes patula)"
    },
    {
      "question": "洒落本",
      "answer": "しゃれぼん",
      "meaning": "late Edo-period novelette about life in the red-light districts"
    },
    {
      "question": "歳費",
      "answer": "さいひ",
      "meaning": "annual expenditure"
    },
    {
      "question": "全通",
      "answer": "ぜんつう",
      "meaning": "opening of the whole (railway line)"
    },
    {
      "question": "外国航路",
      "answer": "がいこくこうろ",
      "meaning": "foreign route, ocean route"
    },
    {
      "question": "言わ猿",
      "answer": "いわざる",
      "meaning": "say-not monkey (one of the three wise monkeys)"
    },
    {
      "question": "月割り",
      "answer": "つきわり",
      "meaning": "per month, monthly installment plan, monthly instalment plan"
    },
    {
      "question": "小笠原流",
      "answer": "おがさわらりゅう",
      "meaning": "Ogasawara-ryu (school of etiquette), punctilious etiquette, Ogasawara-ryu (school of archery, incl."
    },
    {
      "question": "主系列星",
      "answer": "しゅけいれつせい",
      "meaning": "main sequence star, main sequence stars"
    },
    {
      "question": "分籍",
      "answer": "ぶんせき",
      "meaning": "establishment of a family registry (separate from one's parents')"
    },
    {
      "question": "有終",
      "answer": "ゆうしゅう",
      "meaning": "perfection"
    },
    {
      "question": "酢酸菌",
      "answer": "さくさんきん",
      "meaning": "acetobacter, acetic acid bacteria"
    },
    {
      "question": "民族自決",
      "answer": "みんぞくじけつ",
      "meaning": "self-determination of peoples"
    },
    {
      "question": "浮世草子",
      "answer": "うきよぞうし",
      "meaning": "(Edo-period variety of) realistic literature, popular stories of everyday life in the Edo period"
    },
    {
      "question": "演繹法",
      "answer": "えんえきほう",
      "meaning": "(method of) deduction"
    },
    {
      "question": "分封",
      "answer": "ぶんぽう",
      "meaning": "hiving off, swarming, dividing a fief"
    },
    {
      "question": "大衆文化",
      "answer": "たいしゅうぶんか",
      "meaning": "mass culture, pop culture, popular culture, culture of the people (as opposed to the elite)"
    },
    {
      "question": "囃子方",
      "answer": "はやしかた",
      "meaning": "(noh) musician, orchestra leader"
    },
    {
      "question": "玩味",
      "answer": "がんみ",
      "meaning": "tasting, relishing, savouring, savoring, appreciation, enjoyment"
    },
    {
      "question": "山梔子",
      "answer": "くちなし,さんしし",
      "meaning": "Cape jasmine (Gardenia jasminoides), Cape jessamine, gardenia, gardenia fruit"
    },
    {
      "question": "時鳥",
      "answer": "ほととぎす",
      "meaning": "lesser cuckoo (Cuculus poliocephalus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "田舎紳士",
      "answer": "いなかしんし",
      "meaning": "country gentleman (esp. one that's slightly unrefined), squire"
    },
    {
      "question": "終身年金",
      "answer": "しゅうしんねんきん",
      "meaning": "life pension, annuity"
    },
    {
      "question": "衰運",
      "answer": "すいうん",
      "meaning": "declining fortunes"
    },
    {
      "question": "密殺",
      "answer": "みっさつ",
      "meaning": "secret butchery"
    },
    {
      "question": "月天子",
      "answer": "がってんし",
      "meaning": "Chandra (Hindu moon god also revered as one of the twelve devas in Shingon Buddhism), moon"
    },
    {
      "question": "銀河群",
      "answer": "ぎんがぐん",
      "meaning": "group of galaxies"
    },
    {
      "question": "帯紐",
      "answer": "おびひも",
      "meaning": "obi and cord fasteners (for a kimono)"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪隠詰め",
      "answer": "せっちんづめ",
      "meaning": "cornering someone, cornering an opponent's king (shogi)"
    },
    {
      "question": "傷兵",
      "answer": "しょうへい",
      "meaning": "wounded soldier"
    },
    {
      "question": "歳寒三友",
      "answer": "さいかんさんゆう",
      "meaning": "the three friends of winter (pine, bamboo and plum)"
    },
    {
      "question": "葛饅頭",
      "answer": "くずまんじゅう",
      "meaning": "ball of bean paste covered with a kudzu starch glaze"
    },
    {
      "question": "母型",
      "answer": "ぼけい",
      "meaning": "matrix (printing)"
    },
    {
      "question": "船蔵",
      "answer": "ふなぐら",
      "meaning": "boathouse, ship's hold, hatch"
    },
    {
      "question": "桜月",
      "answer": "さくらづき",
      "meaning": "third lunar month"
    },
    {
      "question": "打明け話",
      "answer": "うちあけばなし",
      "meaning": "confession, confidential talk, frank talk"
    },
    {
      "question": "内分",
      "answer": "ないぶん",
      "meaning": "secret, confidential"
    },
    {
      "question": "円顔",
      "answer": "まるがお",
      "meaning": "round face, moon face"
    },
    {
      "question": "分離派",
      "answer": "ぶんりは",
      "meaning": "separatists, secessionists"
    },
    {
      "question": "不偏",
      "answer": "ふへん",
      "meaning": "impartiality, neutrality, fairness"
    },
    {
      "question": "大曼荼羅",
      "answer": "だいまんだら",
      "meaning": "great mandala (in Shingon), mandala with an image of each deity"
    },
    {
      "question": "孑々",
      "answer": "ぼうふら,ぼうふり",
      "meaning": "mosquito larva, wriggler, maggot"
    },
    {
      "question": "平茸",
      "answer": "ひらたけ",
      "meaning": "oyster mushroom (Pleurotus ostreatus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "益鳥",
      "answer": "えきちょう",
      "meaning": "beneficial bird"
    },
    {
      "question": "暗点",
      "answer": "あんてん",
      "meaning": "scotoma, scotomatous"
    },
    {
      "question": "打っ殺す",
      "answer": "ぶっころす",
      "meaning": "to beat to death, to kill"
    },
    {
      "question": "精励恪勤",
      "answer": "せいれいかっきん",
      "meaning": "assiduousness, attending diligently to one's study or duties"
    },
    {
      "question": "集塵",
      "answer": "しゅうじん",
      "meaning": "collecting dust"
    },
    {
      "question": "辣韮",
      "answer": "らっきょう,らっきょ",
      "meaning": "Japanese leek (Allium chinense), Chinese onion, sour-sweet pickle of Japanese leek"
    },
    {
      "question": "食言",
      "answer": "しょくげん",
      "meaning": "eat one's words, break one's promises"
    },
    {
      "question": "食間",
      "answer": "しょっかん",
      "meaning": "between meals"
    },
    {
      "question": "千載",
      "answer": "せんざい",
      "meaning": "millennium, one thousand years, long time"
    },
    {
      "question": "蒼惶",
      "answer": "そうこう",
      "meaning": "hurry, bustle"
    },
    {
      "question": "無考え",
      "answer": "むかんがえ",
      "meaning": "thoughtless, heedless, rash"
    },
    {
      "question": "野鄙",
      "answer": "やひ",
      "meaning": "vulgar, mean, base, coarse, crude"
    },
    {
      "question": "救民",
      "answer": "きゅうみん",
      "meaning": "disaster relief"
    },
    {
      "question": "銅器",
      "answer": "どうき",
      "meaning": "copperware"
    },
    {
      "question": "誓文",
      "answer": "せいもん",
      "meaning": "written oath"
    },
    {
      "question": "糒",
      "answer": "ほしい,ほしいい",
      "meaning": "dried boiled rice used mainly as provisions of samurai troops and travelers (travellers)"
    },
    {
      "question": "隠り世",
      "answer": "かくりよ",
      "meaning": "afterlife, realm of the dead"
    },
    {
      "question": "課役",
      "answer": "かえき",
      "meaning": "distribution of assignments"
    },
    {
      "question": "御用邸",
      "answer": "ごようてい",
      "meaning": "imperial villa"
    },
    {
      "question": "光学異性",
      "answer": "こうがくいせい",
      "meaning": "optical isomerism"
    },
    {
      "question": "共済組合",
      "answer": "きょうさいくみあい",
      "meaning": "cooperative society, mutual-benefit association"
    },
    {
      "question": "産炭",
      "answer": "さんたん",
      "meaning": "coal mining"
    },
    {
      "question": "失業対策",
      "answer": "しつぎょうたいさく",
      "meaning": "relief work for the unemployed"
    },
    {
      "question": "立行司",
      "answer": "たてぎょうじ",
      "meaning": "head referee"
    },
    {
      "question": "開村",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "平温",
      "answer": "へいおん",
      "meaning": "the usual temperature"
    },
    {
      "question": "感作",
      "answer": "かんさ",
      "meaning": "(immunological) sensitization"
    },
    {
      "question": "改質",
      "answer": "かいしつ",
      "meaning": "reforming (esp. gasoline), reformulation, modifying"
    },
    {
      "question": "基剤",
      "answer": "きざい",
      "meaning": "base (e.g. of an ointment or suppository)"
    },
    {
      "question": "一決",
      "answer": "いっけつ",
      "meaning": "agreed, settled"
    },
    {
      "question": "帆影",
      "answer": "ほかげ",
      "meaning": "sight of a sail (in the distance)"
    },
    {
      "question": "長波",
      "answer": "ちょうは",
      "meaning": "long wave"
    },
    {
      "question": "居食い",
      "answer": "いぐい",
      "meaning": "living in idleness"
    },
    {
      "question": "関係詞",
      "answer": "かんけいし",
      "meaning": "relative"
    },
    {
      "question": "徒者",
      "answer": "いたずらもの,ただもの",
      "meaning": "mischief-maker, trickster, prankster, lascivious person (esp. a loose woman), useless fellow, mouse,"
    },
    {
      "question": "一つ書き",
      "answer": "ひとつがき",
      "meaning": "an item, itemization, itemisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "棚卸",
      "answer": "たなおろし",
      "meaning": "stocktaking, inventory count, faultfinding"
    },
    {
      "question": "北洋軍閥",
      "answer": "ほくようぐんばつ",
      "meaning": "Beiyang Army"
    },
    {
      "question": "低率",
      "answer": "ていりつ",
      "meaning": "low rate"
    },
    {
      "question": "石版画",
      "answer": "せきばんが",
      "meaning": "lithograph"
    },
    {
      "question": "安全剃刀",
      "answer": "あんぜんかみそり",
      "meaning": "safety razor"
    },
    {
      "question": "算える",
      "answer": "かぞえる",
      "meaning": "to count, to enumerate"
    },
    {
      "question": "行政学",
      "answer": "ぎょうせいがく",
      "meaning": "public administration"
    },
    {
      "question": "西郊",
      "answer": "せいこう",
      "meaning": "western suburb"
    },
    {
      "question": "雷汞",
      "answer": "らいこう",
      "meaning": "mercury fulminate"
    },
    {
      "question": "丼勘定",
      "answer": "どんぶりかんじょう",
      "meaning": "rough estimate, sloppy accounting, slapdash bookkeeping"
    },
    {
      "question": "球乗り",
      "answer": "たまのり",
      "meaning": "balancing on a ball"
    },
    {
      "question": "上廻る",
      "answer": "うわまわる",
      "meaning": "to exceed (esp. figures: profits, unemployment rate, etc.), to surpass, to be more than, to be bette"
    },
    {
      "question": "先行上映",
      "answer": "せんこうじょうえい",
      "meaning": "advance(d) screening (of a movie)"
    },
    {
      "question": "第四紀",
      "answer": "だいよんき,だいしき",
      "meaning": "Quaternary period"
    },
    {
      "question": "蛇の目傘",
      "answer": "じゃのめがさ",
      "meaning": "paper umbrella (with a bull's-eye design)"
    },
    {
      "question": "文殊菩薩",
      "answer": "もんじゅぼさつ",
      "meaning": "Manjusri (Bodhisattva), Monju, Monjushuri, Wenshu"
    },
    {
      "question": "迎え角",
      "answer": "むかえかく",
      "meaning": "angle of attack"
    },
    {
      "question": "足触り",
      "answer": "あしざわり",
      "meaning": "feel (to the foot), feel (underfoot)"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪業",
      "answer": "あくごう,あくぎょう",
      "meaning": "bad karma, sinful deed, evil deed, misdeed, wrongdoing, wickedness"
    },
    {
      "question": "積み出す",
      "answer": "つみだす",
      "meaning": "to send off"
    },
    {
      "question": "愛孫",
      "answer": "あいそん",
      "meaning": "one's beloved grandchild"
    },
    {
      "question": "祇園社",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "産土神",
      "answer": "うぶすながみ",
      "meaning": "guardian deity of one's birthplace"
    },
    {
      "question": "溶解度",
      "answer": "ようかいど",
      "meaning": "solubility"
    },
    {
      "question": "樹状突起",
      "answer": "じゅじょうとっき",
      "meaning": "dendrite, dendron"
    },
    {
      "question": "御紋",
      "answer": "ごもん",
      "meaning": "crest of a noble family"
    },
    {
      "question": "闌",
      "answer": "たけなわ",
      "meaning": "height (of summer, party, etc.), (in) full swing"
    },
    {
      "question": "声を吞む",
      "answer": "こえをのむ",
      "meaning": "to choke up, to be speechless, to hold one's tongue"
    },
    {
      "question": "伽羅蕗",
      "answer": "きゃらぶき",
      "meaning": "stalks of butterbur boiled in soy sauce"
    },
    {
      "question": "耳糞",
      "answer": "みみくそ",
      "meaning": "earwax, cerumen"
    },
    {
      "question": "棒棒鶏",
      "answer": "バンバンジー",
      "meaning": "bang bang chicken (Szechuan dish of chicken in a spicy sauce)"
    },
    {
      "question": "反照",
      "answer": "はんしょう",
      "meaning": "reflection, evening glow, sunset glow"
    },
    {
      "question": "桜鯛",
      "answer": "さくらだい",
      "meaning": "cherry anthias (Sacura margaritacea)"
    },
    {
      "question": "土工",
      "answer": "どこう",
      "meaning": "earthwork, earthworks, laborer, labourer, navvy, construction worker"
    },
    {
      "question": "風浪",
      "answer": "ふうろう",
      "meaning": "wind and wave, rough seas"
    },
    {
      "question": "快食",
      "answer": "かいしょく",
      "meaning": "good appetite"
    },
    {
      "question": "国税庁",
      "answer": "こくぜいちょう",
      "meaning": "National Tax Agency (Japan)"
    },
    {
      "question": "定率",
      "answer": "ていりつ",
      "meaning": "fixed rate"
    },
    {
      "question": "襟先",
      "answer": "えりさき",
      "meaning": "collar points, tip of a collar"
    },
    {
      "question": "親泣かせ",
      "answer": "おやなかせ",
      "meaning": "(being the) bane of one's parents, disgraceful child, disgrace"
    },
    {
      "question": "有蓋",
      "answer": "ゆうがい",
      "meaning": "covered, roofed, lidded"
    },
    {
      "question": "喧喧囂囂",
      "answer": "けんけんごうごう",
      "meaning": "wild uproar, pandemonium, clamor of voices, tumult, noisy, uproarious, clamorous"
    },
    {
      "question": "反歩",
      "answer": "たんぶ",
      "meaning": "unit of land area (approx. one-tenth hectare)"
    },
    {
      "question": "朗誦",
      "answer": "ろうしょう",
      "meaning": "recitation, chant"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪娘",
      "answer": "ゆきむすめ",
      "meaning": "snow woman"
    },
    {
      "question": "一掬",
      "answer": "いっきく",
      "meaning": "small amount"
    },
    {
      "question": "立ち騒ぐ",
      "answer": "たちさわぐ",
      "meaning": "to make a din"
    },
    {
      "question": "有意差",
      "answer": "ゆういさ",
      "meaning": "significant difference, statistical significance"
    },
    {
      "question": "米語",
      "answer": "べいご",
      "meaning": "American English"
    },
    {
      "question": "垂死",
      "answer": "すいし",
      "meaning": "on the verge of dying"
    },
    {
      "question": "懇書",
      "answer": "こんしょ",
      "meaning": "your kind letter"
    },
    {
      "question": "示度",
      "answer": "しど",
      "meaning": "indication, (thermometer) reading"
    },
    {
      "question": "称讃",
      "answer": "しょうさん",
      "meaning": "praise, admiration, commendation, approbation"
    },
    {
      "question": "先んずる",
      "answer": "さきんずる",
      "meaning": "to go before, to precede, to forestall, to anticipate"
    },
    {
      "question": "菫青石",
      "answer": "きんせいせき",
      "meaning": "cordierite"
    },
    {
      "question": "青海波",
      "answer": "せいがいは",
      "meaning": "seigaiha, wave pattern"
    },
    {
      "question": "組子",
      "answer": "くみこ",
      "meaning": "member (of a group led by a kumigashira), member (of a fire brigade), muntin, mullion, member, fret"
    },
    {
      "question": "摸索",
      "answer": "もさく",
      "meaning": "groping (for), fumbling around (for), searching (for an answer, solution, etc.), trying to find"
    },
    {
      "question": "ヤミ金融",
      "answer": "ヤミきんゆう",
      "meaning": "black-market lending, illegal loan"
    },
    {
      "question": "主客転倒",
      "answer": "しゅかくてんとう,しゅきゃくてんとう",
      "meaning": "reversing the order of (relative) importance (of), putting the cart before the horse, the tables bei"
    },
    {
      "question": "水準器",
      "answer": "すいじゅんき",
      "meaning": "spirit level, level, leveling instrument, levelling instrument"
    },
    {
      "question": "御墨付き",
      "answer": "おすみつき",
      "meaning": "certificate, certified document, authorization, authorisation, (the) thumbs up, seal of approval, pa"
    },
    {
      "question": "石炭殻",
      "answer": "せきたんがら",
      "meaning": "(coal) cinders"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉅鹿",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "私的独占",
      "answer": "してきどくせん",
      "meaning": "private monopolization, private monopoly"
    },
    {
      "question": "慣用",
      "answer": "かんよう",
      "meaning": "customary use, common usage, general usage"
    },
    {
      "question": "其れこそ",
      "answer": "それこそ",
      "meaning": "especially, particularly, surely, clearly, unmistakably, as if, as though, just like"
    },
    {
      "question": "平場",
      "answer": "ひらば",
      "meaning": "flat ground, seats immediately in front of the stage (e.g. in kabuki), multi-brand display area (in"
    },
    {
      "question": "対語",
      "answer": "ついご,たいご",
      "meaning": "kanji compound formed of opposing elements, antonym, conversation (face-to-face)"
    },
    {
      "question": "準用",
      "answer": "じゅんよう",
      "meaning": "to apply (the law) with necessary modifications, to apply mutatis mutandis, to apply correspondingly"
    },
    {
      "question": "退庁",
      "answer": "たいちょう",
      "meaning": "leaving one's office"
    },
    {
      "question": "賢兄",
      "answer": "けんけい",
      "meaning": "wise elder brother, polite reference to another's older brother, or to one's senior"
    },
    {
      "question": "盤領",
      "answer": "まるえり,ばんりょう,あげくび",
      "meaning": "round collar (of traditional Japanese clothing), neckband, round upright collar (on some traditional"
    },
    {
      "question": "検認",
      "answer": "けんにん",
      "meaning": "probate, validation, certification, accreditation"
    },
    {
      "question": "最高法規",
      "answer": "さいこうほうき",
      "meaning": "supreme law (of the land)"
    },
    {
      "question": "銀葉",
      "answer": "ぎんよう",
      "meaning": "thin sheet of silver, silver foil, silverleaf, censer, incense burner made of a sheet of mica hemmed"
    },
    {
      "question": "啼鳥",
      "answer": "ていちょう",
      "meaning": "chirping bird, singing bird"
    },
    {
      "question": "飲み回す",
      "answer": "のみまわす",
      "meaning": "to pass the cup round"
    },
    {
      "question": "宇宙塵",
      "answer": "うちゅうじん,うちゅうごみ",
      "meaning": "space dust, cosmic dust, interstellar dust, space debris, orbital debris"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉛毒",
      "answer": "えんどく",
      "meaning": "toxic substance in lead, lead poisoning"
    },
    {
      "question": "豈",
      "answer": "あに",
      "meaning": "never, by no means, not in the least, in no way, why, what for"
    },
    {
      "question": "ノルド語",
      "answer": "ノルドご",
      "meaning": "Norse, Nordic languages (Danish, Faroese, Icelandic, Norwegian, Swedish)"
    },
    {
      "question": "多体問題",
      "answer": "たたいもんだい",
      "meaning": "n-body problem, many-body problem"
    },
    {
      "question": "速急",
      "answer": "そっきゅう",
      "meaning": "immediate, quick, sudden"
    },
    {
      "question": "髄膜",
      "answer": "ずいまく",
      "meaning": "meninges"
    },
    {
      "question": "第三紀",
      "answer": "だいさんき",
      "meaning": "the Tertiary period"
    },
    {
      "question": "給排水",
      "answer": "きゅうはいすい",
      "meaning": "water supply and drainage"
    },
    {
      "question": "鞭打ち症",
      "answer": "むちうちしょう",
      "meaning": "whiplash"
    },
    {
      "question": "抛物線",
      "answer": "ほうぶつせん",
      "meaning": "parabola"
    },
    {
      "question": "損金",
      "answer": "そんきん",
      "meaning": "financial loss"
    },
    {
      "question": "綿織物",
      "answer": "めんおりもの",
      "meaning": "cotton fabrics, cotton textiles"
    },
    {
      "question": "畏友",
      "answer": "いゆう",
      "meaning": "one's esteemed friend"
    },
    {
      "question": "酔興",
      "answer": "すいきょう",
      "meaning": "whim, vagary, capriciousness, eccentricity"
    },
    {
      "question": "な行",
      "answer": "なぎょう",
      "meaning": "the 'na' column of the Japanese syllabary table (na, ni, nu, ne, no)"
    },
    {
      "question": "匪賊",
      "answer": "ひぞく",
      "meaning": "bandit, rebel"
    },
    {
      "question": "難行苦行",
      "answer": "なんぎょうくぎょう",
      "meaning": "penance, hardship"
    },
    {
      "question": "参鶏湯",
      "answer": "サムゲタン",
      "meaning": "samgyetang (Korean dish), chicken ginseng soup"
    },
    {
      "question": "熊襲",
      "answer": "くまそ",
      "meaning": "Kumaso (ancient Japanese people resident to southern Kyushu)"
    },
    {
      "question": "化生",
      "answer": "かせい,けしょう",
      "meaning": "growth, metamorphosis, goblin"
    },
    {
      "question": "汽水",
      "answer": "きすい",
      "meaning": "brackish water"
    },
    {
      "question": "二六時中",
      "answer": "にろくじちゅう",
      "meaning": "night and day, all the time"
    },
    {
      "question": "化仏",
      "answer": "けぶつ",
      "meaning": "transformed Buddha"
    },
    {
      "question": "激低",
      "answer": "げきひく",
      "meaning": "extremely low"
    },
    {
      "question": "物惜しみ",
      "answer": "ものおしみ",
      "meaning": "stinginess"
    },
    {
      "question": "単于",
      "answer": "ぜんう",
      "meaning": "Chanyu, supreme leader of the Xiongnu people"
    },
    {
      "question": "令孫",
      "answer": "れいそん",
      "meaning": "your grandchild"
    },
    {
      "question": "戯る",
      "answer": "たわむる",
      "meaning": "to be playful, to gambol, to be amused (with something), to play, to sport, to frolic, to joke"
    },
    {
      "question": "京女",
      "answer": "きょうおんな",
      "meaning": "Kyoto woman"
    },
    {
      "question": "改版",
      "answer": "かいはん",
      "meaning": "revision, revised edition"
    },
    {
      "question": "夕影",
      "answer": "ゆうかげ",
      "meaning": "light of the setting sun, figure lit by the evening sun"
    },
    {
      "question": "ハーフ顔",
      "answer": "ハーフがお",
      "meaning": "mixed-race features"
    },
    {
      "question": "電着",
      "answer": "でんちゃく",
      "meaning": "electrodeposition"
    },
    {
      "question": "名残の雪",
      "answer": "なごりのゆき",
      "meaning": "lingering snow, snowfall at the end of the winter or the beginning of spring"
    },
    {
      "question": "魏志",
      "answer": "ぎし",
      "meaning": "the history of Wei"
    },
    {
      "question": "小頭",
      "answer": "こがしら",
      "meaning": "head of an organizational section, head of an organisational section"
    },
    {
      "question": "両損",
      "answer": "りょうそん,りょうぞん",
      "meaning": "loss on both sides"
    },
    {
      "question": "排液",
      "answer": "はいえき",
      "meaning": "drainage, sewerage"
    },
    {
      "question": "貸し衣装",
      "answer": "かしいしょう",
      "meaning": "clothing or costumes for rent"
    },
    {
      "question": "特別活動",
      "answer": "とくべつかつどう",
      "meaning": "extra-curricular activities, special activities"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷評",
      "answer": "れいひょう",
      "meaning": "sarcasm, sneer, jeer"
    },
    {
      "question": "立米",
      "answer": "りゅうべい",
      "meaning": "cubic meter"
    },
    {
      "question": "格天井",
      "answer": "ごうてんじょう",
      "meaning": "coffered ceiling"
    },
    {
      "question": "蒸し菓子",
      "answer": "むしがし",
      "meaning": "steamed confection (e.g. manjū, uirō, steamed yōkan), steamed cake"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝穢い",
      "answer": "いぎたない",
      "meaning": "sound asleep, fast asleep, untidy, slovenly"
    },
    {
      "question": "出来合う",
      "answer": "できあう",
      "meaning": "to be ready-made, to become intimate with"
    },
    {
      "question": "伝馬船",
      "answer": "てんません,てんまぶね",
      "meaning": "large sculling boat"
    },
    {
      "question": "盂蘭盆",
      "answer": "うらぼん",
      "meaning": "Bon festival, Feast of Lanterns"
    },
    {
      "question": "クルド人",
      "answer": "クルドじん",
      "meaning": "Kurd"
    },
    {
      "question": "提灯持ち",
      "answer": "ちょうちんもち",
      "meaning": "lantern bearer, flatterer, booster, brown-noser"
    },
    {
      "question": "薬種屋",
      "answer": "やくしゅや",
      "meaning": "apothecary, druggist, chemist, pharmacy, drugstore"
    },
    {
      "question": "内向性",
      "answer": "ないこうせい",
      "meaning": "introversion"
    },
    {
      "question": "乗り乗り",
      "answer": "のりのり",
      "meaning": "in high spirits"
    },
    {
      "question": "三拝九拝",
      "answer": "さんぱいきゅうはい",
      "meaning": "kowtowing, bowing repeatedly"
    },
    {
      "question": "嬬恋",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "茶臼",
      "answer": "ちゃうす",
      "meaning": "tea grinding mortar (hand mill)"
    },
    {
      "question": "通勤快速",
      "answer": "つうきんかいそく",
      "meaning": "commuter express, commuter limited express, rapid-service commuter train"
    },
    {
      "question": "県都",
      "answer": "けんと",
      "meaning": "prefectural capital"
    },
    {
      "question": "法的整理",
      "answer": "ほうてきせいり",
      "meaning": "legal liquidation, court-mediated winding-up of a company"
    },
    {
      "question": "分引き",
      "answer": "ぶびき",
      "meaning": "discount"
    },
    {
      "question": "正札",
      "answer": "しょうふだ",
      "meaning": "price tag, price label, tag displaying a base price which cannot be reduced by negotiation"
    },
    {
      "question": "僧徒",
      "answer": "そうと",
      "meaning": "priests, monks"
    },
    {
      "question": "三杯酢",
      "answer": "さんばいず",
      "meaning": "vinegar, soy sauce and mirin (or sugar) mixed in roughly equal proportions"
    },
    {
      "question": "腺病質",
      "answer": "せんびょうしつ",
      "meaning": "scrofulosis, being in delicate health, lymphatic temperament"
    },
    {
      "question": "涙金",
      "answer": "なみだきん,なみだかね",
      "meaning": "(token amount of) consolation money"
    },
    {
      "question": "農工",
      "answer": "のうこう",
      "meaning": "agriculture and industry"
    },
    {
      "question": "奉読",
      "answer": "ほうどく",
      "meaning": "respectful reading"
    },
    {
      "question": "眉山",
      "answer": "まゆやま",
      "meaning": "peak of the arch of an eyebrow"
    },
    {
      "question": "昭和維新",
      "answer": "しょうわいしん",
      "meaning": "Shōwa restoration, Showa restoration, call for Imperial restoration by militarists in the 1930s"
    },
    {
      "question": "外蓋",
      "answer": "そとぶた",
      "meaning": "outer lid"
    },
    {
      "question": "香典返し",
      "answer": "こうでんがえし",
      "meaning": "present given in return for funeral offering"
    },
    {
      "question": "聞香",
      "answer": "ぶんこう,もんこう,ききこう",
      "meaning": "smelling incense, savoring incense, distinguishing incense by smell, incense-smelling party"
    },
    {
      "question": "射幸",
      "answer": "しゃこう",
      "meaning": "speculation"
    },
    {
      "question": "人毎",
      "answer": "ひとごと",
      "meaning": "with each person, with everyone"
    },
    {
      "question": "遠慮勝ち",
      "answer": "えんりょがち",
      "meaning": "shy, diffident, retiring, reserved"
    },
    {
      "question": "汎神論",
      "answer": "はんしんろん",
      "meaning": "pantheism"
    },
    {
      "question": "北爆",
      "answer": "ほくばく",
      "meaning": "bombing North (Vietnam)"
    },
    {
      "question": "道府県",
      "answer": "どうふけん",
      "meaning": "prefectures of Japan (excluding Tokyo)"
    },
    {
      "question": "王公",
      "answer": "おうこう",
      "meaning": "king and princes, noble rank"
    },
    {
      "question": "障礙",
      "answer": "しょうがい,しょうげ",
      "meaning": "obstacle, impediment, hindrance, difficulty, barrier, handicap, impairment, disability, disorder, ma"
    },
    {
      "question": "社会集団",
      "answer": "しゃかいしゅうだん",
      "meaning": "social group"
    },
    {
      "question": "愚生",
      "answer": "ぐせい",
      "meaning": "I, me"
    },
    {
      "question": "瓔珞",
      "answer": "ようらく",
      "meaning": "personal ornament (adorned with gemstones, and usu. worn by the nobility in ancient India or adornin"
    },
    {
      "question": "耳環",
      "answer": "みみわ",
      "meaning": "earring (non-pierced), helix"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜暗",
      "answer": "やあん",
      "meaning": "dead of night, shades of night, black of night"
    },
    {
      "question": "春の七草",
      "answer": "はるのななくさ",
      "meaning": "seven vernal flowers (Java water dropwort, shepherd's purse, Jersey cudweed, common chickweed, Japan"
    },
    {
      "question": "投扇興",
      "answer": "とうせんきょう",
      "meaning": "fan tossing game"
    },
    {
      "question": "真否",
      "answer": "しんぴ",
      "meaning": "true or false"
    },
    {
      "question": "跡を絶つ",
      "answer": "あとをたつ",
      "meaning": "to wipe out, to put an end to"
    },
    {
      "question": "宙釣り",
      "answer": "ちゅうづり",
      "meaning": "hanging in midair, suspended in midair, midair stunt, aerial stunt"
    },
    {
      "question": "為替取引",
      "answer": "かわせとりひき",
      "meaning": "currency trading (usu. foreign), exchange dealing, exchange transaction"
    },
    {
      "question": "教委",
      "answer": "きょうい",
      "meaning": "Board of Education"
    },
    {
      "question": "脚半",
      "answer": "きゃはん",
      "meaning": "gaiters, leggings, puttees"
    },
    {
      "question": "貝焼き",
      "answer": "かいやき",
      "meaning": "shellfish baked in the shell, abalone, scallops, etc. simmered in the shell"
    },
    {
      "question": "百度参り",
      "answer": "ひゃくどまいり",
      "meaning": "hundred times worship (e.g. visiting a shrine or temple a hundred times for prayer, walking back and"
    },
    {
      "question": "緩り",
      "answer": "ゆるり",
      "meaning": "unhurriedly, leisurely, slowly, relaxedly, taking one's time"
    },
    {
      "question": "浮き雲",
      "answer": "うきぐも,うきくも",
      "meaning": "drifting cloud, floating cloud, instability"
    },
    {
      "question": "印刷局",
      "answer": "いんさつきょく",
      "meaning": "Printing Bureau"
    },
    {
      "question": "寮歌",
      "answer": "りょうか",
      "meaning": "dormitory song"
    },
    {
      "question": "敗報",
      "answer": "はいほう",
      "meaning": "news of defeat"
    },
    {
      "question": "破婚",
      "answer": "はこん",
      "meaning": "marriage breakup, divorce, engagement breakup"
    },
    {
      "question": "六義",
      "answer": "りくぎ,ろくぎ",
      "meaning": "six forms of the Shi Jing (genre: folk song, festal song, hymn; style: narrative, explicit compariso"
    },
    {
      "question": "推算",
      "answer": "すいさん",
      "meaning": "estimation, rough calculation"
    },
    {
      "question": "破調",
      "answer": "はちょう",
      "meaning": "out of tune, (poetic) broken meter"
    },
    {
      "question": "倍角",
      "answer": "ばいかく",
      "meaning": "double size of character"
    },
    {
      "question": "角帽",
      "answer": "かくぼう",
      "meaning": "mortarboard, trencher, (square) academic cap formerly worn by Japanese university students"
    },
    {
      "question": "生き作り",
      "answer": "いきづくり",
      "meaning": "sashimi prepared from live fish, arranged in its original shape"
    },
    {
      "question": "内掛け",
      "answer": "うちがけ",
      "meaning": "inside leg trip"
    },
    {
      "question": "人民裁判",
      "answer": "じんみんさいばん",
      "meaning": "people's trial (court)"
    },
    {
      "question": "質量数",
      "answer": "しつりょうすう",
      "meaning": "mass number"
    },
    {
      "question": "耽美主義",
      "answer": "たんびしゅぎ",
      "meaning": "aestheticism"
    },
    {
      "question": "刀痕",
      "answer": "とうこん",
      "meaning": "sword scar"
    },
    {
      "question": "副本",
      "answer": "ふくほん",
      "meaning": "duplicate, copy"
    },
    {
      "question": "月経不順",
      "answer": "げっけいふじゅん",
      "meaning": "menstrual irregularity, irregular menstruation"
    },
    {
      "question": "東行",
      "answer": "とうこう",
      "meaning": "going east, heading eastward"
    },
    {
      "question": "俗臭",
      "answer": "ぞくしゅう",
      "meaning": "vulgarity, worldliness"
    },
    {
      "question": "生一本",
      "answer": "きいっぽん",
      "meaning": "straight-forwardness, honesty, purity"
    },
    {
      "question": "花やか",
      "answer": "はなやか",
      "meaning": "showy, brilliant, gorgeous, florid, gay"
    },
    {
      "question": "初荷",
      "answer": "はつに",
      "meaning": "first cargo of the year"
    },
    {
      "question": "他用",
      "answer": "たよう",
      "meaning": "other business, other use, using for another purpose"
    },
    {
      "question": "凍雨",
      "answer": "とうう",
      "meaning": "winter rain, ice pellet"
    },
    {
      "question": "吹流し",
      "answer": "ふきながし",
      "meaning": "streamer, pennant, windsock"
    },
    {
      "question": "盲進",
      "answer": "もうしん",
      "meaning": "rushing recklessly, presumption"
    },
    {
      "question": "球審",
      "answer": "きゅうしん",
      "meaning": "umpire-in-chief, plate umpire"
    },
    {
      "question": "天顔",
      "answer": "てんがん",
      "meaning": "emperor's countenance"
    },
    {
      "question": "邪欲",
      "answer": "じゃよく",
      "meaning": "evil desire"
    },
    {
      "question": "紫斑",
      "answer": "しはん",
      "meaning": "purple spot"
    },
    {
      "question": "簡単服",
      "answer": "かんたんふく",
      "meaning": "simple or lightweight clothing"
    },
    {
      "question": "純良",
      "answer": "じゅんりょう",
      "meaning": "pure and good, unmixed and of high quality, good-natured, genuine, wholesome"
    },
    {
      "question": "大呼",
      "answer": "たいこ",
      "meaning": "loud cry, shout"
    },
    {
      "question": "錐体",
      "answer": "すいたい",
      "meaning": "cone, pyramid, conic solid, petrosa, retinal cone"
    },
    {
      "question": "ジニ係数",
      "answer": "ジニけいすう",
      "meaning": "Gini coefficient, Gini's coefficient"
    },
    {
      "question": "苧麻",
      "answer": "からむし,ちょま,まお",
      "meaning": "ramie (Boehmeria nivea var. nipononivea)"
    },
    {
      "question": "均し",
      "answer": "ならし",
      "meaning": "average, leveling, levelling"
    },
    {
      "question": "虎落笛",
      "answer": "もがりぶえ",
      "meaning": "winter wind whistling through a bamboo fence"
    },
    {
      "question": "煖炉",
      "answer": "だんろ",
      "meaning": "fireplace, hearth, stove"
    },
    {
      "question": "麻実",
      "answer": "おのみ",
      "meaning": "hemp seed"
    },
    {
      "question": "真実一路",
      "answer": "しんじついちろ",
      "meaning": "path of sincerity"
    },
    {
      "question": "主査",
      "answer": "しゅさ",
      "meaning": "chief examiner or investigator"
    },
    {
      "question": "ナ行",
      "answer": "ナぎょう",
      "meaning": "the 'na' column of the Japanese syllabary table (na, ni, nu, ne, no)"
    },
    {
      "question": "貴校",
      "answer": "きこう",
      "meaning": "(your) school"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷コー",
      "answer": "れいコー",
      "meaning": "ice coffee, cold coffee"
    },
    {
      "question": "統語論",
      "answer": "とうごろん",
      "meaning": "syntax"
    },
    {
      "question": "拮抗作用",
      "answer": "きっこうさよう",
      "meaning": "antagonism"
    },
    {
      "question": "医業",
      "answer": "いぎょう",
      "meaning": "medical practice"
    },
    {
      "question": "無灯",
      "answer": "むとう",
      "meaning": "without lights"
    },
    {
      "question": "遊廓",
      "answer": "ゆうかく",
      "meaning": "(licensed) red light district"
    },
    {
      "question": "木棺",
      "answer": "もっかん",
      "meaning": "wooden coffin"
    },
    {
      "question": "画竜",
      "answer": "がりょう,がりゅう",
      "meaning": "drawn dragon, painted dragon"
    },
    {
      "question": "音飛び",
      "answer": "おととび",
      "meaning": "skipping (e.g. on a CD), jumping"
    },
    {
      "question": "終世",
      "answer": "しゅうせい",
      "meaning": "all one's life, throughout one's life, as long as one lives"
    },
    {
      "question": "綴じ込む",
      "answer": "とじこむ",
      "meaning": "to (keep on) file"
    },
    {
      "question": "授かり婚",
      "answer": "さずかりこん",
      "meaning": "marriage due to unintended pregnancy, shotgun wedding"
    },
    {
      "question": "県人会",
      "answer": "けんじんかい",
      "meaning": "association of people from the same prefecture"
    },
    {
      "question": "線審",
      "answer": "せんしん",
      "meaning": "line judge, linesman"
    },
    {
      "question": "欣快",
      "answer": "きんかい",
      "meaning": "pleasant, delightful"
    },
    {
      "question": "綬章",
      "answer": "じゅしょう",
      "meaning": "ribbon, cordon"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄雪",
      "answer": "うすゆき",
      "meaning": "light snowfall"
    },
    {
      "question": "生老病死",
      "answer": "しょうろうびょうし",
      "meaning": "the four inevitables in human life (birth, aging, sickness, and death)"
    },
    {
      "question": "過払い",
      "answer": "かばらい,かはらい",
      "meaning": "overpayment, paying too much"
    },
    {
      "question": "二重窓",
      "answer": "にじゅうまど",
      "meaning": "double-glazed window, double window, storm window"
    },
    {
      "question": "十三夜",
      "answer": "じゅうさんや",
      "meaning": "13th day (of the moon), the night of the 13th day of 9th lunar month"
    },
    {
      "question": "月賦",
      "answer": "げっぷ",
      "meaning": "monthly installment (instalment), monthly payment"
    },
    {
      "question": "遅発",
      "answer": "ちはつ",
      "meaning": "starting late or behind schedule"
    },
    {
      "question": "条痕",
      "answer": "じょうこん",
      "meaning": "linear mark, abrasion, scratch, streak"
    },
    {
      "question": "休閑地",
      "answer": "きゅうかんち",
      "meaning": "fallow land"
    },
    {
      "question": "易姓革命",
      "answer": "えきせいかくめい",
      "meaning": "revolution (change of dynasty) decreed by Heaven when the incumbent emperor is found lacking in mora"
    },
    {
      "question": "地租",
      "answer": "ちそ",
      "meaning": "land tax"
    },
    {
      "question": "破傷風菌",
      "answer": "はしょうふうきん",
      "meaning": "Clostridium tetani (tetanus bacillus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "計算器",
      "answer": "けいさんき",
      "meaning": "calculator, computer"
    },
    {
      "question": "密謀",
      "answer": "みつぼう",
      "meaning": "conspiracy"
    },
    {
      "question": "鼂錯",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "声門",
      "answer": "せいもん",
      "meaning": "glottis"
    },
    {
      "question": "丁と",
      "answer": "ちょうと",
      "meaning": "with a clang, with a bang, with a crash"
    },
    {
      "question": "家父長制",
      "answer": "かふちょうせい",
      "meaning": "patriarchy, system of patriarchy"
    },
    {
      "question": "甲鉄艦",
      "answer": "こうてつかん",
      "meaning": "armored ship, armoured ship"
    },
    {
      "question": "式日",
      "answer": "しきじつ",
      "meaning": "day of a ceremony or event"
    },
    {
      "question": "吊り輪",
      "answer": "つりわ",
      "meaning": "(gymnastic) rings"
    },
    {
      "question": "曲流",
      "answer": "きょくりゅう",
      "meaning": "meandering stream"
    },
    {
      "question": "談ずる",
      "answer": "だんずる",
      "meaning": "to talk, to discuss, to debate, to negotiate"
    },
    {
      "question": "好い加減",
      "answer": "いいかげん",
      "meaning": "irresponsible, perfunctory, careless, lukewarm, half-baked, halfhearted, vague, reasonable, moderate"
    },
    {
      "question": "兵農",
      "answer": "へいのう",
      "meaning": "soldiers and farmers"
    },
    {
      "question": "弘安",
      "answer": "こうあん",
      "meaning": "Kōan era (1278.2.29-1288.4.28)"
    },
    {
      "question": "幸若舞",
      "answer": "こうわかまい",
      "meaning": "style of recitative dance popular during the Muromachi period (often with a military theme)"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒ロリ",
      "answer": "くろロリ",
      "meaning": "black Lolita (fashion style)"
    },
    {
      "question": "労務管理",
      "answer": "ろうむかんり",
      "meaning": "labor management, labour management"
    },
    {
      "question": "攫む",
      "answer": "つかむ",
      "meaning": "to seize, to catch, to grasp, to grip, to grab, to clutch, to hold, to catch hold of, to lay one's h"
    },
    {
      "question": "住宅手当",
      "answer": "じゅうたくてあて",
      "meaning": "housing allowance"
    },
    {
      "question": "幽冥界",
      "answer": "ゆうめいかい",
      "meaning": "hades, realm of the dead"
    },
    {
      "question": "扁桃炎",
      "answer": "へんとうえん",
      "meaning": "tonsillitis"
    },
    {
      "question": "再診",
      "answer": "さいしん",
      "meaning": "re-examination, follow-up examination"
    },
    {
      "question": "生理休暇",
      "answer": "せいりきゅうか",
      "meaning": "menstrual leave"
    },
    {
      "question": "待避所",
      "answer": "たいひじょ",
      "meaning": "turnout, passing-place"
    },
    {
      "question": "満天星",
      "answer": "どうだんつつじ",
      "meaning": "Enkianthus perulatus (species of flowering plant in the Ericaceae family)"
    },
    {
      "question": "替え刃",
      "answer": "かえば",
      "meaning": "spare or new razor blade"
    },
    {
      "question": "別送",
      "answer": "べっそう",
      "meaning": "separate mail, separate shipment"
    },
    {
      "question": "内港",
      "answer": "ないこう",
      "meaning": "inner harbour, inner harbor"
    },
    {
      "question": "所出",
      "answer": "しょしゅつ",
      "meaning": "one's birthplace, source"
    },
    {
      "question": "全音符",
      "answer": "ぜんおんぷ",
      "meaning": "whole note, semibreve"
    },
    {
      "question": "游泳",
      "answer": "ゆうえい",
      "meaning": "swimming, bathing, getting on in the world"
    },
    {
      "question": "燻し銀",
      "answer": "いぶしぎん",
      "meaning": "oxidized silver, oxidised silver, something restrained but impressive (e.g. performance), something"
    },
    {
      "question": "未遂罪",
      "answer": "みすいざい",
      "meaning": "attempted crime"
    },
    {
      "question": "貧寒",
      "answer": "ひんかん",
      "meaning": "destitution"
    },
    {
      "question": "西漢",
      "answer": "せいかん",
      "meaning": "Western Han dynasty (China, 206 BCE-9 CE), Former Han dynasty"
    },
    {
      "question": "引札",
      "answer": "ひきふだ",
      "meaning": "announcement flier (e.g. sale at a shop), raffle ticket, lottery ticket, hikifuda (type of playing c"
    },
    {
      "question": "必衰",
      "answer": "ひっすい",
      "meaning": "inevitable decline (decay, collapse, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "回盲部",
      "answer": "かいもうぶ",
      "meaning": "ileocecum"
    },
    {
      "question": "引き放つ",
      "answer": "ひきはなつ",
      "meaning": "to pull apart"
    },
    {
      "question": "欧化",
      "answer": "おうか",
      "meaning": "Europeanization, Europeanisation, Westernization, Westernisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "祥月命日",
      "answer": "しょうつきめいにち",
      "meaning": "anniversary of a person's death"
    },
    {
      "question": "佐竹義宣",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "大要",
      "answer": "たいよう",
      "meaning": "summary, outline"
    },
    {
      "question": "姫椿",
      "answer": "ひめつばき",
      "meaning": "Chinese guger tree (Schima wallichii), sasanqua (Camellia sasanqua), Japanese privet (Ligustrum japo"
    },
    {
      "question": "会者定離",
      "answer": "えしゃじょうり",
      "meaning": "those who meet must part (suggesting the transient nature of this life), we meet only to part"
    },
    {
      "question": "造影剤",
      "answer": "ぞうえいざい",
      "meaning": "contrast medium, radiopaque substance"
    },
    {
      "question": "立役",
      "answer": "たちやく,たてやく",
      "meaning": "leading male role in kabuki, leading actor, protagonist"
    },
    {
      "question": "機縁",
      "answer": "きえん",
      "meaning": "opportunity, chance"
    },
    {
      "question": "藩邸",
      "answer": "はんてい",
      "meaning": "residence maintained by a daimyo in Edo"
    },
    {
      "question": "条令",
      "answer": "じょうれい",
      "meaning": "regulations, rules"
    },
    {
      "question": "地魚",
      "answer": "じざかな",
      "meaning": "locally caught fish, local fish"
    },
    {
      "question": "酸化物",
      "answer": "さんかぶつ",
      "meaning": "oxide"
    },
    {
      "question": "汚穢屋",
      "answer": "おわいや",
      "meaning": "person who gathers night soil"
    },
    {
      "question": "内証話",
      "answer": "ないしょうばなし",
      "meaning": "confidential talk, whispering"
    },
    {
      "question": "尻押し",
      "answer": "しりおし",
      "meaning": "pushing from behind, backing, supporting, instigation, instigator"
    },
    {
      "question": "公開講座",
      "answer": "こうかいこうざ",
      "meaning": "extension lectures"
    },
    {
      "question": "嗅細胞",
      "answer": "きゅうさいぼう",
      "meaning": "olfactory cell"
    },
    {
      "question": "簡体字",
      "answer": "かんたいじ",
      "meaning": "simplified Chinese character"
    },
    {
      "question": "夢の夢",
      "answer": "ゆめのゆめ",
      "meaning": "dream within a dream, (beyond) one's wildest dreams, entirely unrealizable dream, pie in the sky"
    },
    {
      "question": "知り人",
      "answer": "しりびと",
      "meaning": "acquaintance"
    },
    {
      "question": "矩形波",
      "answer": "くけいは",
      "meaning": "square wave, rectangular wave"
    },
    {
      "question": "斂葬",
      "answer": "れんそう",
      "meaning": "interment, burial"
    },
    {
      "question": "撞木",
      "answer": "しゅもく,しもく",
      "meaning": "T-shaped wooden bell hammer"
    },
    {
      "question": "言行録",
      "answer": "げんこうろく",
      "meaning": "record of a person's words and deeds"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛瀑",
      "answer": "ひばく",
      "meaning": "waterfall from a high place"
    },
    {
      "question": "天神地祇",
      "answer": "てんしんちぎ,てんじんちぎ",
      "meaning": "gods of heaven and earth"
    },
    {
      "question": "抱き癖",
      "answer": "だきぐせ",
      "meaning": "(baby which is) unhappy unless held"
    },
    {
      "question": "衡平法",
      "answer": "こうへいほう",
      "meaning": "equity"
    },
    {
      "question": "黙契",
      "answer": "もっけい",
      "meaning": "implicit agreement, tacit understanding"
    },
    {
      "question": "具象的",
      "answer": "ぐしょうてき",
      "meaning": "concrete, material, definite"
    },
    {
      "question": "御朱印",
      "answer": "ごしゅいん",
      "meaning": "letter bearing the shogun's scarlet seal, seal stamp given to worshippers and visitors to shrines an"
    },
    {
      "question": "倉庫業",
      "answer": "そうこぎょう",
      "meaning": "warehousing business"
    },
    {
      "question": "襟度",
      "answer": "きんど",
      "meaning": "magnanimity, generosity, welcoming personality"
    },
    {
      "question": "鳥黐",
      "answer": "とりもち",
      "meaning": "birdlime"
    },
    {
      "question": "それ来た",
      "answer": "それきた",
      "meaning": "there it is, there it comes, got it, of course, it figures, I knew it"
    },
    {
      "question": "露和",
      "answer": "ろわ",
      "meaning": "Russia and Japan, Russian-Japanese"
    },
    {
      "question": "問罪",
      "answer": "もんざい",
      "meaning": "accusation, indictment"
    },
    {
      "question": "大略",
      "answer": "たいりゃく",
      "meaning": "excellent plan, outline, approximately"
    },
    {
      "question": "婚姻色",
      "answer": "こんいんしょく",
      "meaning": "nuptial coloration (colouration)"
    },
    {
      "question": "接心",
      "answer": "せっしん",
      "meaning": "concentration, period of intensive zazen"
    },
    {
      "question": "直衣",
      "answer": "のうし,なおし,ちょくい",
      "meaning": "everyday robes worn by males of the imperial family, nobility, etc. (from the Heian period onward)"
    },
    {
      "question": "内攻",
      "answer": "ないこう",
      "meaning": "(disease) settling in internal organs, quarreling among companions, quarrelling among companions"
    },
    {
      "question": "論告",
      "answer": "ろんこく",
      "meaning": "prosecutor's closing argument"
    },
    {
      "question": "永正",
      "answer": "えいしょう",
      "meaning": "Eishō era (1504.2.30-1521.8.23)"
    },
    {
      "question": "三途川",
      "answer": "そうずがわ",
      "meaning": "Sanzu River (Buddhist equivalent of the River Styx)"
    },
    {
      "question": "武装平和",
      "answer": "ぶそうへいわ",
      "meaning": "armed peace"
    },
    {
      "question": "胸座",
      "answer": "むなぐら",
      "meaning": "collar, lapels"
    },
    {
      "question": "英雄主義",
      "answer": "えいゆうしゅぎ",
      "meaning": "heroism"
    },
    {
      "question": "諫止",
      "answer": "かんし",
      "meaning": "dissuasion"
    },
    {
      "question": "史記",
      "answer": "しき",
      "meaning": "Shiji, Shih-chi, The Historical Records (ancient Chinese historical record)"
    },
    {
      "question": "包み隠し",
      "answer": "つつみかくし",
      "meaning": "concealment"
    },
    {
      "question": "嬶",
      "answer": "かかあ,かか",
      "meaning": "wife"
    },
    {
      "question": "心願",
      "answer": "しんがん",
      "meaning": "prayer, heartfelt wish"
    },
    {
      "question": "頓服薬",
      "answer": "とんぷくやく",
      "meaning": "dose of medicine to be taken only once"
    },
    {
      "question": "三の糸",
      "answer": "さんのいと",
      "meaning": "third string (of a shamisen, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "位負け",
      "answer": "くらいまけ",
      "meaning": "being unworthy of one's rank, being outranked"
    },
    {
      "question": "尊像",
      "answer": "そんぞう",
      "meaning": "statue of a noble character, your picture"
    },
    {
      "question": "在外公館",
      "answer": "ざいがいこうかん",
      "meaning": "diplomatic mission, overseas diplomatic establishment"
    },
    {
      "question": "藁灰",
      "answer": "わらばい",
      "meaning": "straw ashes"
    },
    {
      "question": "法眼",
      "answer": "ほうげん",
      "meaning": "the dharma eye, second highest priestly rank in Buddhism, title bestowed upon doctors, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "優渥",
      "answer": "ゆうあく",
      "meaning": "gracious"
    },
    {
      "question": "乱杭",
      "answer": "らんぐい",
      "meaning": "palisade, stakes planted at irregular angles and intervals as a defensive barrier"
    },
    {
      "question": "天花粉",
      "answer": "てんかふん",
      "meaning": "talcum powder"
    },
    {
      "question": "諸説紛々",
      "answer": "しょせつふんぷん",
      "meaning": "divergent opinions abound, opinion is divided, there are many rumors afloat"
    },
    {
      "question": "生ゴム",
      "answer": "なまゴム",
      "meaning": "raw rubber, crude rubber"
    },
    {
      "question": "逆数",
      "answer": "ぎゃくすう",
      "meaning": "reciprocal, inverse number, multiplicative inverse"
    },
    {
      "question": "得用",
      "answer": "とくよう",
      "meaning": "economical, economy size, family size (esp. of packaged food)"
    },
    {
      "question": "全都",
      "answer": "ぜんと",
      "meaning": "the whole metropolis"
    },
    {
      "question": "角立つ",
      "answer": "かどだつ",
      "meaning": "to be sharp, to be rough"
    },
    {
      "question": "法面",
      "answer": "のりめん",
      "meaning": "slope (e.g. of embankment)"
    },
    {
      "question": "左心室",
      "answer": "さしんしつ",
      "meaning": "left ventricle"
    },
    {
      "question": "道義心",
      "answer": "どうぎしん",
      "meaning": "moral sense"
    },
    {
      "question": "独創力",
      "answer": "どくそうりょく",
      "meaning": "creative powers"
    },
    {
      "question": "一群れ",
      "answer": "ひとむれ",
      "meaning": "group, flock, crowd, herd, wide expanse (of flowers)"
    },
    {
      "question": "常しえ",
      "answer": "とこしえ",
      "meaning": "eternity, permanence, perpetuity"
    },
    {
      "question": "罪状認否",
      "answer": "ざいじょうにんぴ",
      "meaning": "arraignment, plea (of guilty or not guilty)"
    },
    {
      "question": "朱筆",
      "answer": "しゅひつ",
      "meaning": "red-ink brush"
    },
    {
      "question": "那辺",
      "answer": "なへん",
      "meaning": "where"
    },
    {
      "question": "下膨れ",
      "answer": "しもぶくれ",
      "meaning": "round-faced, bulging at the bottom, swelling toward the bottom"
    },
    {
      "question": "唯識",
      "answer": "ゆいしき",
      "meaning": "vijnapti-matrata (theory that all existence is subjective and nothing exists outside of the mind)"
    },
    {
      "question": "腓腹筋",
      "answer": "ひふくきん",
      "meaning": "gastrocnemius muscle"
    },
    {
      "question": "木の端",
      "answer": "きのはし",
      "meaning": "fragment of wood"
    },
    {
      "question": "里程",
      "answer": "りてい",
      "meaning": "mileage, distance"
    },
    {
      "question": "女道楽",
      "answer": "おんなどうらく",
      "meaning": "womanizing, debauchery, philandering"
    },
    {
      "question": "御仕舞い",
      "answer": "おしまい",
      "meaning": "the end, closing, being done for, that's it, that's enough, that's all"
    },
    {
      "question": "道明寺粉",
      "answer": "どうみょうじこ",
      "meaning": "coarse rice powder"
    },
    {
      "question": "十人並",
      "answer": "じゅうにんなみ",
      "meaning": "being average (capacity, looks) (as good as anyone), mediocrity"
    },
    {
      "question": "保護処分",
      "answer": "ほごしょぶん",
      "meaning": "disposing of a case by placing an offender on probation or under supervision"
    },
    {
      "question": "一番鶏",
      "answer": "いちばんどり",
      "meaning": "first cockcrowing"
    },
    {
      "question": "白ロシア",
      "answer": "はくロシア",
      "meaning": "Belarus"
    },
    {
      "question": "挫滅",
      "answer": "ざめつ",
      "meaning": "crushing (injury)"
    },
    {
      "question": "引波",
      "answer": "ひきなみ",
      "meaning": "backwash, rip current, undertow, stern wave, drawback (of a tsunami, i.e. when a wave trough reaches"
    },
    {
      "question": "何も彼も",
      "answer": "なにもかも",
      "meaning": "anything and everything, just about everything"
    },
    {
      "question": "経常",
      "answer": "けいじょう,けいつね",
      "meaning": "ordinary"
    },
    {
      "question": "大暑",
      "answer": "たいしょ",
      "meaning": "blistering heat, 'major heat' solar term (approx. July 23)"
    },
    {
      "question": "離昇",
      "answer": "りしょう",
      "meaning": "lift-off (e.g. of rockets, planes, etc.), take-off"
    },
    {
      "question": "耳馴れる",
      "answer": "みみなれる",
      "meaning": "to be something familiar"
    },
    {
      "question": "船軍",
      "answer": "ふないくさ,せんぐん",
      "meaning": "naval battle, navy"
    },
    {
      "question": "貸し別荘",
      "answer": "かしべっそう",
      "meaning": "vacation rental (property)"
    },
    {
      "question": "地方時",
      "answer": "ちほうじ",
      "meaning": "local time"
    },
    {
      "question": "礼回り",
      "answer": "れいまわり",
      "meaning": "making the rounds to express thanks"
    },
    {
      "question": "隠し所",
      "answer": "かくしどころ",
      "meaning": "hiding place, genitals"
    },
    {
      "question": "胆管",
      "answer": "たんかん",
      "meaning": "bile duct"
    },
    {
      "question": "敦煌",
      "answer": "とんこう",
      "meaning": "sincerity and kindheartedness, honesty and simplicity"
    },
    {
      "question": "内数",
      "answer": "うちすう",
      "meaning": "included number, number of items, etc. in a total"
    },
    {
      "question": "焚き口",
      "answer": "たきぐち",
      "meaning": "furnace opening"
    },
    {
      "question": "扶翼",
      "answer": "ふよく",
      "meaning": "help, aid, support, assistance"
    },
    {
      "question": "対置",
      "answer": "たいち",
      "meaning": "opposing (a thing) to (another), contrast, contraposition, antithesis, counterposing"
    },
    {
      "question": "通信事業",
      "answer": "つうしんじぎょう",
      "meaning": "communications industry"
    },
    {
      "question": "宗廟",
      "answer": "そうびょう",
      "meaning": "ancestral shrine (temple), mausoleum (of one's ancestors), Imperial mausoleum"
    },
    {
      "question": "起き伏し",
      "answer": "おきふし",
      "meaning": "rising and going to bed, daily life, all the time, constantly, whether awake or asleep"
    },
    {
      "question": "棒先",
      "answer": "ぼうさき",
      "meaning": "end (of a stick, rod, pole, etc.), end of a palanquin carrying pole, palanquin bearer"
    },
    {
      "question": "抜萃",
      "answer": "ばっすい",
      "meaning": "extract, excerpt, selection"
    },
    {
      "question": "家政学",
      "answer": "かせいがく",
      "meaning": "home economics, domestic science"
    },
    {
      "question": "禄高",
      "answer": "ろくだか",
      "meaning": "(amount of a samurai's) stipend"
    },
    {
      "question": "百日草",
      "answer": "ひゃくにちそう",
      "meaning": "zinnia"
    },
    {
      "question": "旗章",
      "answer": "きしょう",
      "meaning": "flag insignia"
    },
    {
      "question": "凋む",
      "answer": "しぼむ",
      "meaning": "to wither (of flowers, dreams, etc.), to wilt, to droop, to shrivel, to fade (away), to sag, to defl"
    },
    {
      "question": "粘滑",
      "answer": "ねんかつ",
      "meaning": "mucilaginous, demulcent"
    },
    {
      "question": "御茶請け",
      "answer": "おちゃうけ",
      "meaning": "cake or snack served with tea"
    },
    {
      "question": "拝火教",
      "answer": "はいかきょう",
      "meaning": "Zoroastrianism"
    },
    {
      "question": "優勝劣敗",
      "answer": "ゆうしょうれっぱい",
      "meaning": "survival of the fittest"
    },
    {
      "question": "付け下げ",
      "answer": "つけさげ",
      "meaning": "method of patterning traditional Japanese clothing (the tops of all of patterns being pointed at the"
    },
    {
      "question": "無礙",
      "answer": "むげ",
      "meaning": "free from obstacles"
    },
    {
      "question": "唐木",
      "answer": "からき",
      "meaning": "exotic non-Japanese wood (rosewood, ebony, blackwood, etc.), imported wood"
    },
    {
      "question": "事業税",
      "answer": "じぎょうぜい",
      "meaning": "business tax"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪魔主義",
      "answer": "あくましゅぎ",
      "meaning": "satanism, devil worship"
    },
    {
      "question": "先考",
      "answer": "せんこう",
      "meaning": "(one's) late father"
    },
    {
      "question": "小熊座",
      "answer": "こぐまざ",
      "meaning": "Ursa Minor (constellation), the Lesser Bear"
    },
    {
      "question": "暴力革命",
      "answer": "ぼうりょくかくめい",
      "meaning": "violent revolution"
    },
    {
      "question": "税務調査",
      "answer": "ぜいむちょうさ",
      "meaning": "tax inquiry, tax enquiry, tax investigation"
    },
    {
      "question": "御洒落",
      "answer": "おしゃれ",
      "meaning": "smartly dressed, stylish, fashion-conscious, someone smartly dressed, to dress up, to be fashionable"
    },
    {
      "question": "再製",
      "answer": "さいせい",
      "meaning": "remanufacture, reconditioning"
    },
    {
      "question": "中飛",
      "answer": "ちゅうひ",
      "meaning": "center fly, centre fly"
    },
    {
      "question": "球戯",
      "answer": "きゅうぎ",
      "meaning": "billiards"
    },
    {
      "question": "正徳",
      "answer": "しょうとく",
      "meaning": "Shōtoku era (1711.4.25-1716.6.22)"
    },
    {
      "question": "端書き",
      "answer": "はがき,はしがき",
      "meaning": "postcard, memo, note, card, foreword, preface, introduction, postscript"
    },
    {
      "question": "虫魚",
      "answer": "ちゅうぎょ",
      "meaning": "insects and fish"
    },
    {
      "question": "地方選挙",
      "answer": "ちほうせんきょ",
      "meaning": "local election, regional elections"
    },
    {
      "question": "仏家",
      "answer": "ぶっけ",
      "meaning": "Buddhist priest"
    },
    {
      "question": "貴学",
      "answer": "きがく",
      "meaning": "your university"
    },
    {
      "question": "低所",
      "answer": "ていしょ",
      "meaning": "low ground"
    },
    {
      "question": "英詩",
      "answer": "えいし",
      "meaning": "English poetry, English poem"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜語り",
      "answer": "よがたり",
      "meaning": "evening chat"
    },
    {
      "question": "仏界",
      "answer": "ぶっかい",
      "meaning": "pure land, spiritual realm of Buddhahood"
    },
    {
      "question": "塊茎",
      "answer": "かいけい",
      "meaning": "tuber"
    },
    {
      "question": "障む",
      "answer": "つつむ",
      "meaning": "to become sick, to be struck by a disaster, to hinder, to be hindered, to run into problems, to have"
    },
    {
      "question": "圧力団体",
      "answer": "あつりょくだんたい",
      "meaning": "pressure group, lobby"
    },
    {
      "question": "開庁",
      "answer": "かいちょう",
      "meaning": "governmental office opening (usually special case)"
    },
    {
      "question": "振替える",
      "answer": "ふりかえる",
      "meaning": "to change (e.g. a bill), to transfer (e.g. money), to switch over, to move over"
    },
    {
      "question": "唐土",
      "answer": "もろこし,とうど",
      "meaning": "China, Chinese"
    },
    {
      "question": "遅出",
      "answer": "おそで",
      "meaning": "late attendance (e.g. at the office)"
    },
    {
      "question": "膝掛",
      "answer": "ひざかけ",
      "meaning": "lap blanket"
    },
    {
      "question": "複写機",
      "answer": "ふくしゃき",
      "meaning": "photocopier, photocopying machine"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉛直",
      "answer": "えんちょく",
      "meaning": "upright, vertical, perpendicular"
    },
    {
      "question": "髢",
      "answer": "かもじ",
      "meaning": "hairpiece, false hair, switch, hair"
    },
    {
      "question": "水中翼船",
      "answer": "すいちゅうよくせん",
      "meaning": "hydrofoil, hydrofoil-equipped watercraft"
    },
    {
      "question": "心覚え",
      "answer": "こころおぼえ",
      "meaning": "memory"
    },
    {
      "question": "俳号",
      "answer": "はいごう",
      "meaning": "pseudonym of a haiku poet"
    },
    {
      "question": "鰓蓋",
      "answer": "えらぶた,さいがい",
      "meaning": "gill cover, operculum"
    },
    {
      "question": "師範学校",
      "answer": "しはんがっこう",
      "meaning": "normal school (pre-war Japan), teachers' training college"
    },
    {
      "question": "標識灯",
      "answer": "ひょうしきとう",
      "meaning": "beacon light"
    },
    {
      "question": "紊乱",
      "answer": "びんらん,ぶんらん",
      "meaning": "disorder, confusion, disturbance (of order, peace, etc.), corruption (e.g. of public morals)"
    },
    {
      "question": "歎声",
      "answer": "たんせい",
      "meaning": "sigh (of admiration or lamentation)"
    },
    {
      "question": "半音階",
      "answer": "はんおんかい",
      "meaning": "chromatic scale"
    },
    {
      "question": "商学",
      "answer": "しょうがく",
      "meaning": "commercial science"
    },
    {
      "question": "斎主",
      "answer": "さいしゅ",
      "meaning": "master of religious ceremonies"
    },
    {
      "question": "生鮭",
      "answer": "なまじゃけ",
      "meaning": "fresh salmon, unsalted salmon, raw salmon"
    },
    {
      "question": "議員特権",
      "answer": "ぎいんとっけん",
      "meaning": "parliamentary privilege"
    },
    {
      "question": "収率",
      "answer": "しゅうりつ",
      "meaning": "yield"
    },
    {
      "question": "遁世",
      "answer": "とんせい",
      "meaning": "seclusion from the world"
    },
    {
      "question": "綴れ織り",
      "answer": "つづれおり",
      "meaning": "(hand-woven) tapestry"
    },
    {
      "question": "進上",
      "answer": "しんじょう",
      "meaning": "giving, presenting"
    },
    {
      "question": "経机",
      "answer": "きょうづくえ",
      "meaning": "sutra-reading desk"
    },
    {
      "question": "安んずる",
      "answer": "やすんずる",
      "meaning": "to be contented, to be at ease"
    },
    {
      "question": "自鳴琴",
      "answer": "じめいきん",
      "meaning": "musical box, music box"
    },
    {
      "question": "横筋",
      "answer": "よこすじ",
      "meaning": "transversal, lateral stripes"
    },
    {
      "question": "几帳",
      "answer": "きちょう",
      "meaning": "screen"
    },
    {
      "question": "画題",
      "answer": "がだい",
      "meaning": "subject (of a painting), motif, theme, title of a painting"
    },
    {
      "question": "砂防ダム",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "母材",
      "answer": "ぼざい",
      "meaning": "welding base metal, parent metal, base material (in construction, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "中正",
      "answer": "ちゅうせい",
      "meaning": "impartiality, fairness"
    },
    {
      "question": "補綴",
      "answer": "ほてつ,ほてい",
      "meaning": "mending, revision, supplementation, (dental) prosthesis, prosthetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "実勢",
      "answer": "じっせい",
      "meaning": "actual, real, true"
    },
    {
      "question": "莓",
      "answer": "いちご",
      "meaning": "strawberry (esp. the garden strawberry, Fragaria x ananassa)"
    },
    {
      "question": "関守",
      "answer": "せきもり",
      "meaning": "barrier keeper"
    },
    {
      "question": "仮名遣い",
      "answer": "かなづかい",
      "meaning": "kana orthography, syllabary spelling"
    },
    {
      "question": "闇物資",
      "answer": "やみぶっし",
      "meaning": "black-market goods"
    },
    {
      "question": "室内遊戯",
      "answer": "しつないゆうぎ",
      "meaning": "indoor game, indoor pastime"
    },
    {
      "question": "ピトー管",
      "answer": "ピトーかん",
      "meaning": "pitot tube, pitot"
    },
    {
      "question": "雛祭",
      "answer": "ひなまつり",
      "meaning": "Hinamatsuri (March 3), Girls' Festival, Dolls' Festival"
    },
    {
      "question": "輝々",
      "answer": "きき",
      "meaning": "brilliance"
    },
    {
      "question": "活き餌",
      "answer": "いきえ",
      "meaning": "live bait"
    },
    {
      "question": "二重織",
      "answer": "にじゅうおり",
      "meaning": "double weave, double cloth"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪血",
      "answer": "あくち,おけつ",
      "meaning": "impure blood"
    },
    {
      "question": "分科会",
      "answer": "ぶんかかい",
      "meaning": "subcommittee, subworking group, breakout session"
    },
    {
      "question": "年賀葉書",
      "answer": "ねんがはがき",
      "meaning": "New Year's postcard"
    },
    {
      "question": "款",
      "answer": "かん",
      "meaning": "title, heading, article, benevolence, friendly feeling"
    },
    {
      "question": "警察医",
      "answer": "けいさつい",
      "meaning": "police surgeon, police medical officer"
    },
    {
      "question": "秋霜",
      "answer": "しゅうそう",
      "meaning": "autumn frost, fall frost"
    },
    {
      "question": "薬価",
      "answer": "やっか,やくか",
      "meaning": "National Health Insurance drug price, NHI drug price"
    },
    {
      "question": "無宿者",
      "answer": "むしゅくもの",
      "meaning": "homeless person, tramp, vagrant, vagabond"
    },
    {
      "question": "中央機関",
      "answer": "ちゅうおうきかん",
      "meaning": "central organization, central authority, central government agency"
    },
    {
      "question": "巨細",
      "answer": "きょさい,こさい",
      "meaning": "large and small matters, particulars, details, greatness and smallness, circumstances"
    },
    {
      "question": "輝き渡る",
      "answer": "かがやきわたる",
      "meaning": "to shine out far and wide"
    },
    {
      "question": "骨膜",
      "answer": "こつまく",
      "meaning": "periosteum"
    },
    {
      "question": "夢見草",
      "answer": "ゆめみぐさ",
      "meaning": "cherry blossom"
    },
    {
      "question": "宏大",
      "answer": "こうだい",
      "meaning": "vast, extensive, immense, huge, large, grand, magnificent"
    },
    {
      "question": "宵待草",
      "answer": "よいまちぐさ",
      "meaning": "evening primrose"
    },
    {
      "question": "晩方",
      "answer": "ばんがた",
      "meaning": "toward evening"
    },
    {
      "question": "回帰分析",
      "answer": "かいきぶんせき",
      "meaning": "regression analysis"
    },
    {
      "question": "転成",
      "answer": "てんせい",
      "meaning": "transformation"
    },
    {
      "question": "西洋松露",
      "answer": "せいようしょうろ",
      "meaning": "(European) truffle"
    },
    {
      "question": "主剤",
      "answer": "しゅざい",
      "meaning": "principal agent (in a medicine)"
    },
    {
      "question": "痩せ馬",
      "answer": "やせうま",
      "meaning": "scrawny horse"
    },
    {
      "question": "坑口",
      "answer": "こうこう",
      "meaning": "pithead, minehead"
    },
    {
      "question": "円口類",
      "answer": "えんこうるい",
      "meaning": "cyclostomes (eel-like jawless fishes with round mouths used for sucking)"
    },
    {
      "question": "毛包",
      "answer": "もうほう",
      "meaning": "hair follicle"
    },
    {
      "question": "封建主義",
      "answer": "ほうけんしゅぎ",
      "meaning": "feudalism"
    },
    {
      "question": "正兵",
      "answer": "せいへい",
      "meaning": "regular soldiers"
    },
    {
      "question": "編上げ靴",
      "answer": "あみあげぐつ",
      "meaning": "lace-up boots"
    },
    {
      "question": "御人好し",
      "answer": "おひとよし",
      "meaning": "good-naturedness, good-natured person, credulous person, easy mark, simple soul, soft touch"
    },
    {
      "question": "露地",
      "answer": "ろじ",
      "meaning": "bare earth (i.e. ground not covered by a roof), open field, outdoors (non-greenhouse cultivation of"
    },
    {
      "question": "甘柿",
      "answer": "あまがき",
      "meaning": "sweet persimmon"
    },
    {
      "question": "突っ放す",
      "answer": "つっぱなす",
      "meaning": "to thrust or cast away, to look upon with detachment"
    },
    {
      "question": "丸取り",
      "answer": "まるどり",
      "meaning": "monopolizing, monopolising, monopolization, monopolisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "神に入る",
      "answer": "しんにいる",
      "meaning": "to be divinely skilled"
    },
    {
      "question": "深部感覚",
      "answer": "しんぶかんかく",
      "meaning": "bathyesthesia, deep sensibility"
    },
    {
      "question": "直接話法",
      "answer": "ちょくせつわほう",
      "meaning": "direct quotation"
    },
    {
      "question": "偶有",
      "answer": "ぐうゆう",
      "meaning": "having an accident"
    },
    {
      "question": "刀圭",
      "answer": "とうけい",
      "meaning": "doctor"
    },
    {
      "question": "札所",
      "answer": "ふだしょ",
      "meaning": "temple which issues amulets"
    },
    {
      "question": "節奏",
      "answer": "せっそう",
      "meaning": "rhythm"
    },
    {
      "question": "鳴石",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "蒸餅",
      "answer": "じょうべい",
      "meaning": "steamed mochi, manjū, bread"
    },
    {
      "question": "焼亡",
      "answer": "しょうぼう,しょうもう,じょうもう",
      "meaning": "destruction by fire"
    },
    {
      "question": "官僚政治",
      "answer": "かんりょうせいじ",
      "meaning": "bureaucratic government"
    },
    {
      "question": "傾れ込む",
      "answer": "なだれこむ",
      "meaning": "to rush into, to surge into, to crowd into"
    },
    {
      "question": "見性",
      "answer": "けんしょう",
      "meaning": "self-awareness, consciousness of one's own character"
    },
    {
      "question": "消磁",
      "answer": "しょうじ",
      "meaning": "demagnetization, demagnetisation, degaussing"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜摩天",
      "answer": "やまてん",
      "meaning": "heaven without fighting, one of the six heavens of the desire realm"
    },
    {
      "question": "床払い",
      "answer": "とこばらい",
      "meaning": "recovery from an illness"
    },
    {
      "question": "切通し",
      "answer": "きりどおし,きりとおし",
      "meaning": "road (or railway) cut through hilly terrain, cutting"
    },
    {
      "question": "測候所",
      "answer": "そっこうじょ",
      "meaning": "weather measurement station"
    },
    {
      "question": "挙止",
      "answer": "きょし",
      "meaning": "bearing, deportment"
    },
    {
      "question": "御真影",
      "answer": "ごしんえい",
      "meaning": "imperial portrait, photograph of the incumbent Emperor and Empress distributed to schools between 18"
    },
    {
      "question": "太歳",
      "answer": "たいさい",
      "meaning": "Taisai, one of the eight gods of the koyomi, Jupiter (planet)"
    },
    {
      "question": "適者",
      "answer": "てきしゃ",
      "meaning": "suitable person, fit person, the fit"
    },
    {
      "question": "専断",
      "answer": "せんだん",
      "meaning": "arbitrary decision, on one's own authority, arbitrariness"
    },
    {
      "question": "破砕機",
      "answer": "はさいき",
      "meaning": "crusher"
    },
    {
      "question": "語意",
      "answer": "ごい",
      "meaning": "meaning of a word"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒蝶貝",
      "answer": "くろちょうがい",
      "meaning": "black-lip pearl oyster (Pinctada margaritifera)"
    },
    {
      "question": "謹賀",
      "answer": "きんが",
      "meaning": "wishes of happiness"
    },
    {
      "question": "専一",
      "answer": "せんいち,せんいつ",
      "meaning": "exclusively, (taking) best care"
    },
    {
      "question": "待機児童",
      "answer": "たいきじどう",
      "meaning": "child on waiting list (kindergarten, school, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "毛脛",
      "answer": "けずね",
      "meaning": "hairy legs"
    },
    {
      "question": "芸術院",
      "answer": "げいじゅついん",
      "meaning": "academy of arts, arts academy"
    },
    {
      "question": "即身成仏",
      "answer": "そくしんじょうぶつ",
      "meaning": "attainment of Buddhahood during life"
    },
    {
      "question": "茅屋",
      "answer": "ぼうおく,かやや",
      "meaning": "thatched cottage, hovel, my humble cottage"
    },
    {
      "question": "遣らかす",
      "answer": "やらかす",
      "meaning": "to fail, to blunder, to make a mess, to perpetrate, to do, to drink up, to eat up"
    },
    {
      "question": "雑ざる",
      "answer": "まざる",
      "meaning": "to be mixed, to be blended with, to associate with, to mingle with, to join"
    },
    {
      "question": "黄斑",
      "answer": "おうはん",
      "meaning": "macula, macule, macula lutea, yellow spot"
    },
    {
      "question": "福禄",
      "answer": "ふくろく",
      "meaning": "happiness and prosperity, Fukurokuju, god of happiness, prosperity and long life"
    },
    {
      "question": "凡戦",
      "answer": "ぼんせん",
      "meaning": "dull game"
    },
    {
      "question": "失認",
      "answer": "しつにん",
      "meaning": "agnosia"
    },
    {
      "question": "何時何時",
      "answer": "いついつ,いつなんどき",
      "meaning": "when, at any time, at any moment, at what moment"
    },
    {
      "question": "切取り",
      "answer": "きりとり,きりどり",
      "meaning": "cutting, tearing off, cutting off, clipping, cutting (for a railroad, highway, etc.), cut, robbery w"
    },
    {
      "question": "補助椅子",
      "answer": "ほじょいす",
      "meaning": "auxiliary seat, booster seat, baby seat"
    },
    {
      "question": "全道",
      "answer": "ぜんどう",
      "meaning": "all Hokkaido"
    },
    {
      "question": "模作",
      "answer": "もさく",
      "meaning": "imitation (work)"
    },
    {
      "question": "花見酒",
      "answer": "はなみざけ",
      "meaning": "sake drunk while viewing cherry blossoms"
    },
    {
      "question": "非我",
      "answer": "ひが",
      "meaning": "non-ego (philosophy), not-self"
    },
    {
      "question": "臣服",
      "answer": "しんぷく",
      "meaning": "vassalage"
    },
    {
      "question": "搾り滓",
      "answer": "しぼりかす",
      "meaning": "strained lees (e.g. sake, tofu), draff"
    },
    {
      "question": "細胞培養",
      "answer": "さいぼうばいよう",
      "meaning": "cell culture"
    },
    {
      "question": "潮待ち",
      "answer": "しおまち",
      "meaning": "waiting for the rising tide or a good opportunity"
    },
    {
      "question": "半夏",
      "answer": "はんげ",
      "meaning": "crow dipper (Pinellia tuber), 11th day after the summer solstice, last seed-sowing and rice-planting"
    },
    {
      "question": "金欠病",
      "answer": "きんけつびょう",
      "meaning": "poverty"
    },
    {
      "question": "愛憐",
      "answer": "あいれん",
      "meaning": "sympathy"
    },
    {
      "question": "東京裁判",
      "answer": "とうきょうさいばん",
      "meaning": "Tokyo Trials, International Military Tribunal for the Far East, IMTFE"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り箸",
      "answer": "とりばし",
      "meaning": "chopsticks used to move food from a serving dish to one's own dish"
    },
    {
      "question": "殖産",
      "answer": "しょくさん",
      "meaning": "production increase, enhancement of one's fortune"
    },
    {
      "question": "天漢",
      "answer": "てんかん",
      "meaning": "Milky Way"
    },
    {
      "question": "手間仕事",
      "answer": "てましごと",
      "meaning": "tedious job, troublesome job, time-consuming job, piecework"
    },
    {
      "question": "百分率",
      "answer": "ひゃくぶんりつ",
      "meaning": "percentage"
    },
    {
      "question": "雄藩",
      "answer": "ゆうはん",
      "meaning": "barony of the first degree, influential feudal clan"
    },
    {
      "question": "鍾愛",
      "answer": "しょうあい",
      "meaning": "deep affection, tender love, devotion, doting upon"
    },
    {
      "question": "愛別離苦",
      "answer": "あいべつりく",
      "meaning": "the pain of separation from loved ones"
    },
    {
      "question": "論題",
      "answer": "ろんだい",
      "meaning": "subject, theme"
    },
    {
      "question": "南京虫",
      "answer": "ナンキンむし",
      "meaning": "bed bug (Cimex lectularius), bedbug"
    },
    {
      "question": "敲く",
      "answer": "たたく",
      "meaning": "to strike, to clap, to knock, to beat, to tap, to pat, to play drums, to abuse, to bash, to flame (e"
    },
    {
      "question": "正月太り",
      "answer": "しょうがつぶとり",
      "meaning": "putting on weight over the New Year's holidays"
    },
    {
      "question": "登録商標",
      "answer": "とうろくしょうひょう",
      "meaning": "registered trademark"
    },
    {
      "question": "木杯",
      "answer": "もくはい",
      "meaning": "wooden cup"
    },
    {
      "question": "一腹",
      "answer": "いっぷく,ひとはら",
      "meaning": "one litter, one clutch (e.g. eggs)"
    },
    {
      "question": "帳台",
      "answer": "ちょうだい",
      "meaning": "curtained sleeping platform in shinden-style residences (used by people of high rank)"
    },
    {
      "question": "粉食",
      "answer": "ふんしょく",
      "meaning": "powdered food, food made from flour"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷菓",
      "answer": "れいか",
      "meaning": "chilled sweets, ices, ice cream"
    },
    {
      "question": "折れ込む",
      "answer": "おれこむ",
      "meaning": "to be folded under or inside"
    },
    {
      "question": "鞍下",
      "answer": "くらした",
      "meaning": "sirloin (beef), saddle (mutton, lamb)"
    },
    {
      "question": "泳力",
      "answer": "えいりょく",
      "meaning": "swimming ability, swimming ability certification"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪戯盛り",
      "answer": "いたずらざかり",
      "meaning": "mischievous age"
    },
    {
      "question": "忍び泣き",
      "answer": "しのびなき",
      "meaning": "quiet weeping"
    },
    {
      "question": "共同謀議",
      "answer": "きょうどうぼうぎ",
      "meaning": "conspiracy"
    },
    {
      "question": "乱費",
      "answer": "らんぴ",
      "meaning": "waste, lavish spending, dissipation"
    },
    {
      "question": "宍",
      "answer": "しし",
      "meaning": "flesh, meat"
    },
    {
      "question": "誤嚥",
      "answer": "ごえん",
      "meaning": "breathing in (of a foreign body, food, etc.), pulmonary aspiration, mis-swallowing, swallowing down"
    },
    {
      "question": "地下運動",
      "answer": "ちかうんどう",
      "meaning": "underground activities"
    },
    {
      "question": "丹頂",
      "answer": "たんちょう",
      "meaning": "red-crowned crane, Japanese crane (Grus japonensis)"
    },
    {
      "question": "万乗",
      "answer": "ばんじょう",
      "meaning": "sovereignty"
    },
    {
      "question": "卜者",
      "answer": "ぼくしゃ",
      "meaning": "fortune teller, soothsayer, diviner"
    },
    {
      "question": "消費者庁",
      "answer": "しょうひしゃちょう",
      "meaning": "Consumer Affairs Agency, CAA"
    },
    {
      "question": "狂瀾怒濤",
      "answer": "きょうらんどとう",
      "meaning": "maelstrom, the state of affairs being in great turmoil"
    },
    {
      "question": "公設",
      "answer": "こうせつ",
      "meaning": "public (institution)"
    },
    {
      "question": "東北弁",
      "answer": "とうほくべん",
      "meaning": "Tōhoku dialect, Tohoku dialect"
    },
    {
      "question": "ソ連邦",
      "answer": "ソれんぽう",
      "meaning": "Soviet Union, Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, USSR"
    },
    {
      "question": "筋細胞",
      "answer": "きんさいぼう",
      "meaning": "muscle cell"
    },
    {
      "question": "消費財",
      "answer": "しょうひざい",
      "meaning": "consumer goods"
    },
    {
      "question": "帯揚げ",
      "answer": "おびあげ",
      "meaning": "obi sash"
    },
    {
      "question": "果し状",
      "answer": "はたしじょう",
      "meaning": "letter of challenge (to a duel, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "垢染みる",
      "answer": "あかじみる",
      "meaning": "to become grimy or dirty"
    },
    {
      "question": "幼君",
      "answer": "ようくん",
      "meaning": "young lord or master"
    },
    {
      "question": "有理数",
      "answer": "ゆうりすう",
      "meaning": "rational number"
    },
    {
      "question": "木通",
      "answer": "あけび",
      "meaning": "chocolate-vine (Akebia quinata), fiveleaf, fiveleaf akebia, fruit of the akebia"
    },
    {
      "question": "清まる",
      "answer": "きよまる",
      "meaning": "to be purified, to be cleansed"
    },
    {
      "question": "間脳",
      "answer": "かんのう",
      "meaning": "the interbrain, the diencephalon"
    },
    {
      "question": "珍問",
      "answer": "ちんもん",
      "meaning": "strange question, offbeat question, odd question, funny question, curious question"
    },
    {
      "question": "白雁",
      "answer": "はくがん",
      "meaning": "snow goose (Chen caerulescens), blue goose"
    },
    {
      "question": "水貝",
      "answer": "みずがい",
      "meaning": "sliced abalone served in cold water"
    },
    {
      "question": "概括",
      "answer": "がいかつ",
      "meaning": "summary, generalization, generalisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "葫",
      "answer": "にんにく,ひる",
      "meaning": "garlic (Allium sativum), strong-smelling edible plant (esp. perennials of the family Liliaceae, e.g."
    },
    {
      "question": "禁漁区",
      "answer": "きんりょうく",
      "meaning": "game preserve, wildlife sanctuary"
    },
    {
      "question": "月極め",
      "answer": "つきぎめ",
      "meaning": "monthly contract, paying by the month"
    },
    {
      "question": "縺れ込む",
      "answer": "もつれこむ",
      "meaning": "to proceed though deadlocked, to be carried over (e.g. to next meeting), to go into a shootout (e.g."
    },
    {
      "question": "冥々",
      "answer": "めいめい",
      "meaning": "dark, invisible"
    },
    {
      "question": "腹が下る",
      "answer": "はらがくだる",
      "meaning": "to have loose bowels"
    },
    {
      "question": "陽明学",
      "answer": "ようめいがく",
      "meaning": "neo-Confucianism (based on the teachings of Wang Yangming and his followers)"
    },
    {
      "question": "熟む",
      "answer": "うむ",
      "meaning": "to ripen"
    },
    {
      "question": "核物理学",
      "answer": "かくぶつりがく",
      "meaning": "nuclear physics"
    },
    {
      "question": "怪童",
      "answer": "かいどう",
      "meaning": "unusually large or strong youth"
    },
    {
      "question": "力落とし",
      "answer": "ちからおとし",
      "meaning": "discouragement, disappointment, loss of energy, fatigue"
    },
    {
      "question": "潑溂",
      "answer": "はつらつ",
      "meaning": "lively, vigorous, sprightly, animated, vivid"
    },
    {
      "question": "痛嘆",
      "answer": "つうたん",
      "meaning": "deep regret, grief"
    },
    {
      "question": "擦り半",
      "answer": "すりばん",
      "meaning": "fire alarm ringing continuously to warn that a fire is extremely near, sound as produced by this ala"
    },
    {
      "question": "掛時計",
      "answer": "かけどけい",
      "meaning": "wall clock"
    },
    {
      "question": "回り持ち",
      "answer": "まわりもち",
      "meaning": "taking turns, in rotation"
    },
    {
      "question": "山伏茸",
      "answer": "やまぶしたけ",
      "meaning": "bearded tooth fungus (Hericium erinaceum), lion's mane mushroom"
    },
    {
      "question": "天来",
      "answer": "てんらい",
      "meaning": "heavenly, divine, inspired, heaven sent"
    },
    {
      "question": "和琴",
      "answer": "わごん",
      "meaning": "wagon, yamatogoto, six-stringed native Japanese zither"
    },
    {
      "question": "前下がり",
      "answer": "まえさがり",
      "meaning": "front part low"
    },
    {
      "question": "魚竜",
      "answer": "ぎょりゅう",
      "meaning": "ichthyosaur"
    },
    {
      "question": "兜巾",
      "answer": "ときん",
      "meaning": "black headgear worn by yamabushi"
    },
    {
      "question": "友垣",
      "answer": "ともがき",
      "meaning": "friend"
    },
    {
      "question": "親任",
      "answer": "しんにん",
      "meaning": "imperial appointment"
    },
    {
      "question": "寸志",
      "answer": "すんし",
      "meaning": "small present, small token of appreciation, with compliments (e.g. written on small gift)"
    },
    {
      "question": "平和運動",
      "answer": "へいわうんどう",
      "meaning": "peace movement"
    },
    {
      "question": "大水青",
      "answer": "おおみずあお",
      "meaning": "emperor moth (Actias artemis), Japanese moon moth"
    },
    {
      "question": "阻却",
      "answer": "そきゃく",
      "meaning": "rejection"
    },
    {
      "question": "丸本",
      "answer": "まるぼん,まるほん",
      "meaning": "reciter's book, complete set of books"
    },
    {
      "question": "榎茸",
      "answer": "えのきたけ,えのきだけ",
      "meaning": "enoki mushroom (Flammulina velutipes), winter mushroom, velvet shank, enokitake, enokidake"
    },
    {
      "question": "縄付き",
      "answer": "なわつき",
      "meaning": "criminal (bound by ropes), prisoner in bonds, being bound by ropes"
    },
    {
      "question": "慈童",
      "answer": "じどう",
      "meaning": "noh mask resembling a dignified youth"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜船",
      "answer": "よふね",
      "meaning": "night boat"
    },
    {
      "question": "負け星",
      "answer": "まけぼし",
      "meaning": "mark indicating a defeat"
    },
    {
      "question": "故里",
      "answer": "ふるさと",
      "meaning": "home town, birthplace, native place, one's old home, ruins, historic remains"
    },
    {
      "question": "宅地造成",
      "answer": "たくちぞうせい",
      "meaning": "residential land development"
    },
    {
      "question": "露の間",
      "answer": "つゆのま",
      "meaning": "instant"
    },
    {
      "question": "忍び返し",
      "answer": "しのびがえし",
      "meaning": "bamboo wall-top spikes (or wood, iron), spikes placed at the top of a wall to repel thieves"
    },
    {
      "question": "局外",
      "answer": "きょくがい",
      "meaning": "the outside"
    },
    {
      "question": "硫酸銅",
      "answer": "りゅうさんどう",
      "meaning": "copper sulfate"
    },
    {
      "question": "私恨",
      "answer": "しこん",
      "meaning": "personal grudge"
    },
    {
      "question": "貴方々",
      "answer": "あなたがた",
      "meaning": "you (plural)"
    },
    {
      "question": "臼茸",
      "answer": "うすたけ",
      "meaning": "shaggy chanterelle (Turbinellus floccosus), scaly chanterelle, woolly chanterelle"
    },
    {
      "question": "安保闘争",
      "answer": "あんぽとうそう",
      "meaning": "campaign against the Japan-U.S. Security Treaty (1959-60, 1970)"
    },
    {
      "question": "ゴム靴",
      "answer": "ゴムぐつ",
      "meaning": "rubber shoes, rubber boots, wellingtons"
    },
    {
      "question": "群盗",
      "answer": "ぐんとう",
      "meaning": "group of robbers, gang of robbers"
    },
    {
      "question": "拙著",
      "answer": "せっちょ",
      "meaning": "my book, my (humble) work, a little thing of mine"
    },
    {
      "question": "甲状軟骨",
      "answer": "こうじょうなんこつ",
      "meaning": "thyroid cartilage"
    },
    {
      "question": "鋭兵",
      "answer": "えいへい",
      "meaning": "picked troops"
    },
    {
      "question": "脚榻",
      "answer": "きゃたつ",
      "meaning": "stepladder, steps"
    },
    {
      "question": "夏蜜柑",
      "answer": "なつみかん",
      "meaning": "Chinese citron (Citrus natsudaidai), bitter summer orange (mandarin)"
    },
    {
      "question": "初経",
      "answer": "しょけい",
      "meaning": "menarche, first menstruation"
    },
    {
      "question": "趣旨説明",
      "answer": "しゅしせつめい",
      "meaning": "explanation of aim (esp. of a legislative bill), rationalization"
    },
    {
      "question": "超高速度",
      "answer": "ちょうこうそくど",
      "meaning": "super-high speed"
    },
    {
      "question": "舟人",
      "answer": "ふなびと",
      "meaning": "sailor, boatman, passenger"
    },
    {
      "question": "知慮",
      "answer": "ちりょ",
      "meaning": "foresight, wisdom, sagacity"
    },
    {
      "question": "岡辺",
      "answer": "おかべ",
      "meaning": "vicinity of a hill"
    },
    {
      "question": "同語反復",
      "answer": "どうごはんぷく",
      "meaning": "tautology"
    },
    {
      "question": "無線局",
      "answer": "むせんきょく",
      "meaning": "radio station"
    },
    {
      "question": "遺産分割",
      "answer": "いさんぶんかつ",
      "meaning": "partition of an estate (inheritance)"
    },
    {
      "question": "旧盆",
      "answer": "きゅうぼん",
      "meaning": "Bon Festival of the lunar calendar"
    },
    {
      "question": "鐚一文",
      "answer": "びたいちもん",
      "meaning": "very small amount of money, penny, cent, nickel, dime"
    },
    {
      "question": "性格検査",
      "answer": "せいかくけんさ",
      "meaning": "personality test"
    },
    {
      "question": "根株",
      "answer": "ねかぶ",
      "meaning": "stump"
    },
    {
      "question": "兵児帯",
      "answer": "へこおび",
      "meaning": "waist band"
    },
    {
      "question": "物権",
      "answer": "ぶっけん",
      "meaning": "(legal terminology) real rights"
    },
    {
      "question": "忘れ草",
      "answer": "わすれぐさ",
      "meaning": "Hemerocallis fulva var. kwanso (variety of daylily), tobacco"
    },
    {
      "question": "契印",
      "answer": "けいいん",
      "meaning": "impression of a seal over the joint of two papers, tally"
    },
    {
      "question": "水和物",
      "answer": "すいわぶつ",
      "meaning": "hydrate"
    },
    {
      "question": "旧法",
      "answer": "きゅうほう",
      "meaning": "old law, old method"
    },
    {
      "question": "帰帆",
      "answer": "きはん",
      "meaning": "returning sailboat, setting sail for home port"
    },
    {
      "question": "拭き消す",
      "answer": "ふきけす",
      "meaning": "to wipe out, to erase"
    },
    {
      "question": "馬刺",
      "answer": "ばさし",
      "meaning": "horse-meat sashimi"
    },
    {
      "question": "使徒行伝",
      "answer": "しとぎょうでん",
      "meaning": "Acts of the Apostles (book of the Bible)"
    },
    {
      "question": "仏教学",
      "answer": "ぶっきょうがく",
      "meaning": "Buddhist studies, Buddhology"
    },
    {
      "question": "後翅",
      "answer": "こうし",
      "meaning": "hindwing"
    },
    {
      "question": "島国根性",
      "answer": "しまぐにこんじょう",
      "meaning": "island country mentality, insular spirit, insularism, insularity"
    },
    {
      "question": "玉偏",
      "answer": "たまへん,ぎょくへん",
      "meaning": "kanji 'jewel' radical at left (radical 96)"
    },
    {
      "question": "大目付",
      "answer": "おおめつけ",
      "meaning": "(government) inspector-general (Edo period), upper superintendent officer"
    },
    {
      "question": "看板倒れ",
      "answer": "かんばんだおれ",
      "meaning": "ostentatious"
    },
    {
      "question": "未就学",
      "answer": "みしゅうがく",
      "meaning": "preschool (not yet entered school)"
    },
    {
      "question": "釣殿",
      "answer": "つりどの",
      "meaning": "buildings on the east and west side of the southern pond (in traditional palatial-style architecture"
    },
    {
      "question": "分限者",
      "answer": "ぶげんじゃ,ぶげんしゃ",
      "meaning": "rich man, man of wealth"
    },
    {
      "question": "官立",
      "answer": "かんりつ",
      "meaning": "national, governmental"
    },
    {
      "question": "溶出",
      "answer": "ようしゅつ",
      "meaning": "liquation, elution"
    },
    {
      "question": "猛勇",
      "answer": "もうゆう",
      "meaning": "valiant courage"
    },
    {
      "question": "開基",
      "answer": "かいき",
      "meaning": "foundation of a temple, laying a foundation (stone), open base"
    },
    {
      "question": "挺する",
      "answer": "ていする",
      "meaning": "to put (oneself) forward, to risk (one's life), to volunteer (bravely)"
    },
    {
      "question": "蔕",
      "answer": "へた,ほぞ",
      "meaning": "calyx"
    },
    {
      "question": "伎楽",
      "answer": "ぎがく",
      "meaning": "ancient music"
    },
    {
      "question": "想望",
      "answer": "そうぼう",
      "meaning": "longing, yearning"
    },
    {
      "question": "老人斑",
      "answer": "ろうじんはん",
      "meaning": "senile plaque, neuritic plaque, senile druse"
    },
    {
      "question": "聴聞",
      "answer": "ちょうもん",
      "meaning": "listening, hearing"
    },
    {
      "question": "共立",
      "answer": "きょうりつ",
      "meaning": "joint, common"
    },
    {
      "question": "遵奉",
      "answer": "じゅんぽう",
      "meaning": "obeying, observing, following"
    },
    {
      "question": "立証責任",
      "answer": "りっしょうせきにん",
      "meaning": "burden of proof"
    },
    {
      "question": "仏事",
      "answer": "ぶつじ",
      "meaning": "Buddhist memorial service"
    },
    {
      "question": "陋屋",
      "answer": "ろうおく",
      "meaning": "cramped home, one's humble abode, hovel, pigsty, cottage, squalid hut"
    },
    {
      "question": "山号",
      "answer": "さんごう",
      "meaning": "honorific mountain name prefixed to a temple's name"
    },
    {
      "question": "絵双紙",
      "answer": "えぞうし",
      "meaning": "picture book"
    },
    {
      "question": "労働市場",
      "answer": "ろうどうしじょう",
      "meaning": "labor market, labour market"
    },
    {
      "question": "春歌",
      "answer": "しゅんか",
      "meaning": "bawdy song, lewd song, obscene song"
    },
    {
      "question": "軀体",
      "answer": "くたい",
      "meaning": "frame (of a building), framework, skeleton, (human) body"
    },
    {
      "question": "選奨",
      "answer": "せんしょう",
      "meaning": "recommendation"
    },
    {
      "question": "空谷",
      "answer": "くうこく",
      "meaning": "lonely or uninhabited valley"
    },
    {
      "question": "暗剣殺",
      "answer": "あんけんさつ",
      "meaning": "unpropitious direction"
    },
    {
      "question": "厳秘",
      "answer": "げんぴ",
      "meaning": "strict secret, top-secret"
    },
    {
      "question": "憐情",
      "answer": "れんじょう",
      "meaning": "compassion, pity"
    },
    {
      "question": "物持",
      "answer": "ものもち",
      "meaning": "rich person, wealthy person, taking good care of things, keeping things for a long time and taking c"
    },
    {
      "question": "手沢",
      "answer": "しゅたく",
      "meaning": "worn or soiled with handling"
    },
    {
      "question": "一具",
      "answer": "いちぐ",
      "meaning": "one set"
    },
    {
      "question": "現法",
      "answer": "げんぽう,げんほう",
      "meaning": "local subsidiary"
    },
    {
      "question": "筒袖",
      "answer": "つつそで",
      "meaning": "tight sleeve (of a kimono or dress)"
    },
    {
      "question": "熱涙",
      "answer": "ねつるい",
      "meaning": "hot tears"
    },
    {
      "question": "主節",
      "answer": "しゅせつ",
      "meaning": "principal clause"
    },
    {
      "question": "主我",
      "answer": "しゅが",
      "meaning": "ego, self"
    },
    {
      "question": "版籍奉還",
      "answer": "はんせきほうかん",
      "meaning": "the return of the land and people from the feudal lords to the Emperor"
    },
    {
      "question": "有期刑",
      "answer": "ゆうきけい",
      "meaning": "definite term (of a prison sentence)"
    },
    {
      "question": "売り掛け",
      "answer": "うりかけ",
      "meaning": "credit sales"
    },
    {
      "question": "内部環境",
      "answer": "ないぶかんきょう",
      "meaning": "internal environment"
    },
    {
      "question": "排水孔",
      "answer": "はいすいこう",
      "meaning": "osculum, scupper (hole)"
    },
    {
      "question": "駈け足",
      "answer": "かけあし",
      "meaning": "running fast, double time, cantering, doing things in a hurry"
    },
    {
      "question": "真率",
      "answer": "しんそつ",
      "meaning": "honesty, sincerity, frankness"
    },
    {
      "question": "九十九髪",
      "answer": "つくもがみ",
      "meaning": "an old woman's gray hair, old woman with white hair"
    },
    {
      "question": "電子会議",
      "answer": "でんしかいぎ",
      "meaning": "electronic conference"
    },
    {
      "question": "参賀",
      "answer": "さんが",
      "meaning": "congratulatory visit to the Imperial Palace (e.g. at New Year)"
    },
    {
      "question": "同流",
      "answer": "どうりゅう",
      "meaning": "the same style, same school, common origin"
    },
    {
      "question": "三卿",
      "answer": "さんきょう",
      "meaning": "three secondary Tokugawa branch families (Tayasu, Shimizu, and Hitotsubashi)"
    },
    {
      "question": "構外",
      "answer": "こうがい",
      "meaning": "off grounds, outside the premises"
    },
    {
      "question": "入坑",
      "answer": "にゅうこう",
      "meaning": "entrance into drift or pit"
    },
    {
      "question": "ハン国",
      "answer": "ハンこく",
      "meaning": "khanate"
    },
    {
      "question": "唐様",
      "answer": "からよう",
      "meaning": "Chinese design, Chinese style, traditional architecture associated with Zen"
    },
    {
      "question": "詩心",
      "answer": "ししん",
      "meaning": "poetic sentiment or inspiration, poetic inclination or taste, poem-composing mood, ability to apprec"
    },
    {
      "question": "四民",
      "answer": "しみん",
      "meaning": "the four social classes (samurai, farmers, artisans, merchants), the masses"
    },
    {
      "question": "才器",
      "answer": "さいき",
      "meaning": "talent, ability"
    },
    {
      "question": "脾肉",
      "answer": "ひにく",
      "meaning": "round meat, meat from a pig's thigh (from which ham is made)"
    },
    {
      "question": "書下し",
      "answer": "かきくだし",
      "meaning": "writing from top to bottom, writing without a pause, translation of classical Chinese into Japanese"
    },
    {
      "question": "信仰告白",
      "answer": "しんこうこくはく",
      "meaning": "profession of faith"
    },
    {
      "question": "駐兵",
      "answer": "ちゅうへい",
      "meaning": "stationing of troops"
    },
    {
      "question": "着彩",
      "answer": "ちゃくさい",
      "meaning": "colouring (a drawing), coloring"
    },
    {
      "question": "吏僚",
      "answer": "りりょう",
      "meaning": "public servant, government official"
    },
    {
      "question": "台石",
      "answer": "だいいし",
      "meaning": "stone pedestal"
    },
    {
      "question": "永々",
      "answer": "えいえい,ながなが",
      "meaning": "forever, long, drawn-out, very long"
    },
    {
      "question": "開経偈",
      "answer": "かいきょうげ",
      "meaning": "opening chant of a sutra"
    },
    {
      "question": "麗姿",
      "answer": "れいし",
      "meaning": "beautiful figure"
    },
    {
      "question": "農高",
      "answer": "のうこう",
      "meaning": "agricultural high school"
    },
    {
      "question": "政友",
      "answer": "せいゆう",
      "meaning": "political friend, friend with the same political views"
    },
    {
      "question": "律令国家",
      "answer": "りつりょうこっか",
      "meaning": "the Japanese nation under the ritsuryo codes"
    },
    {
      "question": "媒鳥",
      "answer": "おとり,ばいちょう",
      "meaning": "decoy (for hunting), stool, lure, decoy, stool pigeon, trap"
    },
    {
      "question": "ボール盤",
      "answer": "ボールばん",
      "meaning": "drill press, drilling machine"
    },
    {
      "question": "織目",
      "answer": "おりめ",
      "meaning": "texture, space between threads (i.e. in cloth)"
    },
    {
      "question": "二義的",
      "answer": "にぎてき",
      "meaning": "secondary"
    },
    {
      "question": "公休日",
      "answer": "こうきゅうび",
      "meaning": "legal holiday"
    },
    {
      "question": "閑談",
      "answer": "かんだん",
      "meaning": "quiet conversation, idle talk"
    },
    {
      "question": "碍子",
      "answer": "がいし",
      "meaning": "insulator"
    },
    {
      "question": "臥する",
      "answer": "がする",
      "meaning": "to lie down (in bed), to take to one's bed"
    },
    {
      "question": "行き摺り",
      "answer": "ゆきずり",
      "meaning": "passing, casual"
    },
    {
      "question": "算用",
      "answer": "さんよう",
      "meaning": "computation, calculation"
    },
    {
      "question": "掛軸",
      "answer": "かけじく",
      "meaning": "hanging scroll"
    },
    {
      "question": "晴雨計",
      "answer": "せいうけい",
      "meaning": "barometer"
    },
    {
      "question": "公教育",
      "answer": "こうきょういく",
      "meaning": "public education"
    },
    {
      "question": "賭け碁",
      "answer": "かけご",
      "meaning": "playing go for stakes"
    },
    {
      "question": "流通機構",
      "answer": "りゅうつうきこう",
      "meaning": "distribution system"
    },
    {
      "question": "造機",
      "answer": "ぞうき",
      "meaning": "engine construction"
    },
    {
      "question": "内着",
      "answer": "うちぎ",
      "meaning": "everyday clothes, underwear"
    },
    {
      "question": "分会",
      "answer": "ぶんかい",
      "meaning": "branch, chapter"
    },
    {
      "question": "廉恥心",
      "answer": "れんちしん",
      "meaning": "sense of honor, sense of honour"
    },
    {
      "question": "性慾",
      "answer": "せいよく",
      "meaning": "sexual desire"
    },
    {
      "question": "半臂",
      "answer": "はんぴ",
      "meaning": "short-sleeved (or sleeveless) undergarment worn by aristocratic men"
    },
    {
      "question": "八つ切り",
      "answer": "やつぎり",
      "meaning": "octavo format (about 21.5 to 16.5 cm), cutting into 8 parts"
    },
    {
      "question": "種種",
      "answer": "しゅじゅ,くさぐさ",
      "meaning": "various, a variety of, all kinds of, many, diverse"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤酢",
      "answer": "あかず",
      "meaning": "red vinegar made from fermented sake lees, plum vinegar with perilla leaves added"
    },
    {
      "question": "支払手形",
      "answer": "しはらいてがた",
      "meaning": "bill payable, note payable"
    },
    {
      "question": "専権",
      "answer": "せんけん",
      "meaning": "arbitrary use of power"
    },
    {
      "question": "産霊",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "わ行",
      "answer": "わぎょう",
      "meaning": "the 'wa' column of the Japanese syllabary table (wa, wi, we, wo)"
    },
    {
      "question": "当職",
      "answer": "とうしょく",
      "meaning": "this duty, this task, this job, I (as the person in charge of this task)"
    },
    {
      "question": "窶れ",
      "answer": "やつれ",
      "meaning": "emaciation, gauntness, haggardness"
    },
    {
      "question": "筬虫",
      "answer": "おさむし",
      "meaning": "ground beetle, carabid (esp. of subfamily Carabinae), millipede"
    },
    {
      "question": "旱害",
      "answer": "かんがい",
      "meaning": "drought disaster, drought damage"
    },
    {
      "question": "索然",
      "answer": "さくぜん",
      "meaning": "dry, desolate"
    },
    {
      "question": "共襟",
      "answer": "ともえり",
      "meaning": "same-colored neckband (coloured)"
    },
    {
      "question": "寄せ植え",
      "answer": "よせうえ",
      "meaning": "flowers planted together"
    },
    {
      "question": "総浚い",
      "answer": "そうざらい",
      "meaning": "general review (e.g. of one's lessons), dress rehearsal"
    },
    {
      "question": "棚機",
      "answer": "たなばた",
      "meaning": "Star Festival (held in July or August), Tanabata, Festival of the Weaver"
    },
    {
      "question": "気が腐る",
      "answer": "きがくさる",
      "meaning": "to feel dispirited, to feel discouraged"
    },
    {
      "question": "予洗い",
      "answer": "よあらい",
      "meaning": "prewashing"
    },
    {
      "question": "簡保",
      "answer": "かんぽ",
      "meaning": "postal life insurance"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕合せ者",
      "answer": "しあわせもの",
      "meaning": "fortunate person, lucky fellow, lucky dog"
    },
    {
      "question": "年差",
      "answer": "ねんさ",
      "meaning": "annual variation"
    },
    {
      "question": "閃電",
      "answer": "せんでん",
      "meaning": "flash of lightning"
    },
    {
      "question": "遮断器",
      "answer": "しゃだんき",
      "meaning": "circuit breaker"
    },
    {
      "question": "立替え",
      "answer": "たてかえ",
      "meaning": "advancing money, temporary payment for someone else, payment on behalf of another party, with the ex"
    },
    {
      "question": "別便",
      "answer": "べつびん",
      "meaning": "separate post, separate mail, separate cover"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍資",
      "answer": "ぐんし",
      "meaning": "war materiel, military expenses, war fund, campaign funds"
    },
    {
      "question": "定見",
      "answer": "ていけん",
      "meaning": "fixed opinion"
    },
    {
      "question": "餓虎",
      "answer": "がこ",
      "meaning": "starving tiger"
    },
    {
      "question": "作陶",
      "answer": "さくとう",
      "meaning": "porcelain making, ceramics making, pottery making"
    },
    {
      "question": "薬理作用",
      "answer": "やくりさよう",
      "meaning": "medicinal action"
    },
    {
      "question": "大息",
      "answer": "たいそく",
      "meaning": "deep sigh"
    },
    {
      "question": "八股",
      "answer": "はっこ",
      "meaning": "eight-legged essay (classical Chinese style of essay writing)"
    },
    {
      "question": "小曲",
      "answer": "しょうきょく",
      "meaning": "short piece of music"
    },
    {
      "question": "晩熟",
      "answer": "おくて,ばんじゅく",
      "meaning": "late-growing rice, late-ripening crops, late-blooming flowers, late developer (e.g. child who reache"
    },
    {
      "question": "腹積り",
      "answer": "はらづもり",
      "meaning": "plan, intention"
    },
    {
      "question": "古楽",
      "answer": "こがく",
      "meaning": "ancient (early) music"
    },
    {
      "question": "中国将棋",
      "answer": "ちゅうごくしょうぎ",
      "meaning": "Chinese chess, xiangqi"
    },
    {
      "question": "呱々",
      "answer": "ここ",
      "meaning": "cry of a baby at its birth"
    },
    {
      "question": "存否",
      "answer": "ぞんぴ,そんぴ",
      "meaning": "(whether) existent or non-existent, life or death"
    },
    {
      "question": "町歩",
      "answer": "ちょうぶ",
      "meaning": "hectare (2.471 acres)"
    },
    {
      "question": "度胆",
      "answer": "どぎも",
      "meaning": "guts, pluck, nerve, spirit"
    },
    {
      "question": "首捻り",
      "answer": "くびひねり",
      "meaning": "head-twisting throw"
    },
    {
      "question": "接線",
      "answer": "せっせん",
      "meaning": "tangent line, tangential line"
    },
    {
      "question": "踏み越す",
      "answer": "ふみこす",
      "meaning": "to step out of the ring, to put one's foot outside the ring"
    },
    {
      "question": "普賢菩薩",
      "answer": "ふげんぼさつ",
      "meaning": "Samantabhadra (Bodhisattva), Fugen, Puxian"
    },
    {
      "question": "児孫",
      "answer": "じそん",
      "meaning": "children and grandchildren, descendants"
    },
    {
      "question": "鋤鍬",
      "answer": "すきくわ,すきとくわ",
      "meaning": "farming implement"
    },
    {
      "question": "イタ車",
      "answer": "イタしゃ",
      "meaning": "car painted with anime characters, painful car (because some people consider it painful to look at),"
    },
    {
      "question": "活断層",
      "answer": "かつだんそう",
      "meaning": "active fault"
    },
    {
      "question": "饂飩屋",
      "answer": "うどんや",
      "meaning": "noodle shop"
    },
    {
      "question": "公述人",
      "answer": "こうじゅつにん",
      "meaning": "speaker at a public hearing"
    },
    {
      "question": "水脹れ",
      "answer": "みずぶくれ",
      "meaning": "blister"
    },
    {
      "question": "番を張る",
      "answer": "ばんをはる",
      "meaning": "to be the leader of a group of juvenile delinquents"
    },
    {
      "question": "姫御子",
      "answer": "ひめみこ",
      "meaning": "imperial princess"
    },
    {
      "question": "妾宅",
      "answer": "しょうたく",
      "meaning": "house in which a mistress is kept"
    },
    {
      "question": "手足れ",
      "answer": "てだれ",
      "meaning": "skill, dexterity, master hand"
    },
    {
      "question": "俗情",
      "answer": "ぞくじょう",
      "meaning": "worldly-mindedness, worldly affairs"
    },
    {
      "question": "検索避け",
      "answer": "けんさくよけ",
      "meaning": "making a web page hard to find through search engines, avoiding search engines"
    },
    {
      "question": "潜血",
      "answer": "せんけつ",
      "meaning": "occult blood"
    },
    {
      "question": "奸策",
      "answer": "かんさく",
      "meaning": "shrewd (dirty) trick, sinister scheme (design), sly art"
    },
    {
      "question": "名句",
      "answer": "めいく",
      "meaning": "famous saying, noted haiku"
    },
    {
      "question": "社会階層",
      "answer": "しゃかいかいそう",
      "meaning": "social class, social strata, social scale"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒御影",
      "answer": "くろみかげ",
      "meaning": "black granite"
    },
    {
      "question": "俊秀",
      "answer": "しゅんしゅう",
      "meaning": "genius, prodigy, talented person"
    },
    {
      "question": "廃退",
      "answer": "はいたい",
      "meaning": "decay, decadence"
    },
    {
      "question": "禍言",
      "answer": "まがごと,まがこと",
      "meaning": "ominous word, ill-omened word, misfortune"
    },
    {
      "question": "艫綱",
      "answer": "ともづな",
      "meaning": "stern line, mooring line"
    },
    {
      "question": "空芯菜",
      "answer": "くうしんさい",
      "meaning": "Chinese water spinach (Ipomoea aquatica), ong choy, kang kong, water morning glory, water convolvulu"
    },
    {
      "question": "病犬",
      "answer": "やまいぬ",
      "meaning": "bad dog, rabid dog"
    },
    {
      "question": "空閑地",
      "answer": "くうかんち",
      "meaning": "vacant lot or land"
    },
    {
      "question": "外耳道",
      "answer": "がいじどう",
      "meaning": "external auditory canal, ear canal, external auditory meatus"
    },
    {
      "question": "陰画",
      "answer": "いんが",
      "meaning": "(photographic) negative"
    },
    {
      "question": "題意",
      "answer": "だいい",
      "meaning": "meaning of a title (of a book, poem, etc.), point of a question (on an exam, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "長足",
      "answer": "ちょうそく",
      "meaning": "rapid progress, great strides"
    },
    {
      "question": "民選",
      "answer": "みんせん",
      "meaning": "popular election"
    },
    {
      "question": "万夫",
      "answer": "ばんぷ",
      "meaning": "many people"
    },
    {
      "question": "蛍雪の功",
      "answer": "けいせつのこう",
      "meaning": "the fruit of diligent study"
    },
    {
      "question": "打製",
      "answer": "だせい",
      "meaning": "made by hitting (e.g. striking stone flakes from a tool stone), made using lithic reduction"
    },
    {
      "question": "立合う",
      "answer": "たちあう",
      "meaning": "to be matched against (in a sports contest)"
    },
    {
      "question": "侮言",
      "answer": "ぶげん",
      "meaning": "insult"
    },
    {
      "question": "割込み",
      "answer": "わりこみ",
      "meaning": "queue jumping, breaking into a line, muscling in on, wedging oneself in, interruption, sharing a the"
    },
    {
      "question": "船外機",
      "answer": "せんがいき",
      "meaning": "outboard motor"
    },
    {
      "question": "脂肪質",
      "answer": "しぼうしつ",
      "meaning": "fatty"
    },
    {
      "question": "月半ば",
      "answer": "つきなかば",
      "meaning": "middle of the month"
    },
    {
      "question": "円墳",
      "answer": "えんぷん,えんふん",
      "meaning": "round burial mound"
    },
    {
      "question": "肉食鳥",
      "answer": "にくしょくちょう",
      "meaning": "carnivorous bird"
    },
    {
      "question": "延性",
      "answer": "えんせい",
      "meaning": "ductility, malleability"
    },
    {
      "question": "身体改造",
      "answer": "しんたいかいぞう",
      "meaning": "body modification"
    },
    {
      "question": "三冬",
      "answer": "さんとう",
      "meaning": "three winter months"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪溜まり",
      "answer": "ゆきだまり",
      "meaning": "snowdrift"
    },
    {
      "question": "無限後退",
      "answer": "むげんこうたい",
      "meaning": "infinite regress"
    },
    {
      "question": "学制",
      "answer": "がくせい",
      "meaning": "educational or school system"
    },
    {
      "question": "返し縫い",
      "answer": "かえしぬい",
      "meaning": "backstitch"
    },
    {
      "question": "三角測量",
      "answer": "さんかくそくりょう",
      "meaning": "triangulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "草毟り",
      "answer": "くさむしり",
      "meaning": "weeding, weeder, weeding fork"
    },
    {
      "question": "行跡",
      "answer": "ぎょうせき",
      "meaning": "behavior, behaviour"
    },
    {
      "question": "耽美派",
      "answer": "たんびは",
      "meaning": "aesthetic school"
    },
    {
      "question": "西洋音楽",
      "answer": "せいようおんがく",
      "meaning": "Western music"
    },
    {
      "question": "三人三様",
      "answer": "さんにんさんよう",
      "meaning": "each of the three being different from the other two, each of the three having his (her) own way"
    },
    {
      "question": "蒼々",
      "answer": "あおあお",
      "meaning": "verdant, fresh and green, bright green, lush"
    },
    {
      "question": "別売",
      "answer": "べつうり,べつばい",
      "meaning": "selling separately, not being included in the price"
    },
    {
      "question": "癲癇",
      "answer": "てんかん",
      "meaning": "epilepsy, epileptic fit"
    },
    {
      "question": "国つ神",
      "answer": "くにつかみ",
      "meaning": "gods of the land, earthly deities"
    },
    {
      "question": "箱書き",
      "answer": "はこがき",
      "meaning": "autograph or note of authentication written on a box containing an art work"
    },
    {
      "question": "香箱",
      "answer": "こうばこ",
      "meaning": "incense box"
    },
    {
      "question": "白焼",
      "answer": "しらやき",
      "meaning": "seafood grilled without seasoning, unglazed ceramic ware"
    },
    {
      "question": "代表社員",
      "answer": "だいひょうしゃいん",
      "meaning": "senior partner"
    },
    {
      "question": "米麦",
      "answer": "べいばく",
      "meaning": "rice and barley, corn"
    },
    {
      "question": "文芸復興",
      "answer": "ぶんげいふっこう",
      "meaning": "Renaissance"
    },
    {
      "question": "寒九",
      "answer": "かんく",
      "meaning": "ninth day of the cold season (approx January 13th)"
    },
    {
      "question": "心経",
      "answer": "しんぎょう,しんきょう",
      "meaning": "Heart Sutra"
    },
    {
      "question": "紙数",
      "answer": "しすう",
      "meaning": "number of pages, page space"
    },
    {
      "question": "欣求浄土",
      "answer": "ごんぐじょうど",
      "meaning": "seeking rebirth in the Pure Land"
    },
    {
      "question": "本木",
      "answer": "もとき",
      "meaning": "original stock"
    },
    {
      "question": "歴年",
      "answer": "れきねん",
      "meaning": "calendar year, civil year, time, year after year"
    },
    {
      "question": "水金",
      "answer": "みずきん,すいきん",
      "meaning": "liquid gold (used for applying gold to ceramics, etc.), bribe, sweetener, douceur, Wednesday and Fri"
    },
    {
      "question": "灰塗れ",
      "answer": "はいまみれ",
      "meaning": "covered with ashes"
    },
    {
      "question": "舟運",
      "answer": "しゅううん",
      "meaning": "transportation by water (e.g. by ship)"
    },
    {
      "question": "磯魚",
      "answer": "いそうお",
      "meaning": "inshore fish, fish that lives in rocky coastal waters"
    },
    {
      "question": "語族",
      "answer": "ごぞく",
      "meaning": "language family, family of languages"
    },
    {
      "question": "葡",
      "answer": "ぽ",
      "meaning": "Portugal, Portuguese language"
    },
    {
      "question": "薬籠",
      "answer": "やくろう",
      "meaning": "medicine chest (container)"
    },
    {
      "question": "因循",
      "answer": "いんじゅん",
      "meaning": "indecision, vacillation"
    },
    {
      "question": "空相",
      "answer": "くうそう",
      "meaning": "the empty nature of all things"
    },
    {
      "question": "粘土団子",
      "answer": "ねんどだんご",
      "meaning": "seed ball ('natural farming' technique)"
    },
    {
      "question": "結びの神",
      "answer": "むすびのかみ",
      "meaning": "Cupid"
    },
    {
      "question": "肝玉",
      "answer": "きもったま,きもだま",
      "meaning": "guts, pluck, nerve, spirit"
    },
    {
      "question": "不生不滅",
      "answer": "ふしょうふめつ",
      "meaning": "neither arising nor ceasing"
    },
    {
      "question": "売地",
      "answer": "うりち",
      "meaning": "land for sale"
    },
    {
      "question": "疎略",
      "answer": "そりゃく",
      "meaning": "coarse, crude, rough"
    },
    {
      "question": "艱苦",
      "answer": "かんく",
      "meaning": "privation suffering"
    },
    {
      "question": "各種学校",
      "answer": "かくしゅがっこう",
      "meaning": "vocational school"
    },
    {
      "question": "糠雨",
      "answer": "ぬかあめ",
      "meaning": "drizzle, light rain"
    },
    {
      "question": "春の水",
      "answer": "はるのみず",
      "meaning": "lakes and torrents of spring (overflowing with water)"
    },
    {
      "question": "ハブ空港",
      "answer": "ハブくうこう",
      "meaning": "hub airport"
    },
    {
      "question": "王党",
      "answer": "おうとう",
      "meaning": "royalists, monarchists"
    },
    {
      "question": "補則",
      "answer": "ほそく",
      "meaning": "supplementary rules"
    },
    {
      "question": "競漕",
      "answer": "きょうそう",
      "meaning": "regatta, boat race"
    },
    {
      "question": "飄逸",
      "answer": "ひょういつ",
      "meaning": "easygoing, unconventional, happy-go-lucky, light"
    },
    {
      "question": "寒地",
      "answer": "かんち",
      "meaning": "cold region"
    },
    {
      "question": "尺を取る",
      "answer": "しゃくをとる",
      "meaning": "to measure (the length)"
    },
    {
      "question": "声掛り",
      "answer": "こえがかり",
      "meaning": "recommendation of an influential person"
    },
    {
      "question": "社会化",
      "answer": "しゃかいか",
      "meaning": "socialization, socialisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "トロ箱",
      "answer": "トロばこ",
      "meaning": "box for shipping seafood (usually made of styrofoam)"
    },
    {
      "question": "復習う",
      "answer": "さらう",
      "meaning": "to review, to rehearse, to practise, to practice"
    },
    {
      "question": "凶状",
      "answer": "きょうじょう",
      "meaning": "crime, offense, offence"
    },
    {
      "question": "灰重石",
      "answer": "かいじゅうせき",
      "meaning": "scheelite"
    },
    {
      "question": "蠅帳",
      "answer": "はいちょう",
      "meaning": "fly-net cupboard"
    },
    {
      "question": "紳商",
      "answer": "しんしょう",
      "meaning": "wealthy merchant"
    },
    {
      "question": "蓄電器",
      "answer": "ちくでんき",
      "meaning": "(electric) condensor"
    },
    {
      "question": "立て切る",
      "answer": "たてきる",
      "meaning": "to close tight"
    },
    {
      "question": "長円",
      "answer": "ちょうえん",
      "meaning": "ellipse, oval"
    },
    {
      "question": "誘起",
      "answer": "ゆうき",
      "meaning": "evocation, inducement, giving rise to"
    },
    {
      "question": "歌学",
      "answer": "かがく",
      "meaning": "poetry, versification"
    },
    {
      "question": "眉墨",
      "answer": "まゆずみ",
      "meaning": "eyebrow pencil, blackened eyebrows, (metaphorically) distant mountain range"
    },
    {
      "question": "無蓋",
      "answer": "むがい",
      "meaning": "open, uncovered"
    },
    {
      "question": "漁り火",
      "answer": "いさりび",
      "meaning": "fire for luring fish at night"
    },
    {
      "question": "量目",
      "answer": "りょうめ,はかりめ,りょうもく",
      "meaning": "weight"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭株",
      "answer": "あたまかぶ",
      "meaning": "chief, leader, head, executive"
    },
    {
      "question": "宿望",
      "answer": "しゅくぼう,しゅくもう",
      "meaning": "long-cherished desire"
    },
    {
      "question": "競り市",
      "answer": "せりいち",
      "meaning": "auction market"
    },
    {
      "question": "金融緩和",
      "answer": "きんゆうかんわ",
      "meaning": "monetary easing"
    },
    {
      "question": "伝動",
      "answer": "でんどう",
      "meaning": "transmission (of motive power), drive, gearing"
    },
    {
      "question": "生かる",
      "answer": "いかる",
      "meaning": "to be arranged (flowers, etc.), to be on display, to be buried"
    },
    {
      "question": "怖怖",
      "answer": "こわごわ",
      "meaning": "fearfully, timidly, cautiously, nervously"
    },
    {
      "question": "海淵",
      "answer": "かいえん",
      "meaning": "(ocean) deep, deepest part of a trench"
    },
    {
      "question": "公開状",
      "answer": "こうかいじょう",
      "meaning": "open letter"
    },
    {
      "question": "農商務省",
      "answer": "のうしょうむしょう",
      "meaning": "Ministry of Agriculture and Commerce (Meiji-Taisho)"
    },
    {
      "question": "換骨奪胎",
      "answer": "かんこつだったい",
      "meaning": "adaptation (e.g. of a poem or novel), rewriting, recasting, modification, rehashing"
    },
    {
      "question": "具する",
      "answer": "ぐする",
      "meaning": "to accompany, to follow, to assemble (necessary items), to prepare"
    },
    {
      "question": "既往歴",
      "answer": "きおうれき",
      "meaning": "case or medical history"
    },
    {
      "question": "銀銭",
      "answer": "ぎんせん",
      "meaning": "silver coin"
    },
    {
      "question": "馴鹿",
      "answer": "となかい,じゅんろく",
      "meaning": "reindeer (Rangifer tarandus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "上薬",
      "answer": "うわぐすり",
      "meaning": "glaze, overglaze, enamel"
    },
    {
      "question": "口三味線",
      "answer": "くちざみせん,くちじゃみせん",
      "meaning": "humming a samisen tune"
    },
    {
      "question": "書き下す",
      "answer": "かきくだす",
      "meaning": "to write from top to bottom, to write out (at a stretch), to write without a pause, to rewrite class"
    },
    {
      "question": "北京料理",
      "answer": "ペキンりょうり",
      "meaning": "Beijing cuisine"
    },
    {
      "question": "異字同訓",
      "answer": "いじどうくん",
      "meaning": "different kanji with the same Japanese reading (and usu. a similar meaning)"
    },
    {
      "question": "心悸亢進",
      "answer": "しんきこうしん",
      "meaning": "palpitations (of the heart)"
    },
    {
      "question": "固定票",
      "answer": "こていひょう",
      "meaning": "solid (an assured, a safe) vote, solid (assured) support"
    },
    {
      "question": "放火罪",
      "answer": "ほうかざい",
      "meaning": "(the crime of) arson"
    },
    {
      "question": "何処やら",
      "answer": "どこやら",
      "meaning": "somewhere, somehow"
    },
    {
      "question": "槍烏賊",
      "answer": "やりいか",
      "meaning": "spear squid (Loligo bleekeri)"
    },
    {
      "question": "脱毛器",
      "answer": "だつもうき",
      "meaning": "depilator"
    },
    {
      "question": "唯唯諾諾",
      "answer": "いいだくだく",
      "meaning": "obedient, submissive, tame, slavish"
    },
    {
      "question": "袖付け",
      "answer": "そでつけ",
      "meaning": "attaching a sleeve to the body of a shirt, sleeve seam"
    },
    {
      "question": "方伯",
      "answer": "ほうはく",
      "meaning": "landgrave"
    },
    {
      "question": "粗製品",
      "answer": "そせいひん",
      "meaning": "inferior goods"
    },
    {
      "question": "裁定取引",
      "answer": "さいていとりひき",
      "meaning": "arbitrage, arbitrage position, arbitrage transaction"
    },
    {
      "question": "荒磯",
      "answer": "あらいそ",
      "meaning": "reefy coast, windswept and wave-beaten shore"
    },
    {
      "question": "転置",
      "answer": "てんち",
      "meaning": "transposition"
    },
    {
      "question": "苦厄",
      "answer": "くやく",
      "meaning": "hardship and misfortune"
    },
    {
      "question": "鶸",
      "answer": "ひわ",
      "meaning": "cardueline finch (any finch of subfamily Carduelinae, esp. the Eurasian siskin, Carduelis spinus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "高山帯",
      "answer": "こうざんたい",
      "meaning": "alpine zone"
    },
    {
      "question": "原薬",
      "answer": "げんやく",
      "meaning": "(bulk) drug substance"
    },
    {
      "question": "横紋筋",
      "answer": "おうもんきん",
      "meaning": "striated muscle"
    },
    {
      "question": "賢弟",
      "answer": "けんてい",
      "meaning": "wise younger brother, polite reference to another's younger brother, or to one's junior"
    },
    {
      "question": "夕靄",
      "answer": "ゆうもや",
      "meaning": "evening haze or mist"
    },
    {
      "question": "元請",
      "answer": "もとうけ",
      "meaning": "prime contract work, prime contractor"
    },
    {
      "question": "整数論",
      "answer": "せいすうろん",
      "meaning": "theory of numbers, number theory"
    },
    {
      "question": "大衆魚",
      "answer": "たいしゅうぎょ",
      "meaning": "cheap fish for the masses (e.g. sardines, mackerel, pike)"
    },
    {
      "question": "済世",
      "answer": "さいせい,せいせい",
      "meaning": "saving the world, promoting national welfare"
    },
    {
      "question": "吸物",
      "answer": "すいもの",
      "meaning": "clear broth soup, with ingredients and garnish floating in and on it"
    },
    {
      "question": "満堂",
      "answer": "まんどう",
      "meaning": "the whole audience"
    },
    {
      "question": "苧",
      "answer": "お,からむし,むし",
      "meaning": "cannabis (Cannabis sativa), hemp (plant), hemp (fiber), linen, flax, jute, ramie (Boehmeria nivea va"
    },
    {
      "question": "早仕舞い",
      "answer": "はやじまい",
      "meaning": "early closing, finishing (work) early"
    },
    {
      "question": "原論",
      "answer": "げんろん",
      "meaning": "theory, principles"
    },
    {
      "question": "永別",
      "answer": "えいべつ",
      "meaning": "last farewell"
    },
    {
      "question": "冠毛",
      "answer": "かんもう",
      "meaning": "thistledown"
    },
    {
      "question": "攻守同盟",
      "answer": "こうしゅどうめい",
      "meaning": "offensive and defensive alliance"
    },
    {
      "question": "鶴首",
      "answer": "かくしゅ,つるくび",
      "meaning": "looking forward to, item with a long slender neck (e.g. vase, bottle), long-necked person"
    },
    {
      "question": "京都五山",
      "answer": "きょうとござん",
      "meaning": "Kyoto Gozan, the five most important Rinzai temples of Kyoto, as well as Nanzen-ji"
    },
    {
      "question": "口糧",
      "answer": "こうりょう",
      "meaning": "rations"
    },
    {
      "question": "異心",
      "answer": "いしん,ことごころ",
      "meaning": "treachery, treacherous designs"
    },
    {
      "question": "キスカ島",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "一本占地",
      "answer": "いっぽんしめじ",
      "meaning": "livid pinkgill (species of poisonous mushroom, Entoloma sinuatum)"
    },
    {
      "question": "惰気",
      "answer": "だき",
      "meaning": "indolence, listlessness"
    },
    {
      "question": "学位論文",
      "answer": "がくいろんぶん",
      "meaning": "thesis, dissertation"
    },
    {
      "question": "内釜",
      "answer": "うちがま",
      "meaning": "rice cooker pot, pot inside rice cooker, indoor bathwater heater"
    },
    {
      "question": "卵豆腐",
      "answer": "たまごどうふ",
      "meaning": "tamago dofu, tamago-dofu, steamed egg custard with soup stock, cooked in a square mould"
    },
    {
      "question": "森林限界",
      "answer": "しんりんげんかい",
      "meaning": "tree line, forest line, timberline"
    },
    {
      "question": "塩化水素",
      "answer": "えんかすいそ",
      "meaning": "hydrogen chloride"
    },
    {
      "question": "微小管",
      "answer": "びしょうかん",
      "meaning": "microtubule"
    },
    {
      "question": "茶托",
      "answer": "ちゃたく",
      "meaning": "teacup saucer"
    },
    {
      "question": "海洋汚染",
      "answer": "かいようおせん",
      "meaning": "marine pollution, oceanic pollution, sea pollution"
    },
    {
      "question": "船人",
      "answer": "ふなびと",
      "meaning": "sailor, boatman, passenger"
    },
    {
      "question": "逆さ言葉",
      "answer": "さかさことば",
      "meaning": "word said backwards, word of opposite meaning"
    },
    {
      "question": "弔花",
      "answer": "ちょうか",
      "meaning": "funeral flowers"
    },
    {
      "question": "凡々",
      "answer": "ぼんぼん",
      "meaning": "ordinary, usual"
    },
    {
      "question": "統幕",
      "answer": "とうばく",
      "meaning": "general staff headquarters"
    },
    {
      "question": "城趾",
      "answer": "じょうし",
      "meaning": "castle site, ruins of a castle"
    },
    {
      "question": "糸倉",
      "answer": "いとぐら",
      "meaning": "pegbox (of a shamisen, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "制振",
      "answer": "せいしん",
      "meaning": "vibration control (in earthquake-resistant construction)"
    },
    {
      "question": "悠々閑々",
      "answer": "ゆうゆうかんかん",
      "meaning": "composed and unhurried, easygoing and leisurely, in indolence"
    },
    {
      "question": "祖語",
      "answer": "そご",
      "meaning": "protolanguage, parent language"
    },
    {
      "question": "沢辺",
      "answer": "さわべ",
      "meaning": "edge of a swamp"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭韻",
      "answer": "とういん",
      "meaning": "alliteration"
    },
    {
      "question": "大山椒魚",
      "answer": "おおさんしょううお",
      "meaning": "Japanese giant salamander (Andrias japonicus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "砂紋",
      "answer": "さもん",
      "meaning": "raked gravel waves (in a rock garden), ripple mark"
    },
    {
      "question": "古顔",
      "answer": "ふるがお",
      "meaning": "familiar face, old timer"
    },
    {
      "question": "新撰",
      "answer": "しんせん",
      "meaning": "newly compiled, selected or edited"
    },
    {
      "question": "雨上り",
      "answer": "あめあがり,あまあがり",
      "meaning": "after the rain"
    },
    {
      "question": "法人格",
      "answer": "ほうじんかく",
      "meaning": "legal personality, juridical personality, corporate status, non-person legal entity"
    },
    {
      "question": "清閑",
      "answer": "せいかん",
      "meaning": "peaceful, quiet, tranquility, tranquillity"
    },
    {
      "question": "行宮",
      "answer": "あんぐう",
      "meaning": "temporary lodging built to accommodate an Imperial visit"
    },
    {
      "question": "本源",
      "answer": "ほんげん",
      "meaning": "origin, root, cause, principle"
    },
    {
      "question": "末成り",
      "answer": "うらなり",
      "meaning": "fruit grown near the tip of the vine (hence stunted and unripe), weak-looking fellow, pale-faced man"
    },
    {
      "question": "取組み",
      "answer": "とりくみ",
      "meaning": "bout (in sports, etc.), match, effort, initiative, dealing with, grappling with, wrestling with"
    },
    {
      "question": "長寛",
      "answer": "ちょうかん",
      "meaning": "Chōkan era (1163.3.29-1165.6.5)"
    },
    {
      "question": "乳臭",
      "answer": "にゅうしゅう",
      "meaning": "boyishness, inexperience"
    },
    {
      "question": "雇い止め",
      "answer": "やといどめ",
      "meaning": "termination of employment contract, unfair termination"
    },
    {
      "question": "擦半鐘",
      "answer": "すりばんしょう",
      "meaning": "fire alarm ringing continuously to warn that a fire is extremely near, sound as produced by this ala"
    },
    {
      "question": "親文字",
      "answer": "おやもじ",
      "meaning": "entry kanji in a kanji dictionary, capital letter, matrix (printing), kanji corresponding to furigan"
    },
    {
      "question": "強飯",
      "answer": "こわめし,こわいい,ごうはん",
      "meaning": "glutinous rice with red beans (eaten on celebratory occasions), mochi rice with red beans, event in"
    },
    {
      "question": "恣意性",
      "answer": "しいせい",
      "meaning": "arbitrariness"
    },
    {
      "question": "一塁手",
      "answer": "いちるいしゅ",
      "meaning": "first baseman"
    },
    {
      "question": "薬理学",
      "answer": "やくりがく",
      "meaning": "pharmacology"
    },
    {
      "question": "豆絞り",
      "answer": "まめしぼり",
      "meaning": "spotted pattern"
    },
    {
      "question": "愁訴",
      "answer": "しゅうそ",
      "meaning": "complaint"
    },
    {
      "question": "酒石酸",
      "answer": "しゅせきさん",
      "meaning": "tartaric acid"
    },
    {
      "question": "蟀谷",
      "answer": "こめかみ",
      "meaning": "temple (side of head)"
    },
    {
      "question": "外径",
      "answer": "がいけい",
      "meaning": "outer diameter"
    },
    {
      "question": "栄典",
      "answer": "えいてん",
      "meaning": "honours, honors, ceremony, exercises"
    },
    {
      "question": "引き窓",
      "answer": "ひきまど",
      "meaning": "skylight, trap door"
    },
    {
      "question": "提灯記事",
      "answer": "ちょうちんきじ",
      "meaning": "puff piece (in a newspaper, etc.), flatteringly exaggerated article, sycophantic article"
    },
    {
      "question": "焙じる",
      "answer": "ほうじる",
      "meaning": "to roast (i.e. tea leaves)"
    },
    {
      "question": "風炎",
      "answer": "ふうえん",
      "meaning": "foehn, föhn, foehn wind, föhn wind"
    },
    {
      "question": "装花",
      "answer": "そうか",
      "meaning": "floral decorations, e.g. at a wedding"
    },
    {
      "question": "観想",
      "answer": "かんそう",
      "meaning": "meditation, contemplation"
    },
    {
      "question": "劫略",
      "answer": "きょうりゃく,ごうりゃく",
      "meaning": "pillage, plunder"
    },
    {
      "question": "等圧線",
      "answer": "とうあつせん",
      "meaning": "isobar"
    },
    {
      "question": "真善美",
      "answer": "しんぜんび",
      "meaning": "the true, the good, and the beautiful"
    },
    {
      "question": "兼併",
      "answer": "けんぺい",
      "meaning": "uniting, unity"
    },
    {
      "question": "半旗",
      "answer": "はんき",
      "meaning": "flag at half-mast"
    },
    {
      "question": "審級",
      "answer": "しんきゅう",
      "meaning": "instance (e.g. first instance, second instance, etc. in a legal proceeding)"
    },
    {
      "question": "止揚",
      "answer": "しよう",
      "meaning": "sublation (philosophy)"
    },
    {
      "question": "人我",
      "answer": "じんが",
      "meaning": "oneself and others"
    },
    {
      "question": "打身",
      "answer": "うちみ",
      "meaning": "bruise"
    },
    {
      "question": "櫺子",
      "answer": "れんじ",
      "meaning": "latticework"
    },
    {
      "question": "方今",
      "answer": "ほうこん",
      "meaning": "present time, now, nowadays"
    },
    {
      "question": "生き馬",
      "answer": "いきうま",
      "meaning": "live horse, living horse"
    },
    {
      "question": "無躾",
      "answer": "ぶしつけ",
      "meaning": "ill-bred, impolite, rude, impudent, insolent, blunt"
    },
    {
      "question": "対位法",
      "answer": "たいいほう",
      "meaning": "counterpoint, contrapuntal"
    },
    {
      "question": "天承",
      "answer": "てんしょう",
      "meaning": "Tenshō era (1131.1.29-1132.8.11)"
    },
    {
      "question": "結党",
      "answer": "けっとう",
      "meaning": "formation of a party"
    },
    {
      "question": "歌碑",
      "answer": "かひ",
      "meaning": "monument (stele, gravestone, etc.) engraved with a waka"
    },
    {
      "question": "八間",
      "answer": "はちけん",
      "meaning": "large hanging paper lantern"
    },
    {
      "question": "亭々",
      "answer": "ていてい",
      "meaning": "lofty (tree)"
    },
    {
      "question": "御面相",
      "answer": "ごめんそう",
      "meaning": "frightful face"
    },
    {
      "question": "衛所",
      "answer": "えいしょ",
      "meaning": "place guarded by soldiers, torpedo room"
    },
    {
      "question": "大耳",
      "answer": "おおみみ",
      "meaning": "big ears, listening without paying attention"
    },
    {
      "question": "力拳",
      "answer": "ちからこぶし",
      "meaning": "clenched fist"
    },
    {
      "question": "鹿の子",
      "answer": "かのこ",
      "meaning": "cloth dyed in a dappled pattern, pattern of white spots, dapples, mochi containing red bean paste, f"
    },
    {
      "question": "国有林",
      "answer": "こくゆうりん",
      "meaning": "national forest"
    },
    {
      "question": "労災保険",
      "answer": "ろうさいほけん",
      "meaning": "worker's accident insurance"
    },
    {
      "question": "万寿",
      "answer": "ばんじゅ,まんじゅ",
      "meaning": "longevity, Manju era (1024.7.13-1028.7.25)"
    },
    {
      "question": "唐人",
      "answer": "とうじん,からびと",
      "meaning": "Chinese person, foreigner, Korean person"
    },
    {
      "question": "大正天皇",
      "answer": "たいしょうてんのう",
      "meaning": "Emperor Taishō (1879-1926, reigned 1912-1926), Emperor Yoshihito"
    },
    {
      "question": "字足らず",
      "answer": "じたらず",
      "meaning": "waka, haiku, etc. with insufficient syllables"
    },
    {
      "question": "史観",
      "answer": "しかん",
      "meaning": "historical view, view of history (from a given point of view)"
    },
    {
      "question": "旧仮名",
      "answer": "きゅうかな",
      "meaning": "old kana orthography (used before 1946 reform), historical kana orthography"
    },
    {
      "question": "霞草",
      "answer": "かすみそう",
      "meaning": "common gypsophila (Gypsophila elegans), baby's breath, babies' breath, soaproot"
    },
    {
      "question": "利敵",
      "answer": "りてき",
      "meaning": "benefitting the enemy, benefiting the enemy"
    },
    {
      "question": "表層雪崩",
      "answer": "ひょうそうなだれ",
      "meaning": "surface avalanche"
    },
    {
      "question": "一渡り",
      "answer": "ひとわたり",
      "meaning": "generally, in the main, briefly (look over, explain, etc.), roughly, more or less"
    },
    {
      "question": "基底状態",
      "answer": "きていじょうたい",
      "meaning": "ground state"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り手",
      "answer": "とりて",
      "meaning": "recipient, receiver, acceptor, taker, skilled practitioner (of judo, sumo, etc.), person who picks u"
    },
    {
      "question": "訳本",
      "answer": "やくほん",
      "meaning": "translated book"
    },
    {
      "question": "屍蠟",
      "answer": "しろう",
      "meaning": "adipocere, grave wax, greying of the body fats of a corpse which rests in a moist but airless place"
    },
    {
      "question": "膏血",
      "answer": "こうけつ",
      "meaning": "(hard-earned rewards of) sweat and blood"
    },
    {
      "question": "西半球",
      "answer": "にしはんきゅう",
      "meaning": "western hemisphere, the Occident"
    },
    {
      "question": "翼廊",
      "answer": "よくろう",
      "meaning": "transept"
    },
    {
      "question": "晴雨",
      "answer": "せいう",
      "meaning": "(clear or rainy) weather"
    },
    {
      "question": "駻馬",
      "answer": "かんば",
      "meaning": "unruly horse, unmanageable horse, unbroken horse"
    },
    {
      "question": "出口戦略",
      "answer": "でぐちせんりゃく",
      "meaning": "exit strategy"
    },
    {
      "question": "富ます",
      "answer": "とます",
      "meaning": "to enrich, to make wealthy"
    },
    {
      "question": "免責特権",
      "answer": "めんせきとっけん",
      "meaning": "diplomatic immunity"
    },
    {
      "question": "先陣争い",
      "answer": "せんじんあらそい",
      "meaning": "competition (rivalry) to first (e.g. rider in a charge)"
    },
    {
      "question": "書き流す",
      "answer": "かきながす",
      "meaning": "to write off"
    },
    {
      "question": "デカ目",
      "answer": "デカめ",
      "meaning": "'large eyes' look (makeup technique)"
    },
    {
      "question": "高御座",
      "answer": "たかみくら",
      "meaning": "Imperial throne"
    },
    {
      "question": "三枚肉",
      "answer": "さんまいにく",
      "meaning": "boneless rib (esp. of pork or beef), boned rib"
    },
    {
      "question": "等差数列",
      "answer": "とうさすうれつ",
      "meaning": "arithmetic progression, arithmetic sequence"
    },
    {
      "question": "玄麦",
      "answer": "げんばく",
      "meaning": "unpolished wheat or barley"
    },
    {
      "question": "担担麺",
      "answer": "タンタンめん",
      "meaning": "Szechuan dish of noodles covered with a sauce of sesame paste and chili oil"
    },
    {
      "question": "回り階段",
      "answer": "まわりかいだん",
      "meaning": "winder staircase"
    },
    {
      "question": "纜",
      "answer": "ともづな",
      "meaning": "stern line, mooring line"
    },
    {
      "question": "火明り",
      "answer": "ほあかり,ひあかり",
      "meaning": "lamplight, torchlight, firelight"
    },
    {
      "question": "境域",
      "answer": "きょういき",
      "meaning": "boundary, border, precinct, grounds"
    },
    {
      "question": "委しい",
      "answer": "くわしい",
      "meaning": "detailed, full, accurate, knowing very well, well-acquainted, well-informed"
    },
    {
      "question": "統一行動",
      "answer": "とういつこうどう",
      "meaning": "joint action, acting in unison"
    },
    {
      "question": "金札",
      "answer": "きんさつ",
      "meaning": "golden label, golden protective talisman, kinsatsu (Edo period paper money), kinsatsu (early Meiji p"
    },
    {
      "question": "武装中立",
      "answer": "ぶそうちゅうりつ",
      "meaning": "armed neutrality"
    },
    {
      "question": "手回り品",
      "answer": "てまわりひん",
      "meaning": "personal effects or belongings"
    },
    {
      "question": "唯心論",
      "answer": "ゆいしんろん",
      "meaning": "spiritualism, idealism, mentalism"
    },
    {
      "question": "敵失",
      "answer": "てきしつ",
      "meaning": "error made by the enemy or opposing team"
    },
    {
      "question": "酢漿草",
      "answer": "かたばみ",
      "meaning": "creeping woodsorrel (Oxalis corniculata), family crest shaped like creeping woodsorrel"
    },
    {
      "question": "伴食",
      "answer": "ばんしょく",
      "meaning": "eating with a guest, nominal official (a slighting term)"
    },
    {
      "question": "彫塑",
      "answer": "ちょうそ",
      "meaning": "carving, engraving, clay model, plastic art"
    },
    {
      "question": "強直",
      "answer": "きょうちょく",
      "meaning": "rigidity, uprightness"
    },
    {
      "question": "光化学",
      "answer": "こうかがく",
      "meaning": "photochemistry"
    },
    {
      "question": "中編小説",
      "answer": "ちゅうへんしょうせつ",
      "meaning": "novelette, novella, short novel, long short story, medium-length story"
    },
    {
      "question": "千枚漬け",
      "answer": "せんまいずけ",
      "meaning": "pickled sliced radishes"
    },
    {
      "question": "士業",
      "answer": "しぎょう",
      "meaning": "professional occupation, professional practice"
    },
    {
      "question": "明証",
      "answer": "めいしょう",
      "meaning": "proof, evidence, corroboration"
    },
    {
      "question": "寂として",
      "answer": "せきとして",
      "meaning": "silently, hushed, in a still manner"
    },
    {
      "question": "点景",
      "answer": "てんけい",
      "meaning": "persons or animals added to a picture, incidental details of a picture"
    },
    {
      "question": "常法",
      "answer": "じょうほう",
      "meaning": "fixed rule, usual way, usual method"
    },
    {
      "question": "病癖",
      "answer": "びょうへき",
      "meaning": "bad habit, peculiarity, weakness"
    },
    {
      "question": "雀躍",
      "answer": "じゃくやく",
      "meaning": "leaping for joy, exultation"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷し中華",
      "answer": "ひやしちゅうか",
      "meaning": "chilled Chinese noodles"
    },
    {
      "question": "苔桃",
      "answer": "こけもも",
      "meaning": "lingonberry (Vaccinium vitis-idaea), cowberry"
    },
    {
      "question": "愛唱",
      "answer": "あいしょう",
      "meaning": "loving to sing (a song), singing with great fondness"
    },
    {
      "question": "聾者",
      "answer": "ろうしゃ",
      "meaning": "deaf person"
    },
    {
      "question": "凸面鏡",
      "answer": "とつめんきょう",
      "meaning": "convex mirror"
    },
    {
      "question": "絃楽",
      "answer": "げんがく",
      "meaning": "music for strings, string music"
    },
    {
      "question": "卜う",
      "answer": "うらなう",
      "meaning": "to tell someone's fortune, to forecast, to predict, to divine"
    },
    {
      "question": "過渡的",
      "answer": "かとてき",
      "meaning": "transitional"
    },
    {
      "question": "海氷",
      "answer": "かいひょう",
      "meaning": "sea ice"
    },
    {
      "question": "連体",
      "answer": "れんたい",
      "meaning": "pre-noun adjectival, adnominal adjective"
    },
    {
      "question": "学術会議",
      "answer": "がくじゅつかいぎ",
      "meaning": "Japan Science Council"
    },
    {
      "question": "野積み",
      "answer": "のづみ",
      "meaning": "piled out in the open"
    },
    {
      "question": "天安",
      "answer": "てんあん",
      "meaning": "Ten'an era (857.2.21-859.4.15)"
    },
    {
      "question": "合の子",
      "answer": "あいのこ",
      "meaning": "person of mixed parentage, crossbreed, Eurasian, mulatto, hybrid"
    },
    {
      "question": "徳義",
      "answer": "とくぎ",
      "meaning": "morals, morality, sincerity"
    },
    {
      "question": "険路",
      "answer": "けんろ",
      "meaning": "steep path"
    },
    {
      "question": "水平思考",
      "answer": "すいへいしこう",
      "meaning": "lateral thinking"
    },
    {
      "question": "軸物",
      "answer": "じくもの",
      "meaning": "scroll (picture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "妊る",
      "answer": "みごもる",
      "meaning": "to become pregnant"
    },
    {
      "question": "心中立て",
      "answer": "しんじゅうだて",
      "meaning": "fidelity (in a romantic relationship), loyalty"
    },
    {
      "question": "民情",
      "answer": "みんじょう",
      "meaning": "condition (sentiment) of the people"
    },
    {
      "question": "擡頭",
      "answer": "たいとう",
      "meaning": "rise (e.g. of a movement), emergence, rearing one's head, gaining prominence, coming to the fore, ga"
    },
    {
      "question": "毀棄",
      "answer": "きき",
      "meaning": "destruction, demolition, damage"
    },
    {
      "question": "湯垢",
      "answer": "ゆあか",
      "meaning": "scale (i.e. hard water coating in a kettle, etc.), fur"
    },
    {
      "question": "噎び泣き",
      "answer": "むせびなき",
      "meaning": "sobbing"
    },
    {
      "question": "容積率",
      "answer": "ようせきりつ",
      "meaning": "floor space index, FSI, floor area ratio, FAR, ratio of building size to lot, plot ratio"
    },
    {
      "question": "全面講和",
      "answer": "ぜんめんこうわ",
      "meaning": "overall peace treaty"
    },
    {
      "question": "蟯虫",
      "answer": "ぎょうちゅう",
      "meaning": "pinworm (Enterobius vermicularis), threadworm"
    },
    {
      "question": "袖章",
      "answer": "そでしょう",
      "meaning": "sleeve badge, sleeve patch, chevrons"
    },
    {
      "question": "彼此",
      "answer": "あれこれ,かれこれ,ひし",
      "meaning": "this and that, this or that, one thing or another, this way and that, around, about, round about, ro"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤墨",
      "answer": "あかずみ",
      "meaning": "vermillion stick, red ink"
    },
    {
      "question": "自学自習",
      "answer": "じがくじしゅう",
      "meaning": "teaching oneself, learning by oneself, self-study"
    },
    {
      "question": "築地塀",
      "answer": "ついじべい",
      "meaning": "mud wall with a roof, roofed mud wall"
    },
    {
      "question": "佝僂",
      "answer": "くる",
      "meaning": "rickets, someone suffering from rickets"
    },
    {
      "question": "摩り込む",
      "answer": "すりこむ",
      "meaning": "to rub in (e.g. cream into the skin), to grind and mix (e.g. pepper into miso)"
    },
    {
      "question": "韻文",
      "answer": "いんぶん",
      "meaning": "verse, poetry"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪婆",
      "answer": "あくば",
      "meaning": "mean old woman"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪材料",
      "answer": "あくざいりょう",
      "meaning": "adverse stock market factor, bearish market factor, negative factor"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷雨",
      "answer": "れいう",
      "meaning": "chilly rain"
    },
    {
      "question": "涅槃像",
      "answer": "ねはんぞう",
      "meaning": "image of the Buddha entering nirvana"
    },
    {
      "question": "愁嘆",
      "answer": "しゅうたん",
      "meaning": "lamentation, sorrow, grief"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜仕事",
      "answer": "よしごと",
      "meaning": "night work"
    },
    {
      "question": "侍臣",
      "answer": "じしん",
      "meaning": "courtier, attendant"
    },
    {
      "question": "入寂",
      "answer": "にゅうじゃく",
      "meaning": "death of a priest, nirvana, spiritual liberty"
    },
    {
      "question": "玄米パン",
      "answer": "げんまいパン",
      "meaning": "steamed bread made with unpolished rice flour"
    },
    {
      "question": "小座敷",
      "answer": "こざしき",
      "meaning": "small tatami room, extension of the main room of a home (in traditional palatial-style architecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "盲管",
      "answer": "もうかん",
      "meaning": "cul-de-sac, blind pouch"
    },
    {
      "question": "職住一体",
      "answer": "しょくじゅういったい",
      "meaning": "having one's workplace at home, living and working at the same location (independent farmers, home w"
    },
    {
      "question": "社史",
      "answer": "しゃし",
      "meaning": "history of a company"
    },
    {
      "question": "蚕蛾",
      "answer": "かいこが",
      "meaning": "silkworm moth, silk moth (Bombyx mori)"
    },
    {
      "question": "鴇",
      "answer": "とき,つき,のがん",
      "meaning": "Japanese crested ibis (Nipponia nippon), crested ibis, bustard (esp. the great bustard, Otis tarda)"
    },
    {
      "question": "冪",
      "answer": "べき",
      "meaning": "exponent, power"
    },
    {
      "question": "感動詞",
      "answer": "かんどうし",
      "meaning": "interjection"
    },
    {
      "question": "会計学",
      "answer": "かいけいがく",
      "meaning": "(study of) accounting, accountancy"
    },
    {
      "question": "青天白日",
      "answer": "せいてんはくじつ",
      "meaning": "being cleared of all the charge (brought against one), being found completely innocent"
    },
    {
      "question": "東御",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "映写幕",
      "answer": "えいしゃまく",
      "meaning": "(projection) screen"
    },
    {
      "question": "透磁率",
      "answer": "とうじりつ",
      "meaning": "magnetic permeability"
    },
    {
      "question": "鱶鰭",
      "answer": "ふかひれ",
      "meaning": "shark fin"
    },
    {
      "question": "已然形",
      "answer": "いぜんけい",
      "meaning": "realis form (of verbs and adjectives in classical Japanese), perfective form"
    },
    {
      "question": "胴切り",
      "answer": "どうぎり",
      "meaning": "cutting horizontally into the torso (with a sword)"
    },
    {
      "question": "選者",
      "answer": "せんじゃ",
      "meaning": "judge, selector"
    },
    {
      "question": "葉酸",
      "answer": "ようさん",
      "meaning": "folic acid"
    },
    {
      "question": "α化",
      "answer": "アルファか",
      "meaning": "pregelatinization"
    },
    {
      "question": "ガス体",
      "answer": "ガスたい",
      "meaning": "gas"
    },
    {
      "question": "本月",
      "answer": "ほんげつ",
      "meaning": "this month"
    },
    {
      "question": "中店",
      "answer": "ちゅうみせ",
      "meaning": "mid-sized store, middle-class brothel (in a red-light district)"
    },
    {
      "question": "管楽",
      "answer": "かんがく",
      "meaning": "wind music"
    },
    {
      "question": "急冷",
      "answer": "きゅうれい",
      "meaning": "rapid cooling"
    },
    {
      "question": "浙江",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "勝利投手",
      "answer": "しょうりとうしゅ",
      "meaning": "winning pitcher"
    },
    {
      "question": "人造絹糸",
      "answer": "じんぞうけんし",
      "meaning": "rayon"
    },
    {
      "question": "公約数",
      "answer": "こうやくすう",
      "meaning": "common divisor"
    },
    {
      "question": "黄水仙",
      "answer": "きずいせん,きすいせん",
      "meaning": "jonquil (Narcissus jonquilla)"
    },
    {
      "question": "何方様",
      "answer": "どちらさま",
      "meaning": "who"
    },
    {
      "question": "反意語",
      "answer": "はんいご",
      "meaning": "antonym"
    },
    {
      "question": "南蛮貿易",
      "answer": "なんばんぼうえき",
      "meaning": "Nanban trade, Japanese trade with Spain and Portugal (1543-1641)"
    },
    {
      "question": "心理検査",
      "answer": "しんりけんさ",
      "meaning": "psychological examination, mental test"
    },
    {
      "question": "心の柱",
      "answer": "しんのはしら",
      "meaning": "central pillar of a pagoda"
    },
    {
      "question": "前端",
      "answer": "ぜんたん",
      "meaning": "front end"
    },
    {
      "question": "敬畏",
      "answer": "けいい",
      "meaning": "awe, reverence, fear (e.g. of authority)"
    },
    {
      "question": "浪曼",
      "answer": "ろうまん",
      "meaning": "romance (e.g. Arthurian romances), heroic tale, (nigh) impossible dream, adventurous spirit, great u"
    },
    {
      "question": "満州族",
      "answer": "まんしゅうぞく",
      "meaning": "Manchu (people)"
    },
    {
      "question": "塞栓症",
      "answer": "そくせんしょう",
      "meaning": "embolism"
    },
    {
      "question": "核抑止",
      "answer": "かくよくし",
      "meaning": "nuclear deterrence"
    },
    {
      "question": "金頭",
      "answer": "かながしら",
      "meaning": "redwing searobin (species of gurnard, Lepidotrigla microptera)"
    },
    {
      "question": "一半",
      "answer": "いっぱん",
      "meaning": "half, part"
    },
    {
      "question": "納金",
      "answer": "のうきん",
      "meaning": "payment"
    },
    {
      "question": "末枯れる",
      "answer": "うらがれる,すがれる",
      "meaning": "to die (esp. foliage as winter approaches), to wither (esp. plants as winter draws near), to fade, t"
    },
    {
      "question": "狂牛病",
      "answer": "きょうぎゅうびょう",
      "meaning": "bovine spongiform encephalopathy, BSE, mad cow disease"
    },
    {
      "question": "堡塁",
      "answer": "ほうるい,ほるい",
      "meaning": "fort, stronghold"
    },
    {
      "question": "守り本尊",
      "answer": "まもりほんぞん",
      "meaning": "guardian deity"
    },
    {
      "question": "遠退ける",
      "answer": "とおのける",
      "meaning": "to keep (someone) at a distance"
    },
    {
      "question": "栄耀",
      "answer": "えいよう",
      "meaning": "luxury, splendour, splendor, prosperity"
    },
    {
      "question": "電気器具",
      "answer": "でんききぐ",
      "meaning": "electrical appliance"
    },
    {
      "question": "杏茸",
      "answer": "あんずたけ",
      "meaning": "chanterelle mushroom (Cantharellus cibarius)"
    },
    {
      "question": "一封",
      "answer": "いっぷう",
      "meaning": "sealed letter, sealed document, enclosure"
    },
    {
      "question": "鬼皮",
      "answer": "おにかわ",
      "meaning": "hard shell of a nut, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "白皮症",
      "answer": "はくひしょう",
      "meaning": "albinism"
    },
    {
      "question": "落字",
      "answer": "らくじ",
      "meaning": "omitted character, omitted letter"
    },
    {
      "question": "曲り道",
      "answer": "まがりみち",
      "meaning": "roundabout road, curving road"
    },
    {
      "question": "醋",
      "answer": "す",
      "meaning": "vinegar"
    },
    {
      "question": "鬼宿",
      "answer": "きしゅく",
      "meaning": "Chinese 'ghost' constellation (one of the 28 mansions), 'day of the ghost'"
    },
    {
      "question": "殺菌灯",
      "answer": "さっきんとう",
      "meaning": "germicidal lamp"
    },
    {
      "question": "逆引き",
      "answer": "ぎゃくびき",
      "meaning": "reverse lookup (e.g. dictionary, address resolution, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "山女魚",
      "answer": "やまめ",
      "meaning": "landlocked masu salmon (Oncorhynchus masou masou)"
    },
    {
      "question": "乾上がる",
      "answer": "ひあがる",
      "meaning": "to dry up, to parch, to ebb away"
    },
    {
      "question": "受動喫煙",
      "answer": "じゅどうきつえん",
      "meaning": "passive smoking, second-hand smoking"
    },
    {
      "question": "筮",
      "answer": "めどぎ,めどき",
      "meaning": "divination sticks"
    },
    {
      "question": "一層の事",
      "answer": "いっそのこと,いっそうのこと",
      "meaning": "rather, sooner, preferably"
    },
    {
      "question": "強腰",
      "answer": "つよごし",
      "meaning": "firm or tough stance"
    },
    {
      "question": "佐藤春夫",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "踏倒す",
      "answer": "ふみたおす",
      "meaning": "to trample down, to crush underfoot, to kick down, to avoid paying (e.g. a debt), to jump (a bill),"
    },
    {
      "question": "雌株",
      "answer": "めかぶ",
      "meaning": "female plant"
    },
    {
      "question": "朗詠",
      "answer": "ろうえい",
      "meaning": "recitation (of Japanese or Chinese poem)"
    },
    {
      "question": "貸し家",
      "answer": "かしや,かしいえ",
      "meaning": "house for rent"
    },
    {
      "question": "某氏",
      "answer": "ぼうし",
      "meaning": "a certain person, unnamed person, Mr. So-and-so, a certain someone who shall remain unnamed"
    },
    {
      "question": "水蜜",
      "answer": "すいみつ",
      "meaning": "white peach"
    },
    {
      "question": "蹴上がり",
      "answer": "けあがり",
      "meaning": "a kick, mounting a bar with a kick"
    },
    {
      "question": "死没",
      "answer": "しぼつ",
      "meaning": "death"
    },
    {
      "question": "池畔",
      "answer": "ちはん",
      "meaning": "near the pond, edge of a pond"
    },
    {
      "question": "八苦",
      "answer": "はっく",
      "meaning": "the eight kinds of suffering (birth, old age, disease, death, parting from loved ones, meeting disli"
    },
    {
      "question": "固定金利",
      "answer": "こていきんり",
      "meaning": "fixed interest rate"
    },
    {
      "question": "朱墨",
      "answer": "しゅずみ,しゅぼく",
      "meaning": "red-ink stick, red and black"
    },
    {
      "question": "味噌和え",
      "answer": "みそあえ",
      "meaning": "salad (or fish, etc.) dressed with miso"
    },
    {
      "question": "立論",
      "answer": "りつろん",
      "meaning": "argument(ation)"
    },
    {
      "question": "妻問婚",
      "answer": "つまどいこん",
      "meaning": "type of marriage where the man merely visits his wife without living with her, duolocal marriage"
    },
    {
      "question": "居留民",
      "answer": "きょりゅうみん",
      "meaning": "a resident"
    },
    {
      "question": "蔓性",
      "answer": "つるせい",
      "meaning": "vine-like, climbing, creeping"
    },
    {
      "question": "網猟",
      "answer": "あみりょう",
      "meaning": "hunting with a net"
    },
    {
      "question": "環境衛生",
      "answer": "かんきょうえいせい",
      "meaning": "environmental hygiene"
    },
    {
      "question": "日仏",
      "answer": "にちふつ",
      "meaning": "Japan and France"
    },
    {
      "question": "折れ口",
      "answer": "おれくち",
      "meaning": "a fold or crease"
    },
    {
      "question": "没義道",
      "answer": "もぎどう,ぼつぎどう",
      "meaning": "brutality, inhumanity"
    },
    {
      "question": "立法府",
      "answer": "りっぽうふ",
      "meaning": "assize, court, legislature"
    },
    {
      "question": "氏寺",
      "answer": "うじでら",
      "meaning": "shrine built to a guardian deity"
    },
    {
      "question": "壮語",
      "answer": "そうご",
      "meaning": "bragging, exaggeration"
    },
    {
      "question": "周航",
      "answer": "しゅうこう",
      "meaning": "circumnavigation, circle tour by ship"
    },
    {
      "question": "玉箒",
      "answer": "たまははき,たまばはき",
      "meaning": "broom (esp. one for sweeping a silkworm-raising room on the first Day of the Rat of the New Year), p"
    },
    {
      "question": "玉子焼",
      "answer": "たまごやき",
      "meaning": "rolled egg, rolled omelette (omelet), fried egg, frying pan for making rolled eggs"
    },
    {
      "question": "論敵",
      "answer": "ろんてき",
      "meaning": "opponent in a debate or argument"
    },
    {
      "question": "恩典",
      "answer": "おんてん",
      "meaning": "favour, favor, act of grace, special privilege"
    },
    {
      "question": "疾う",
      "answer": "とう",
      "meaning": "quickly, swiftly, a long time ago"
    },
    {
      "question": "邪魔っ気",
      "answer": "じゃまっけ",
      "meaning": "nuisance, obstructive (person), troublesome (person)"
    },
    {
      "question": "心付く",
      "answer": "こころづく",
      "meaning": "to perceive, to notice"
    },
    {
      "question": "強精剤",
      "answer": "きょうせいざい",
      "meaning": "aphrodisiac, tonic"
    },
    {
      "question": "立志",
      "answer": "りっし",
      "meaning": "fixing one's aim in life, deciding one's life goal"
    },
    {
      "question": "混合気",
      "answer": "こんごうき",
      "meaning": "air-fuel mixture"
    },
    {
      "question": "肉入れ",
      "answer": "にくいれ",
      "meaning": "ink-pad case"
    },
    {
      "question": "割下",
      "answer": "わりした",
      "meaning": "sukiyaki stock, stock mixed with soy sauce, mirin and sugar (used to flavor sukiyaki)"
    },
    {
      "question": "肺循環",
      "answer": "はいじゅんかん",
      "meaning": "pulmonary circulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "旅行家",
      "answer": "りょこうか",
      "meaning": "traveller, traveler"
    },
    {
      "question": "完工",
      "answer": "かんこう",
      "meaning": "completion of construction work"
    },
    {
      "question": "持ち扱う",
      "answer": "もちあつかう",
      "meaning": "to hold or operate with one's hands, to handle, to find difficult to manage"
    },
    {
      "question": "嬌羞",
      "answer": "きょうしゅう",
      "meaning": "charming and coy"
    },
    {
      "question": "窃取",
      "answer": "せっしゅ",
      "meaning": "theft, stealing, larceny"
    },
    {
      "question": "水争い",
      "answer": "みずあらそい",
      "meaning": "dispute over water rights, dispute over the distribution of water into paddies during the summer (in"
    },
    {
      "question": "新盆",
      "answer": "にいぼん,あらぼん,しんぼん",
      "meaning": "first Obon following someone's death"
    },
    {
      "question": "資性",
      "answer": "しせい",
      "meaning": "one's nature, one's disposition"
    },
    {
      "question": "記録文学",
      "answer": "きろくぶんがく",
      "meaning": "reportage, documentary"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り札",
      "answer": "とりふだ",
      "meaning": "card to pick up (in card games), card that is picked up by players instead of read (in karuta), card"
    },
    {
      "question": "倹しい",
      "answer": "つましい",
      "meaning": "thrifty, frugal, economical"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪平等",
      "answer": "あくびょうどう",
      "meaning": "misguided equality, misconceived equality, leaning over backwards to be impartial"
    },
    {
      "question": "灰白",
      "answer": "かいはく",
      "meaning": "gray, grey, griseous"
    },
    {
      "question": "餡パン",
      "answer": "あんパン",
      "meaning": "anpan, bread roll filled with red bean paste"
    },
    {
      "question": "草枕",
      "answer": "くさまくら",
      "meaning": "overnight stay when traveling (travelling), sleeping on grass in an open field"
    },
    {
      "question": "退園",
      "answer": "たいえん",
      "meaning": "leaving a park, garden, zoo, etc., leaving kindergarten (e.g. end of day, on completion, expulsion)"
    },
    {
      "question": "生酢",
      "answer": "きず",
      "meaning": "unadulterated vinegar, pure vinegar"
    },
    {
      "question": "機関人形",
      "answer": "からくりにんぎょう",
      "meaning": "mechanical doll, automaton, string puppet, marionette, person who follows orders blindly"
    },
    {
      "question": "体循環",
      "answer": "たいじゅんかん",
      "meaning": "systemic circulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "腫瘤",
      "answer": "しゅりゅう",
      "meaning": "lump, mass, tumor (tumour)"
    },
    {
      "question": "快作",
      "answer": "かいさく",
      "meaning": "splendid work, masterpiece"
    },
    {
      "question": "頑冥",
      "answer": "がんめい",
      "meaning": "bigoted, obstinate, stubborn, pigheaded"
    },
    {
      "question": "佳良",
      "answer": "かりょう",
      "meaning": "good, favourable, favorable, successful"
    },
    {
      "question": "白物",
      "answer": "しろもの",
      "meaning": "white goods, large household electrical appliances, salt, tofu, white sake"
    },
    {
      "question": "小企業",
      "answer": "しょうきぎょう",
      "meaning": "small business, small company"
    },
    {
      "question": "単糸",
      "answer": "たんし",
      "meaning": "single yarn (in spinning)"
    },
    {
      "question": "枝神",
      "answer": "えだがみ",
      "meaning": "enshrined deity of a subordinate shrine"
    },
    {
      "question": "片利共生",
      "answer": "へんりきょうせい",
      "meaning": "commensalism"
    },
    {
      "question": "権臣",
      "answer": "けんしん",
      "meaning": "influential vassal, powerful retainer, powerful courtier"
    },
    {
      "question": "御呪い",
      "answer": "おまじない",
      "meaning": "good luck charm, uttered when using magic, abracadabra, presto"
    },
    {
      "question": "語幹",
      "answer": "ごかん",
      "meaning": "stem, root of a word"
    },
    {
      "question": "直系尊属",
      "answer": "ちょっけいそんぞく",
      "meaning": "lineal ascendant"
    },
    {
      "question": "マレー語",
      "answer": "マレーご",
      "meaning": "Malay (language)"
    },
    {
      "question": "其の後",
      "answer": "そのあと,そのご,そののち",
      "meaning": "after that, afterwards, thereafter"
    },
    {
      "question": "峻嶺",
      "answer": "しゅんれい",
      "meaning": "steep peak, steep ridge, high rugged mountain"
    },
    {
      "question": "国守",
      "answer": "こくしゅ",
      "meaning": "daimyo"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝入り端",
      "answer": "ねいりばな",
      "meaning": "first stage of sleep"
    },
    {
      "question": "不離",
      "answer": "ふり",
      "meaning": "inseparability"
    },
    {
      "question": "北回帰線",
      "answer": "きたかいきせん",
      "meaning": "Tropic of Cancer"
    },
    {
      "question": "免ずる",
      "answer": "めんずる",
      "meaning": "to dismiss (from a position), to exempt, to excuse from, to forgive"
    },
    {
      "question": "鐶",
      "answer": "かん,たまき",
      "meaning": "ring, link, open spirals of heavy metal wire twisted into a kettle and used to lift it (tea ceremony"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪天",
      "answer": "あくてん",
      "meaning": "bad weather"
    },
    {
      "question": "不成",
      "answer": "ふなり",
      "meaning": "unpromoted (piece), limit orders that become market orders at the closing auction if not already exe"
    },
    {
      "question": "漢書",
      "answer": "かんしょ",
      "meaning": "Chinese book, book written in Chinese"
    },
    {
      "question": "捩子",
      "answer": "ねじ",
      "meaning": "screw, key (of a clock, watch, etc.), spring (of a clock, watch, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "韓ドラ",
      "answer": "かんドラ",
      "meaning": "Korean TV drama"
    },
    {
      "question": "渋団扇",
      "answer": "しぶうちわ",
      "meaning": "fan varnished with persimmon juice"
    },
    {
      "question": "飯櫃",
      "answer": "めしびつ,いいびつ",
      "meaning": "round, wooden container for cooked rice"
    },
    {
      "question": "中中",
      "answer": "なかなか",
      "meaning": "very, considerably, easily, readily, fairly, quite, highly, rather, by no means, not readily, middle"
    },
    {
      "question": "正念",
      "answer": "しょうねん",
      "meaning": "right mindfulness, true faith (in rebirth in the promised land)"
    },
    {
      "question": "馬跳び",
      "answer": "うまとび",
      "meaning": "(game of) leapfrog, leapfrogging"
    },
    {
      "question": "青身",
      "answer": "あおみ",
      "meaning": "flesh of a blueback fish"
    },
    {
      "question": "内衣",
      "answer": "ないい,ないえ",
      "meaning": "single-layer absorbent bathrobe (worn during or after a bath), monk's waist robe"
    },
    {
      "question": "海綿質",
      "answer": "かいめんしつ",
      "meaning": "spongin"
    },
    {
      "question": "皇室典範",
      "answer": "こうしつてんぱん",
      "meaning": "Imperial Household Law"
    },
    {
      "question": "浅茅",
      "answer": "あさじ,あさぢ",
      "meaning": "sparsely growing cogon grass, short cogon grass"
    },
    {
      "question": "煙硝",
      "answer": "えんしょう",
      "meaning": "gunpowder"
    },
    {
      "question": "使用価値",
      "answer": "しようかち",
      "meaning": "utility value"
    },
    {
      "question": "諷する",
      "answer": "ふうする",
      "meaning": "to hint, to insinuate, to satirize, to satirise"
    },
    {
      "question": "櫓投げ",
      "answer": "やぐらなげ",
      "meaning": "inner thigh throw"
    },
    {
      "question": "白票",
      "answer": "はくひょう",
      "meaning": "blank ballot, white ballot"
    },
    {
      "question": "僭上",
      "answer": "せんじょう,せんしょう",
      "meaning": "audacity, forwardness, effrontery, impertinence"
    },
    {
      "question": "歔欷",
      "answer": "きょき",
      "meaning": "sobbing, weeping"
    },
    {
      "question": "毛孔",
      "answer": "けあな,もうく",
      "meaning": "pore (of the skin)"
    },
    {
      "question": "転地療法",
      "answer": "てんちりょうほう",
      "meaning": "climatotherapy, change of air for convalescence"
    },
    {
      "question": "陶酔境",
      "answer": "とうすいきょう",
      "meaning": "intoxication (by liquor, music, etc.), rapture, fascination"
    },
    {
      "question": "動物相",
      "answer": "どうぶつそう",
      "meaning": "fauna"
    },
    {
      "question": "管外",
      "answer": "かんがい",
      "meaning": "outside the control or jurisdiction (of), extra-"
    },
    {
      "question": "暗々裏",
      "answer": "あんあんり",
      "meaning": "secretly, covertly, tacitly"
    },
    {
      "question": "弾力的",
      "answer": "だんりょくてき",
      "meaning": "elastic, flexible"
    },
    {
      "question": "仰望",
      "answer": "ぎょうぼう",
      "meaning": "look to (for help), look up to, reverence"
    },
    {
      "question": "了簡",
      "answer": "りょうけん",
      "meaning": "idea, thought, intention, design, view, inclination, decision, motive, discretion, forgiveness, pard"
    },
    {
      "question": "横断的",
      "answer": "おうだんてき",
      "meaning": "cross-sectional, lateral, transverse, transversal, cross-cutting"
    },
    {
      "question": "固形食",
      "answer": "こけいしょく",
      "meaning": "solid food, solids"
    },
    {
      "question": "向拝",
      "answer": "ごはい,こうはい",
      "meaning": "pent roof built atop the stairs of a shrine or temple"
    },
    {
      "question": "大和言葉",
      "answer": "やまとことば",
      "meaning": "word of Japanese origin, native Japanese word"
    },
    {
      "question": "神品",
      "answer": "しんぴん",
      "meaning": "inspired work, masterpiece"
    },
    {
      "question": "薩摩芋",
      "answer": "さつまいも",
      "meaning": "sweet potato (Ipomoea batatas)"
    },
    {
      "question": "出猟",
      "answer": "しゅつりょう",
      "meaning": "going hunting"
    },
    {
      "question": "琉球諸島",
      "answer": "りゅうきゅうしょとう",
      "meaning": "Ryukyu Islands, southern chain of the Nansei Islands comprising Okinawa Prefecture"
    },
    {
      "question": "義臣",
      "answer": "ぎしん",
      "meaning": "loyal retainer"
    },
    {
      "question": "専修学校",
      "answer": "せんしゅうがっこう",
      "meaning": "(special) vocational school"
    },
    {
      "question": "胴巻き",
      "answer": "どうまき",
      "meaning": "bellyband, money belt"
    },
    {
      "question": "人工言語",
      "answer": "じんこうげんご",
      "meaning": "artificial language (e.g. Esperanto), constructed language, conlang, language for defining structure"
    },
    {
      "question": "離合集散",
      "answer": "りごうしゅうさん",
      "meaning": "alliance and rupture"
    },
    {
      "question": "破算",
      "answer": "はさん",
      "meaning": "starting afresh, going back to square one, abandoning (e.g. a plan), calling off, clearing an abacus"
    },
    {
      "question": "貰い事故",
      "answer": "もらいじこ",
      "meaning": "traffic accident for which the other side is at fault"
    },
    {
      "question": "亜砒酸",
      "answer": "あひさん",
      "meaning": "arsenious acid, arsenous acid (H3AsO3), arsenic trioxide, white arsenic (As2O3)"
    },
    {
      "question": "章立て",
      "answer": "しょうだて",
      "meaning": "arrangement of chapters, dividing into chapters"
    },
    {
      "question": "参会",
      "answer": "さんかい",
      "meaning": "attendance (at a meeting)"
    },
    {
      "question": "午餐会",
      "answer": "ごさんかい",
      "meaning": "luncheon party"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍人恩給",
      "answer": "ぐんじんおんきゅう",
      "meaning": "military pension"
    },
    {
      "question": "妊産婦",
      "answer": "にんさんぷ",
      "meaning": "expectant and nursing mothers"
    },
    {
      "question": "聞き書き",
      "answer": "ききがき",
      "meaning": "writing down what one hears, account of what one hears"
    },
    {
      "question": "地変",
      "answer": "ちへん",
      "meaning": "natural calamity"
    },
    {
      "question": "横流れ",
      "answer": "よこながれ",
      "meaning": "flowing into the black market"
    },
    {
      "question": "中垣",
      "answer": "なかがき",
      "meaning": "middle fence"
    },
    {
      "question": "偽造罪",
      "answer": "ぎぞうざい",
      "meaning": "forgery"
    },
    {
      "question": "緯線",
      "answer": "いせん",
      "meaning": "parallel"
    },
    {
      "question": "上敷",
      "answer": "うわしき,うわじき",
      "meaning": "bordered matting, rug, carpet, saddlecloth, harness"
    },
    {
      "question": "内祝い",
      "answer": "うちいわい",
      "meaning": "gift for close relatives or friends (given on the occasion of a family celebration), family celebrat"
    },
    {
      "question": "立羽",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "県営",
      "answer": "けんえい",
      "meaning": "(under) prefectural management"
    },
    {
      "question": "御旨",
      "answer": "ぎょし,みむね",
      "meaning": "thoughts, feelings, God's will (in Christianity)"
    },
    {
      "question": "画期",
      "answer": "かっき",
      "meaning": "transition from one epoch to another, change of era"
    },
    {
      "question": "応用数学",
      "answer": "おうようすうがく",
      "meaning": "applied mathematics"
    },
    {
      "question": "逸失利益",
      "answer": "いっしつりえき",
      "meaning": "lost profit"
    },
    {
      "question": "煽情",
      "answer": "せんじょう",
      "meaning": "suggestiveness, sensationalism, stirring up strong emotions"
    },
    {
      "question": "楊子",
      "answer": "ようじ",
      "meaning": "toothpick, skewer for eating moist wagashi (steel, bamboo, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "分かち",
      "answer": "わかち",
      "meaning": "distinction, differentiation, discrimination"
    },
    {
      "question": "合歓",
      "answer": "ごうかん,ねむ",
      "meaning": "enjoying pleasure together, silk tree (Albizia julibrissin)"
    },
    {
      "question": "断り書き",
      "answer": "ことわりがき",
      "meaning": "explanatory note"
    },
    {
      "question": "時評",
      "answer": "じひょう",
      "meaning": "commentary on current events"
    },
    {
      "question": "丸太船",
      "answer": "まるたぶね",
      "meaning": "wooden transport ship used on Lake Biwa, vessel made from logs, e.g. large dugout canoe"
    },
    {
      "question": "大詔",
      "answer": "たいしょう",
      "meaning": "imperial rescript"
    },
    {
      "question": "僧帽弁",
      "answer": "そうぼうべん",
      "meaning": "mitral valve, bicuspid valve"
    },
    {
      "question": "中間期",
      "answer": "ちゅうかんき",
      "meaning": "interphase, interkinesis, midcycle"
    },
    {
      "question": "暗ます",
      "answer": "くらます",
      "meaning": "to conceal (oneself), to hide, to abscond, to deceive, to dissemble, to fool"
    },
    {
      "question": "即ギレ",
      "answer": "そくギレ",
      "meaning": "instantly exploding into a rage, sudden outburst"
    },
    {
      "question": "火山雷",
      "answer": "かざんらい",
      "meaning": "volcanic thunderstorm"
    },
    {
      "question": "胸に一物",
      "answer": "むねにいちもつ",
      "meaning": "machination, secret plan, plot, trick up one's sleeve"
    },
    {
      "question": "吃逆",
      "answer": "しゃっくり",
      "meaning": "hiccup, hiccough"
    },
    {
      "question": "神信心",
      "answer": "かみしんじん",
      "meaning": "belief in god"
    },
    {
      "question": "紙巻",
      "answer": "かみまき",
      "meaning": "something rolled in paper, paper roll, cigarette"
    },
    {
      "question": "青嶺",
      "answer": "あおね,あおねろ",
      "meaning": "lush mountain, green mountain"
    },
    {
      "question": "前意識",
      "answer": "ぜんいしき",
      "meaning": "preconscious (psychoanalysis)"
    },
    {
      "question": "放出音",
      "answer": "ほうしゅつおん",
      "meaning": "ejective consonant"
    },
    {
      "question": "貸し本",
      "answer": "かしほん",
      "meaning": "books for loan"
    },
    {
      "question": "寸地",
      "answer": "すんち",
      "meaning": "an inch of ground"
    },
    {
      "question": "散光",
      "answer": "さんこう",
      "meaning": "scattered light"
    },
    {
      "question": "小宴",
      "answer": "しょうえん",
      "meaning": "small (dinner) party"
    },
    {
      "question": "狸囃子",
      "answer": "たぬきばやし",
      "meaning": "tanuki drumming on their stomachs"
    },
    {
      "question": "行き悩む",
      "answer": "ゆきなやむ,いきなやむ",
      "meaning": "to reach an impasse or deadlock"
    },
    {
      "question": "生生流転",
      "answer": "せいせいるてん,しょうじょうるてん",
      "meaning": "all things being in flux through the endless circle of birth, death, and rebirth, the circle of tran"
    },
    {
      "question": "認識論",
      "answer": "にんしきろん",
      "meaning": "epistemology"
    },
    {
      "question": "土偏",
      "answer": "つちへん",
      "meaning": "kanji 'earth' radical at left (radical 32)"
    },
    {
      "question": "邪説",
      "answer": "じゃせつ",
      "meaning": "heretical doctrine"
    },
    {
      "question": "叢生",
      "answer": "そうせい",
      "meaning": "dense growth, healthy growth"
    },
    {
      "question": "池水",
      "answer": "ちすい",
      "meaning": "pond water, pond"
    },
    {
      "question": "国自慢",
      "answer": "くにじまん",
      "meaning": "national or local pride, the pride of one's native place"
    },
    {
      "question": "諤々",
      "answer": "がくがく",
      "meaning": "outspoken"
    },
    {
      "question": "顕性",
      "answer": "けんせい",
      "meaning": "dominance"
    },
    {
      "question": "其所",
      "answer": "そこ",
      "meaning": "there (place relatively near listener), there (place just mentioned), that place, then (of some inci"
    },
    {
      "question": "馬喰",
      "answer": "ばくろう",
      "meaning": "cattle or horse trader, good judge of horses or cattle"
    },
    {
      "question": "南海道",
      "answer": "なんかいどう",
      "meaning": "Nankaidō (alt. name for the Shikoku region)"
    },
    {
      "question": "賃借権",
      "answer": "ちんしゃくけん",
      "meaning": "right to lease"
    },
    {
      "question": "和方",
      "answer": "わほう",
      "meaning": "traditional Japanese medicine"
    },
    {
      "question": "三元",
      "answer": "さんげん",
      "meaning": "15th day of the 1st, 7th and 10th lunar months, heaven, earth and man, January 1, New Year's Day, te"
    },
    {
      "question": "増床",
      "answer": "ぞうしょう",
      "meaning": "expansion (in space) of a sales area, increase in the number of beds (in a hospital, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "朝潮",
      "answer": "あさしお",
      "meaning": "morning tide"
    },
    {
      "question": "年払い",
      "answer": "ねんばらい",
      "meaning": "yearly payment, annual payment"
    },
    {
      "question": "微量元素",
      "answer": "びりょうげんそ",
      "meaning": "trace element, micronutrient"
    },
    {
      "question": "再話",
      "answer": "さいわ",
      "meaning": "retelling (tale, legend)"
    },
    {
      "question": "奸知",
      "answer": "かんち",
      "meaning": "cunning, craft, wiles"
    },
    {
      "question": "南庭",
      "answer": "なんてい",
      "meaning": "grounds south of a building, southern garden, garden south of the Hall for State Ceremonies (in the"
    },
    {
      "question": "根太",
      "answer": "ねぶと,ねだ",
      "meaning": "(skin) boil, joist"
    },
    {
      "question": "金属結合",
      "answer": "きんぞくけつごう",
      "meaning": "metallic bond"
    },
    {
      "question": "丸字",
      "answer": "まるじ",
      "meaning": "rounded handwriting"
    },
    {
      "question": "絡げ",
      "answer": "からげ",
      "meaning": "bundle, sheaf"
    },
    {
      "question": "川向かい",
      "answer": "かわむかい",
      "meaning": "across a river"
    },
    {
      "question": "墨流し",
      "answer": "すみながし",
      "meaning": "marbling print, paper marbling"
    },
    {
      "question": "代赭",
      "answer": "たいしゃ",
      "meaning": "red ocher (ochre)"
    },
    {
      "question": "特快",
      "answer": "とっかい",
      "meaning": "special fast (local) train"
    },
    {
      "question": "液剤",
      "answer": "えきざい",
      "meaning": "liquid medicine"
    },
    {
      "question": "物質量",
      "answer": "ぶっしつりょう",
      "meaning": "amount of substance"
    },
    {
      "question": "日覆い",
      "answer": "ひおおい,ひおい",
      "meaning": "sunshade, sunscreen, window shade, blinds"
    },
    {
      "question": "菜飯",
      "answer": "なめし",
      "meaning": "rice boiled with greens"
    },
    {
      "question": "塩素酸",
      "answer": "えんそさん",
      "meaning": "chloric acid"
    },
    {
      "question": "多読",
      "answer": "たどく",
      "meaning": "wide (extensive) reading"
    },
    {
      "question": "稽首",
      "answer": "けいしゅ",
      "meaning": "bowing to the floor"
    },
    {
      "question": "通常選挙",
      "answer": "つうじょうせんきょ",
      "meaning": "regular election (triennial election of half of the House of Councillors)"
    },
    {
      "question": "磨崖仏",
      "answer": "まがいぶつ",
      "meaning": "Buddha figure carved on a rock face"
    },
    {
      "question": "顋",
      "answer": "あご,えら",
      "meaning": "jaw, chin, barb (of a fishhook), gills, branchia, angle of the mandible, gonial angle"
    },
    {
      "question": "療育",
      "answer": "りょういく",
      "meaning": "rehabilitation (e.g. of disabled children)"
    },
    {
      "question": "卒後",
      "answer": "そつご",
      "meaning": "after graduation"
    },
    {
      "question": "鳩派",
      "answer": "はとは",
      "meaning": "dove, moderate, soft-liner"
    },
    {
      "question": "格率",
      "answer": "かくりつ",
      "meaning": "maxim, personal standard"
    },
    {
      "question": "片影",
      "answer": "へんえい",
      "meaning": "speck, glimpse"
    },
    {
      "question": "口蹄疫",
      "answer": "こうていえき",
      "meaning": "foot-and-mouth disease, hoof-and-mouth disease"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪僧",
      "answer": "あくそう",
      "meaning": "dissolute priest, depraved monk, ferocious warrior monk"
    },
    {
      "question": "廃藩",
      "answer": "はいはん",
      "meaning": "abolition of the han system"
    },
    {
      "question": "公証役場",
      "answer": "こうしょうやくば",
      "meaning": "notary public's office"
    },
    {
      "question": "増枠",
      "answer": "ぞうわく",
      "meaning": "quota increase, allowance increase, limit increase, increase in one's share"
    },
    {
      "question": "乱伐",
      "answer": "らんばつ",
      "meaning": "reckless deforestation, overcutting of forests"
    },
    {
      "question": "白し",
      "answer": "びゃくし",
      "meaning": "bai zhi (Chinese name for angelica species Angelica dahurica), traditional Chinese cure made from th"
    },
    {
      "question": "密密",
      "answer": "みつみつ",
      "meaning": "secretly, privately"
    },
    {
      "question": "空身",
      "answer": "からみ",
      "meaning": "traveling alone and with little luggage (travelling)"
    },
    {
      "question": "義捐金",
      "answer": "ぎえんきん",
      "meaning": "donation money (esp. disaster relief or charity), contribution"
    },
    {
      "question": "虎斑",
      "answer": "とらふ",
      "meaning": "tiger stripes"
    },
    {
      "question": "段だら",
      "answer": "だんだら",
      "meaning": "(with) broad horizontal stripes of different colors, unevenness"
    },
    {
      "question": "保護主義",
      "answer": "ほごしゅぎ",
      "meaning": "protectionism"
    },
    {
      "question": "抄訳",
      "answer": "しょうやく",
      "meaning": "abridged translation"
    },
    {
      "question": "珪藻土",
      "answer": "けいそうど",
      "meaning": "diatomaceous earth, diatomite, siliceous marl, kieselguhr"
    },
    {
      "question": "渡島",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "青蛙",
      "answer": "あおがえる",
      "meaning": "green (tree) frog"
    },
    {
      "question": "停年",
      "answer": "ていねん",
      "meaning": "retirement age, years of service in a military rank before eligibility for promotion"
    },
    {
      "question": "風信子",
      "answer": "ふうしんし",
      "meaning": "hyacinth (Hyacinthus orientalis)"
    },
    {
      "question": "虫籠窓",
      "answer": "むしこまど",
      "meaning": "window with an ultra-fine lattice (often on upper floors of traditional buildings, e.g. Kyoto townho"
    },
    {
      "question": "老死",
      "answer": "ろうし",
      "meaning": "die of old age"
    },
    {
      "question": "立冬",
      "answer": "りっとう",
      "meaning": "first day of winter (approx. November 8)"
    },
    {
      "question": "進航",
      "answer": "しんこう",
      "meaning": "sailing on"
    },
    {
      "question": "野育ち",
      "answer": "のそだち",
      "meaning": "untutored, wild"
    },
    {
      "question": "着る毛布",
      "answer": "きるもうふ",
      "meaning": "wearable blanket"
    },
    {
      "question": "装飾音",
      "answer": "そうしょくおん",
      "meaning": "grace note"
    },
    {
      "question": "異国趣味",
      "answer": "いこくしゅみ",
      "meaning": "taste for the exotic, infatuation with a foreign way of life, exoticism"
    },
    {
      "question": "下膊",
      "answer": "かはく",
      "meaning": "forearm"
    },
    {
      "question": "引き船",
      "answer": "ひきふね",
      "meaning": "tugboat, tug, towboat, tugging (a boat), towing, towage"
    },
    {
      "question": "外腿",
      "answer": "そともも",
      "meaning": "outer thigh"
    },
    {
      "question": "断乳",
      "answer": "だんにゅう",
      "meaning": "weaning"
    },
    {
      "question": "鬼歯",
      "answer": "おにば",
      "meaning": "protruding tooth (like a fang)"
    },
    {
      "question": "蝗虫",
      "answer": "ばった,こうちゅう",
      "meaning": "grasshopper, locust (of superfamily Acridoidea), rice grasshopper (of genus Oxya)"
    },
    {
      "question": "主日",
      "answer": "しゅじつ",
      "meaning": "the Sabbath, the Lord's Day"
    },
    {
      "question": "忙中",
      "answer": "ぼうちゅう",
      "meaning": "(in the midst of) busyness"
    },
    {
      "question": "軽躁",
      "answer": "けいそう",
      "meaning": "thoughtless, flighty"
    },
    {
      "question": "木鉢",
      "answer": "きばち",
      "meaning": "wooden bowl"
    },
    {
      "question": "真田紐",
      "answer": "さなだひも",
      "meaning": "braid"
    },
    {
      "question": "向性",
      "answer": "こうせい",
      "meaning": "tropism"
    },
    {
      "question": "期間工",
      "answer": "きかんこう",
      "meaning": "factory worker with a fixed term contract of employment"
    },
    {
      "question": "組替え",
      "answer": "くみかえ",
      "meaning": "rearrangement (of classes), recomposition, recombination, reclassification"
    },
    {
      "question": "感奮",
      "answer": "かんぷん",
      "meaning": "stirred up, inspired, moved to action"
    },
    {
      "question": "活け締め",
      "answer": "いけじめ,いけしめ",
      "meaning": "draining blood from a live fish (from above the gills and at the base of the tail) to keep it fresh,"
    },
    {
      "question": "即完",
      "answer": "そっかん",
      "meaning": "same-day sellout, selling out on the first day (of sale)"
    },
    {
      "question": "真蛸",
      "answer": "まだこ",
      "meaning": "common octopus (Octopus vulgaris)"
    },
    {
      "question": "食べ出",
      "answer": "たべで",
      "meaning": "substantiality (of a meal), fillingness, solidity"
    },
    {
      "question": "盛り蕎麦",
      "answer": "もりそば",
      "meaning": "chilled soba served on a dish (often on a wicker basket or in a shallow steaming basket) with dippin"
    },
    {
      "question": "大谷石",
      "answer": "おおやいし",
      "meaning": "Oya tuff stone"
    },
    {
      "question": "婉美",
      "answer": "えんび",
      "meaning": "beauty, charm"
    },
    {
      "question": "宗徒",
      "answer": "しゅうと",
      "meaning": "believer, follower"
    },
    {
      "question": "非戦論",
      "answer": "ひせんろん",
      "meaning": "pacifism"
    },
    {
      "question": "簗",
      "answer": "やな",
      "meaning": "(fish) weir, fish trap"
    },
    {
      "question": "堅木",
      "answer": "かたぎ",
      "meaning": "hardwood"
    },
    {
      "question": "俎上の魚",
      "answer": "そじょうのうお",
      "meaning": "being in a helpless situation, (like a) fish on a chopping board"
    },
    {
      "question": "梁木",
      "answer": "りょうぼく",
      "meaning": "beam"
    },
    {
      "question": "剤形",
      "answer": "ざいけい",
      "meaning": "dosage form"
    },
    {
      "question": "審判委員",
      "answer": "しんぱんいいん",
      "meaning": "five ringside judges"
    },
    {
      "question": "脈管",
      "answer": "みゃっかん,みゃくかん",
      "meaning": "blood vessel, duct"
    },
    {
      "question": "大蚊",
      "answer": "ががんぼ,かがんぼ",
      "meaning": "crane fly, daddy longlegs (insect of family Tipulidae)"
    },
    {
      "question": "大洋州",
      "answer": "たいようしゅう",
      "meaning": "Oceania"
    },
    {
      "question": "愚図つく",
      "answer": "ぐずつく",
      "meaning": "to dawdle, to waste time doing nothing in particular, to fret, to sulk, to complain, to rain on and"
    },
    {
      "question": "年給",
      "answer": "ねんきゅう",
      "meaning": "annual salary"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪消",
      "answer": "ゆきげ",
      "meaning": "snow melting, water from melting snow"
    },
    {
      "question": "尊王",
      "answer": "そんのう",
      "meaning": "reverence for the emperor, advocate of imperial rule"
    },
    {
      "question": "宅建",
      "answer": "たっけん",
      "meaning": "registered real-estate broker"
    },
    {
      "question": "空屋敷",
      "answer": "あきやしき",
      "meaning": "empty residence, empty estate, empty lot"
    },
    {
      "question": "突出し",
      "answer": "つきだし",
      "meaning": "protrusion, projection, hors d'oeuvre, appetizer, snack (served with a drink), frontal thrust out (w"
    },
    {
      "question": "貴紳",
      "answer": "きしん",
      "meaning": "noble, men of rank, notables"
    },
    {
      "question": "目抜",
      "answer": "めぬけ",
      "meaning": "any large, red, deep-water scorpionfish with big eyes, Matsubara's red rockfish (Sebastes matsubarae"
    },
    {
      "question": "仏文",
      "answer": "ふつぶん",
      "meaning": "French, French writing, French literature"
    },
    {
      "question": "狸顔",
      "answer": "たぬきがお",
      "meaning": "facial expression of feigned ignorance"
    },
    {
      "question": "歩引き",
      "answer": "ぶびき",
      "meaning": "discount"
    },
    {
      "question": "反例",
      "answer": "はんれい",
      "meaning": "counterexample, counter-example"
    },
    {
      "question": "生活環",
      "answer": "せいかつかん",
      "meaning": "life cycle"
    },
    {
      "question": "離散的",
      "answer": "りさんてき",
      "meaning": "discrete, separate"
    },
    {
      "question": "自損",
      "answer": "じそん",
      "meaning": "self-inflicted injury, loss, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "気候帯",
      "answer": "きこうたい",
      "meaning": "climatic zone"
    },
    {
      "question": "建て売り",
      "answer": "たてうり",
      "meaning": "constructing and selling a ready-built house"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤誠",
      "answer": "せきせい",
      "meaning": "sincerity, true heart, devotion"
    },
    {
      "question": "粗汁",
      "answer": "あらじる",
      "meaning": "soup made from boiling leftover fish scraps, fishhead soup"
    },
    {
      "question": "女腹",
      "answer": "おんなばら",
      "meaning": "woman who has produced only daughters"
    },
    {
      "question": "諫死",
      "answer": "かんし",
      "meaning": "committing suicide (to remonstrate or dissuade one's lord), preparing to die in an effort to dissuad"
    },
    {
      "question": "公明",
      "answer": "こうめい",
      "meaning": "fairness, openness, impartiality, Komeito (Japanese political party)"
    },
    {
      "question": "席割",
      "answer": "せきわり",
      "meaning": "seat allocation, fee paid to an performer (at a vaudeville hall), appearance fee"
    },
    {
      "question": "拡大家族",
      "answer": "かくだいかぞく",
      "meaning": "extended family"
    },
    {
      "question": "元払い",
      "answer": "もとばらい",
      "meaning": "prepayment"
    },
    {
      "question": "偉勲",
      "answer": "いくん",
      "meaning": "great achievement"
    },
    {
      "question": "同派",
      "answer": "どうは",
      "meaning": "same sect, same faction"
    },
    {
      "question": "言行一致",
      "answer": "げんこういっち",
      "meaning": "acting up to one's words, consistency between speech and action"
    },
    {
      "question": "祝儀袋",
      "answer": "しゅうぎぶくろ",
      "meaning": "special envelope for monetary gifts"
    },
    {
      "question": "欲心",
      "answer": "よくしん",
      "meaning": "greed"
    },
    {
      "question": "専管",
      "answer": "せんかん",
      "meaning": "exclusive jurisdiction"
    },
    {
      "question": "一昨晩",
      "answer": "いっさくばん",
      "meaning": "night before last"
    },
    {
      "question": "撮む",
      "answer": "つまむ",
      "meaning": "to pinch, to hold (between one's fingers), to pick up (with chopsticks, tweezers, etc.), to pick up"
    },
    {
      "question": "唯物的",
      "answer": "ゆいぶつてき",
      "meaning": "materialistic"
    },
    {
      "question": "成案",
      "answer": "せいあん",
      "meaning": "definite plan"
    },
    {
      "question": "池泉",
      "answer": "ちせん",
      "meaning": "pond in a garden"
    },
    {
      "question": "上昇線",
      "answer": "じょうしょうせん",
      "meaning": "rising curve"
    },
    {
      "question": "神色",
      "answer": "しんしょく",
      "meaning": "mind and composure"
    },
    {
      "question": "限界状況",
      "answer": "げんかいじょうきょう",
      "meaning": "critical situation"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤手",
      "answer": "せきしゅ",
      "meaning": "bare handed"
    },
    {
      "question": "改良種",
      "answer": "かいりょうしゅ",
      "meaning": "improved strain, improved breed"
    },
    {
      "question": "活版本",
      "answer": "かっぱんぼん",
      "meaning": "printed book"
    },
    {
      "question": "高脂血症",
      "answer": "こうしけっしょう",
      "meaning": "hyperlipidaemia (hyperlipidemia, hyperlipemia), excessive fat in blood"
    },
    {
      "question": "氷河湖",
      "answer": "ひょうがこ",
      "meaning": "glacial lake"
    },
    {
      "question": "宵祭り",
      "answer": "よいまつり",
      "meaning": "small festival held the night before the main festival, eve of a festival"
    },
    {
      "question": "行政処分",
      "answer": "ぎょうせいしょぶん",
      "meaning": "administrative measures (disposition)"
    },
    {
      "question": "分地",
      "answer": "ぶんち",
      "meaning": "parceling out an estate"
    },
    {
      "question": "九谷焼",
      "answer": "くたにやき",
      "meaning": "Kutani ware, style of Japanese porcelain"
    },
    {
      "question": "鋏角類",
      "answer": "きょうかくるい",
      "meaning": "Chelicerata, chelicerates"
    },
    {
      "question": "旧宅",
      "answer": "きゅうたく",
      "meaning": "former residence"
    },
    {
      "question": "祐筆",
      "answer": "ゆうひつ",
      "meaning": "private secretary, amanuensis"
    },
    {
      "question": "二重露出",
      "answer": "にじゅうろしゅつ",
      "meaning": "double exposure"
    },
    {
      "question": "餅代",
      "answer": "もちだい",
      "meaning": "money to see one over the New Year period"
    },
    {
      "question": "雲珠",
      "answer": "うず",
      "meaning": "crupper ornament"
    },
    {
      "question": "尊皇",
      "answer": "そんのう",
      "meaning": "reverence for the emperor, advocate of imperial rule"
    },
    {
      "question": "熊蜂",
      "answer": "くまばち",
      "meaning": "Japanese carpenter bee (Xylocopa appendiculata circumvolans), wasp, hornet, yellow jacket"
    },
    {
      "question": "無始",
      "answer": "むし",
      "meaning": "beginninglessness, distant past"
    },
    {
      "question": "露宿",
      "answer": "ろしゅく",
      "meaning": "sleeping outdoors"
    },
    {
      "question": "高級言語",
      "answer": "こうきゅうげんご",
      "meaning": "high-level language"
    },
    {
      "question": "震音",
      "answer": "しんおん",
      "meaning": "tremolo, trill, vibratory sound, warble tone"
    },
    {
      "question": "柚餅子",
      "answer": "ゆべし",
      "meaning": "sweet yuzu-flavoured steamed dumpling"
    },
    {
      "question": "独禁法",
      "answer": "どっきんほう",
      "meaning": "antitrust law, Antitrust Act"
    },
    {
      "question": "平平凡凡",
      "answer": "へいへいぼんぼん",
      "meaning": "very ordinary, mediocre, all-too-common, quite commonplace"
    },
    {
      "question": "日新",
      "answer": "にっしん,じっしん",
      "meaning": "day-by-day renewal, rapid progress"
    },
    {
      "question": "異化",
      "answer": "いか",
      "meaning": "dissimilation, catabolism, dissimilation (phonology), defamiliarization (artistic technique), ostran"
    },
    {
      "question": "三柱鳥居",
      "answer": "みつばしらとりい,みつはしらとりい",
      "meaning": "triangular three-pillar torii"
    },
    {
      "question": "非職",
      "answer": "ひしょく",
      "meaning": "not employed, holding a post but having no duties"
    },
    {
      "question": "水晶の夜",
      "answer": "すいしょうのよる",
      "meaning": "Kristallnacht (night of concerted violence against Jews in Germany and Austria from November 9-10, 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "中肉",
      "answer": "ちゅうにく",
      "meaning": "medium build, meat of medium quality"
    },
    {
      "question": "緑虫",
      "answer": "みどりむし",
      "meaning": "euglena (freshwater flagellate)"
    },
    {
      "question": "多言語化",
      "answer": "たげんごか",
      "meaning": "multilingualization, multilingualisation, localization, localisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "竦然",
      "answer": "しょうぜん",
      "meaning": "terrified, horrified"
    },
    {
      "question": "塁審",
      "answer": "るいしん",
      "meaning": "base umpire"
    },
    {
      "question": "聞き物",
      "answer": "ききもの",
      "meaning": "worth listening to"
    },
    {
      "question": "河原乞食",
      "answer": "かわらこじき",
      "meaning": "actors, players, riverbank beggars"
    },
    {
      "question": "擬足",
      "answer": "ぎそく",
      "meaning": "pseudopodium, pseudopod (temporary protrusion of an ameboid cell)"
    },
    {
      "question": "人事考課",
      "answer": "じんじこうか",
      "meaning": "merit (ability, efficiency) rating, employee performance evaluation"
    },
    {
      "question": "墨痕淋漓",
      "answer": "ぼっこんりんり",
      "meaning": "dripping ink marks, a work of calligraphy being written in bold and vivid strokes"
    },
    {
      "question": "内発的",
      "answer": "ないはつてき",
      "meaning": "spontaneous, arising from within, voluntary, intristic (psychology)"
    },
    {
      "question": "近地点",
      "answer": "きんちてん",
      "meaning": "perigee"
    },
    {
      "question": "眉月",
      "answer": "まゆづき",
      "meaning": "crescent moon"
    },
    {
      "question": "天蚕",
      "answer": "やままゆ,てんさん",
      "meaning": "Japanese oak silkmoth (Antheraea yamamai)"
    },
    {
      "question": "炳",
      "answer": "へい",
      "meaning": "bright, shining, clear, evident"
    },
    {
      "question": "収取",
      "answer": "しゅうしゅ",
      "meaning": "collection, acquisition"
    },
    {
      "question": "煤塵",
      "answer": "ばいじん",
      "meaning": "dust and soot, particulate matter"
    },
    {
      "question": "郁子",
      "answer": "むべ,うべ",
      "meaning": "Japanese staunton-vine (Stauntonia hexaphylla)"
    },
    {
      "question": "面容",
      "answer": "めんよう",
      "meaning": "looks, features"
    },
    {
      "question": "奉献",
      "answer": "ほうけん",
      "meaning": "dedication, presentation, consecration, offer (to a shrine)"
    },
    {
      "question": "達見",
      "answer": "たっけん",
      "meaning": "farsightedness, insight"
    },
    {
      "question": "国際通貨",
      "answer": "こくさいつうか",
      "meaning": "international currency"
    },
    {
      "question": "床脇",
      "answer": "とこわき",
      "meaning": "section of a room next to the alcove (where shelves are often placed)"
    },
    {
      "question": "全射",
      "answer": "ぜんしゃ",
      "meaning": "surjection, onto mapping, epimorphism"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤蜻蛉",
      "answer": "あかとんぼ",
      "meaning": "(small) red dragonfly, darter (dragonfly of genus Sympetrum, esp. the autumn darter, Sympetrum frequ"
    },
    {
      "question": "日雇",
      "answer": "ひやとい",
      "meaning": "daily employment, hiring by the day, day laborer, day labourer"
    },
    {
      "question": "哀叫",
      "answer": "あいきょう",
      "meaning": "crying loudly with sadness"
    },
    {
      "question": "仏顔",
      "answer": "ほとけがお",
      "meaning": "gentle face"
    },
    {
      "question": "飴湯",
      "answer": "あめゆ",
      "meaning": "thick malt syrup poured into boiling water and sprinkled with cinnamon (used as a refreshing summer"
    },
    {
      "question": "陸援隊",
      "answer": "りくえんたい",
      "meaning": "Rikuentai, anti-shogunate army formed in Kyoto in 1867 by Nakaoka Shintaro"
    },
    {
      "question": "豊作貧乏",
      "answer": "ほうさくびんぼう",
      "meaning": "impoverishment of farmers because of a bumper harvest, decline in farmers' income caused by the shar"
    },
    {
      "question": "具備",
      "answer": "ぐび",
      "meaning": "possessing (what is required), having, fulfilling (conditions), satisfying (requisites), being endow"
    },
    {
      "question": "漸う",
      "answer": "ようよう",
      "meaning": "finally, barely, only just, gradually"
    },
    {
      "question": "時運",
      "answer": "じうん",
      "meaning": "tide of the times"
    },
    {
      "question": "無着陸",
      "answer": "むちゃくりく",
      "meaning": "nonstop"
    },
    {
      "question": "凝着",
      "answer": "ぎょうちゃく",
      "meaning": "adhesion"
    },
    {
      "question": "水産庁",
      "answer": "すいさんちょう",
      "meaning": "(Japanese) Fisheries Agency"
    },
    {
      "question": "論説委員",
      "answer": "ろんせついいん",
      "meaning": "editorial writer"
    },
    {
      "question": "背戸",
      "answer": "せど",
      "meaning": "back door, back entrance"
    },
    {
      "question": "長岡京",
      "answer": "ながおかきょう,ながおかのみやこ",
      "meaning": "Nagaoka-kyō (capital of Japan 784-794)"
    },
    {
      "question": "凝結核",
      "answer": "ぎょうけつかく",
      "meaning": "condensation nucleus"
    },
    {
      "question": "艨艟",
      "answer": "もうどう",
      "meaning": "warship"
    },
    {
      "question": "電気鰻",
      "answer": "でんきうなぎ",
      "meaning": "electric eel (Electrophorus electricus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "粉米",
      "answer": "こごめ",
      "meaning": "crushed rice, tiny pieces of rice"
    },
    {
      "question": "下洗い",
      "answer": "したあらい",
      "meaning": "prewashing, preliminary washing"
    },
    {
      "question": "宝典",
      "answer": "ほうてん",
      "meaning": "precious book, handbook, thesaurus, treasury of words"
    },
    {
      "question": "無水酢酸",
      "answer": "むすいさくさん",
      "meaning": "acetic anhydride"
    },
    {
      "question": "頂礼",
      "answer": "ちょうらい",
      "meaning": "prostration, placing knees, hands and forehead on the ground to show utmost respect"
    },
    {
      "question": "白孔雀",
      "answer": "しろくじゃく",
      "meaning": "white peafowl (white variety of Indian peafowl)"
    },
    {
      "question": "令弟",
      "answer": "れいてい",
      "meaning": "your younger brother"
    },
    {
      "question": "引火点",
      "answer": "いんかてん",
      "meaning": "flash point, flashing point"
    },
    {
      "question": "現存在",
      "answer": "げんそんざい",
      "meaning": "Dasein, philosophical concept introduced by Heidegger"
    },
    {
      "question": "文旦",
      "answer": "ぶんたん,ぼんたん",
      "meaning": "pomelo (Citrus maxima), shaddock"
    },
    {
      "question": "名誉心",
      "answer": "めいよしん",
      "meaning": "desire for fame"
    },
    {
      "question": "総トン数",
      "answer": "そうトンすう",
      "meaning": "gross tonnage, aggregate tonnage"
    },
    {
      "question": "真因",
      "answer": "しんいん",
      "meaning": "true reason, true motive"
    },
    {
      "question": "有理",
      "answer": "ゆうり",
      "meaning": "rational, rational (number or function)"
    },
    {
      "question": "余情",
      "answer": "よじょう",
      "meaning": "suggestiveness (of a poem), lingering charm, lasting impression"
    },
    {
      "question": "陰陽和合",
      "answer": "いんようわごう",
      "meaning": "the harmony of yin and yang energies"
    },
    {
      "question": "冥護",
      "answer": "みょうご,めいご",
      "meaning": "secret aid by the gods"
    },
    {
      "question": "亜寒帯",
      "answer": "あかんたい",
      "meaning": "subarctic zone"
    },
    {
      "question": "古拙",
      "answer": "こせつ",
      "meaning": "artless but attractive in a quaint sense"
    },
    {
      "question": "蝶形",
      "answer": "ちょうがた,ちょうけい",
      "meaning": "papilionaceous, butterfly-shaped"
    },
    {
      "question": "弭",
      "answer": "はず",
      "meaning": "should (be), bound (to be), expected (to be), must (be), nock (of a bow), nock (of an arrow), nock-s"
    },
    {
      "question": "本姓",
      "answer": "ほんせい",
      "meaning": "real or original name"
    },
    {
      "question": "基体",
      "answer": "きたい",
      "meaning": "base, substrate, substratum"
    },
    {
      "question": "大祖父",
      "answer": "おおおおじ",
      "meaning": "great-grandfather"
    },
    {
      "question": "概念論",
      "answer": "がいねんろん",
      "meaning": "conceptualism"
    },
    {
      "question": "甲冑師",
      "answer": "かっちゅうし",
      "meaning": "armorer, armourer"
    },
    {
      "question": "小児喘息",
      "answer": "しょうにぜんそく",
      "meaning": "infantile asthma"
    },
    {
      "question": "屠場",
      "answer": "とじょう",
      "meaning": "abattoir, slaughterhouse"
    },
    {
      "question": "乳飲料",
      "answer": "にゅういんりょう",
      "meaning": "milk beverage, milk product with added vitamins or flavour"
    },
    {
      "question": "背任罪",
      "answer": "はいにんざい",
      "meaning": "breach of trust"
    },
    {
      "question": "大著",
      "answer": "たいちょ",
      "meaning": "voluminous work, bulky volume, tome, great work, masterpiece, magnum opus"
    },
    {
      "question": "減光",
      "answer": "げんこう",
      "meaning": "light reduction, dimming of a light"
    },
    {
      "question": "嚇し",
      "answer": "おどし",
      "meaning": "threat, bird-scaring device (scarecrow, gun, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "売笑婦",
      "answer": "ばいしょうふ",
      "meaning": "prostitute"
    },
    {
      "question": "草箒",
      "answer": "くさぼうき",
      "meaning": "broom"
    },
    {
      "question": "貝割",
      "answer": "かいわり",
      "meaning": "radish sprout"
    },
    {
      "question": "嫗",
      "answer": "おうな",
      "meaning": "elderly woman"
    },
    {
      "question": "法筵",
      "answer": "ほうえん",
      "meaning": "preaching place"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄塗り",
      "answer": "うすぬり",
      "meaning": "thinly painted, thinly lacquered"
    },
    {
      "question": "嫂",
      "answer": "あによめ",
      "meaning": "elder brother's wife, sister-in-law"
    },
    {
      "question": "痘痕も靨",
      "answer": "あばたもえくぼ",
      "meaning": "love is blind, (when in love) even pockmarks are dimples"
    },
    {
      "question": "強淫",
      "answer": "ごういん",
      "meaning": "rape, sexual assault"
    },
    {
      "question": "血族結婚",
      "answer": "けつぞくけっこん",
      "meaning": "consanguineous marriage"
    },
    {
      "question": "搏動",
      "answer": "はくどう",
      "meaning": "pulsation, pulsebeat"
    },
    {
      "question": "自己誘導",
      "answer": "じこゆうどう",
      "meaning": "self-induction"
    },
    {
      "question": "歯切り盤",
      "answer": "はぎりばん",
      "meaning": "gear cutting machine"
    },
    {
      "question": "既卒",
      "answer": "きそつ",
      "meaning": "previously graduated"
    },
    {
      "question": "音楽配信",
      "answer": "おんがくはいしん",
      "meaning": "online music distribution"
    },
    {
      "question": "夏枯れ",
      "answer": "なつがれ",
      "meaning": "summer slump"
    },
    {
      "question": "桜桃忌",
      "answer": "おうとうき",
      "meaning": "anniversary that celebrates author Dazai Osamu's birthday, and incidentally, the day his body was fo"
    },
    {
      "question": "罪を着る",
      "answer": "つみをきる",
      "meaning": "to take (another's guilt) on oneself, to be accused of"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄縁",
      "answer": "うすべり",
      "meaning": "thin, bordered mat"
    },
    {
      "question": "双発機",
      "answer": "そうはつき",
      "meaning": "two-motored plane"
    },
    {
      "question": "論難",
      "answer": "ろんなん",
      "meaning": "criticism, censure"
    },
    {
      "question": "炉端焼き",
      "answer": "ろばたやき",
      "meaning": "food cooked on a grill in front of customers"
    },
    {
      "question": "口偏",
      "answer": "くちへん",
      "meaning": "kanji 'mouth' radical at left (radical 30)"
    },
    {
      "question": "交織",
      "answer": "こうしょく",
      "meaning": "mixed weave"
    },
    {
      "question": "嘸",
      "answer": "さぞ",
      "meaning": "surely, certainly, no doubt, indeed"
    },
    {
      "question": "諸点",
      "answer": "しょてん",
      "meaning": "various points (of discussion), various places, various spots, various matters"
    },
    {
      "question": "公選",
      "answer": "こうせん",
      "meaning": "public election"
    },
    {
      "question": "仙窟",
      "answer": "せんくつ",
      "meaning": "enchanted cave"
    },
    {
      "question": "虚弱児",
      "answer": "きょじゃくじ",
      "meaning": "physically weak or sickly child"
    },
    {
      "question": "経済白書",
      "answer": "けいざいはくしょ",
      "meaning": "economic white paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "売文",
      "answer": "ばいぶん",
      "meaning": "hack writer"
    },
    {
      "question": "加速度計",
      "answer": "かそくどけい",
      "meaning": "accelerometer"
    },
    {
      "question": "垣根越し",
      "answer": "かきねごし",
      "meaning": "over the fence (e.g. looking, conducting a conversation), back-fence"
    },
    {
      "question": "米糠",
      "answer": "こめぬか",
      "meaning": "rice bran"
    },
    {
      "question": "外題",
      "answer": "げだい",
      "meaning": "title (of a play)"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄肉",
      "answer": "うすにく",
      "meaning": "light red"
    },
    {
      "question": "遊び歌",
      "answer": "あそびうた",
      "meaning": "action rhymes, song sung (by children) as part of a game"
    },
    {
      "question": "可動橋",
      "answer": "かどうきょう",
      "meaning": "movable bridge"
    },
    {
      "question": "生塵",
      "answer": "なまごみ",
      "meaning": "kitchen waste, food scraps, raw garbage"
    },
    {
      "question": "継穂",
      "answer": "つぎほ,つぎぼ",
      "meaning": "scion, cion, (horticultural) graft, opportunity to continue a conversation"
    },
    {
      "question": "分散投資",
      "answer": "ぶんさんとうし",
      "meaning": "diversified investment"
    },
    {
      "question": "指し値",
      "answer": "さしね",
      "meaning": "limit price (e.g. on a stock transaction), price limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "故知",
      "answer": "こち",
      "meaning": "the wisdom of the ancients"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪因縁",
      "answer": "あくいんねん",
      "meaning": "evil destiny"
    },
    {
      "question": "柄長",
      "answer": "えなが",
      "meaning": "long-tailed tit (Aegithalos caudatus), long-tailed bushtit"
    },
    {
      "question": "四死球",
      "answer": "ししきゅう",
      "meaning": "bases on balls and pitches striking the batsmen"
    },
    {
      "question": "神聖同盟",
      "answer": "しんせいどうめい",
      "meaning": "Holy Alliance (of Russia, Austria and Prussia in 1815)"
    },
    {
      "question": "継手",
      "answer": "つぎて",
      "meaning": "a coupler, a splice, a successor, an heir"
    },
    {
      "question": "刮げる",
      "answer": "こそげる",
      "meaning": "to scrape off, to shave off"
    },
    {
      "question": "坊主刈り",
      "answer": "ぼうずがり",
      "meaning": "closely cropped hair"
    },
    {
      "question": "連子窓",
      "answer": "れんじまど",
      "meaning": "lattice window"
    },
    {
      "question": "納豆汁",
      "answer": "なっとうじる",
      "meaning": "miso soup with natto"
    },
    {
      "question": "甘塩",
      "answer": "あまじお",
      "meaning": "slightly salted"
    },
    {
      "question": "無二無三",
      "answer": "むにむさん,むにむざん",
      "meaning": "in earnest, single-minded, with intense concentration, rushing headlong into, one and only, unique"
    },
    {
      "question": "公共心",
      "answer": "こうきょうしん",
      "meaning": "public spirit"
    },
    {
      "question": "香味料",
      "answer": "こうみりょう",
      "meaning": "flavoring, flavouring, spice"
    },
    {
      "question": "落ち口",
      "answer": "おちぐち",
      "meaning": "crest (of a waterfall), mouth (of a sewer, etc.), outfall, spout (e.g. of a watering can), start of"
    },
    {
      "question": "装用",
      "answer": "そうよう",
      "meaning": "clothing"
    },
    {
      "question": "引き摺り",
      "answer": "ひきずり",
      "meaning": "train of dress, trailing skirt, woman who doesn't work and only thinks about fashion"
    },
    {
      "question": "大宮司",
      "answer": "だいぐうじ",
      "meaning": "high priest of a great shrine"
    },
    {
      "question": "田夫野人",
      "answer": "でんぷやじん",
      "meaning": "rustic, boor, hick"
    },
    {
      "question": "鋒鋩",
      "answer": "ほうぼう",
      "meaning": "the tip of an edged instrument, sharp words, vicious character"
    },
    {
      "question": "物馴れる",
      "answer": "ものなれる",
      "meaning": "to add to one's experience, to become skillful"
    },
    {
      "question": "癪の種",
      "answer": "しゃくのたね",
      "meaning": "irritant, cause of irritation, cause of annoyance"
    },
    {
      "question": "院宣",
      "answer": "いんぜん,いんせん",
      "meaning": "imperial command (decree), decree of cloistered emperor"
    },
    {
      "question": "花譜",
      "answer": "かふ",
      "meaning": "flower album"
    },
    {
      "question": "奮い起す",
      "answer": "ふるいおこす",
      "meaning": "to muster (e.g. courage), to gather, to collect, to pluck up"
    },
    {
      "question": "切金",
      "answer": "きりかね",
      "meaning": "metallic foil cut into strips or other shapes to form decorative motifs, cutting a thin sheet of met"
    },
    {
      "question": "福禄寿",
      "answer": "ふくろくじゅ",
      "meaning": "Fukurokuju, god of happiness, prosperity and long life"
    },
    {
      "question": "御題目",
      "answer": "おだいもく",
      "meaning": "Nichiren chant, (an empty) slogan"
    },
    {
      "question": "揚揚",
      "answer": "ようよう",
      "meaning": "triumphant, exultant, in high and proud spirits"
    },
    {
      "question": "弔旗",
      "answer": "ちょうき",
      "meaning": "flag at half-mast"
    },
    {
      "question": "明き",
      "answer": "あき",
      "meaning": "space, room, gap, emptiness, vacancy, opening, empty seat, free time, time to spare, disuse, unused"
    },
    {
      "question": "声声",
      "answer": "こえごえ",
      "meaning": "voices (of many people)"
    },
    {
      "question": "寸陰",
      "answer": "すんいん",
      "meaning": "moment, short time"
    },
    {
      "question": "骨腫",
      "answer": "こっしゅ,こつしゅ",
      "meaning": "osteoma"
    },
    {
      "question": "目的的",
      "answer": "もくてきてき",
      "meaning": "purposeful, purposive, intentional"
    },
    {
      "question": "色弱",
      "answer": "しきじゃく",
      "meaning": "slight color-blindness, slight colour-blindness"
    },
    {
      "question": "中文",
      "answer": "ちゅうぶん",
      "meaning": "Chinese language (written), Chinese literature"
    },
    {
      "question": "揮発油",
      "answer": "きはつゆ",
      "meaning": "gasoline, petrol, petroleum, benzine, volatile oil"
    },
    {
      "question": "大衆化",
      "answer": "たいしゅうか",
      "meaning": "popularization, popularisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "裏帆",
      "answer": "うらほ",
      "meaning": "sail with the wind at its back, aback"
    },
    {
      "question": "挟み将棋",
      "answer": "はさみしょうぎ",
      "meaning": "piece-capturing board game"
    },
    {
      "question": "好き好み",
      "answer": "すきこのみ",
      "meaning": "liking, taste, preference"
    },
    {
      "question": "月遅れ",
      "answer": "つきおくれ",
      "meaning": "a month or older, back numbers of a monthly"
    },
    {
      "question": "乱杙",
      "answer": "らんぐい",
      "meaning": "palisade, stakes planted at irregular angles and intervals as a defensive barrier"
    },
    {
      "question": "糞味噌",
      "answer": "くそみそ",
      "meaning": "harsh, severe (e.g. criticism, verbal attack), sweeping denunciation"
    },
    {
      "question": "改廃",
      "answer": "かいはい",
      "meaning": "reform and (or) abolition, alteration or repeal, revision, reorganization, reorganisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "誤伝",
      "answer": "ごでん",
      "meaning": "misinformation"
    },
    {
      "question": "花期",
      "answer": "かき",
      "meaning": "flowering season"
    },
    {
      "question": "疏通",
      "answer": "そつう",
      "meaning": "(mutual) understanding, communication, passing without obstruction"
    },
    {
      "question": "栄華の夢",
      "answer": "えいがのゆめ",
      "meaning": "visions of glory, evanescent glory"
    },
    {
      "question": "熊鼠",
      "answer": "くまねずみ",
      "meaning": "black rat (Rattus rattus), roof rat"
    },
    {
      "question": "調法",
      "answer": "ちょうほう",
      "meaning": "convenient, useful, handy, helpful"
    },
    {
      "question": "蛇座",
      "answer": "へびざ",
      "meaning": "Serpens (constellation), the Snake"
    },
    {
      "question": "衒気",
      "answer": "げんき",
      "meaning": "affectation, ostentation, vanity"
    },
    {
      "question": "独断論",
      "answer": "どくだんろん",
      "meaning": "dogmatism, dogma"
    },
    {
      "question": "揚げ場",
      "answer": "あげば",
      "meaning": "landing-stage"
    },
    {
      "question": "著明",
      "answer": "ちょめい",
      "meaning": "clarity"
    },
    {
      "question": "養魚",
      "answer": "ようぎょ",
      "meaning": "fish breeding, pisciculture"
    },
    {
      "question": "旧師",
      "answer": "きゅうし",
      "meaning": "one's former teacher, one's old teacher"
    },
    {
      "question": "両様",
      "answer": "りょうよう",
      "meaning": "two ways, both ways, two kinds"
    },
    {
      "question": "五畿内",
      "answer": "ごきない",
      "meaning": "the Five Home Provinces (Yamato, Yamashiro, Settsu, Kawachi, and Izumi)"
    },
    {
      "question": "長軸",
      "answer": "ちょうじく",
      "meaning": "major axis"
    },
    {
      "question": "殷賑",
      "answer": "いんしん",
      "meaning": "prosperity"
    },
    {
      "question": "相婿",
      "answer": "あいむこ",
      "meaning": "brother-in-law"
    },
    {
      "question": "海水着",
      "answer": "かいすいぎ",
      "meaning": "bathing suit, swimsuit"
    },
    {
      "question": "無政府",
      "answer": "むせいふ",
      "meaning": "anarchy"
    },
    {
      "question": "勇み肌",
      "answer": "いさみはだ",
      "meaning": "gallantry"
    },
    {
      "question": "仮想記憶",
      "answer": "かそうきおく",
      "meaning": "virtual memory, virtual storage"
    },
    {
      "question": "大鍬形",
      "answer": "おおくわがた",
      "meaning": "giant stag beetle (Dorcus hopei)"
    },
    {
      "question": "泊り掛け",
      "answer": "とまりがけ",
      "meaning": "staying over"
    },
    {
      "question": "臥床",
      "answer": "がしょう",
      "meaning": "confined to bed"
    },
    {
      "question": "宿世",
      "answer": "しゅくせ,すくせ",
      "meaning": "one's previous existence"
    },
    {
      "question": "光軸",
      "answer": "こうじく",
      "meaning": "optical axis (of a lens, spherical mirror, etc.), optic axis (of a crystal)"
    },
    {
      "question": "鼻鏡",
      "answer": "はなかがみ,びきょう",
      "meaning": "nasal speculum"
    },
    {
      "question": "合わせ酢",
      "answer": "あわせず",
      "meaning": "mixture of vinegar and some other flavouring (e.g. soy sauce, sugar, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "海禁",
      "answer": "かいきん",
      "meaning": "ban on maritime activities during China's Ming and Qing dynasties"
    },
    {
      "question": "鳴鳥",
      "answer": "なきどり,めいちょう",
      "meaning": "songbird, bird with a beautiful song"
    },
    {
      "question": "欠課",
      "answer": "けっか",
      "meaning": "cutting class, absence from school"
    },
    {
      "question": "約める",
      "answer": "つづめる",
      "meaning": "to abridge, to shorten, to economize"
    },
    {
      "question": "旧皮質",
      "answer": "きゅうひしつ",
      "meaning": "archicortex, archipallium"
    },
    {
      "question": "斬奸状",
      "answer": "ざんかんじょう",
      "meaning": "letter explaining the reasons for cutting down an alleged villain, assassin's written vindication of"
    },
    {
      "question": "農業革命",
      "answer": "のうぎょうかくめい",
      "meaning": "agricultural revolution, agrarian revolution"
    },
    {
      "question": "孰れ",
      "answer": "いずれ,いづれ",
      "meaning": "where, which, who, anyway, anyhow, at any rate, sooner or later, eventually, one of these days, at s"
    },
    {
      "question": "大茴香",
      "answer": "だいういきょう",
      "meaning": "star anise (Illicium verum)"
    },
    {
      "question": "滲入",
      "answer": "しんにゅう",
      "meaning": "permeation"
    },
    {
      "question": "公倍数",
      "answer": "こうばいすう",
      "meaning": "common multiple"
    },
    {
      "question": "推測る",
      "answer": "おしはかる",
      "meaning": "to guess, to conjecture, to surmise"
    },
    {
      "question": "耳底",
      "answer": "じてい",
      "meaning": "ears"
    },
    {
      "question": "水掛論",
      "answer": "みずかけろん",
      "meaning": "endless argument, pointless argument, fruitless dispute, futile discussion, argument over whose fiel"
    },
    {
      "question": "先達て",
      "answer": "せんだって",
      "meaning": "the other day, some time ago, recently"
    },
    {
      "question": "除夜",
      "answer": "じょや",
      "meaning": "New Year's Eve"
    },
    {
      "question": "里方",
      "answer": "さとかた",
      "meaning": "wife's family"
    },
    {
      "question": "屠竜",
      "answer": "とりょう,とりゅう",
      "meaning": "dragon-slaying, Kawasaki Ki-45 (WWII heavy fighter aircraft)"
    },
    {
      "question": "配偶",
      "answer": "はいぐう",
      "meaning": "combination, spouse, husband or wife, partner, married couple, husband and wife"
    },
    {
      "question": "尋常一様",
      "answer": "じんじょういちよう",
      "meaning": "ordinary, common, mediocre"
    },
    {
      "question": "口吟",
      "answer": "こうぎん",
      "meaning": "humming to oneself"
    },
    {
      "question": "セ氏",
      "answer": "セし",
      "meaning": "Celsius, centigrade"
    },
    {
      "question": "縮らせる",
      "answer": "ちぢらせる",
      "meaning": "to curl, to crimp"
    },
    {
      "question": "片寄り",
      "answer": "かたより",
      "meaning": "deviation, inclination, offset, bias, prejudice, polarization, polarisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "股擦れ",
      "answer": "またずれ",
      "meaning": "sore crotch, sore thigh, chafing of the inner thighs"
    },
    {
      "question": "示達",
      "answer": "じたつ,したつ",
      "meaning": "instructions, directions"
    },
    {
      "question": "混合酒",
      "answer": "こんごうしゅ",
      "meaning": "cocktail, mixed drink, blended liquor"
    },
    {
      "question": "渺茫",
      "answer": "びょうぼう",
      "meaning": "vast, boundless"
    },
    {
      "question": "昼光色",
      "answer": "ちゅうこうしょく",
      "meaning": "daylight color, daylight colour"
    },
    {
      "question": "閑地",
      "answer": "かんち",
      "meaning": "quiet place, vacant land, fallow ground, undemanding job, sinecure, life of leisurely retirement"
    },
    {
      "question": "資源配分",
      "answer": "しげんはいぶん",
      "meaning": "resource allocation"
    },
    {
      "question": "救貧",
      "answer": "きゅうひん",
      "meaning": "poor relief"
    },
    {
      "question": "冕",
      "answer": "べん",
      "meaning": "crown"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝刃",
      "answer": "ねたば",
      "meaning": "dull blade(d instrument)"
    },
    {
      "question": "鈕",
      "answer": "ぼたん",
      "meaning": "button"
    },
    {
      "question": "臨界量",
      "answer": "りんかいりょう",
      "meaning": "critical mass"
    },
    {
      "question": "犯し難い",
      "answer": "おかしがたい",
      "meaning": "dignified"
    },
    {
      "question": "三頭政治",
      "answer": "さんとうせいじ",
      "meaning": "triumvirate"
    },
    {
      "question": "緬甸",
      "answer": "めんでん",
      "meaning": "Burma"
    },
    {
      "question": "賀茂茄子",
      "answer": "かもなす",
      "meaning": "Kamo eggplant (Solanum melongena), round variety of eggplant famously grown in Kyoto"
    },
    {
      "question": "鳴禽類",
      "answer": "めいきんるい",
      "meaning": "oscines (birds of suborder Oscines), songbirds"
    },
    {
      "question": "労使",
      "answer": "ろうし",
      "meaning": "labour and management, labor and management"
    },
    {
      "question": "幼鳥",
      "answer": "ようちょう",
      "meaning": "young bird, juvenile, chick"
    },
    {
      "question": "枯骨",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "三尊",
      "answer": "さんぞん,さんそん",
      "meaning": "Buddha triad, image of a Buddha attended by two Bodhisattvas, The Three Jewels, Buddha, the teaching"
    },
    {
      "question": "食が細る",
      "answer": "しょくがほそる",
      "meaning": "to lose one's appetite"
    },
    {
      "question": "駒落ち",
      "answer": "こまおち",
      "meaning": "handicap"
    },
    {
      "question": "仏和辞典",
      "answer": "ふつわじてん",
      "meaning": "French-Japanese dictionary"
    },
    {
      "question": "配所",
      "answer": "はいしょ",
      "meaning": "place of exile"
    },
    {
      "question": "殺虫灯",
      "answer": "さっちゅうとう",
      "meaning": "light trap, electric insect killer, bug zapper"
    },
    {
      "question": "自然対数",
      "answer": "しぜんたいすう",
      "meaning": "natural logarithm"
    },
    {
      "question": "有期",
      "answer": "ゆうき",
      "meaning": "definite (period or term)"
    },
    {
      "question": "多雨",
      "answer": "たう",
      "meaning": "heavy rain"
    },
    {
      "question": "碧水",
      "answer": "へきすい",
      "meaning": "blue water, green water"
    },
    {
      "question": "聞分け",
      "answer": "ききわけ",
      "meaning": "reasonableness (esp. of children), obedience"
    },
    {
      "question": "乱層雲",
      "answer": "らんそううん",
      "meaning": "nimbostratus"
    },
    {
      "question": "長音符",
      "answer": "ちょうおんぷ",
      "meaning": "katakana-hiragana prolonged sound mark, macron (indicating a long vowel), circumflex (indicating a l"
    },
    {
      "question": "仏頂尊",
      "answer": "ぶっちょうそん",
      "meaning": "Butchōson (type of Buddha representing omniscience in Mikkyō Buddhism), Butchō"
    },
    {
      "question": "主部",
      "answer": "しゅぶ",
      "meaning": "main part, complete subject, grammatical subject"
    },
    {
      "question": "三角点",
      "answer": "さんかくてん",
      "meaning": "triangulation point"
    },
    {
      "question": "島巡り",
      "answer": "しまめぐり",
      "meaning": "island tour"
    },
    {
      "question": "百戦百勝",
      "answer": "ひゃくせんひゃくしょう",
      "meaning": "ever-victorious, many successful campaigns, invincibility"
    },
    {
      "question": "脂粉",
      "answer": "しふん",
      "meaning": "rouge and powder, cosmetics"
    },
    {
      "question": "た行",
      "answer": "たぎょう",
      "meaning": "the 'ta' column of the Japanese syllabary table (ta, chi, tsu, te, to)"
    },
    {
      "question": "氷食",
      "answer": "ひょうしょく",
      "meaning": "glacial scouring, glacial erosion, glacial abrasion"
    },
    {
      "question": "鼠返し",
      "answer": "ねずみがえし",
      "meaning": "rat guard, disk of wood on storehouse pillars, ropes, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "折線",
      "answer": "せっせん",
      "meaning": "broken line"
    },
    {
      "question": "関税同盟",
      "answer": "かんぜいどうめい",
      "meaning": "customs union"
    },
    {
      "question": "牢固",
      "answer": "ろうこ",
      "meaning": "firm, solid"
    },
    {
      "question": "女権",
      "answer": "じょけん",
      "meaning": "women's rights"
    },
    {
      "question": "梵鐘",
      "answer": "ぼんしょう",
      "meaning": "bonshō, Buddhist temple bell"
    },
    {
      "question": "中耳",
      "answer": "ちゅうじ",
      "meaning": "middle ear, tympanum"
    },
    {
      "question": "弥立つ",
      "answer": "よだつ,いよだつ",
      "meaning": "to stand up straight, to stand on end (e.g. of hair), to have the creeps"
    },
    {
      "question": "好期",
      "answer": "こうき",
      "meaning": "ideal time"
    },
    {
      "question": "書中",
      "answer": "しょちゅう",
      "meaning": "contained in a letter"
    },
    {
      "question": "講読",
      "answer": "こうどく",
      "meaning": "reading, translation"
    },
    {
      "question": "那須野",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "漁撈",
      "answer": "ぎょろう",
      "meaning": "fishing, fishery"
    },
    {
      "question": "蛮カラ",
      "answer": "ばんカラ",
      "meaning": "scruffy, unconcerned about one's personal appearance, rough and uncouth vigor (vigour)"
    },
    {
      "question": "善用",
      "answer": "ぜんよう",
      "meaning": "good use"
    },
    {
      "question": "跪座",
      "answer": "きざ",
      "meaning": "kneeling with the balls of the feet on the floor and sitting on one's heels"
    },
    {
      "question": "茶瓶",
      "answer": "ちゃびん",
      "meaning": "teapot"
    },
    {
      "question": "持越し",
      "answer": "もちこし",
      "meaning": "work, items, etc. carried over from earlier, hangover, what you ate the day before (and is still bei"
    },
    {
      "question": "愛慾",
      "answer": "あいよく",
      "meaning": "passion, sexual desire, lust, attachment (esp. to one's family or a member of the opposite sex)"
    },
    {
      "question": "反覆",
      "answer": "はんぷく",
      "meaning": "repetition, iteration, recursion, recurrence, recapitulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "末年",
      "answer": "まつねん",
      "meaning": "the last days, the final years, the last generation"
    },
    {
      "question": "高調",
      "answer": "こうちょう",
      "meaning": "high spirits"
    },
    {
      "question": "古詩",
      "answer": "こし",
      "meaning": "ancient poems"
    },
    {
      "question": "青海原",
      "answer": "あおうなばら",
      "meaning": "the blue sea"
    },
    {
      "question": "スパ銭",
      "answer": "スパせん",
      "meaning": "large bathhouse with many different services, deluxe public bath"
    },
    {
      "question": "千切れ雲",
      "answer": "ちぎれぐも",
      "meaning": "scattered clouds"
    },
    {
      "question": "奉迎",
      "answer": "ほうげい",
      "meaning": "welcome"
    },
    {
      "question": "績む",
      "answer": "うむ",
      "meaning": "to spin (e.g. ramie, hemp, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "複素数",
      "answer": "ふくそすう",
      "meaning": "complex number"
    },
    {
      "question": "緑膿菌",
      "answer": "りょくのうきん",
      "meaning": "Pseudomonas aeruginosa"
    },
    {
      "question": "胡麻豆腐",
      "answer": "ごまどうふ",
      "meaning": "crushed sesame seeds boiled in water and chilled like tofu"
    },
    {
      "question": "吹き寄せ",
      "answer": "ふきよせ",
      "meaning": "medley (of food, songs, etc.), (snow or sand) drift"
    },
    {
      "question": "秋霜烈日",
      "answer": "しゅうそうれつじつ",
      "meaning": "harshness, severity"
    },
    {
      "question": "煮やす",
      "answer": "にやす",
      "meaning": "to cook inside"
    },
    {
      "question": "動顚",
      "answer": "どうてん",
      "meaning": "disturbance of mind, losing one's head, being upset, being astonished, being frightened, transition,"
    },
    {
      "question": "地方史",
      "answer": "ちほうし",
      "meaning": "local history"
    },
    {
      "question": "山陽地方",
      "answer": "さんようちほう",
      "meaning": "San-you region of western Honshu (incl. Okayama, Hiroshima, southern Yamaguchi and sometimes western"
    },
    {
      "question": "先夫",
      "answer": "せんぷ",
      "meaning": "former husband, late husband"
    },
    {
      "question": "修する",
      "answer": "しゅうする,しゅする",
      "meaning": "to study, to complete (a course), to cultivate, to master, to fix, to correct, to repair, to conduct"
    },
    {
      "question": "黄経",
      "answer": "こうけい,おうけい",
      "meaning": "ecliptic longitude, celestial longitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "弁ずる",
      "answer": "べんずる",
      "meaning": "to manage, to dispose of, to carry through, to distinguish, to discriminate"
    },
    {
      "question": "投影図",
      "answer": "とうえいず",
      "meaning": "a projection drawing"
    },
    {
      "question": "酔眼朦朧",
      "answer": "すいがんもうろう",
      "meaning": "(with) one's eyes blurred from drinking, with drunken eyes, dazed by wine"
    },
    {
      "question": "一陽来復",
      "answer": "いちようらいふく",
      "meaning": "return of spring, long-awaited, favorable turn of fortune (favourable)"
    },
    {
      "question": "労金",
      "answer": "ろうきん",
      "meaning": "workers' credit union, labour credit association"
    },
    {
      "question": "含め煮",
      "answer": "ふくめに",
      "meaning": "food boiled in sugar syrup"
    },
    {
      "question": "貝塚",
      "answer": "かいづか,かいずか",
      "meaning": "shell heap, shell mound, kitchen midden"
    },
    {
      "question": "腕首",
      "answer": "うでくび",
      "meaning": "wrist"
    },
    {
      "question": "武弁",
      "answer": "ぶべん",
      "meaning": "soldier"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝棺",
      "answer": "ねかん",
      "meaning": "coffin, casket"
    },
    {
      "question": "死に恥",
      "answer": "しにはじ",
      "meaning": "dishonor that persists after death, shame at the moment of one's death"
    },
    {
      "question": "刑事補償",
      "answer": "けいじほしょう",
      "meaning": "criminal indemnity"
    },
    {
      "question": "語り物",
      "answer": "かたりもの",
      "meaning": "a narrative"
    },
    {
      "question": "半夏生",
      "answer": "はんげしょう",
      "meaning": "Chinese lizard's tail (Saururus chinensis), 11th day after the summer solstice, last seed-sowing and"
    },
    {
      "question": "圧入",
      "answer": "あつにゅう",
      "meaning": "indentation"
    },
    {
      "question": "時知らず",
      "answer": "ときしらず",
      "meaning": "summer-catch salmon"
    },
    {
      "question": "小陰",
      "answer": "しょういん",
      "meaning": "the lesser yin (within yin-yang)"
    },
    {
      "question": "塩物",
      "answer": "しおもの",
      "meaning": "salted fish"
    },
    {
      "question": "ずっ友",
      "answer": "ずっとも",
      "meaning": "friends forever"
    },
    {
      "question": "老妻",
      "answer": "ろうさい",
      "meaning": "old woman"
    },
    {
      "question": "馬追い",
      "answer": "うまおい",
      "meaning": "loading a horse with passengers or baggage, driving a horse into a pen, Hexacentrus japonicus (speci"
    },
    {
      "question": "家法",
      "answer": "かほう",
      "meaning": "family code"
    },
    {
      "question": "対頂角",
      "answer": "たいちょうかく",
      "meaning": "vertical angles, vertically opposite angles"
    },
    {
      "question": "帰命",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "情意",
      "answer": "じょうい",
      "meaning": "feeling, emotion, will"
    },
    {
      "question": "球際",
      "answer": "たまぎわ",
      "meaning": "ball control, focus on the ball"
    },
    {
      "question": "梧桐",
      "answer": "あおぎり,ごとう",
      "meaning": "Chinese parasol-tree (Firmiana simplex), Chinese-bottletree, Japanese varnishtree, phoenix-tree"
    },
    {
      "question": "御裾分け",
      "answer": "おすそわけ",
      "meaning": "sharing with others what has been given to you, sharing a portion of the profit with others"
    },
    {
      "question": "諸行",
      "answer": "しょぎょう",
      "meaning": "all worldly phenomena, meritorious acts leading to enlightenment, (Jodo school) all practices other"
    },
    {
      "question": "他山の石",
      "answer": "たざんのいし",
      "meaning": "lesson learned from someone's else mistake, object lesson, food for thought, stones from other mount"
    },
    {
      "question": "相利共生",
      "answer": "そうりきょうせい",
      "meaning": "mutualism, symbiosis"
    },
    {
      "question": "種本",
      "answer": "たねほん",
      "meaning": "source book"
    },
    {
      "question": "自由刑",
      "answer": "じゆうけい",
      "meaning": "freedom-restricting punishment, imprisonment"
    },
    {
      "question": "河岸段丘",
      "answer": "かがんだんきゅう",
      "meaning": "river terrace"
    },
    {
      "question": "勾引",
      "answer": "こういん,かどわかし",
      "meaning": "arrest, custody, seduction, abduction, kidnapper"
    },
    {
      "question": "身を誤る",
      "answer": "みをあやまる",
      "meaning": "to err, to take the wrong path, to go astray"
    },
    {
      "question": "立て看",
      "answer": "たてかん",
      "meaning": "standing signboard, billboard, hoarding"
    },
    {
      "question": "役者絵",
      "answer": "やくしゃえ",
      "meaning": "actor print, ukiyo-e print of kabuki actors"
    },
    {
      "question": "新論",
      "answer": "しんろん",
      "meaning": "new debate"
    },
    {
      "question": "剪る",
      "answer": "きる",
      "meaning": "to cut, to prune, to trim (branches, leaves, flowers, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "送達",
      "answer": "そうたつ",
      "meaning": "delivery, dispatch, despatch, conveyance, service of process"
    },
    {
      "question": "起き掛け",
      "answer": "おきがけ",
      "meaning": "first thing after rising"
    },
    {
      "question": "関特演",
      "answer": "かんとくえん",
      "meaning": "plan for the invasion of the Soviet Far East in July 1941"
    },
    {
      "question": "釈迦牟尼",
      "answer": "しゃかむに",
      "meaning": "Gautama Buddha, Shakyamuni, the historical Buddha (5th c. BCE?)"
    },
    {
      "question": "菖蒲湯",
      "answer": "しょうぶゆ",
      "meaning": "bathwater with iris petals"
    },
    {
      "question": "定式幕",
      "answer": "じょうしきまく",
      "meaning": "kabuki curtain, usu. of three coloured panels"
    },
    {
      "question": "力闘",
      "answer": "りきとう",
      "meaning": "hard fight"
    },
    {
      "question": "夙に",
      "answer": "つとに",
      "meaning": "for a long time, since long ago, from childhood, bright and early, early in the morning"
    },
    {
      "question": "古写本",
      "answer": "こしゃほん",
      "meaning": "old manuscript, codex"
    },
    {
      "question": "春霰",
      "answer": "しゅんさん",
      "meaning": "spring hail"
    },
    {
      "question": "薫物",
      "answer": "たきもの",
      "meaning": "incense, mixture of fragrant woods, etc. used for making incense"
    },
    {
      "question": "遠海",
      "answer": "えんかい",
      "meaning": "deep sea, ocean"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛電",
      "answer": "ひでん",
      "meaning": "flash of lightning, urgent telegram, express telegraph"
    },
    {
      "question": "新紀元",
      "answer": "しんきげん",
      "meaning": "new era or epoch"
    },
    {
      "question": "濡れ色",
      "answer": "ぬれいろ",
      "meaning": "color of something wet, colour of something wet"
    },
    {
      "question": "波面",
      "answer": "はめん",
      "meaning": "wave surface, wave-front"
    },
    {
      "question": "液相",
      "answer": "えきそう",
      "meaning": "liquid phase"
    },
    {
      "question": "荷鞍",
      "answer": "にぐら",
      "meaning": "packsaddle"
    },
    {
      "question": "簿冊",
      "answer": "ぼさつ",
      "meaning": "(bound) book, notebook"
    },
    {
      "question": "張り扇",
      "answer": "はりせん,はりおうぎ",
      "meaning": "paper-covered folded fan used in noh and storytelling, paper fan used in slapstick comedy"
    },
    {
      "question": "春楡",
      "answer": "はるにれ",
      "meaning": "Japanese elm (Ulmus davidiana var. japonica)"
    },
    {
      "question": "不猟",
      "answer": "ふりょう",
      "meaning": "poor bag (hunting)"
    },
    {
      "question": "歌風",
      "answer": "かふう",
      "meaning": "poetic style"
    },
    {
      "question": "新券",
      "answer": "しんけん",
      "meaning": "new banknote"
    },
    {
      "question": "両棲",
      "answer": "りょうせい",
      "meaning": "amphibious, amphibian"
    },
    {
      "question": "各人各様",
      "answer": "かくじんかくよう",
      "meaning": "different strokes for different folks, people doing something in their own way"
    },
    {
      "question": "一塩",
      "answer": "ひとしお",
      "meaning": "slightly salted"
    },
    {
      "question": "田舎訛り",
      "answer": "いなかなまり",
      "meaning": "provincial accent"
    },
    {
      "question": "山っ気",
      "answer": "やまっけ",
      "meaning": "speculative spirit"
    },
    {
      "question": "当座預金",
      "answer": "とうざよきん",
      "meaning": "current account, transactional account, checking account, cheque account, demand account"
    },
    {
      "question": "水禍",
      "answer": "すいか",
      "meaning": "flood disaster, drowning"
    },
    {
      "question": "実らしい",
      "answer": "じちらしい",
      "meaning": "honest (appearance), sincere (impression)"
    },
    {
      "question": "登載",
      "answer": "とうさい",
      "meaning": "register, record, printing"
    },
    {
      "question": "文部大臣",
      "answer": "もんぶだいじん",
      "meaning": "Minister of Education"
    },
    {
      "question": "西方浄土",
      "answer": "さいほうじょうど",
      "meaning": "Western Pure Land (Amitabha's Buddhist paradise)"
    },
    {
      "question": "球宴",
      "answer": "きゅうえん",
      "meaning": "baseball all-star game"
    },
    {
      "question": "銅合金",
      "answer": "どうごうきん",
      "meaning": "copper alloy"
    },
    {
      "question": "太り肉",
      "answer": "ふとりじし",
      "meaning": "corpulent, fat, chubby"
    },
    {
      "question": "信用経済",
      "answer": "しんようけいざい",
      "meaning": "credit economy"
    },
    {
      "question": "恭悦",
      "answer": "きょうえつ",
      "meaning": "delight"
    },
    {
      "question": "鼠穴",
      "answer": "ねずみあな",
      "meaning": "rathole, mousehole"
    },
    {
      "question": "事々しい",
      "answer": "ことごとしい",
      "meaning": "bombastic, pretentious, exaggerated"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤鹿",
      "answer": "あかしか",
      "meaning": "red deer (Cervus elaphus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "潤色",
      "answer": "じゅんしょく",
      "meaning": "rhetorical flourishes"
    },
    {
      "question": "汗水漬く",
      "answer": "あせみずく,あせみづく",
      "meaning": "drenched with sweat, sweaty all over"
    },
    {
      "question": "養畜",
      "answer": "ようちく",
      "meaning": "stock keeping, raising livestock"
    },
    {
      "question": "在宿",
      "answer": "ざいしゅく",
      "meaning": "being at home"
    },
    {
      "question": "枕経",
      "answer": "まくらぎょう",
      "meaning": "sutra recitation at the bedside of a deceased person, pillow sutra"
    },
    {
      "question": "立退く",
      "answer": "たちのく",
      "meaning": "to leave, to evacuate, to withdraw (from), to clear out, to move out (of a house, etc.), to vacate"
    },
    {
      "question": "元文",
      "answer": "げんぶん",
      "meaning": "Genbun era (1736.4.28-1741.2.27)"
    },
    {
      "question": "魔所",
      "answer": "ましょ",
      "meaning": "location where a magical being resides, cursed place where disaster after disaster occurs"
    },
    {
      "question": "甲走る",
      "answer": "かんばしる",
      "meaning": "to make a shrill sound"
    },
    {
      "question": "迷迭香",
      "answer": "まんねんろう",
      "meaning": "rosemary"
    },
    {
      "question": "防臭剤",
      "answer": "ぼうしゅうざい",
      "meaning": "deodorant, deodorizer, deodoriser"
    },
    {
      "question": "花曇り",
      "answer": "はなぐもり",
      "meaning": "hazy weather in spring"
    },
    {
      "question": "三族",
      "answer": "さんぞく",
      "meaning": "three types of relatives (e.g. father, children and grandchildren; parents, siblings, wife and child"
    },
    {
      "question": "蛮夷",
      "answer": "ばんい",
      "meaning": "savages, barbarians"
    },
    {
      "question": "昏冥",
      "answer": "こんめい",
      "meaning": "darkness, gloom"
    },
    {
      "question": "差し掛け",
      "answer": "さしかけ",
      "meaning": "holding (an umbrella) over something, lean-to roof"
    },
    {
      "question": "上作",
      "answer": "じょうさく",
      "meaning": "good crop, masterpiece"
    },
    {
      "question": "把捉",
      "answer": "はそく",
      "meaning": "grasping (a meaning)"
    },
    {
      "question": "雑色",
      "answer": "ざっしょく,ざっしき,ぞうしき",
      "meaning": "assorted colors, assorted colours"
    },
    {
      "question": "国立銀行",
      "answer": "こくりつぎんこう",
      "meaning": "national bank"
    },
    {
      "question": "火国",
      "answer": "ひのくに",
      "meaning": "Hi (former province located in present-day Nagasaki, Saga and Kumamoto prefectures; later split into"
    },
    {
      "question": "少雨",
      "answer": "しょうう",
      "meaning": "small amount of rainfall, (a) light rainfall"
    },
    {
      "question": "欣喜",
      "answer": "きんき",
      "meaning": "pleasure"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭脳流出",
      "answer": "ずのうりゅうしゅつ",
      "meaning": "brain drain, outflow of talent"
    },
    {
      "question": "尖り声",
      "answer": "とがりごえ",
      "meaning": "sharp or angry voice"
    },
    {
      "question": "閣内",
      "answer": "かくない",
      "meaning": "(inside the) Cabinet"
    },
    {
      "question": "机下",
      "answer": "きか",
      "meaning": "word of respect added to the addressee's name on a letter, under the desk"
    },
    {
      "question": "幽邃",
      "answer": "ゆうすい",
      "meaning": "retired and quiet, secluded"
    },
    {
      "question": "万愚節",
      "answer": "ばんぐせつ",
      "meaning": "April Fools' Day"
    },
    {
      "question": "時人",
      "answer": "じじん",
      "meaning": "contemporaries"
    },
    {
      "question": "大出来",
      "answer": "おおでき",
      "meaning": "well-made, well-done, great success"
    },
    {
      "question": "反故紙",
      "answer": "ほごがみ",
      "meaning": "wastepaper, scrap paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "頸静脈",
      "answer": "けいじょうみゃく",
      "meaning": "jugular vein"
    },
    {
      "question": "柴垣",
      "answer": "しばがき",
      "meaning": "brushwood fence"
    },
    {
      "question": "原子論",
      "answer": "げんしろん",
      "meaning": "atomic theory, atomism"
    },
    {
      "question": "浄衣",
      "answer": "じょうえ",
      "meaning": "white robe or costume"
    },
    {
      "question": "兵法者",
      "answer": "へいほうしゃ",
      "meaning": "tactician, strategist, master swordsman"
    },
    {
      "question": "尾鉱",
      "answer": "びこう",
      "meaning": "tailing"
    },
    {
      "question": "仮す",
      "answer": "かす",
      "meaning": "to grant, to allow, to forgive"
    },
    {
      "question": "学績",
      "answer": "がくせき",
      "meaning": "school record, achievement"
    },
    {
      "question": "時間芸術",
      "answer": "じかんげいじゅつ",
      "meaning": "temporal art, art forms which unfold over time"
    },
    {
      "question": "能装束",
      "answer": "のうしょうぞく",
      "meaning": "noh costume"
    },
    {
      "question": "対蹠的",
      "answer": "たいしょてき,たいせきてき",
      "meaning": "diametrically opposed, antipodal"
    },
    {
      "question": "日本犬",
      "answer": "にほんけん,にほんいぬ,にっぽんいぬ",
      "meaning": "Japanese dog breed (i.e. Shiba, Akita)"
    },
    {
      "question": "詰草",
      "answer": "つめくさ",
      "meaning": "white Dutch clover"
    },
    {
      "question": "烏羽玉",
      "answer": "うばたま",
      "meaning": "jet black, pitch dark, peyote (Lophophora williamsii), mescaline"
    },
    {
      "question": "野衾",
      "answer": "ももんが,のぶすま",
      "meaning": "Japanese flying squirrel (Pteromys momonga), small Japanese flying squirrel, Japanese dwarf flying s"
    },
    {
      "question": "供人",
      "answer": "ともびと",
      "meaning": "companion"
    },
    {
      "question": "駿台",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "丑の日",
      "answer": "うしのひ",
      "meaning": "day of the Ox (esp. in midsummer or midwinter)"
    },
    {
      "question": "純増",
      "answer": "じゅんぞう",
      "meaning": "net increase"
    },
    {
      "question": "無理数",
      "answer": "むりすう",
      "meaning": "irrational number"
    },
    {
      "question": "冠状動脈",
      "answer": "かんじょうどうみゃく",
      "meaning": "coronary artery"
    },
    {
      "question": "水先",
      "answer": "みずさき",
      "meaning": "direction of a current, course of a ship"
    },
    {
      "question": "訓電",
      "answer": "くんでん",
      "meaning": "telegraphed instructions"
    },
    {
      "question": "失費",
      "answer": "しっぴ",
      "meaning": "expenses"
    },
    {
      "question": "初発",
      "answer": "しょはつ",
      "meaning": "start, first departure"
    },
    {
      "question": "豊熟",
      "answer": "ほうじゅく",
      "meaning": "abundant harvest"
    },
    {
      "question": "改憲",
      "answer": "かいけん",
      "meaning": "constitutional change, revising the constitution"
    },
    {
      "question": "河鹿",
      "answer": "かじか",
      "meaning": "kajika frog (Buergeria buergeri)"
    },
    {
      "question": "愚見",
      "answer": "ぐけん",
      "meaning": "one's humble opinion"
    },
    {
      "question": "黄瓜",
      "answer": "きゅうり,きうり",
      "meaning": "cucumber (Cucumis sativus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "能力給",
      "answer": "のうりょくきゅう",
      "meaning": "payment based on ability"
    },
    {
      "question": "印地",
      "answer": "いんじ",
      "meaning": "big rock fight for children on the fifth day of the fifth month (adults also participated during the"
    },
    {
      "question": "両頭",
      "answer": "りょうとう",
      "meaning": "double-headed"
    },
    {
      "question": "片結び",
      "answer": "かたむすび",
      "meaning": "half-hitch, half knot, slipknot"
    },
    {
      "question": "地下経済",
      "answer": "ちかけいざい",
      "meaning": "underground economy, black economy"
    },
    {
      "question": "温習",
      "answer": "おんしゅう,さらい",
      "meaning": "review, rehearsal"
    },
    {
      "question": "岩組",
      "answer": "いわぐみ",
      "meaning": "arrangement of stones in a garden"
    },
    {
      "question": "肉骨粉",
      "answer": "にくこっぷん",
      "meaning": "meat-and-bone meal, MBM"
    },
    {
      "question": "花鶏",
      "answer": "あとり",
      "meaning": "brambling (bird) (Fringilla montifringilla)"
    },
    {
      "question": "起電",
      "answer": "きでん",
      "meaning": "generation of electricity"
    },
    {
      "question": "工業規格",
      "answer": "こうぎょうきかく",
      "meaning": "industrial standard, engineering standard"
    },
    {
      "question": "爽涼",
      "answer": "そうりょう",
      "meaning": "cool and refreshing"
    },
    {
      "question": "繰上げ",
      "answer": "くりあげ",
      "meaning": "upward move, advance"
    },
    {
      "question": "烹炊",
      "answer": "ほうすい",
      "meaning": "cooking by boiling"
    },
    {
      "question": "全共闘",
      "answer": "ぜんきょうとう",
      "meaning": "All-Campus Joint Struggle League, student group active at universities throughout Japan between 1968"
    },
    {
      "question": "順良",
      "answer": "じゅんりょう",
      "meaning": "good and obedient, gentle, meek"
    },
    {
      "question": "寄り掛る",
      "answer": "よりかかる",
      "meaning": "to lean against, to recline on, to lean on, to rely on, to depend on"
    },
    {
      "question": "半ぺら",
      "answer": "はんぺら",
      "meaning": "half of a piece of paper, half-size paper, (ticket) stub"
    },
    {
      "question": "人身取引",
      "answer": "じんしんとりひき",
      "meaning": "human trafficking"
    },
    {
      "question": "文正",
      "answer": "ぶんしょう",
      "meaning": "Bunshō era (1466.2.28-1467.3.5)"
    },
    {
      "question": "ノー問題",
      "answer": "ノーもんだい",
      "meaning": "no problem"
    },
    {
      "question": "閏日",
      "answer": "うるうび,じゅんじつ",
      "meaning": "leap day"
    },
    {
      "question": "高根",
      "answer": "たかね",
      "meaning": "high peak"
    },
    {
      "question": "放談",
      "answer": "ほうだん",
      "meaning": "free talk, irresponsible talk"
    },
    {
      "question": "細根",
      "answer": "さいこん",
      "meaning": "rootlet"
    },
    {
      "question": "改号",
      "answer": "かいごう",
      "meaning": "change of name or title, change of era"
    },
    {
      "question": "金襴緞子",
      "answer": "きんらんどんす",
      "meaning": "gold-brocaded satin damask"
    },
    {
      "question": "表紙買い",
      "answer": "ひょうしがい",
      "meaning": "buying a book, magazine because of its cover"
    },
    {
      "question": "科の木",
      "answer": "しなのき",
      "meaning": "Japanese linden (Tilia japonica)"
    },
    {
      "question": "下書",
      "answer": "げしょ",
      "meaning": "draft, rough copy"
    },
    {
      "question": "捕り縄",
      "answer": "とりなわ",
      "meaning": "policeman's rope (used for restraining criminals)"
    },
    {
      "question": "氏素姓",
      "answer": "うじすじょう",
      "meaning": "(a person's) family background, lineage"
    },
    {
      "question": "吾妻鏡",
      "answer": "あずまかがみ,あづまかがみ",
      "meaning": "Japanese medieval text that chronicles events of the Kamakura Shogunate"
    },
    {
      "question": "白糖",
      "answer": "はくとう",
      "meaning": "white sugar"
    },
    {
      "question": "念珠",
      "answer": "ねんじゅ,ねんず",
      "meaning": "rosary, string of prayer beads"
    },
    {
      "question": "津波警報",
      "answer": "つなみけいほう",
      "meaning": "tsunami warning"
    },
    {
      "question": "慢性中毒",
      "answer": "まんせいちゅうどく",
      "meaning": "chronic addiction, chronic intoxication"
    },
    {
      "question": "肌脱ぎ",
      "answer": "はだぬぎ",
      "meaning": "naked to the waist"
    },
    {
      "question": "細管",
      "answer": "さいかん",
      "meaning": "small tube, pipette, tubule"
    },
    {
      "question": "楽屋落ち",
      "answer": "がくやおち",
      "meaning": "shoptalk, matters incomprehensible to outsiders, inside joke, private joke"
    },
    {
      "question": "風蝕",
      "answer": "ふうしょく",
      "meaning": "wind erosion"
    },
    {
      "question": "吶々",
      "answer": "とつとつ",
      "meaning": "halting (speech), faltering, stammering"
    },
    {
      "question": "空中線",
      "answer": "くうちゅうせん",
      "meaning": "antenna"
    },
    {
      "question": "随順",
      "answer": "ずいじゅん",
      "meaning": "obeying meekly, faithfully following (one's master)"
    },
    {
      "question": "御布施",
      "answer": "おふせ",
      "meaning": "alms-giving, charity, offerings (usu. money) to a priest (for reading sutras, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "機嫌伺い",
      "answer": "きげんうかがい",
      "meaning": "courtesy call, courtesy visit"
    },
    {
      "question": "痕跡器官",
      "answer": "こんせききかん",
      "meaning": "vestigial (rudimentary) organ"
    },
    {
      "question": "夢々",
      "answer": "ゆめゆめ",
      "meaning": "(not even) a little bit, diligently, dreams"
    },
    {
      "question": "展延",
      "answer": "てんえん",
      "meaning": "spreading out, stretching out, expansion, extension"
    },
    {
      "question": "万聖節",
      "answer": "ばんせいせつ",
      "meaning": "All Saints' Day, All Hallows' Day"
    },
    {
      "question": "胎蔵",
      "answer": "たいぞう",
      "meaning": "Garbhadhatu, Womb Realm, Matrix Realm"
    },
    {
      "question": "ベン図",
      "answer": "ベンず",
      "meaning": "Venn diagram"
    },
    {
      "question": "千仞",
      "answer": "せんじん",
      "meaning": "great depth, bottomless, great height"
    },
    {
      "question": "両班",
      "answer": "りょうはん,ヤンバン,リャンバン",
      "meaning": "preliminary introduction (Zen), traditional ruling class of Korea during the Joseon dynasty, yangban"
    },
    {
      "question": "肝煎",
      "answer": "きもいり",
      "meaning": "good offices, auspices, sponsorship, help, assistance, village official (during the Edo period)"
    },
    {
      "question": "与那国島",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "所作事",
      "answer": "しょさごと",
      "meaning": "dance (in kabuki), dance play"
    },
    {
      "question": "製靴",
      "answer": "せいか",
      "meaning": "shoe-making"
    },
    {
      "question": "小天地",
      "answer": "しょうてんち",
      "meaning": "a small world"
    },
    {
      "question": "物の哀れ",
      "answer": "もののあわれ,もののあはれ",
      "meaning": "mono no aware, appreciation of the fleeting nature of beauty, pathos of things, strong aesthetic sen"
    },
    {
      "question": "人別帳",
      "answer": "にんべつちょう",
      "meaning": "family registry (of the district) (Edo period), population registry, records of an Edo period census"
    },
    {
      "question": "望蜀",
      "answer": "ぼうしょく",
      "meaning": "insatiability"
    },
    {
      "question": "律速",
      "answer": "りっそく",
      "meaning": "rate-limiting, rate-determining"
    },
    {
      "question": "神庫",
      "answer": "ほくら,じんこ",
      "meaning": "small shrine, depository for sacred objects"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕付け糸",
      "answer": "しつけいと",
      "meaning": "tacking, basting (thread)"
    },
    {
      "question": "搾菜",
      "answer": "ザーサイ,ザーツァイ",
      "meaning": "Szechuan pickles, Sichuan vegetables, zha cai, pickled mustard plant stem"
    },
    {
      "question": "儲け口",
      "answer": "もうけぐち",
      "meaning": "profitable job, way to make a fast buck"
    },
    {
      "question": "十二門",
      "answer": "じゅうにもん",
      "meaning": "the twelve gates of Heian's greater palace"
    },
    {
      "question": "長春",
      "answer": "ちょうしゅん",
      "meaning": "everlasting spring, China rose (Rosa chinensis)"
    },
    {
      "question": "杓文字",
      "answer": "しゃもじ,さもじ",
      "meaning": "wooden spoon, ladle, rice scoop"
    },
    {
      "question": "花鰹",
      "answer": "はながつお,はなかつお",
      "meaning": "dried bonito shavings"
    },
    {
      "question": "華語",
      "answer": "かご",
      "meaning": "Chinese (language)"
    },
    {
      "question": "暮れ残る",
      "answer": "くれのこる",
      "meaning": "to linger (faint light of twilight), to remain lit in the lingering twilight"
    },
    {
      "question": "更かす",
      "answer": "ふかす",
      "meaning": "to sit up late"
    },
    {
      "question": "陸産",
      "answer": "りくさん",
      "meaning": "land products"
    },
    {
      "question": "総則",
      "answer": "そうそく",
      "meaning": "general provisions, general rules"
    },
    {
      "question": "抽出法",
      "answer": "ちゅうしゅつほう",
      "meaning": "sampling (i.e. as a survey method)"
    },
    {
      "question": "劇変",
      "answer": "げきへん",
      "meaning": "sudden change, upheaval"
    },
    {
      "question": "好色本",
      "answer": "こうしょくぼん",
      "meaning": "erotic or pornographic book (Edo period)"
    },
    {
      "question": "証紙",
      "answer": "しょうし",
      "meaning": "(inspection or certification) stamp"
    },
    {
      "question": "内障",
      "answer": "ないしょう,そこひ",
      "meaning": "internal hindrance, any visual disorder caused by a problem within the eye (i.e. glaucoma, amaurosis"
    },
    {
      "question": "角通",
      "answer": "かくつう",
      "meaning": "expert"
    },
    {
      "question": "端午",
      "answer": "たんご",
      "meaning": "Boy's Day celebration (May 5)"
    },
    {
      "question": "乃木希典",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "夜間学校",
      "answer": "やかんがっこう",
      "meaning": "evening school, night school"
    },
    {
      "question": "吸収剤",
      "answer": "きゅうしゅうざい",
      "meaning": "absorbent"
    },
    {
      "question": "新形",
      "answer": "しんがた",
      "meaning": "new type, new style, new model, new strain (e.g. infectious disease)"
    },
    {
      "question": "艇身",
      "answer": "ていしん",
      "meaning": "boat length"
    },
    {
      "question": "酔い醒め",
      "answer": "よいざめ",
      "meaning": "recovering from intoxication, sobering up"
    },
    {
      "question": "忌中",
      "answer": "きちゅう",
      "meaning": "mourning"
    },
    {
      "question": "都議",
      "answer": "とぎ",
      "meaning": "Metropolitan assemblyman"
    },
    {
      "question": "午飯",
      "answer": "ごはん",
      "meaning": "lunch"
    },
    {
      "question": "苧環",
      "answer": "おだまき",
      "meaning": "fan columbine (Aquilegia flabellata)"
    },
    {
      "question": "別記",
      "answer": "べっき",
      "meaning": "addendum, supplementary material, afterword, postscript, marginal notes"
    },
    {
      "question": "世馴れる",
      "answer": "よなれる",
      "meaning": "to become used to the (ways of the) world, to become worldly or sophisticated"
    },
    {
      "question": "普請場",
      "answer": "ふしんば",
      "meaning": "building plot"
    },
    {
      "question": "粋狂",
      "answer": "すいきょう",
      "meaning": "whim, vagary, capriciousness, eccentricity"
    },
    {
      "question": "小鴨",
      "answer": "こがも",
      "meaning": "green-winged teal (species of duck, Anas crecca)"
    },
    {
      "question": "螟蛾",
      "answer": "めいが",
      "meaning": "pyralid (any moth of family Pyralidae, many of which have larvae that devour foodstuffs)"
    },
    {
      "question": "飲み潰す",
      "answer": "のみつぶす",
      "meaning": "to drink away one's money, to be a sot, to get wasted, to drink someone under the table"
    },
    {
      "question": "破牢",
      "answer": "はろう",
      "meaning": "breaking out of prison, jailbreak"
    },
    {
      "question": "一管",
      "answer": "いっかん",
      "meaning": "one flute, one brush"
    },
    {
      "question": "半割",
      "answer": "はんざき",
      "meaning": "Japanese giant salamander (Andrias japonicus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "腰折れ",
      "answer": "こしおれ",
      "meaning": "bad poem, my humble poem, stooped over (e.g. old people), bowed, stalling, having a relapse"
    },
    {
      "question": "替地",
      "answer": "かえち",
      "meaning": "substitute land, substitute lot, land substitution, land exchange"
    },
    {
      "question": "文教地区",
      "answer": "ぶんきょうちく",
      "meaning": "school zone"
    },
    {
      "question": "煮切る",
      "answer": "にきる",
      "meaning": "to boil down sake, mirin, etc. to reduce the alcohol content"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪降り",
      "answer": "ゆきふり",
      "meaning": "snowfall"
    },
    {
      "question": "弊所",
      "answer": "へいしょ",
      "meaning": "our office"
    },
    {
      "question": "備砲",
      "answer": "びほう",
      "meaning": "armament"
    },
    {
      "question": "手詰め",
      "answer": "てづめ",
      "meaning": "pressing, urging"
    },
    {
      "question": "基層",
      "answer": "きそう",
      "meaning": "base layer, substratum, binder course"
    },
    {
      "question": "練り薬",
      "answer": "ねりぐすり",
      "meaning": "electuary"
    },
    {
      "question": "最頻値",
      "answer": "さいひんち",
      "meaning": "mode"
    },
    {
      "question": "僻遠",
      "answer": "へきえん",
      "meaning": "remote, outlying"
    },
    {
      "question": "病児",
      "answer": "びょうじ",
      "meaning": "sick child"
    },
    {
      "question": "御用人",
      "answer": "ごようにん",
      "meaning": "manager, steward, person next in rank to the chief retainer and in charge of general management and"
    },
    {
      "question": "主訴",
      "answer": "しゅそ",
      "meaning": "main complaint"
    },
    {
      "question": "曙色",
      "answer": "あけぼのいろ",
      "meaning": "salmon (color, colour), pink with a yellow tinge"
    },
    {
      "question": "筒音",
      "answer": "つつおと",
      "meaning": "the sound of gunfire"
    },
    {
      "question": "反軍",
      "answer": "はんぐん",
      "meaning": "antimilitary"
    },
    {
      "question": "竜顔",
      "answer": "りゅうがん,りょうがん",
      "meaning": "Imperial countenance, face of the Emperor"
    },
    {
      "question": "粗漏",
      "answer": "そろう",
      "meaning": "carelessness, negligence, oversight"
    },
    {
      "question": "沸沸",
      "answer": "ふつふつ",
      "meaning": "simmer, bubble out, flow out"
    },
    {
      "question": "盛花",
      "answer": "もりばな,せいか",
      "meaning": "flower arrangement in a built-up style, placing salt by the entrance to one's establishment to bring"
    },
    {
      "question": "帆綱",
      "answer": "ほづな",
      "meaning": "halyard"
    },
    {
      "question": "瞞着",
      "answer": "まんちゃく",
      "meaning": "deception, cheating, trickery, fraud"
    },
    {
      "question": "馬革",
      "answer": "ばかく",
      "meaning": "horsehide"
    },
    {
      "question": "耀う",
      "answer": "かがよう",
      "meaning": "to shimmer, to sparkle"
    },
    {
      "question": "批評眼",
      "answer": "ひひょうがん",
      "meaning": "critical eye"
    },
    {
      "question": "印加",
      "answer": "いんか",
      "meaning": "impression, superimposition, application"
    },
    {
      "question": "ずわい蟹",
      "answer": "ずわいがに",
      "meaning": "snow crab (Chionoecetes opilio), queen crab"
    },
    {
      "question": "大羽",
      "answer": "おおばね,おおば",
      "meaning": "contour feather, quill feather, large Japanese pilchard"
    },
    {
      "question": "唐茶",
      "answer": "からちゃ",
      "meaning": "tawny brown, dark vermillion"
    },
    {
      "question": "静座",
      "answer": "せいざ",
      "meaning": "sitting calmly and quietly (i.e. in order to meditate)"
    },
    {
      "question": "橋台",
      "answer": "きょうだい",
      "meaning": "bridge abutment"
    },
    {
      "question": "観桜",
      "answer": "かんおう",
      "meaning": "cherry blossom viewing"
    },
    {
      "question": "公器",
      "answer": "こうき",
      "meaning": "public institution"
    },
    {
      "question": "相思",
      "answer": "そうし",
      "meaning": "mutual affection, mutual love"
    },
    {
      "question": "補体",
      "answer": "ほたい",
      "meaning": "complement (blood proteins)"
    },
    {
      "question": "平家蟹",
      "answer": "へいけがに",
      "meaning": "Heike crab"
    },
    {
      "question": "千千",
      "answer": "ちぢ",
      "meaning": "thousands, great number of, variety"
    },
    {
      "question": "力代",
      "answer": "ちからしろ",
      "meaning": "tax paid to avoid forced labor (ritsuryo period), tax in kind"
    },
    {
      "question": "利尿薬",
      "answer": "りにょうやく",
      "meaning": "diuretic"
    },
    {
      "question": "自然遺産",
      "answer": "しぜんいさん",
      "meaning": "natural heritage, natural heritage site"
    },
    {
      "question": "登舷礼",
      "answer": "とうげんれい",
      "meaning": "ceremonial assembling of a ship's crew on deck"
    },
    {
      "question": "口語文",
      "answer": "こうごぶん",
      "meaning": "colloquial writing, text written in a spoken form of the language"
    },
    {
      "question": "快打",
      "answer": "かいだ",
      "meaning": "clean hit"
    },
    {
      "question": "四分音符",
      "answer": "しぶおんぷ,しぶんおんぷ",
      "meaning": "quarter note, crotchet"
    },
    {
      "question": "取換える",
      "answer": "とりかえる",
      "meaning": "to exchange, to swap, to barter, to replace, to substitute"
    },
    {
      "question": "箱物行政",
      "answer": "はこものぎょうせい",
      "meaning": "government (public policy) focusing on the construction of public (community) buildings"
    },
    {
      "question": "擦寄る",
      "answer": "すりよる",
      "meaning": "to draw close to, to edge up to, to snuggle up to, to nestle close to, to cuddle with, to draw close"
    },
    {
      "question": "死文",
      "answer": "しぶん",
      "meaning": "dead letter, meaningless writing"
    },
    {
      "question": "截る",
      "answer": "きる",
      "meaning": "to cut (e.g. cloth)"
    },
    {
      "question": "認否",
      "answer": "にんぴ",
      "meaning": "approval or disapproval, admission or denial"
    },
    {
      "question": "華瓶",
      "answer": "けびょう",
      "meaning": "vase used to hold flower offerings (often made of gilded copper)"
    },
    {
      "question": "焼き金",
      "answer": "やきがね",
      "meaning": "branding iron"
    },
    {
      "question": "梨子地",
      "answer": "なしじ",
      "meaning": "nashiji (lacquering technique using gold or silver powder or flakes)"
    },
    {
      "question": "当用",
      "answer": "とうよう",
      "meaning": "present use, business in hand, necessary for the current time"
    },
    {
      "question": "機械編み",
      "answer": "きかいあみ",
      "meaning": "machine-woven, machine-knit"
    },
    {
      "question": "弓弭",
      "answer": "ゆみはず,ゆはず",
      "meaning": "nock (of a bow)"
    },
    {
      "question": "係り結び",
      "answer": "かかりむすび",
      "meaning": "connection, relation, linked form, bounded form"
    },
    {
      "question": "函嶺",
      "answer": "かんれい",
      "meaning": "the Hakone Mountains"
    },
    {
      "question": "藩庁",
      "answer": "はんちょう",
      "meaning": "domain administrative headquarters (early Meiji)"
    },
    {
      "question": "高層雲",
      "answer": "こうそううん",
      "meaning": "altostratus clouds"
    },
    {
      "question": "収差",
      "answer": "しゅうさ",
      "meaning": "aberration"
    },
    {
      "question": "牧野",
      "answer": "ぼくや",
      "meaning": "pasture land, ranch"
    },
    {
      "question": "臨済録",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "面輪",
      "answer": "おもわ",
      "meaning": "features"
    },
    {
      "question": "既遂",
      "answer": "きすい",
      "meaning": "already finished (action), already accomplished, committed (crime; as opposed to attempted), perpetr"
    },
    {
      "question": "花鳥画",
      "answer": "かちょうが",
      "meaning": "painting of flowers and birds, bird-and-flower genre in Chinese and Japanese painting"
    },
    {
      "question": "勇兵",
      "answer": "ゆうへい",
      "meaning": "brave soldier, brave warrior"
    },
    {
      "question": "会計年度",
      "answer": "かいけいねんど",
      "meaning": "fiscal year"
    },
    {
      "question": "転園",
      "answer": "てんえん",
      "meaning": "changing kindergartens, moving (an animal) to a different zoo"
    },
    {
      "question": "三々",
      "answer": "さんさん",
      "meaning": "3-3 point (in go)"
    },
    {
      "question": "石持",
      "answer": "いしもち",
      "meaning": "silver white croaker (Pennahia argentata), silver croaker, white croaker, Nibe croaker (Nibea mitsuk"
    },
    {
      "question": "半跏",
      "answer": "はんか",
      "meaning": "half lotus position (meditation posture), sitting with one foot placed on the opposite thigh"
    },
    {
      "question": "而も",
      "answer": "しかも",
      "meaning": "moreover, furthermore, nevertheless, and yet"
    },
    {
      "question": "国文科",
      "answer": "こくぶんか",
      "meaning": "department of Japanese literature"
    },
    {
      "question": "切り立て",
      "answer": "きりたて",
      "meaning": "freshly cut, freshly tailored, tree cut to specified length, especially for corners of a kemari cour"
    },
    {
      "question": "内状",
      "answer": "ないじょう",
      "meaning": "internal conditions, true state of affairs"
    },
    {
      "question": "監事",
      "answer": "かんじ",
      "meaning": "auditor, controller, comptroller, supervisor, inspector, manager"
    },
    {
      "question": "海嶺",
      "answer": "かいれい",
      "meaning": "(submarine) ridge"
    },
    {
      "question": "付け汁",
      "answer": "つけじる,つけしる",
      "meaning": "dipping sauce"
    },
    {
      "question": "本会",
      "answer": "ほんかい",
      "meaning": "formal meeting (committee, etc.), session, this (the aforementioned, our) association (society, orga"
    },
    {
      "question": "細胞質",
      "answer": "さいぼうしつ",
      "meaning": "cytoplasm"
    },
    {
      "question": "老い込む",
      "answer": "おいこむ",
      "meaning": "to grow old, to weaken with age, to become senile"
    },
    {
      "question": "全村",
      "answer": "ぜんそん",
      "meaning": "the whole village, all the villages (in an area)"
    },
    {
      "question": "鹹湖",
      "answer": "かんこ",
      "meaning": "salt lake, lagoon"
    },
    {
      "question": "様体",
      "answer": "ようだい,ようたい",
      "meaning": "condition, state (of health), appearance"
    },
    {
      "question": "旧稿",
      "answer": "きゅうこう",
      "meaning": "old manuscript"
    },
    {
      "question": "公有",
      "answer": "こうゆう",
      "meaning": "public ownership, public domain"
    },
    {
      "question": "イタ語",
      "answer": "イタご",
      "meaning": "Italian language (esp. as a school subject)"
    },
    {
      "question": "禁治産者",
      "answer": "きんちさんしゃ",
      "meaning": "(legally) incompetent individual"
    },
    {
      "question": "井戸側",
      "answer": "いどがわ",
      "meaning": "well curb"
    },
    {
      "question": "薪水",
      "answer": "しんすい",
      "meaning": "fuel and water, firewood and water, gathering firewood and drawing water, kitchen work, housework"
    },
    {
      "question": "親許",
      "answer": "おやもと",
      "meaning": "one's parents' home"
    },
    {
      "question": "子の日",
      "answer": "ねのひ,ねのび",
      "meaning": "day of the Rat (esp. the first day of the Rat in the New Year), collecting herbs and pulling out you"
    },
    {
      "question": "取皿",
      "answer": "とりざら",
      "meaning": "individual plate, single individual's small dish on which food taken from shared serving dishes is p"
    },
    {
      "question": "欺罔",
      "answer": "きもう,きぼう,ぎもう",
      "meaning": "deception, defrauding someone, fooling someone, swindling, false pretences"
    },
    {
      "question": "伊弉諾尊",
      "answer": "いざなぎのみこと,いざなきのみこと",
      "meaning": "Izanagi, male deity who fathered Japan and the sun, moon, and storm gods"
    },
    {
      "question": "詩劇",
      "answer": "しげき",
      "meaning": "drama in verse"
    },
    {
      "question": "低湿",
      "answer": "ていしつ",
      "meaning": "low and damp"
    },
    {
      "question": "輪奈",
      "answer": "わな",
      "meaning": "loop (of thread, string, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "尊卑",
      "answer": "そんぴ",
      "meaning": "high and low, aristocrat and plebeian"
    },
    {
      "question": "中農",
      "answer": "ちゅうのう",
      "meaning": "middle-class farmer"
    },
    {
      "question": "形態形成",
      "answer": "けいたいけいせい",
      "meaning": "morphogenesis"
    },
    {
      "question": "相する",
      "answer": "そうする",
      "meaning": "to assess (often one's fate)"
    },
    {
      "question": "辻強盗",
      "answer": "つじごうとう",
      "meaning": "highwayman"
    },
    {
      "question": "草莽",
      "answer": "そうもう,そうぼう",
      "meaning": "commoner, patriot, humble subject, late Edo period commoner opposition movement (mid-18th century to"
    },
    {
      "question": "漁猟",
      "answer": "ぎょりょう",
      "meaning": "fishing and hunting"
    },
    {
      "question": "文身",
      "answer": "ぶんしん,いれずみ",
      "meaning": "tattoo (esp. a traditional Japanese one), tattooing"
    },
    {
      "question": "嘖む",
      "answer": "さいなむ",
      "meaning": "to torment, to torture, to harass"
    },
    {
      "question": "附帯",
      "answer": "ふたい",
      "meaning": "incidental, ancillary, accessory, secondary, collateral"
    },
    {
      "question": "自然哲学",
      "answer": "しぜんてつがく",
      "meaning": "natural philosophy"
    },
    {
      "question": "引受け",
      "answer": "ひきうけ",
      "meaning": "undertaking, underwriting, acceptance"
    },
    {
      "question": "唯心的",
      "answer": "ゆいしんてき",
      "meaning": "spiritualistic"
    },
    {
      "question": "相会う",
      "answer": "あいあう",
      "meaning": "to meet one another"
    },
    {
      "question": "師僧",
      "answer": "しそう",
      "meaning": "priestly teacher"
    },
    {
      "question": "澳",
      "answer": "おき",
      "meaning": "open sea"
    },
    {
      "question": "生体膜",
      "answer": "せいたいまく",
      "meaning": "biological membrane, biomembrane"
    },
    {
      "question": "炷く",
      "answer": "たく",
      "meaning": "to burn (usu. incense)"
    },
    {
      "question": "反語法",
      "answer": "はんごほう",
      "meaning": "irony"
    },
    {
      "question": "道中記",
      "answer": "どうちゅうき",
      "meaning": "travel journal"
    },
    {
      "question": "干乾し",
      "answer": "ひぼし",
      "meaning": "starving"
    },
    {
      "question": "前号",
      "answer": "ぜんごう",
      "meaning": "preceding issue"
    },
    {
      "question": "閉息",
      "answer": "へいそく",
      "meaning": "bated breath, being cowed into silence"
    },
    {
      "question": "前撮り",
      "answer": "まえどり",
      "meaning": "taking pictures (for a wedding, etc.) prior to the event"
    },
    {
      "question": "標本化",
      "answer": "ひょうほんか",
      "meaning": "sampling (e.g. in signal processing)"
    },
    {
      "question": "前車",
      "answer": "ぜんしゃ",
      "meaning": "car in front, the car ahead, preceding car"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕事率",
      "answer": "しごとりつ",
      "meaning": "power"
    },
    {
      "question": "役夫",
      "answer": "えきふ",
      "meaning": "laborer, labourer"
    },
    {
      "question": "酢和え",
      "answer": "すあえ",
      "meaning": "dressing (vegetables, fish, etc.) with vinegar, vegetables (or fish, etc.) dressed with vinegar"
    },
    {
      "question": "蒼翠",
      "answer": "そうすい",
      "meaning": "blue-green, lush growth"
    },
    {
      "question": "雄蕊",
      "answer": "おしべ,ゆうずい",
      "meaning": "stamen"
    },
    {
      "question": "西ゴート",
      "answer": "にしゴート",
      "meaning": "Visigoth"
    },
    {
      "question": "人情噺",
      "answer": "にんじょうばなし",
      "meaning": "story about human nature or emotions (esp. rakugo), emotional rakugo story lacking a punch line"
    },
    {
      "question": "伝家",
      "answer": "でんか",
      "meaning": "heirloom, trump card, last resort, family tradition"
    },
    {
      "question": "米搗き",
      "answer": "こめつき",
      "meaning": "rice polishing"
    },
    {
      "question": "含浸",
      "answer": "がんしん",
      "meaning": "impregnation"
    },
    {
      "question": "酸化銅",
      "answer": "さんかどう",
      "meaning": "copper oxide (i.e. cuprous oxide, cupric oxide)"
    },
    {
      "question": "日脚",
      "answer": "ひあし",
      "meaning": "daytime, position of the Sun"
    },
    {
      "question": "裂肛",
      "answer": "れっこう",
      "meaning": "anal fissure"
    },
    {
      "question": "小屋根",
      "answer": "こやね",
      "meaning": "small roof (e.g. over the first storey of a building, a window, an attached shed or veranda, etc.),"
    },
    {
      "question": "単打",
      "answer": "たんだ",
      "meaning": "base hit, one-base hit, single"
    },
    {
      "question": "外航船",
      "answer": "がいこうせん",
      "meaning": "ocean-going ship"
    },
    {
      "question": "真筆",
      "answer": "しんぴつ",
      "meaning": "autograph, one's own handwriting, personal note"
    },
    {
      "question": "濫発",
      "answer": "らんぱつ",
      "meaning": "random firing, reckless firing, excessive issue"
    },
    {
      "question": "銑",
      "answer": "ずく",
      "meaning": "pig iron"
    },
    {
      "question": "書簡箋",
      "answer": "しょかんせん",
      "meaning": "letter paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "仮名文字",
      "answer": "かなもじ",
      "meaning": "the Japanese syllabary symbols"
    },
    {
      "question": "鳴管",
      "answer": "めいかん",
      "meaning": "syrinx (part of a bird), lower larynx"
    },
    {
      "question": "珍味佳肴",
      "answer": "ちんみかこう",
      "meaning": "rare delicacies, rare treat"
    },
    {
      "question": "独航船",
      "answer": "どっこうせん",
      "meaning": "independent fishing boat"
    },
    {
      "question": "雄株",
      "answer": "おかぶ",
      "meaning": "male plant"
    },
    {
      "question": "漁労",
      "answer": "ぎょろう",
      "meaning": "fishing, fishery"
    },
    {
      "question": "後件",
      "answer": "こうけん",
      "meaning": "consequent (in logic)"
    },
    {
      "question": "耕耘",
      "answer": "こううん",
      "meaning": "plowing and weeding, farming, cultivation, tillage"
    },
    {
      "question": "艙口",
      "answer": "そうこう",
      "meaning": "hatch, hatchway (ship)"
    },
    {
      "question": "迷信家",
      "answer": "めいしんか",
      "meaning": "superstitious person"
    },
    {
      "question": "塩魚",
      "answer": "しおざかな",
      "meaning": "salted fish"
    },
    {
      "question": "無塩",
      "answer": "むえん,ぶえん",
      "meaning": "salt free, no-salt, unsalted, raw fish, fresh fish, purity, naive person, ugly woman"
    },
    {
      "question": "授章",
      "answer": "じゅしょう",
      "meaning": "bestowing a decoration, bestowing an order"
    },
    {
      "question": "通信使",
      "answer": "つうしんし",
      "meaning": "Korean delegation to Japan (Edo period)"
    },
    {
      "question": "角帯",
      "answer": "かくおび",
      "meaning": "man's stiff sash"
    },
    {
      "question": "粘板岩",
      "answer": "ねんばんがん",
      "meaning": "clay rock, slate"
    },
    {
      "question": "鰓呼吸",
      "answer": "えらこきゅう",
      "meaning": "branchial respiration (breathing using gills)"
    },
    {
      "question": "連語",
      "answer": "れんご",
      "meaning": "compound word, phrase, collocation"
    },
    {
      "question": "国際放送",
      "answer": "こくさいほうそう",
      "meaning": "international broadcast(ing)"
    },
    {
      "question": "手箒",
      "answer": "てぼうき",
      "meaning": "whisk broom"
    },
    {
      "question": "箸枕",
      "answer": "はしまくら",
      "meaning": "chopstick rest"
    },
    {
      "question": "妙計",
      "answer": "みょうけい",
      "meaning": "ingenious trick, good idea, clever scheme"
    },
    {
      "question": "教会暦",
      "answer": "きょうかいれき",
      "meaning": "church calendar"
    },
    {
      "question": "潮焼け",
      "answer": "しおやけ",
      "meaning": "tanned by the sun and sea breezes"
    },
    {
      "question": "植物界",
      "answer": "しょくぶつかい",
      "meaning": "the plant kingdom, Plantae"
    },
    {
      "question": "旬間",
      "answer": "じゅんかん",
      "meaning": "period of ten days"
    },
    {
      "question": "仮名書き",
      "answer": "かながき",
      "meaning": "writing in kana, something written in kana"
    },
    {
      "question": "洗い晒し",
      "answer": "あらいざらし",
      "meaning": "faded from washing"
    },
    {
      "question": "未聞",
      "answer": "みもん",
      "meaning": "unheard"
    },
    {
      "question": "恐れ気",
      "answer": "おそれげ",
      "meaning": "fear, dread, fright"
    },
    {
      "question": "唐松",
      "answer": "からまつ",
      "meaning": "(Japanese) larch (Larix leptolepis, Larix kaempferi)"
    },
    {
      "question": "歩み足",
      "answer": "あゆみあし",
      "meaning": "ayumi-ashi, walking forwards or backwards with a sliding motion (kendo)"
    },
    {
      "question": "病舎",
      "answer": "びょうしゃ",
      "meaning": "hospital, infirmary, ward"
    },
    {
      "question": "詐り",
      "answer": "いつわり",
      "meaning": "lie, falsehood, fiction, fabrication"
    },
    {
      "question": "木構造",
      "answer": "きこうぞう",
      "meaning": "tree structure"
    },
    {
      "question": "殺陣師",
      "answer": "たてし",
      "meaning": "sword fight scene choreographer"
    },
    {
      "question": "陸相",
      "answer": "りくしょう",
      "meaning": "army minister"
    },
    {
      "question": "神灯",
      "answer": "しんとう",
      "meaning": "sacred light"
    },
    {
      "question": "藩王国",
      "answer": "はんおうこく",
      "meaning": "native state (of pre-independence India), princely state"
    },
    {
      "question": "祝い箸",
      "answer": "いわいばし",
      "meaning": "festive chopsticks, thick round chopsticks used on festive occasions"
    },
    {
      "question": "縁付ける",
      "answer": "えんづける",
      "meaning": "to marry off, to give in marriage"
    },
    {
      "question": "横雲",
      "answer": "よこぐも",
      "meaning": "wall or bank of clouds"
    },
    {
      "question": "靡かす",
      "answer": "なびかす",
      "meaning": "to seduce, to win over, to conquer"
    },
    {
      "question": "若隠居",
      "answer": "わかいんきょ",
      "meaning": "early retirement"
    },
    {
      "question": "連合政権",
      "answer": "れんごうせいけん",
      "meaning": "coalition government"
    },
    {
      "question": "重過失",
      "answer": "じゅうかしつ",
      "meaning": "gross negligence"
    },
    {
      "question": "理神論",
      "answer": "りしんろん",
      "meaning": "deism"
    },
    {
      "question": "一致点",
      "answer": "いっちてん",
      "meaning": "point of agreement"
    },
    {
      "question": "付合",
      "answer": "ふごう,つけあい",
      "meaning": "accession, linking poems"
    },
    {
      "question": "僧位",
      "answer": "そうい",
      "meaning": "rank (of a monk)"
    },
    {
      "question": "蠅頭",
      "answer": "ようとう",
      "meaning": "small characters, tiny handwriting, as small as the head of a fly, small profit"
    },
    {
      "question": "固定資産",
      "answer": "こていしさん",
      "meaning": "fixed assets"
    },
    {
      "question": "血液銀行",
      "answer": "けつえきぎんこう",
      "meaning": "blood bank"
    },
    {
      "question": "長歌",
      "answer": "ちょうか,ながうた",
      "meaning": "traditional Japanese poem with verses of five and seven morae repeated at least three times, usu. en"
    },
    {
      "question": "西蔵",
      "answer": "せいぞう",
      "meaning": "Tibet"
    },
    {
      "question": "池沼",
      "answer": "ちしょう",
      "meaning": "ponds and swamps, mentally-handicapped person"
    },
    {
      "question": "精霊会",
      "answer": "しょうりょうえ",
      "meaning": "Bon Festival, Buddhist service for the anniversary of the death of Prince Shōtoku (orig. the 22nd da"
    },
    {
      "question": "酸性紙",
      "answer": "さんせいし",
      "meaning": "acidic paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "間接話法",
      "answer": "かんせつわほう",
      "meaning": "indirect speech, indirect narration"
    },
    {
      "question": "営利主義",
      "answer": "えいりしゅぎ",
      "meaning": "commercialism"
    },
    {
      "question": "暮れ泥む",
      "answer": "くれなずむ",
      "meaning": "to grow dark slowly"
    },
    {
      "question": "校友",
      "answer": "こうゆう",
      "meaning": "schoolmate, alumnus"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷寒",
      "answer": "れいかん",
      "meaning": "cold, chilly"
    },
    {
      "question": "他律",
      "answer": "たりつ",
      "meaning": "heteronomy, subjection, subordination"
    },
    {
      "question": "金剛界",
      "answer": "こんごうかい",
      "meaning": "Vajradhatu, Diamond Realm, Vajradathu Mandala, Diamond Realm Mandala"
    },
    {
      "question": "胸間",
      "answer": "きょうかん",
      "meaning": "chest, breast"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜直",
      "answer": "やちょく",
      "meaning": "night duty, night shift"
    },
    {
      "question": "教学",
      "answer": "きょうがく",
      "meaning": "education and learning"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪因悪果",
      "answer": "あくいんあっか",
      "meaning": "sow evil and reap evil, evil acts bring evil outcomes"
    },
    {
      "question": "疝痛",
      "answer": "せんつう",
      "meaning": "colic, celialgia, enteralgia, gripes"
    },
    {
      "question": "防熱",
      "answer": "ぼうねつ",
      "meaning": "heat resistance"
    },
    {
      "question": "対話者",
      "answer": "たいわしゃ",
      "meaning": "interlocutor"
    },
    {
      "question": "流れ図",
      "answer": "ながれず",
      "meaning": "flowchart, flow diagram"
    },
    {
      "question": "熱帯気候",
      "answer": "ねったいきこう",
      "meaning": "tropical climate"
    },
    {
      "question": "性善",
      "answer": "せいぜん,しょうぜん",
      "meaning": "intrinsic goodness"
    },
    {
      "question": "裘",
      "answer": "かわごろも,けごろも",
      "meaning": "fur coat, fur coat (to protect against the cold), clothes made with the down of birds"
    },
    {
      "question": "譜表",
      "answer": "ふひょう",
      "meaning": "staff, stave, score"
    },
    {
      "question": "狂言綺語",
      "answer": "きょうげんきご,きょうげんきぎょ",
      "meaning": "make-believe fiction"
    },
    {
      "question": "月相",
      "answer": "げっそう",
      "meaning": "lunar phase, phase of the Moon"
    },
    {
      "question": "久田",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "医用",
      "answer": "いよう",
      "meaning": "medical use"
    },
    {
      "question": "蛸焼",
      "answer": "たこやき",
      "meaning": "takoyaki, octopus dumplings"
    },
    {
      "question": "胴囲",
      "answer": "どうい",
      "meaning": "waist, girth, measurement around waist"
    },
    {
      "question": "溶岩台地",
      "answer": "ようがんだいち",
      "meaning": "lava plateau"
    },
    {
      "question": "寒菊",
      "answer": "かんぎく",
      "meaning": "winter chrysanthemum (cultivar of Chrysanthemum indicum)"
    },
    {
      "question": "ジャガ芋",
      "answer": "ジャガいも",
      "meaning": "potato (Solanum tuberosum)"
    },
    {
      "question": "端を開く",
      "answer": "たんをひらく",
      "meaning": "to provide impetus"
    },
    {
      "question": "外寇",
      "answer": "がいこう",
      "meaning": "foreign invasion, foreign attack, foreign force"
    },
    {
      "question": "小難",
      "answer": "しょうなん",
      "meaning": "small misfortune"
    },
    {
      "question": "通産省",
      "answer": "つうさんしょう",
      "meaning": "(former) Ministry of International Trade and Industry (now Ministry of Economy, Trade and Industry),"
    },
    {
      "question": "徒手体操",
      "answer": "としゅたいそう",
      "meaning": "free-standing exercises, calisthenics (performed without using any apparatus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "相互主義",
      "answer": "そうごしゅぎ",
      "meaning": "principle of reciprocity"
    },
    {
      "question": "補巻",
      "answer": "ほかん",
      "meaning": "supplement, supplementary volume"
    },
    {
      "question": "豌豆",
      "answer": "えんどう",
      "meaning": "green peas"
    },
    {
      "question": "形姿",
      "answer": "なりすがた",
      "meaning": "appearance, clothing, costume, dress"
    },
    {
      "question": "性腺",
      "answer": "せいせん",
      "meaning": "gonad, sexual gland"
    },
    {
      "question": "水蚤",
      "answer": "みじんこ",
      "meaning": "water flea (Daphnia spp.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "截断",
      "answer": "せつだん,さいだん",
      "meaning": "cutting, severance, section, amputation, disconnection"
    },
    {
      "question": "単糖類",
      "answer": "たんとうるい",
      "meaning": "monosaccharides"
    },
    {
      "question": "遣り直し",
      "answer": "やりなおし",
      "meaning": "redoing"
    },
    {
      "question": "入京",
      "answer": "にゅうきょう",
      "meaning": "entering the capital, entering Tokyo"
    },
    {
      "question": "付け出す",
      "answer": "つけだす",
      "meaning": "to charge"
    },
    {
      "question": "陽春",
      "answer": "ようしゅん",
      "meaning": "spring, the springtime"
    },
    {
      "question": "弊風",
      "answer": "へいふう",
      "meaning": "evil or corrupt or abusive practice"
    },
    {
      "question": "大鋸屑",
      "answer": "おがくず",
      "meaning": "sawdust"
    },
    {
      "question": "突っ掛け",
      "answer": "つっかけ",
      "meaning": "slip-on shoe"
    },
    {
      "question": "踏査",
      "answer": "とうさ",
      "meaning": "survey, exploration, field investigation"
    },
    {
      "question": "世界銀行",
      "answer": "せかいぎんこう",
      "meaning": "World Bank"
    },
    {
      "question": "丈六",
      "answer": "じょうろく",
      "meaning": "one jō and six shaku (4.85m), statue of Buddha measuring one jō and six shaku, sitting cross-legged"
    },
    {
      "question": "地利",
      "answer": "ちり,じり",
      "meaning": "locational advantage, advantageous position, products from the land (farm output, timber, minerals,"
    },
    {
      "question": "浪曲",
      "answer": "ろうきょく",
      "meaning": "rōkyoku, naniwabushi, recitation of stories accompanied by samisen"
    },
    {
      "question": "浴後",
      "answer": "よくご",
      "meaning": "after bathing"
    },
    {
      "question": "当所",
      "answer": "とうしょ",
      "meaning": "this place, this office"
    },
    {
      "question": "熔接",
      "answer": "ようせつ",
      "meaning": "weld, welding"
    },
    {
      "question": "懶",
      "answer": "ものぐさ",
      "meaning": "laziness, lazy person"
    },
    {
      "question": "弱震",
      "answer": "じゃくしん",
      "meaning": "mild earthquake"
    },
    {
      "question": "介意",
      "answer": "かいい",
      "meaning": "worrying about, caring about"
    },
    {
      "question": "近郷",
      "answer": "きんごう",
      "meaning": "neighboring districts, neighbouring districts, countryside"
    },
    {
      "question": "椀種",
      "answer": "わんだね",
      "meaning": "soup ingredients (esp. seafood, tofu, egg)"
    },
    {
      "question": "嚔",
      "answer": "くしゃみ,くさめ,くっさめ",
      "meaning": "sneeze, spoken twice in response to someone sneezing as a charm against an early death"
    },
    {
      "question": "稲束",
      "answer": "いなづか",
      "meaning": "sheaf of rice, bundle of rice plants"
    },
    {
      "question": "耳コピー",
      "answer": "みみコピー",
      "meaning": "playing (music) by ear, transcribing (music) by ear"
    },
    {
      "question": "生活年齢",
      "answer": "せいかつねんれい",
      "meaning": "chronological age"
    },
    {
      "question": "百科全書",
      "answer": "ひゃっかぜんしょ",
      "meaning": "encyclopedia, Encyclopedie universelle des arts et sciences (Diderot)"
    },
    {
      "question": "胚乳",
      "answer": "はいにゅう",
      "meaning": "albumen (of a seed, esp. the endosperm)"
    },
    {
      "question": "後胤",
      "answer": "こういん",
      "meaning": "descendant, scion"
    },
    {
      "question": "謹白",
      "answer": "きんぱく",
      "meaning": "Dear Sir or Madam, Dear Sirs, Gentlemen"
    },
    {
      "question": "液体空気",
      "answer": "えきたいくうき",
      "meaning": "liquid air"
    },
    {
      "question": "瘋癲",
      "answer": "ふうてん",
      "meaning": "insanity, insane person, vagabond, wanderer"
    },
    {
      "question": "交戦者",
      "answer": "こうせんしゃ",
      "meaning": "combatant, interested party in warfare, warring nation, belligerent"
    },
    {
      "question": "風力計",
      "answer": "ふうりょくけい",
      "meaning": "anemometer, wind gauge"
    },
    {
      "question": "月球儀",
      "answer": "げっきゅうぎ",
      "meaning": "moon globe"
    },
    {
      "question": "鋲釘",
      "answer": "びょうくぎ",
      "meaning": "rivet, tack, thumbtack, drawing-pin, hobnail"
    },
    {
      "question": "車庫証明",
      "answer": "しゃこしょうめい",
      "meaning": "parking space certificate (sometimes required for car ownership)"
    },
    {
      "question": "葉身",
      "answer": "ようしん",
      "meaning": "leaf blade"
    },
    {
      "question": "櫛目",
      "answer": "くしめ",
      "meaning": "(sign of) combing, comb pattern (esp. pottery)"
    },
    {
      "question": "代作",
      "answer": "だいさく",
      "meaning": "ghost-writing"
    },
    {
      "question": "常夜鍋",
      "answer": "じょうやなべ,じょうよなべ,とこやなべ",
      "meaning": "shabu-shabu-like hotpot dish with pork, spinach, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "所説",
      "answer": "しょせつ",
      "meaning": "explanation, matter under discussion, contents, one's opinion"
    },
    {
      "question": "人怖じ",
      "answer": "ひとおじ",
      "meaning": "bashfulness before strangers"
    },
    {
      "question": "固有値",
      "answer": "こゆうち",
      "meaning": "eigenvalue"
    },
    {
      "question": "椿餅",
      "answer": "つばいもちい,つばきもち,つばいもち",
      "meaning": "rice-cake sweet sandwiched between two camellia leaves"
    },
    {
      "question": "和机",
      "answer": "わづくえ",
      "meaning": "Japanese-style desk (short, used while sitting on the floor)"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷感症",
      "answer": "れいかんしょう",
      "meaning": "female sexual arousal disorder, FSAD, anaphrodisia, hyphedonia, frigidity"
    },
    {
      "question": "末社",
      "answer": "まっしゃ",
      "meaning": "subordinate shrine, professional entertainer"
    },
    {
      "question": "本歌",
      "answer": "ほんか,もとうた",
      "meaning": "original verse poem"
    },
    {
      "question": "朧夜",
      "answer": "おぼろよ",
      "meaning": "misty, moonlit night"
    },
    {
      "question": "褒詞",
      "answer": "ほうし",
      "meaning": "praise, eulogy"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤鉄鉱",
      "answer": "せきてっこう",
      "meaning": "hematite"
    },
    {
      "question": "リンパ液",
      "answer": "リンパえき",
      "meaning": "lymph fluid"
    },
    {
      "question": "草屋",
      "answer": "そうおく,くさや",
      "meaning": "thatched hut"
    },
    {
      "question": "氏姓制度",
      "answer": "しせいせいど",
      "meaning": "uji-kabane system, system of clans and hereditary titles (of the Yamato court)"
    },
    {
      "question": "機業",
      "answer": "きぎょう",
      "meaning": "weaving industry, textile industry"
    },
    {
      "question": "刀背",
      "answer": "とうはい,むね",
      "meaning": "back of a sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "簓",
      "answer": "ささら",
      "meaning": "bamboo whisk"
    },
    {
      "question": "秋高",
      "answer": "あきだか",
      "meaning": "increased rice prices in autumn due to a poor harvest, good autumn rice harvest"
    },
    {
      "question": "雛僧",
      "answer": "すうそう",
      "meaning": "young priest"
    },
    {
      "question": "悄気返る",
      "answer": "しょげかえる",
      "meaning": "to be dispirited, to be dejected, to lose heart, to become discouraged, to be crestfallen, to be utt"
    },
    {
      "question": "家構え",
      "answer": "いえがまえ",
      "meaning": "appearance or style of a house"
    },
    {
      "question": "大知",
      "answer": "たいち,だいち",
      "meaning": "supreme wisdom, sage"
    },
    {
      "question": "棒々鶏",
      "answer": "バンバンジー",
      "meaning": "bang bang chicken (Szechuan dish of chicken in a spicy sauce)"
    },
    {
      "question": "弓懸",
      "answer": "ゆがけ",
      "meaning": "archer's glove (with a groove for pulling the string)"
    },
    {
      "question": "撚糸",
      "answer": "ねんし,よりいと",
      "meaning": "twisted thread or yarn, twining of thread or yarn, twisting (thread, etc.), twisted yarn, twisted th"
    },
    {
      "question": "雅称",
      "answer": "がしょう",
      "meaning": "elegant name, alias, pseudonym, pen name, nom de plume"
    },
    {
      "question": "大所高所",
      "answer": "たいしょこうしょ",
      "meaning": "broad perspective"
    },
    {
      "question": "糸偏",
      "answer": "いとへん",
      "meaning": "kanji 'thread' radical at left, textile industry"
    },
    {
      "question": "蛔虫",
      "answer": "かいちゅう",
      "meaning": "roundworm (Ascaris lumbricoides), mawworm, intestinal worm"
    },
    {
      "question": "文化住宅",
      "answer": "ぶんかじゅうたく",
      "meaning": "semi-European-style house, type of Japanese house incorporating Western elements that was made popul"
    },
    {
      "question": "勝ち栗",
      "answer": "かちぐり",
      "meaning": "dried chestnut"
    },
    {
      "question": "たんぽ槍",
      "answer": "たんぽやり",
      "meaning": "padded spear (for practice)"
    },
    {
      "question": "腔腸動物",
      "answer": "こうちょうどうぶつ,くうちょうどうぶつ",
      "meaning": "coelenterate"
    },
    {
      "question": "金扇",
      "answer": "きんせん",
      "meaning": "gilded folding fan"
    },
    {
      "question": "密売買",
      "answer": "みつばいばい",
      "meaning": "illicit traffic, contraband"
    },
    {
      "question": "平仄",
      "answer": "ひょうそく",
      "meaning": "meter (in Chinese poetry), consistency"
    },
    {
      "question": "二八蕎麦",
      "answer": "にはちそば",
      "meaning": "soba made with two parts wheat flour to eight parts buckwheat flour"
    },
    {
      "question": "引用符",
      "answer": "いんようふ",
      "meaning": "quotation marks, quote marks"
    },
    {
      "question": "地震津波",
      "answer": "じしんつなみ",
      "meaning": "tsunami (caused by an earthquake)"
    },
    {
      "question": "版下",
      "answer": "はんした",
      "meaning": "artwork, block copy, paste-up"
    },
    {
      "question": "大犬座",
      "answer": "おおいぬざ",
      "meaning": "Canis Major (constellation), the Greater Dog"
    },
    {
      "question": "白化現象",
      "answer": "はっかげんしょう,はくかげんしょう",
      "meaning": "albinism, chlorosis, bleaching (of coral)"
    },
    {
      "question": "常世の国",
      "answer": "とこよのくに",
      "meaning": "distant country, heaven, hades"
    },
    {
      "question": "擬人法",
      "answer": "ぎしんほう,ぎじんほう",
      "meaning": "personification"
    },
    {
      "question": "西洋紙",
      "answer": "せいようし",
      "meaning": "(western) paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "並み足",
      "answer": "なみあし",
      "meaning": "walking pace, slow march"
    },
    {
      "question": "喬木",
      "answer": "きょうぼく",
      "meaning": "tall tree, forest tree, arbor, arbour"
    },
    {
      "question": "用達",
      "answer": "ようたし,ようたつ",
      "meaning": "running errands, going on errands, (transaction of) business, going about one's business, doing one'"
    },
    {
      "question": "交通遺児",
      "answer": "こうつういじ",
      "meaning": "child orphaned from a traffic accident"
    },
    {
      "question": "宗教音楽",
      "answer": "しゅうきょうおんがく",
      "meaning": "religious music"
    },
    {
      "question": "消除",
      "answer": "しょうじょ",
      "meaning": "deletion, removal, elimination, erasure, cancellation, revocation"
    },
    {
      "question": "大島紬",
      "answer": "おおしまつむぎ",
      "meaning": "Oshima tsumugi weave, type of pongee from Oshima"
    },
    {
      "question": "注文生産",
      "answer": "ちゅうもんせいさん",
      "meaning": "made-to-order production, job order production, production to order"
    },
    {
      "question": "尻が重い",
      "answer": "しりがおもい",
      "meaning": "lazy, indolent, reluctant to get up off one's backside, clumsy"
    },
    {
      "question": "保元",
      "answer": "ほうげん,ほげん",
      "meaning": "Hōgen era (1156.4.27-1159.4.20), Hogen era"
    },
    {
      "question": "万世一系",
      "answer": "ばんせいいっけい",
      "meaning": "unbroken imperial line"
    },
    {
      "question": "中締め",
      "answer": "なかじめ",
      "meaning": "closing mid-way, taking a break mid-way through an event, sometimes with ceremonial hand-clapping"
    },
    {
      "question": "年忌",
      "answer": "ねんき",
      "meaning": "death anniversary, Buddhist anniversary service"
    },
    {
      "question": "瞳孔反射",
      "answer": "どうこうはんしゃ",
      "meaning": "pupillary reflex"
    },
    {
      "question": "如法暗夜",
      "answer": "にょほうあんや",
      "meaning": "total (utter) darkness"
    },
    {
      "question": "植樹祭",
      "answer": "しょくじゅさい",
      "meaning": "tree-planting ceremony, Arbor Day"
    },
    {
      "question": "安定器",
      "answer": "あんていき",
      "meaning": "stabilizer, stabiliser, electrical ballast (e.g. fluorescent light)"
    },
    {
      "question": "導電率",
      "answer": "どうでんりつ",
      "meaning": "conductivity"
    },
    {
      "question": "白燐",
      "answer": "はくりん",
      "meaning": "white phosphorus"
    },
    {
      "question": "斫る",
      "answer": "はつる",
      "meaning": "to shave off (esp. concrete), to take a percentage, to take a cut"
    },
    {
      "question": "家父",
      "answer": "かふ",
      "meaning": "one's father"
    },
    {
      "question": "電磁界",
      "answer": "でんじかい",
      "meaning": "electromagnetic field"
    },
    {
      "question": "世俗化",
      "answer": "せぞくか",
      "meaning": "secularization, secularisation, popularization, popularisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "来局",
      "answer": "らいきょく",
      "meaning": "coming to a post office, broadcasting station, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "肺浸潤",
      "answer": "はいしんじゅん",
      "meaning": "pulmonary infiltration, infiltration of the lungs"
    },
    {
      "question": "交通巡査",
      "answer": "こうつうじゅんさ",
      "meaning": "traffic officer"
    },
    {
      "question": "表意",
      "answer": "ひょうい",
      "meaning": "expressing one's intent, gesture, ideography"
    },
    {
      "question": "剛猛",
      "answer": "ごうもう",
      "meaning": "strongly ferocious"
    },
    {
      "question": "驢",
      "answer": "うさぎうま,ろ",
      "meaning": "donkey"
    },
    {
      "question": "一竿",
      "answer": "いっかん",
      "meaning": "one pole (esp. used for fishing poles), one rod"
    },
    {
      "question": "受益者",
      "answer": "じゅえきしゃ",
      "meaning": "beneficiary"
    },
    {
      "question": "速達郵便",
      "answer": "そくたつゆうびん",
      "meaning": "special delivery mail, express delivery post"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭頂葉",
      "answer": "とうちょうよう",
      "meaning": "parietal lobe"
    },
    {
      "question": "美辞",
      "answer": "びじ",
      "meaning": "flowery language, pretty words"
    },
    {
      "question": "謁する",
      "answer": "えっする",
      "meaning": "to have an audience with"
    },
    {
      "question": "空き屋敷",
      "answer": "あきやしき",
      "meaning": "empty residence, empty estate, empty lot"
    },
    {
      "question": "全山",
      "answer": "ぜんざん",
      "meaning": "the whole mountain"
    },
    {
      "question": "千日紅",
      "answer": "せんにちこう",
      "meaning": "globe amaranth"
    },
    {
      "question": "指嗾",
      "answer": "しそう,しぞく",
      "meaning": "instigation"
    },
    {
      "question": "高殿",
      "answer": "たかどの",
      "meaning": "stately mansion"
    },
    {
      "question": "蚤取り",
      "answer": "のみとり",
      "meaning": "flea powder, flea medicine, flea medication, getting rid of fleas, killing fleas"
    },
    {
      "question": "変形菌",
      "answer": "へんけいきん",
      "meaning": "myxomycete, slime mold"
    },
    {
      "question": "和楽",
      "answer": "わがく,わらく",
      "meaning": "Japanese music, peace and harmony"
    },
    {
      "question": "伊達者",
      "answer": "だてしゃ",
      "meaning": "dandy, dude"
    },
    {
      "question": "六波羅蜜",
      "answer": "ろくはらみつ,ろっぱらみつ",
      "meaning": "the six virtues (perfections) a Buddha elect practices to attain supreme enlightenment"
    },
    {
      "question": "罪責",
      "answer": "ざいせき",
      "meaning": "responsibility or liability for a crime"
    },
    {
      "question": "御握り",
      "answer": "おにぎり",
      "meaning": "onigiri, rice ball (often triangular, sometimes with a filling and wrapped in nori)"
    },
    {
      "question": "清老頭",
      "answer": "チンラオトウ",
      "meaning": "all terminals, winning hand consisting of only ones and nines as pungs or kongs plus a pair"
    },
    {
      "question": "豆油",
      "answer": "まめあぶら,ご",
      "meaning": "soybean oil, go, soy beans soaked and mashed to a creamy paste (ingredient of tofu and soy milk)"
    },
    {
      "question": "割り付け",
      "answer": "わりつけ",
      "meaning": "allotment, assignment, allocation, distribution, layout, editing"
    },
    {
      "question": "張板",
      "answer": "はりいた",
      "meaning": "plank used to dry wet clothes or paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "唐破風",
      "answer": "からはふ",
      "meaning": "karahafu, bow-shaped eaves of a gabled roof, undulating gable, cusped gable"
    },
    {
      "question": "尻を捲る",
      "answer": "しりをまくる,けつをまくる",
      "meaning": "to suddenly assume an antagonistic attitude, to suddenly become defiant, to turn aggressive (in one'"
    },
    {
      "question": "草競馬",
      "answer": "くさけいば",
      "meaning": "local horse race"
    },
    {
      "question": "乳酸飲料",
      "answer": "にゅうさんいんりょう",
      "meaning": "lactic-acid drink"
    },
    {
      "question": "本則",
      "answer": "ほんそく",
      "meaning": "rules, original rules"
    },
    {
      "question": "止し",
      "answer": "さし,よし",
      "meaning": "stopped in the midst of, half- (i.e. half-read), quitting, ceasing, giving up"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍荼利",
      "answer": "ぐんだり",
      "meaning": "Kundali (tantric Buddhist deity)"
    },
    {
      "question": "蓋然的",
      "answer": "がいぜんてき",
      "meaning": "probable, likely"
    },
    {
      "question": "八咫の鏡",
      "answer": "やたのかがみ",
      "meaning": "Yata no Kagami (the eight-span mirror; one of the Imperial regalia)"
    },
    {
      "question": "自作農",
      "answer": "じさくのう",
      "meaning": "landed farmer, owner farmer"
    },
    {
      "question": "複屈折",
      "answer": "ふくくっせつ",
      "meaning": "double refraction, birefringence"
    },
    {
      "question": "暦年",
      "answer": "れきねん",
      "meaning": "calendar year, civil year, time, year after year"
    },
    {
      "question": "平曲",
      "answer": "へいきょく",
      "meaning": "chanting of the Heike Monogatari to biwa accompaniment"
    },
    {
      "question": "浄書",
      "answer": "じょうしょ",
      "meaning": "fair copy, clean copy"
    },
    {
      "question": "遺徳",
      "answer": "いとく",
      "meaning": "benefit from ancestors' virtue"
    },
    {
      "question": "御手元",
      "answer": "おてもと",
      "meaning": "chopsticks"
    },
    {
      "question": "五音",
      "answer": "ごいん,ごおん",
      "meaning": "pentatonic scale"
    },
    {
      "question": "巫祝",
      "answer": "ふしゅく",
      "meaning": "shrine maiden, ancient priest"
    },
    {
      "question": "復姓",
      "answer": "ふくせい",
      "meaning": "reverting to one's original family name, reverting to one's maiden name"
    },
    {
      "question": "前カノ",
      "answer": "まえカノ",
      "meaning": "former girlfriend, ex-girlfriend"
    },
    {
      "question": "閻羅王",
      "answer": "えんらおう",
      "meaning": "Yama (king of the world of the dead, who judges the dead), Emma, Yan, Yomna"
    },
    {
      "question": "残痕",
      "answer": "ざんこん",
      "meaning": "vestige, scar"
    },
    {
      "question": "打ち刀",
      "answer": "うちがたな",
      "meaning": "katana (sword worn on the hip edge up by samurai)"
    },
    {
      "question": "出花",
      "answer": "でばな",
      "meaning": "first brew of tea"
    },
    {
      "question": "約諾",
      "answer": "やくだく",
      "meaning": "agreement, promise"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜尿症",
      "answer": "やにょうしょう",
      "meaning": "bed-wetting, enuresis"
    },
    {
      "question": "中足骨",
      "answer": "ちゅうそっこつ,ちゅうそくこつ",
      "meaning": "metatarsal"
    },
    {
      "question": "姦婦",
      "answer": "かんぷ",
      "meaning": "adulteress"
    },
    {
      "question": "創痕",
      "answer": "そうこん",
      "meaning": "scar"
    },
    {
      "question": "甲骨文字",
      "answer": "こうこつもじ",
      "meaning": "oracle bone script"
    },
    {
      "question": "普通名詞",
      "answer": "ふつうめいし",
      "meaning": "common noun"
    },
    {
      "question": "豆汁",
      "answer": "とうじゅう,ご",
      "meaning": "mung bean milk, douzhi, go, soy beans soaked and mashed to a creamy paste (ingredient of tofu and so"
    },
    {
      "question": "傅育",
      "answer": "ふいく",
      "meaning": "bringing up, tuition"
    },
    {
      "question": "分子式",
      "answer": "ぶんししき",
      "meaning": "molecular formula"
    },
    {
      "question": "火手",
      "answer": "かしゅ",
      "meaning": "stoker"
    },
    {
      "question": "半農半漁",
      "answer": "はんのうはんぎょ",
      "meaning": "half-agricultural and half-fishing (village or economy)"
    },
    {
      "question": "鬢付け油",
      "answer": "びんつけあぶら",
      "meaning": "pomade, pomatum, hair oil"
    },
    {
      "question": "虫卵",
      "answer": "ちゅうらん",
      "meaning": "insect egg, insect eggs, parasite egg, parasite eggs"
    },
    {
      "question": "地蔵盆",
      "answer": "じぞうぼん",
      "meaning": "Jizo Festival (child-focused religious festival, in which Jizo statues are decorated, esp. in Kyoto;"
    },
    {
      "question": "白頭鷲",
      "answer": "はくとうわし",
      "meaning": "bald eagle (Haliaeetus leucocephalus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "労働運動",
      "answer": "ろうどううんどう",
      "meaning": "labour movement, labor movement"
    },
    {
      "question": "叺",
      "answer": "かます",
      "meaning": "straw bag"
    },
    {
      "question": "オック語",
      "answer": "オックご",
      "meaning": "langue d'oc, Occitan"
    },
    {
      "question": "簡易書留",
      "answer": "かんいかきとめ",
      "meaning": "simplified registered mail, recorded delivery"
    },
    {
      "question": "末節",
      "answer": "まっせつ",
      "meaning": "minor details, nonessentials"
    },
    {
      "question": "閑居",
      "answer": "かんきょ",
      "meaning": "quiet and secluded life, quiet retreat, idle life"
    },
    {
      "question": "約物",
      "answer": "やくもの",
      "meaning": "punctuation marks and other special symbols"
    },
    {
      "question": "勧進相撲",
      "answer": "かんじんずもう",
      "meaning": "fund-raising tournaments of Edo period"
    },
    {
      "question": "統覚",
      "answer": "とうかく",
      "meaning": "apperception"
    },
    {
      "question": "疎密波",
      "answer": "そみつは",
      "meaning": "compressional wave, longitudinal wave, dilatational wave, wave of condensation and rarefaction"
    },
    {
      "question": "鹹味",
      "answer": "かんみ",
      "meaning": "saltiness"
    },
    {
      "question": "金力",
      "answer": "きんりょく",
      "meaning": "monetary power"
    },
    {
      "question": "攀じる",
      "answer": "よじる",
      "meaning": "to clamber (up), to scale"
    },
    {
      "question": "空腸",
      "answer": "くうちょう",
      "meaning": "jejunum"
    },
    {
      "question": "未病",
      "answer": "みびょう",
      "meaning": "ill health before symptoms appear, presymptomatic, pre-symptomatic"
    },
    {
      "question": "葵祭",
      "answer": "あおいまつり",
      "meaning": "Aoi Festival (Kyoto, May 15), Aoi Matsuri"
    },
    {
      "question": "回船",
      "answer": "かいせん",
      "meaning": "lighter, (small) cargo vessel"
    },
    {
      "question": "内濠",
      "answer": "うちぼり",
      "meaning": "inner moat, moat within the castle walls"
    },
    {
      "question": "放射相称",
      "answer": "ほうしゃそうしょう",
      "meaning": "radial symmetry"
    },
    {
      "question": "都有",
      "answer": "とゆう",
      "meaning": "being owned by the Tokyo metropolitan government"
    },
    {
      "question": "塞栓",
      "answer": "そくせん",
      "meaning": "embolus, abnormal substance (i.e. air) circulating in the blood"
    },
    {
      "question": "漬く",
      "answer": "つく",
      "meaning": "to be immersed, to be pickled"
    },
    {
      "question": "紅樹",
      "answer": "ひるぎ,こうじゅ",
      "meaning": "mangrove (of family Rhizophoraceae), mangrove (esp. the black mangrove, Bruguiera gymnorrhiza), tree"
    },
    {
      "question": "遑",
      "answer": "いとま",
      "meaning": "spare time, free time, leisure, time off, day off, vacation, holiday, leave, quitting (one's job), f"
    },
    {
      "question": "自主管理",
      "answer": "じしゅかんり",
      "meaning": "self-management, self-imposed control"
    },
    {
      "question": "情態",
      "answer": "じょうたい",
      "meaning": "state, condition, situation, appearance, circumstances"
    },
    {
      "question": "御仕舞",
      "answer": "おしまい",
      "meaning": "the end, closing, being done for, that's it, that's enough, that's all"
    },
    {
      "question": "目見え",
      "answer": "めみえ",
      "meaning": "interview, stage debut, first appearance, meeting, trial for a servant"
    },
    {
      "question": "合成酒",
      "answer": "ごうせいしゅ",
      "meaning": "synthetic sake"
    },
    {
      "question": "五奉行",
      "answer": "ごぶぎょう",
      "meaning": "the five commissioners (administrative organ of feudal Japan established by Toyotomi Hideyoshi)"
    },
    {
      "question": "忠霊",
      "answer": "ちゅうれい",
      "meaning": "the loyal dead"
    },
    {
      "question": "題号",
      "answer": "だいごう",
      "meaning": "title"
    },
    {
      "question": "枝折",
      "answer": "しおり",
      "meaning": "bookmark, guidebook"
    },
    {
      "question": "斉一",
      "answer": "せいいつ",
      "meaning": "uniformity, equality"
    },
    {
      "question": "有声",
      "answer": "ゆうせい",
      "meaning": "voiced, vocal"
    },
    {
      "question": "賢愚",
      "answer": "けんぐ",
      "meaning": "the wise and the foolish"
    },
    {
      "question": "樹影",
      "answer": "じゅえい",
      "meaning": "shadow of a tree"
    },
    {
      "question": "吸煙",
      "answer": "きゅうえん",
      "meaning": "smoking"
    },
    {
      "question": "襟腰",
      "answer": "えりこし",
      "meaning": "height of the neck"
    },
    {
      "question": "石炭紀",
      "answer": "せきたんき",
      "meaning": "the Carboniferous Period"
    },
    {
      "question": "川越し",
      "answer": "かわごし",
      "meaning": "crossing a river"
    },
    {
      "question": "浮説",
      "answer": "ふせつ",
      "meaning": "groundless rumor, groundless rumour"
    },
    {
      "question": "希書",
      "answer": "きしょ",
      "meaning": "rare book"
    },
    {
      "question": "本元",
      "answer": "ほんもと",
      "meaning": "origin, main branch of family"
    },
    {
      "question": "児童手当",
      "answer": "じどうてあて",
      "meaning": "child-rearing assistance, support for young parents, child-care allowance"
    },
    {
      "question": "理事国",
      "answer": "りじこく",
      "meaning": "member country of the executive committee in an international organization (organisation)"
    },
    {
      "question": "金属工業",
      "answer": "きんぞくこうぎょう",
      "meaning": "metalworking industry"
    },
    {
      "question": "埋め草",
      "answer": "うめくさ",
      "meaning": "(page) filler"
    },
    {
      "question": "貴店",
      "answer": "きてん",
      "meaning": "your store, your shop"
    },
    {
      "question": "一夫一婦",
      "answer": "いっぷいっぷ",
      "meaning": "monogamy"
    },
    {
      "question": "恋着",
      "answer": "れんちゃく",
      "meaning": "attachment, love"
    },
    {
      "question": "重連",
      "answer": "じゅうれん",
      "meaning": "double heading (using two locomotives at the front of a train), double-headed train, doubleheader"
    },
    {
      "question": "准看護師",
      "answer": "じゅんかんごし",
      "meaning": "assistant nurse, practical nurse"
    },
    {
      "question": "同君連合",
      "answer": "どうくんれんごう",
      "meaning": "alliance of two countries or more under one ruler"
    },
    {
      "question": "鷺草",
      "answer": "さぎそう",
      "meaning": "fringed orchid (Pecteilis radiata), white egret flower, sagiso"
    },
    {
      "question": "組み重",
      "answer": "くみじゅう",
      "meaning": "nest of lacquer boxes"
    },
    {
      "question": "行き戻り",
      "answer": "ゆきもどり",
      "meaning": "going and returning, divorced woman"
    },
    {
      "question": "宮刑",
      "answer": "きゅうけい",
      "meaning": "ancient Chinese punishment (castration for men, confinement for women)"
    },
    {
      "question": "低糖",
      "answer": "ていとう",
      "meaning": "low-sugar"
    },
    {
      "question": "南斗六星",
      "answer": "なんとろくせい",
      "meaning": "Milk Dipper, southern dipper asterism (star pattern) within Sagittarius"
    },
    {
      "question": "交々",
      "answer": "こもごも",
      "meaning": "alternately, in succession"
    },
    {
      "question": "鈍才",
      "answer": "どんさい",
      "meaning": "stupidity, dull person, dullness"
    },
    {
      "question": "筆癖",
      "answer": "ふでくせ,ふでぐせ",
      "meaning": "habits of handwriting, handwriting idiosyncrasies, style of writing, style of painting"
    },
    {
      "question": "脊髄炎",
      "answer": "せきずいえん",
      "meaning": "myelitis"
    },
    {
      "question": "釣り天井",
      "answer": "つりてんじょう",
      "meaning": "suspended ceiling"
    },
    {
      "question": "白質",
      "answer": "はくしつ",
      "meaning": "white matter (e.g. in the brain), substantia alba"
    },
    {
      "question": "下前",
      "answer": "したまえ",
      "meaning": "part of the fabric that is tucked closest to the skin when wearing a garment that is wrapped in fron"
    },
    {
      "question": "歳星",
      "answer": "さいせい",
      "meaning": "Jupiter"
    },
    {
      "question": "七子",
      "answer": "ななこ",
      "meaning": "decorating a metal surface with small dots resembling fish eggs, twill weave, basket weave"
    },
    {
      "question": "依命",
      "answer": "いめい",
      "meaning": "by order (of a superior), as instructed, official (e.g. notification)"
    },
    {
      "question": "セーム革",
      "answer": "セームがわ",
      "meaning": "chamois leather"
    },
    {
      "question": "古謡",
      "answer": "こよう",
      "meaning": "traditional (folk) song"
    },
    {
      "question": "羽団扇",
      "answer": "はうちわ",
      "meaning": "Japanese fan made of feathers"
    },
    {
      "question": "盛時",
      "answer": "せいじ",
      "meaning": "prime of life, era of national prosperity"
    },
    {
      "question": "直接選挙",
      "answer": "ちょくせつせんきょ",
      "meaning": "direct election"
    },
    {
      "question": "柑子",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "僧尼",
      "answer": "そうに",
      "meaning": "monks and nuns"
    },
    {
      "question": "便壺",
      "answer": "べんつぼ,べんこ",
      "meaning": "night-soil vault, clay pot used to collect feces in an outhouse"
    },
    {
      "question": "疎漏",
      "answer": "そろう",
      "meaning": "carelessness, negligence, oversight"
    },
    {
      "question": "角番",
      "answer": "かどばん",
      "meaning": "make-or-break game in a go or shogi tournament, ozeki-ranked wrestler being in danger of losing his"
    },
    {
      "question": "軟投",
      "answer": "なんとう",
      "meaning": "soft pitch"
    },
    {
      "question": "濫費",
      "answer": "らんぴ",
      "meaning": "waste, lavish spending, dissipation"
    },
    {
      "question": "楽員",
      "answer": "がくいん",
      "meaning": "bandsman"
    },
    {
      "question": "端書",
      "answer": "はがき",
      "meaning": "postcard, memo, note, card"
    },
    {
      "question": "情況証拠",
      "answer": "じょうきょうしょうこ",
      "meaning": "circumstantial evidence"
    },
    {
      "question": "昼夜兼行",
      "answer": "ちゅうやけんこう",
      "meaning": "around-the-clock, (working) day and night"
    },
    {
      "question": "岩漿",
      "answer": "がんしょう",
      "meaning": "magma"
    },
    {
      "question": "部屋食",
      "answer": "へやしょく",
      "meaning": "meal (esp. dinner) served in one's room (at a ryokan)"
    },
    {
      "question": "当歳",
      "answer": "とうさい",
      "meaning": "year of birth, this year"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜学校",
      "answer": "やがっこう",
      "meaning": "night school"
    },
    {
      "question": "和布",
      "answer": "わかめ",
      "meaning": "wakame (species of edible brown seaweed, Undaria pinnatifida)"
    },
    {
      "question": "映射",
      "answer": "えいしゃ",
      "meaning": "reflecting, shining"
    },
    {
      "question": "両三",
      "answer": "りょうさん",
      "meaning": "two or three"
    },
    {
      "question": "荒物屋",
      "answer": "あらものや",
      "meaning": "variety store"
    },
    {
      "question": "磨ぎ汁",
      "answer": "とぎじる,とぎしる",
      "meaning": "water that has been used to wash rice"
    },
    {
      "question": "鎧鼠",
      "answer": "よろいねずみ",
      "meaning": "armadillo"
    },
    {
      "question": "山焼け",
      "answer": "やまやけ",
      "meaning": "mountain fire, bush fire"
    },
    {
      "question": "受難劇",
      "answer": "じゅなんげき",
      "meaning": "Passion Play"
    },
    {
      "question": "永代供養",
      "answer": "えいたいくよう",
      "meaning": "services performed in perpetuity by a Buddhist temple for the repose of a departed soul"
    },
    {
      "question": "ヨハネ伝",
      "answer": "ヨハネでん",
      "meaning": "Gospel of John (book of the Bible)"
    },
    {
      "question": "斯界",
      "answer": "しかい",
      "meaning": "this field, this subject"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷凍機",
      "answer": "れいとうき",
      "meaning": "refrigerator, freezer"
    },
    {
      "question": "粘稠",
      "answer": "ねんちゅう",
      "meaning": "viscous"
    },
    {
      "question": "松飾り",
      "answer": "まつかざり",
      "meaning": "New Year's pine decorations"
    },
    {
      "question": "山居",
      "answer": "やまい",
      "meaning": "living in the mountains, house in the mountains"
    },
    {
      "question": "文臣",
      "answer": "ぶんしん",
      "meaning": "civil official (esp. dealing with literary matters)"
    },
    {
      "question": "写り込み",
      "answer": "うつりこみ",
      "meaning": "ghost image, unexpected appearance of something unwanted in a photograph, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "万般",
      "answer": "ばんぱん",
      "meaning": "all things"
    },
    {
      "question": "御礼参り",
      "answer": "おれいまいり",
      "meaning": "visiting a shrine or temple to give thanks, settling scores"
    },
    {
      "question": "打ち物",
      "answer": "うちもの",
      "meaning": "forged weaponry (e.g. swords, spears, etc.), forged weapon, molded dry confectionery, moulded dry co"
    },
    {
      "question": "野駒",
      "answer": "のごま",
      "meaning": "Siberian rubythroat (Luscinia calliope)"
    },
    {
      "question": "泥除け",
      "answer": "どろよけ",
      "meaning": "protection against (flying) mud, mudguard, mudflap, fender (of a car), wing"
    },
    {
      "question": "駕籠屋",
      "answer": "かごや",
      "meaning": "sedan chair bearer, palanquin bearer, sedan chair business"
    },
    {
      "question": "心裏",
      "answer": "しんり",
      "meaning": "one's mind, the bottom of one's heart, inner feelings"
    },
    {
      "question": "多士済々",
      "answer": "たしせいせい,たしさいさい",
      "meaning": "galaxy of able persons, collection of intellectuals"
    },
    {
      "question": "花糸",
      "answer": "かし",
      "meaning": "(flower's) filament"
    },
    {
      "question": "不可触民",
      "answer": "ふかしょくみん",
      "meaning": "untouchable (of the Indian caste system)"
    },
    {
      "question": "献言",
      "answer": "けんげん",
      "meaning": "offering an opinion (to a superior, the government, etc.), proposal, suggestion, advice"
    },
    {
      "question": "松露",
      "answer": "しょうろ",
      "meaning": "Rhizopogon rubescens (species of edible mushroom)"
    },
    {
      "question": "組織学",
      "answer": "そしきがく",
      "meaning": "histology"
    },
    {
      "question": "渦流",
      "answer": "かりゅう",
      "meaning": "swirling current, eddy, whirlpool, vortex, maelstrom, eddy current"
    },
    {
      "question": "面出し",
      "answer": "つらだし,めんだし",
      "meaning": "putting in an appearance, showing one's face, displaying books face-outwards"
    },
    {
      "question": "昨朝",
      "answer": "さくちょう",
      "meaning": "yesterday morning"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉄観音",
      "answer": "てっかんのん,てつかんのん",
      "meaning": "Tieguanyin (variety of oolong tea)"
    },
    {
      "question": "通知簿",
      "answer": "つうちぼ",
      "meaning": "report card (book)"
    },
    {
      "question": "案分",
      "answer": "あんぶん",
      "meaning": "proportional division, proportional distribution"
    },
    {
      "question": "産前",
      "answer": "さんぜん",
      "meaning": "prior to childbirth"
    },
    {
      "question": "花序",
      "answer": "かじょ",
      "meaning": "inflorescence"
    },
    {
      "question": "低落",
      "answer": "ていらく",
      "meaning": "fall, decline, slump"
    },
    {
      "question": "濫造",
      "answer": "らんぞう",
      "meaning": "overproduction, careless manufacture, churning out (substandard goods)"
    },
    {
      "question": "地震予知",
      "answer": "じしんよち",
      "meaning": "earthquake prediction"
    },
    {
      "question": "大鑑",
      "answer": "たいかん",
      "meaning": "encyclopedia"
    },
    {
      "question": "合成洗剤",
      "answer": "ごうせいせんざい",
      "meaning": "synthetic detergent"
    },
    {
      "question": "可惜",
      "answer": "あたら,あったら",
      "meaning": "alas, regrettably, to my great regret, tragically"
    },
    {
      "question": "切石",
      "answer": "きりいし",
      "meaning": "hewn stone, quarried stone, ashlar, flagstone"
    },
    {
      "question": "売品",
      "answer": "ばいひん",
      "meaning": "articles for sale"
    },
    {
      "question": "他動詞",
      "answer": "たどうし",
      "meaning": "transitive verb"
    },
    {
      "question": "画然",
      "answer": "かくぜん",
      "meaning": "distinct, clear-cut, sharp"
    },
    {
      "question": "皸",
      "answer": "ひび,あかぎれ",
      "meaning": "crack, fissure, rift, split, chaps, skin fissure"
    },
    {
      "question": "粗餐",
      "answer": "そさん",
      "meaning": "plain meal"
    },
    {
      "question": "炒り子",
      "answer": "いりこ",
      "meaning": "small dried sardine"
    },
    {
      "question": "床を払う",
      "answer": "とこをはらう",
      "meaning": "to recover from an illness (and put away one's sickbed)"
    },
    {
      "question": "書林",
      "answer": "しょりん",
      "meaning": "vast stock of books, bookstore, bookshop"
    },
    {
      "question": "杯事",
      "answer": "さかずきごと",
      "meaning": "pledge made over sake cups, exchange of nuptial cups"
    },
    {
      "question": "令室",
      "answer": "れいしつ",
      "meaning": "your wife"
    },
    {
      "question": "属名",
      "answer": "ぞくめい",
      "meaning": "generic name, genus name"
    },
    {
      "question": "千社札",
      "answer": "せんじゃふだ",
      "meaning": "slips of paper posted on shrine pillars by pilgrims"
    },
    {
      "question": "桃林",
      "answer": "とうりん",
      "meaning": "peach grove, peach garden, peach orchard"
    },
    {
      "question": "免疫学",
      "answer": "めんえきがく",
      "meaning": "immunology"
    },
    {
      "question": "抱合",
      "answer": "ほうごう",
      "meaning": "conjugation, incorporation, embrace"
    },
    {
      "question": "尊攘",
      "answer": "そんじょう",
      "meaning": "revere the Emperor; expel the western barbarians (19th century slogan)"
    },
    {
      "question": "付き切り",
      "answer": "つききり",
      "meaning": "constant attendance, uninterrupted supervision, staying with someone all the time"
    },
    {
      "question": "返照",
      "answer": "へんしょう",
      "meaning": "reflection of light (sunlight)"
    },
    {
      "question": "肉太",
      "answer": "にくぶと",
      "meaning": "boldface (type)"
    },
    {
      "question": "巣離れ",
      "answer": "すばなれ",
      "meaning": "leaving the nest, becoming independent of one's parents"
    },
    {
      "question": "俗論",
      "answer": "ぞくろん",
      "meaning": "popular opinion"
    },
    {
      "question": "身体刑",
      "answer": "しんたいけい",
      "meaning": "corporal punishment, physical punishment"
    },
    {
      "question": "閉回路",
      "answer": "へいかいろ",
      "meaning": "closed circuit"
    },
    {
      "question": "鞭毛",
      "answer": "べんもう",
      "meaning": "flagellum"
    },
    {
      "question": "育児休業",
      "answer": "いくじきゅうぎょう",
      "meaning": "childcare leave, leave taken after the compulsory maternity leave"
    },
    {
      "question": "危険情報",
      "answer": "きけんじょうほう",
      "meaning": "information about a danger, danger warning, risk information"
    },
    {
      "question": "山を越す",
      "answer": "やまをこす",
      "meaning": "to surmount a difficulty, to go across a mountain"
    },
    {
      "question": "吊り戸棚",
      "answer": "つりとだな",
      "meaning": "hanging cupboard, wall cabinet"
    },
    {
      "question": "生麩",
      "answer": "なまふ,しょうふ",
      "meaning": "nama-fu, wheat gluten mixed with rice flour and steamed in large blocks"
    },
    {
      "question": "用土",
      "answer": "ようど",
      "meaning": "soil for horticulture, soil for seed planting"
    },
    {
      "question": "開口数",
      "answer": "かいこうすう",
      "meaning": "numerical aperture (in photography)"
    },
    {
      "question": "引綱",
      "answer": "ひきづな",
      "meaning": "tow rope, bell rope, dog lead, lanyard, sash cord"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪貨",
      "answer": "あっか,あくか",
      "meaning": "bad money"
    },
    {
      "question": "為手",
      "answer": "なりて,して",
      "meaning": "person willing to take on a role, willing candidate, doer, performer, protagonist (in noh or kyogen)"
    },
    {
      "question": "早天",
      "answer": "そうてん",
      "meaning": "early morning, dawn"
    },
    {
      "question": "阿弥陀堂",
      "answer": "あみだどう",
      "meaning": "temple hall containing an enshrined image of Amitabha"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒犀",
      "answer": "くろさい",
      "meaning": "black rhinoceros (Diceros bicornis)"
    },
    {
      "question": "笙の笛",
      "answer": "しょうのふえ,そうのふえ",
      "meaning": "shō (Japanese free reed musical instrument)"
    },
    {
      "question": "御題",
      "answer": "ぎょだい",
      "meaning": "theme chosen for an imperial poetry contest"
    },
    {
      "question": "代金引換",
      "answer": "だいきんひきかえ",
      "meaning": "cash on delivery, COD"
    },
    {
      "question": "楔状",
      "answer": "けつじょう",
      "meaning": "wedge-shaped, cuneate, cuneiform"
    },
    {
      "question": "中綴じ",
      "answer": "なかとじ",
      "meaning": "saddle stitch"
    },
    {
      "question": "等値",
      "answer": "とうち",
      "meaning": "equal value, equivalence"
    },
    {
      "question": "野菜工場",
      "answer": "やさいこうじょう",
      "meaning": "vegetable plant, vegetable factory, closed growing system for year-round production of vegetables"
    },
    {
      "question": "空念仏",
      "answer": "そらねんぶつ,からねんぶつ",
      "meaning": "empty words"
    },
    {
      "question": "輔佐",
      "answer": "ほさ",
      "meaning": "aid, help, assistance, assistant, counselor, counsellor, adviser, advisor"
    },
    {
      "question": "宿便",
      "answer": "しゅくべん",
      "meaning": "feces contained long in the intestines, fecal stasis, coprostasis"
    },
    {
      "question": "森々",
      "answer": "しんしん",
      "meaning": "deeply forested"
    },
    {
      "question": "店借り",
      "answer": "たながり",
      "meaning": "tenancy"
    },
    {
      "question": "言い条",
      "answer": "いいじょう",
      "meaning": "an excuse, however, nonetheless"
    },
    {
      "question": "耐火煉瓦",
      "answer": "たいかれんが",
      "meaning": "firebrick"
    },
    {
      "question": "雑ぜる",
      "answer": "まぜる",
      "meaning": "to mix, to stir, to blend"
    },
    {
      "question": "内発",
      "answer": "ないはつ",
      "meaning": "burst of energy from within"
    },
    {
      "question": "追いコン",
      "answer": "おいコン",
      "meaning": "farewell party, send-off party"
    },
    {
      "question": "両義",
      "answer": "りょうぎ",
      "meaning": "double meaning, two meanings, amphibolous"
    },
    {
      "question": "衆生済度",
      "answer": "しゅじょうさいど",
      "meaning": "enlightenment of the masses, leading the masses on the path of enlightenment (Buddhism)"
    },
    {
      "question": "厚薄",
      "answer": "こうはく",
      "meaning": "thickness, partiality"
    },
    {
      "question": "俘虜",
      "answer": "ふりょ,とりこ",
      "meaning": "captive, prisoner of war, prisoner, victim (of love, etc.), slave (to one's lust, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "注意人物",
      "answer": "ちゅういじんぶつ",
      "meaning": "marked person (by the police, etc.), person to be watched, person considered dangerous, person on a"
    },
    {
      "question": "辺塞",
      "answer": "へんさい",
      "meaning": "frontier fort, remote area, frontier"
    },
    {
      "question": "煎ずる",
      "answer": "せんずる",
      "meaning": "to boil, to decoct, to infuse"
    },
    {
      "question": "対症的",
      "answer": "たいしょうてき",
      "meaning": "temporary (of medical care), palliative, dealing only with the symptoms, symptomatic, superficial"
    },
    {
      "question": "無代",
      "answer": "むだい,むたい",
      "meaning": "free of charge, intangible, incorporeal, by force, outrageous, cruel, unreasonable, making light of,"
    },
    {
      "question": "別誂え",
      "answer": "べつあつらえ",
      "meaning": "special order"
    },
    {
      "question": "断金",
      "answer": "だんきん,たんぎん",
      "meaning": "close friendship (i.e. strong enough to cut metal), (in Japan) 2nd note of the ancient chromatic sca"
    },
    {
      "question": "医道",
      "answer": "いどう",
      "meaning": "the art of medicine"
    },
    {
      "question": "石切り",
      "answer": "いしきり",
      "meaning": "quarrying (stone), quarryman, stonecutting, stonemasonry, stonecutter, stonemason"
    },
    {
      "question": "姉婿",
      "answer": "あねむこ",
      "meaning": "the husband of one's elder sister"
    },
    {
      "question": "散薬",
      "answer": "さんやく",
      "meaning": "powdered medicine"
    },
    {
      "question": "藤蔓",
      "answer": "ふじづる",
      "meaning": "wisteria vine"
    },
    {
      "question": "小異",
      "answer": "しょうい",
      "meaning": "minor differences"
    },
    {
      "question": "上乗り",
      "answer": "うわのり",
      "meaning": "supercargo"
    },
    {
      "question": "疵付く",
      "answer": "きずつく",
      "meaning": "to be wounded, to get injured, to get hurt feelings, to get damaged, to get chipped, to get scratche"
    },
    {
      "question": "障壁画",
      "answer": "しょうへきが",
      "meaning": "pictures on (room) partitions"
    },
    {
      "question": "周忌",
      "answer": "しゅうき",
      "meaning": "death anniversary"
    },
    {
      "question": "ぴり辛",
      "answer": "ぴりから",
      "meaning": "spicy, piquant"
    },
    {
      "question": "歯齦",
      "answer": "しぎん",
      "meaning": "the gums"
    },
    {
      "question": "銀側",
      "answer": "ぎんがわ",
      "meaning": "silver case"
    },
    {
      "question": "変圧",
      "answer": "へんあつ",
      "meaning": "transformation (of a current)"
    },
    {
      "question": "楫",
      "answer": "かじ",
      "meaning": "rudder, helm"
    },
    {
      "question": "象牙海岸",
      "answer": "ぞうげかいがん",
      "meaning": "(Republic of) Ivory Coast, Côte d'Ivoire"
    },
    {
      "question": "明主",
      "answer": "めいしゅ",
      "meaning": "wise ruler"
    },
    {
      "question": "防潜網",
      "answer": "ぼうせんもう",
      "meaning": "anti-submarine net"
    },
    {
      "question": "曲射砲",
      "answer": "きょくしゃほう",
      "meaning": "howitzer, high-angle gun"
    },
    {
      "question": "日本猿",
      "answer": "にほんざる",
      "meaning": "Japanese macaque (Macaca fuscata)"
    },
    {
      "question": "多剤耐性",
      "answer": "たざいたいせい",
      "meaning": "multi-drug-resistance, MDR"
    },
    {
      "question": "通所",
      "answer": "つうしょ",
      "meaning": "making regular visits to a social welfare facility"
    },
    {
      "question": "緩衝器",
      "answer": "かんしょうき",
      "meaning": "shock absorber, buffer"
    },
    {
      "question": "外来生物",
      "answer": "がいらいせいぶつ",
      "meaning": "adventive species, non-native species, introduced species, alien species"
    },
    {
      "question": "法律案",
      "answer": "ほうりつあん",
      "meaning": "(legislative) bill"
    },
    {
      "question": "大小便",
      "answer": "だいしょうべん",
      "meaning": "feces and urine"
    },
    {
      "question": "鎖編み",
      "answer": "くさりあみ",
      "meaning": "chain stitch"
    },
    {
      "question": "暑気中り",
      "answer": "しょきあたり",
      "meaning": "suffering from the heat, heatstroke, heat prostration"
    },
    {
      "question": "両君",
      "answer": "りょうくん",
      "meaning": "two people, two monarchs, two rulers"
    },
    {
      "question": "死に身",
      "answer": "しにみ",
      "meaning": "at the risk of one's life, dead body"
    },
    {
      "question": "正伝",
      "answer": "せいでん",
      "meaning": "authentic biography"
    },
    {
      "question": "菠薐草",
      "answer": "ほうれんそう",
      "meaning": "spinach"
    },
    {
      "question": "陰金田虫",
      "answer": "いんきんたむし",
      "meaning": "ringworm (of the groin), jock itch, tinea cruris"
    },
    {
      "question": "予定説",
      "answer": "よていせつ",
      "meaning": "predestination"
    },
    {
      "question": "限外",
      "answer": "げんがい",
      "meaning": "excess, extra"
    },
    {
      "question": "上値",
      "answer": "うわね",
      "meaning": "higher price, price rise"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉄工場",
      "answer": "てっこうじょう",
      "meaning": "iron workers shop, ironworks"
    },
    {
      "question": "落し所",
      "answer": "おとしどころ",
      "meaning": "point of compromise, common ground"
    },
    {
      "question": "昼光",
      "answer": "ちゅうこう",
      "meaning": "daylight"
    },
    {
      "question": "大角鹿",
      "answer": "おおつのじか",
      "meaning": "giant fallow deer (extinct)"
    },
    {
      "question": "背割",
      "answer": "せわり",
      "meaning": "slicing a fish down its back, slit in the back of a garment, split in a piece of lumber (to prevent"
    },
    {
      "question": "危める",
      "answer": "あやめる",
      "meaning": "to wound, to murder"
    },
    {
      "question": "炭俵",
      "answer": "すみだわら",
      "meaning": "sack for charcoal"
    },
    {
      "question": "商船学校",
      "answer": "しょうせんがっこう",
      "meaning": "merchant-marine school"
    },
    {
      "question": "取札",
      "answer": "とりふだ",
      "meaning": "card to pick up (in card games), card that is picked up by players instead of read (in karuta), card"
    },
    {
      "question": "甑",
      "answer": "こしき,そう",
      "meaning": "steaming basket (traditionally clay or wood), steaming vat (for steaming rice in sake production)"
    },
    {
      "question": "近景",
      "answer": "きんけい",
      "meaning": "foreground"
    },
    {
      "question": "性科学",
      "answer": "せいかがく",
      "meaning": "sexology"
    },
    {
      "question": "筆法",
      "answer": "ひっぽう",
      "meaning": "style of penmanship"
    },
    {
      "question": "海底地震",
      "answer": "かいていじしん",
      "meaning": "submarine earthquake"
    },
    {
      "question": "遷宮",
      "answer": "せんぐう",
      "meaning": "installation of a deity in a new shrine, transfer of a shrine"
    },
    {
      "question": "雑人",
      "answer": "ぞうにん",
      "meaning": "low-call people"
    },
    {
      "question": "臍下",
      "answer": "せいか",
      "meaning": "lower abdomen"
    },
    {
      "question": "徴兵検査",
      "answer": "ちょうへいけんさ",
      "meaning": "physical examination (given at conscription)"
    },
    {
      "question": "増益",
      "answer": "ぞうえき",
      "meaning": "increased (profit)"
    },
    {
      "question": "検印",
      "answer": "けんいん",
      "meaning": "seal of approval"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛雲",
      "answer": "ひうん",
      "meaning": "cloud flying through the sky"
    },
    {
      "question": "隔年",
      "answer": "かくねん",
      "meaning": "biennially, every second year, every other year"
    },
    {
      "question": "勝地",
      "answer": "しょうち",
      "meaning": "place of scenic beauty, beauty spot, scenic spot, suitable land"
    },
    {
      "question": "蕭条",
      "answer": "しょうじょう",
      "meaning": "dreary, bleak, lonely"
    },
    {
      "question": "慈心",
      "answer": "じしん",
      "meaning": "benevolence, mercy"
    },
    {
      "question": "配意",
      "answer": "はいい",
      "meaning": "regard, consideration, thoughtfulness"
    },
    {
      "question": "塗炭",
      "answer": "とたん",
      "meaning": "misery, distress"
    },
    {
      "question": "音数",
      "answer": "おんすう",
      "meaning": "number of syllabic sounds in a language"
    },
    {
      "question": "売家",
      "answer": "うりや,うりいえ",
      "meaning": "house for sale"
    },
    {
      "question": "根限り",
      "answer": "こんかぎり",
      "meaning": "with all one's might"
    },
    {
      "question": "天正大判",
      "answer": "てんしょうおおばん",
      "meaning": "oval gold coin struck by Toyotomi Hideyoshi in 1588"
    },
    {
      "question": "書き替え",
      "answer": "かきかえ",
      "meaning": "rewriting (book), renewal, transfer of ownership"
    },
    {
      "question": "集団就職",
      "answer": "しゅうだんしゅうしょく",
      "meaning": "employment en masse (esp. of middle and high school graduates from the rural districts during Japan'"
    },
    {
      "question": "典拠",
      "answer": "てんきょ",
      "meaning": "(an) authority, (a) source, (written) reference"
    },
    {
      "question": "当て物",
      "answer": "あてもの",
      "meaning": "guessing, covering"
    },
    {
      "question": "問答法",
      "answer": "もんどうほう",
      "meaning": "dialectic, dialectics"
    },
    {
      "question": "熊鷹",
      "answer": "くまたか",
      "meaning": "Hodgson's hawk eagle (Nisaetus nipalensis), mountain hawk-eagle"
    },
    {
      "question": "板屋根",
      "answer": "いたやね",
      "meaning": "shingle roof"
    },
    {
      "question": "膿疱",
      "answer": "のうほう",
      "meaning": "pustule, pustula"
    },
    {
      "question": "乾湿",
      "answer": "かんしつ",
      "meaning": "degree of humidity"
    },
    {
      "question": "不言",
      "answer": "ふげん",
      "meaning": "silence"
    },
    {
      "question": "優曇華",
      "answer": "うどんげ",
      "meaning": "udumbara (mythical Indian plant often identified with the cluster fig, Ficus glomerata), something v"
    },
    {
      "question": "銭亀",
      "answer": "ぜにがめ",
      "meaning": "baby spotted turtle, immature Japanese pond turtle, young Japanese terrapin"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄志弱行",
      "answer": "はくしじゃっこう",
      "meaning": "infirm of purpose and lacking in decision"
    },
    {
      "question": "被害地",
      "answer": "ひがいち",
      "meaning": "the stricken area, damaged area"
    },
    {
      "question": "廃炉",
      "answer": "はいろ",
      "meaning": "decommissioning (of a nuclear reactor, furnace, incinerator etc.), decommissioned nuclear reactor (o"
    },
    {
      "question": "豬",
      "answer": "い",
      "meaning": "hog (esp. a wild boar, but also including the domesticated pig)"
    },
    {
      "question": "禁獄",
      "answer": "きんごく",
      "meaning": "imprisonment, incarceration"
    },
    {
      "question": "雄蜂",
      "answer": "おばち",
      "meaning": "drone (bee)"
    },
    {
      "question": "在阪",
      "answer": "ざいはん",
      "meaning": "being based in Osaka, being in Osaka"
    },
    {
      "question": "掛け買い",
      "answer": "かけがい",
      "meaning": "credit purchase"
    },
    {
      "question": "壮丁",
      "answer": "そうてい",
      "meaning": "youth, young man who has reached adulthood (conscription age)"
    },
    {
      "question": "試遊",
      "answer": "しゆう",
      "meaning": "test-playing (of a video game before release or purchase), playing a demo"
    },
    {
      "question": "早老",
      "answer": "そうろう",
      "meaning": "premature aging, premature ageing"
    },
    {
      "question": "先ず先ず",
      "answer": "まずまず",
      "meaning": "tolerable, passable, adequate, so-so"
    },
    {
      "question": "西晋",
      "answer": "せいしん",
      "meaning": "Western Jin dynasty (China, 265-317), Western Chin dynasty"
    },
    {
      "question": "翠嵐",
      "answer": "すいらん",
      "meaning": "the sense of being engulfed in a green, mountainous atmosphere"
    },
    {
      "question": "西京味噌",
      "answer": "さいきょうみそ",
      "meaning": "Kyoto-style miso, Kyoto-style sweet white bean paste (esp. used for pickling fish)"
    },
    {
      "question": "鳥の子色",
      "answer": "とりのこいろ",
      "meaning": "eggshell (colour)"
    },
    {
      "question": "旅歩き",
      "answer": "たびあるき",
      "meaning": "travelling on foot"
    },
    {
      "question": "乗り鉄",
      "answer": "のりてつ",
      "meaning": "railway enthusiast who enjoys riding trains"
    },
    {
      "question": "主謀",
      "answer": "しゅぼう",
      "meaning": "plotting, planning (crime, intrigue), ringleader, mastermind, leader (of a plot)"
    },
    {
      "question": "縁切り寺",
      "answer": "えんきりでら",
      "meaning": "(historic) a temple in which women seeking release from marriage could take refuge"
    },
    {
      "question": "抱朴子",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "加水分解",
      "answer": "かすいぶんかい",
      "meaning": "hydrolysis"
    },
    {
      "question": "温覚",
      "answer": "おんかく",
      "meaning": "sense of warmth"
    },
    {
      "question": "腰ばき",
      "answer": "こしばき",
      "meaning": "wearing one's pants low (so that they hang from the hip rather than the waist)"
    },
    {
      "question": "整理屋",
      "answer": "せいりや",
      "meaning": "loan shark who specializes in refinancing debts"
    },
    {
      "question": "禾本科",
      "answer": "かほんか",
      "meaning": "Poaceae, Gramineae, family of flowering plants"
    },
    {
      "question": "摘心",
      "answer": "てきしん",
      "meaning": "thinning (buds and branches)"
    },
    {
      "question": "厭忌",
      "answer": "えんき",
      "meaning": "hatred, dislike, abhorrence, detestation"
    },
    {
      "question": "勿怪",
      "answer": "もっけ",
      "meaning": "unexpected"
    },
    {
      "question": "我を折る",
      "answer": "がをおる",
      "meaning": "to concede a point, to yield, to give in"
    },
    {
      "question": "音頭取り",
      "answer": "おんどとり",
      "meaning": "taking the lead, leadership, leader, pacemaker, chorus leader"
    },
    {
      "question": "お姉系",
      "answer": "おねえけい",
      "meaning": "fashion style characterized by brown hair and deep-tanned skin, expensive brand-name clothes and acc"
    },
    {
      "question": "耕耘機",
      "answer": "こううんき",
      "meaning": "cultivator, farm tractor, tiller"
    },
    {
      "question": "血管系",
      "answer": "けっかんけい",
      "meaning": "blood circulatory system, vascular system"
    },
    {
      "question": "符呪",
      "answer": "ふじゅ",
      "meaning": "incantation"
    },
    {
      "question": "学参",
      "answer": "がくさん",
      "meaning": "study reference, study-aid book"
    },
    {
      "question": "苦況",
      "answer": "くきょう",
      "meaning": "difficult situation, adverse circumstances, predicament, trouble, dilemma, distress"
    },
    {
      "question": "超越論的",
      "answer": "ちょうえつろんてき",
      "meaning": "transcendental"
    },
    {
      "question": "党議拘束",
      "answer": "とうぎこうそく",
      "meaning": "compulsory adherence to a party decision, restrictions on party debate"
    },
    {
      "question": "餡ころ",
      "answer": "あんころ",
      "meaning": "mochi wrapped with sweet bean jam"
    },
    {
      "question": "定式",
      "answer": "ていしき,じょうしき",
      "meaning": "formula, prescribed form, established formality"
    },
    {
      "question": "発根",
      "answer": "はっこん",
      "meaning": "taking root, rooting"
    },
    {
      "question": "待乳山",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "照葉樹林",
      "answer": "しょうようじゅりん",
      "meaning": "evergreen (glossy-leaved) forest"
    },
    {
      "question": "乾留",
      "answer": "かんりゅう",
      "meaning": "dry distillation"
    },
    {
      "question": "合成紙",
      "answer": "ごうせいし",
      "meaning": "synthetic paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "花の宴",
      "answer": "はなのえん",
      "meaning": "cherry blossom viewing drinking party"
    },
    {
      "question": "新開地",
      "answer": "しんかいち",
      "meaning": "newly-opened land, recently-settled region, frontier, new residential area, new development"
    },
    {
      "question": "男姿",
      "answer": "おとこすがた",
      "meaning": "man's appearance, man's behaviour, someone disguised as a man"
    },
    {
      "question": "熱雷",
      "answer": "ねつらい",
      "meaning": "heat thunderstorm"
    },
    {
      "question": "延べ板",
      "answer": "のべいた",
      "meaning": "hammered-out plates"
    },
    {
      "question": "衆望",
      "answer": "しゅうぼう",
      "meaning": "public confidence, popular support"
    },
    {
      "question": "涼味",
      "answer": "りょうみ",
      "meaning": "cool, coolness"
    },
    {
      "question": "爆燃",
      "answer": "ばくねん",
      "meaning": "deflagration, knocking (e.g. in car engines)"
    },
    {
      "question": "小犬座",
      "answer": "こいぬざ",
      "meaning": "Canis Minor (constellation), the Lesser Dog"
    },
    {
      "question": "痂",
      "answer": "かさぶた",
      "meaning": "scab, crust"
    },
    {
      "question": "腹背",
      "answer": "ふくはい",
      "meaning": "back and front, opposition in the heart"
    },
    {
      "question": "勾引かす",
      "answer": "かどわかす",
      "meaning": "to kidnap"
    },
    {
      "question": "微醺",
      "answer": "びくん",
      "meaning": "slight intoxication"
    },
    {
      "question": "無産階級",
      "answer": "むさんかいきゅう",
      "meaning": "the proletarian class"
    },
    {
      "question": "忍冬",
      "answer": "すいかずら",
      "meaning": "Japanese honeysuckle (Lonicera japonica)"
    },
    {
      "question": "山颪",
      "answer": "やまおろし",
      "meaning": "wind blowing down from a mountain"
    },
    {
      "question": "蕎麦殻",
      "answer": "そばがら",
      "meaning": "buckwheat chaff"
    },
    {
      "question": "陰道",
      "answer": "いんどう",
      "meaning": "vagina, love-making technique"
    },
    {
      "question": "刺草",
      "answer": "いらくさ",
      "meaning": "Urtica thunbergiana (species of stinging nettle)"
    },
    {
      "question": "独り子",
      "answer": "ひとりご",
      "meaning": "(an) only child"
    },
    {
      "question": "一本歯",
      "answer": "いっぽんば",
      "meaning": "tall geta with a single tooth"
    },
    {
      "question": "不才",
      "answer": "ふさい",
      "meaning": "lack of talent, incompetency"
    },
    {
      "question": "尻っぺた",
      "answer": "しりっぺた",
      "meaning": "backside"
    },
    {
      "question": "炭田",
      "answer": "たんでん",
      "meaning": "coalfield, coal field"
    },
    {
      "question": "御神楽",
      "answer": "みかぐら",
      "meaning": "kagura (esp. when performed at the imperial palace)"
    },
    {
      "question": "損亡",
      "answer": "そんぼう",
      "meaning": "loss"
    },
    {
      "question": "鷂",
      "answer": "はいたか,はしたか,はしばみ",
      "meaning": "Eurasian sparrowhawk (Accipiter nisus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "転訛",
      "answer": "てんか",
      "meaning": "corruption, bastardisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "狩り込み",
      "answer": "かりこみ",
      "meaning": "roundup"
    },
    {
      "question": "浮図",
      "answer": "ふと",
      "meaning": "Buddha, stupa, Buddhist temple, Buddhist monk"
    },
    {
      "question": "陸屋根",
      "answer": "ろくやね",
      "meaning": "flat roof"
    },
    {
      "question": "麋",
      "answer": "おおじか",
      "meaning": "large deer, moose, elk, red deer"
    },
    {
      "question": "混植",
      "answer": "こんしょく",
      "meaning": "mixed planting, mixed typesetting"
    },
    {
      "question": "二次曲線",
      "answer": "にじきょくせん",
      "meaning": "quadratic curve"
    },
    {
      "question": "田楽刺し",
      "answer": "でんがくざし",
      "meaning": "skewering"
    },
    {
      "question": "煙筒",
      "answer": "えんとう",
      "meaning": "chimney, kiseru, Japanese smoking pipe"
    },
    {
      "question": "安着",
      "answer": "あんちゃく",
      "meaning": "safe arrival"
    },
    {
      "question": "勧学",
      "answer": "かんがく",
      "meaning": "encouragement of learning"
    },
    {
      "question": "長治",
      "answer": "ちょうじ",
      "meaning": "Chōji era (1104.2.10-1106.4.9)"
    },
    {
      "question": "縁覚",
      "answer": "えんがく",
      "meaning": "pratyekabuddha (one who achieves enlightenment without a teacher)"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤む",
      "answer": "あかむ",
      "meaning": "to blush, to redden"
    },
    {
      "question": "走向",
      "answer": "そうこう",
      "meaning": "strike, direction"
    },
    {
      "question": "猟官",
      "answer": "りょうかん",
      "meaning": "office-seeking"
    },
    {
      "question": "淙々",
      "answer": "そうそう",
      "meaning": "gurgling, babbling, murmuring (stream, brook, etc...)"
    },
    {
      "question": "色女",
      "answer": "いろおんな",
      "meaning": "good-looking woman, concubine"
    },
    {
      "question": "情調",
      "answer": "じょうちょう",
      "meaning": "atmosphere, mood, sentiment"
    },
    {
      "question": "言漏らす",
      "answer": "いいもらす",
      "meaning": "to forget to mention, to leave unspoken, to let slip a secret"
    },
    {
      "question": "編上げる",
      "answer": "あみあげる",
      "meaning": "to finish knitting, to lace from bottom to top, to finish compiling (e.g. a dictionary), to finish e"
    },
    {
      "question": "武臣",
      "answer": "ぶしん",
      "meaning": "military retainer"
    },
    {
      "question": "広軌",
      "answer": "こうき",
      "meaning": "broad gauge"
    },
    {
      "question": "公印",
      "answer": "こういん",
      "meaning": "official seal"
    },
    {
      "question": "目明かし",
      "answer": "めあかし",
      "meaning": "hired thief taker (Edo-period), private detective, private secret policeman"
    },
    {
      "question": "併有",
      "answer": "へいゆう",
      "meaning": "owning together, combination"
    },
    {
      "question": "乗り馬",
      "answer": "のりうま",
      "meaning": "riding horse, saddle horse"
    },
    {
      "question": "鮫皮",
      "answer": "さめがわ",
      "meaning": "shagreen (from a shark or stingray), sharkskin, shark leather"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪女郎",
      "answer": "ゆきじょろう",
      "meaning": "snow woman"
    },
    {
      "question": "普及版",
      "answer": "ふきゅうばん",
      "meaning": "cheap edition (of a book), popular edition"
    },
    {
      "question": "猿滑",
      "answer": "さるすべり,しび",
      "meaning": "crape myrtle (Lagerstroemia indica)"
    },
    {
      "question": "巻き網",
      "answer": "まきあみ",
      "meaning": "purse seine, round haul net"
    },
    {
      "question": "五七日",
      "answer": "ごしちにち",
      "meaning": "35th day after a person's death"
    },
    {
      "question": "暴慢",
      "answer": "ぼうまん",
      "meaning": "ill-mannered, overbearing"
    },
    {
      "question": "同床異夢",
      "answer": "どうしょういむ",
      "meaning": "cohabiting but living in different worlds"
    },
    {
      "question": "略礼装",
      "answer": "りゃくれいそう",
      "meaning": "semiformal attire, semiformal dress"
    },
    {
      "question": "中屋敷",
      "answer": "なかやしき",
      "meaning": "daimyo's spare residence or emergency refuge, residence of a daimyo's successor"
    },
    {
      "question": "磯遊び",
      "answer": "いそあそび",
      "meaning": "gathering shellfish, crabs, etc. on the seashore"
    },
    {
      "question": "代置",
      "answer": "だいち",
      "meaning": "replace"
    },
    {
      "question": "普選",
      "answer": "ふせん",
      "meaning": "universal suffrage"
    },
    {
      "question": "摩する",
      "answer": "まする",
      "meaning": "to rub, to scrub, to scrape, to draw near, to press"
    },
    {
      "question": "吐物",
      "answer": "とぶつ",
      "meaning": "vomit, vomitus"
    },
    {
      "question": "評者",
      "answer": "ひょうしゃ",
      "meaning": "critic, reviewer"
    },
    {
      "question": "緑草",
      "answer": "りょくそう",
      "meaning": "green grass, verdure"
    },
    {
      "question": "盛期",
      "answer": "せいき",
      "meaning": "prosperous period"
    },
    {
      "question": "合繊",
      "answer": "ごうせん",
      "meaning": "synthetic fiber, synthetic fibre"
    },
    {
      "question": "訳詞",
      "answer": "やくし",
      "meaning": "translation of lyrics"
    },
    {
      "question": "産経新聞",
      "answer": "さんけいしんぶん",
      "meaning": "Sankei newspaper"
    },
    {
      "question": "折り山",
      "answer": "おりやま",
      "meaning": "pleat or fold peak"
    },
    {
      "question": "建家",
      "answer": "たちいえ,たてや",
      "meaning": "house, building"
    },
    {
      "question": "財政出動",
      "answer": "ざいせいしゅつどう",
      "meaning": "fiscal stimulus, increasing public spending"
    },
    {
      "question": "誰知らぬ",
      "answer": "だれしらぬ",
      "meaning": "nobody knows"
    },
    {
      "question": "蓋し",
      "answer": "けだし",
      "meaning": "certainly, really, truly, indeed, possibly, maybe, perhaps, probably"
    },
    {
      "question": "安息香酸",
      "answer": "あんそくこうさん",
      "meaning": "benzoic acid"
    },
    {
      "question": "附記",
      "answer": "ふき",
      "meaning": "addition, appendix, note, supplement"
    },
    {
      "question": "変り目",
      "answer": "かわりめ",
      "meaning": "turning point, change, transition, turn (of the tide, century, etc.), point of difference"
    },
    {
      "question": "出郷",
      "answer": "しゅっきょう",
      "meaning": "leaving one's home town, priest going out to teach"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕立券",
      "answer": "したてけん",
      "meaning": "free dressmaking ticket (with a purchase of cloth)"
    },
    {
      "question": "航海図",
      "answer": "こうかいず",
      "meaning": "nautical table, sailing chart"
    },
    {
      "question": "悖理",
      "answer": "はいり",
      "meaning": "absurdity, irrationality"
    },
    {
      "question": "清和",
      "answer": "せいわ",
      "meaning": "season when the sky is clear and the air warm (spring), first ten days of the fourth lunar month"
    },
    {
      "question": "前頭骨",
      "answer": "ぜんとうこつ",
      "meaning": "frontal bone (of the skull)"
    },
    {
      "question": "能役者",
      "answer": "のうやくしゃ",
      "meaning": "noh actor"
    },
    {
      "question": "融通性",
      "answer": "ゆうずうせい",
      "meaning": "flexibility, elasticity"
    },
    {
      "question": "梭",
      "answer": "ひ",
      "meaning": "shuttle (of a loom)"
    },
    {
      "question": "曲がり目",
      "answer": "まがりめ",
      "meaning": "corner, turn, bend in the road, curve, turning point"
    },
    {
      "question": "案文",
      "answer": "あんぶん,あんもん",
      "meaning": "draft, draft proposal"
    },
    {
      "question": "禅門",
      "answer": "ぜんもん",
      "meaning": "Zen, entering the path of Zen"
    },
    {
      "question": "蛍族",
      "answer": "ほたるぞく",
      "meaning": "smokers forced to smoke outside, firefly tribe"
    },
    {
      "question": "擽り",
      "answer": "くすぐり",
      "meaning": "tickling, tickle, joke, gag"
    },
    {
      "question": "鼈甲色",
      "answer": "べっこういろ",
      "meaning": "amber (colour, color)"
    },
    {
      "question": "彩飾",
      "answer": "さいしょく",
      "meaning": "illumination (e.g. of a manuscript)"
    },
    {
      "question": "中仕切り",
      "answer": "なかじきり",
      "meaning": "partition, divider"
    },
    {
      "question": "高調子",
      "answer": "たかちょうし",
      "meaning": "high pitch"
    },
    {
      "question": "角刈",
      "answer": "かくがり",
      "meaning": "crew cut"
    },
    {
      "question": "庫裡",
      "answer": "くり",
      "meaning": "temple kitchen, monastery kitchen, quarters of a head priest (and his family)"
    },
    {
      "question": "三周忌",
      "answer": "さんしゅうき",
      "meaning": "second anniversary of a death"
    },
    {
      "question": "御歳暮",
      "answer": "おせいぼ",
      "meaning": "year-end gift, end of the year, year end"
    },
    {
      "question": "ゴム編み",
      "answer": "ゴムあみ",
      "meaning": "rib stitch, ribbing (in knitting)"
    },
    {
      "question": "肌寒",
      "answer": "はださむ",
      "meaning": "autumn chill"
    },
    {
      "question": "後篇",
      "answer": "こうへん",
      "meaning": "latter part (of book, etc.), sequel, concluding part"
    },
    {
      "question": "饌",
      "answer": "せん",
      "meaning": "food offering to the gods, prepared food"
    },
    {
      "question": "多様体",
      "answer": "たようたい",
      "meaning": "manifold"
    },
    {
      "question": "ミトラ教",
      "answer": "ミトラきょう",
      "meaning": "Mithraism"
    },
    {
      "question": "腮",
      "answer": "あご,えら,あぎと",
      "meaning": "jaw, chin, barb (of a fishhook), gills, branchia, angle of the mandible, gonial angle"
    },
    {
      "question": "何時ぞや",
      "answer": "いつぞや",
      "meaning": "some time ago, the other day, at some time or other, once"
    },
    {
      "question": "三光鳥",
      "answer": "さんこうちょう",
      "meaning": "Japanese paradise flycatcher (Terpsiphone atrocaudata)"
    },
    {
      "question": "熱り",
      "answer": "ほてり,ほとぼり",
      "meaning": "a glow, heat, burning sensation, hot flash, remaining heat, residual excitement, lingering enthusias"
    },
    {
      "question": "焼土",
      "answer": "しょうど",
      "meaning": "burning earth, e.g. for sterilization and converting compost"
    },
    {
      "question": "逓減",
      "answer": "ていげん",
      "meaning": "gradual decrease, gradual diminution"
    },
    {
      "question": "雨曇り",
      "answer": "あまぐもり",
      "meaning": "overcast weather"
    },
    {
      "question": "水芭蕉",
      "answer": "みずばしょう",
      "meaning": "Asian skunk cabbage (Lysichiton camtschatcense)"
    },
    {
      "question": "水利組合",
      "answer": "すいりくみあい",
      "meaning": "irrigation association, water utilization association"
    },
    {
      "question": "脱脂",
      "answer": "だっし",
      "meaning": "removal of fat"
    },
    {
      "question": "微行",
      "answer": "びこう",
      "meaning": "traveling incognito, travelling incognito"
    },
    {
      "question": "還元剤",
      "answer": "かんげんざい",
      "meaning": "reducing agent, reductant"
    },
    {
      "question": "丹頂鶴",
      "answer": "たんちょうづる",
      "meaning": "red-crowned crane, Japanese crane (Grus japonensis)"
    },
    {
      "question": "法華宗",
      "answer": "ほっけしゅう",
      "meaning": "Nichiren sect of Buddhism (sometimes specifically referring to the Hokke school of Nichiren), Tendai"
    },
    {
      "question": "肉界",
      "answer": "にくかい",
      "meaning": "physical or sensual world"
    },
    {
      "question": "役割理論",
      "answer": "やくわりりろん",
      "meaning": "role theory"
    },
    {
      "question": "墓苑",
      "answer": "ぼえん",
      "meaning": "cemetery, graveyard"
    },
    {
      "question": "雉鳩",
      "answer": "きじばと",
      "meaning": "Oriental turtle dove (Streptopelia orientalis), eastern turtle dove, rufous turtledove"
    },
    {
      "question": "膜電位",
      "answer": "まくでんい",
      "meaning": "membrane potential"
    },
    {
      "question": "修錬",
      "answer": "しゅうれん",
      "meaning": "training, drill, practice, practising, discipline"
    },
    {
      "question": "孝子",
      "answer": "こうし",
      "meaning": "filial child"
    },
    {
      "question": "三悪道",
      "answer": "さんあくどう,さんなくどう,さんまくどう",
      "meaning": "the world of hungry spirits and the world of animals, three evil worlds hell"
    },
    {
      "question": "点火栓",
      "answer": "てんかせん",
      "meaning": "spark plug"
    },
    {
      "question": "粗利益",
      "answer": "あらりえき",
      "meaning": "gross profit, gross margin"
    },
    {
      "question": "肝胆",
      "answer": "かんたん",
      "meaning": "the liver and gall bladder, one's inner being"
    },
    {
      "question": "雁木",
      "answer": "がんぎ",
      "meaning": "zigzag pattern, zigzag formation, steps down from a pier, pathway covered by extended eaves to prote"
    },
    {
      "question": "単簡",
      "answer": "たんかん",
      "meaning": "brevity, simplicity"
    },
    {
      "question": "日収",
      "answer": "にっしゅう",
      "meaning": "daily income"
    },
    {
      "question": "欧亜",
      "answer": "おうあ",
      "meaning": "Europe and Asia"
    },
    {
      "question": "悉皆",
      "answer": "しっかい",
      "meaning": "all"
    },
    {
      "question": "病虫害",
      "answer": "びょうちゅうがい",
      "meaning": "(crop) damage from disease and harmful insects"
    },
    {
      "question": "廉売",
      "answer": "れんばい",
      "meaning": "bargain sale"
    },
    {
      "question": "緩衝液",
      "answer": "かんしょうえき",
      "meaning": "buffer solution"
    },
    {
      "question": "高梁",
      "answer": "こうりょう,こうりゃん",
      "meaning": "kaoliang, variety of sorghum, esp. used in making spirits"
    },
    {
      "question": "千振",
      "answer": "せんぶり",
      "meaning": "Japanese green gentian (Swertia japonica), alderfly (esp. species Sialis japonica), alder fly"
    },
    {
      "question": "御霊前",
      "answer": "ごれいぜん",
      "meaning": "before the spirit of the deceased"
    },
    {
      "question": "輔弼",
      "answer": "ほひつ",
      "meaning": "giving the Emperor advice on affairs of state, assistance, counsel"
    },
    {
      "question": "真昆布",
      "answer": "まこんぶ",
      "meaning": "Japanese kelp (Laminaria japonica)"
    },
    {
      "question": "部面",
      "answer": "ぶめん",
      "meaning": "phase, aspect, field, side"
    },
    {
      "question": "食作用",
      "answer": "しょくさよう",
      "meaning": "phagocytosis"
    },
    {
      "question": "紙切り",
      "answer": "かみきり",
      "meaning": "paper silhouette cutout, paper knife"
    },
    {
      "question": "膏肓",
      "answer": "こうこう,こうもう",
      "meaning": "innermost part of the body (where a disease cannot be treated)"
    },
    {
      "question": "気団",
      "answer": "きだん",
      "meaning": "air mass, married man"
    },
    {
      "question": "鎮星",
      "answer": "ちんせい",
      "meaning": "Saturn (planet)"
    },
    {
      "question": "民族意識",
      "answer": "みんぞくいしき",
      "meaning": "national consciousness"
    },
    {
      "question": "粗糖",
      "answer": "そとう",
      "meaning": "raw sugar, unrefined sugar"
    },
    {
      "question": "蛍烏賊",
      "answer": "ほたるいか",
      "meaning": "firefly squid (Watasenia scintillans), sparkling enope squid"
    },
    {
      "question": "手相術",
      "answer": "しゅそうじゅつ",
      "meaning": "palmistry"
    },
    {
      "question": "外憂",
      "answer": "がいゆう",
      "meaning": "external troubles, foreign threat"
    },
    {
      "question": "深緋",
      "answer": "ふかひ",
      "meaning": "deep scarlet"
    },
    {
      "question": "剣ヶ峰",
      "answer": "けんがみね",
      "meaning": "rim of a volcano, esp. Mt. Fuji, wrestling ring, dire or risky situation with no room for error, sin"
    },
    {
      "question": "和装本",
      "answer": "わそうぼん",
      "meaning": "book bound in the traditional Japanese style"
    },
    {
      "question": "暖衣飽食",
      "answer": "だんいほうしょく",
      "meaning": "well-fed and well-dressed"
    },
    {
      "question": "歴史哲学",
      "answer": "れきしてつがく",
      "meaning": "historical philosophy"
    },
    {
      "question": "外税",
      "answer": "そとぜい",
      "meaning": "tax-exclusive pricing, tax added to a price"
    },
    {
      "question": "役向き",
      "answer": "やくむき",
      "meaning": "nature of one's position"
    },
    {
      "question": "酸模",
      "answer": "すかんぽ",
      "meaning": "garden sorrel (Rumex acetosa), cock sorrel, sour dock"
    },
    {
      "question": "埋没費用",
      "answer": "まいぼつひよう",
      "meaning": "sunk cost"
    },
    {
      "question": "地平面",
      "answer": "ちへいめん",
      "meaning": "horizontal plane"
    },
    {
      "question": "象亀",
      "answer": "ぞうがめ",
      "meaning": "giant tortoise"
    },
    {
      "question": "自責点",
      "answer": "じせきてん",
      "meaning": "an earned run"
    },
    {
      "question": "角瓶",
      "answer": "かくびん",
      "meaning": "rectangular bottle"
    },
    {
      "question": "泉州",
      "answer": "せんしゅう,チュアンチョウ",
      "meaning": "Quanzhou (China), Chinchew"
    },
    {
      "question": "嫡嗣",
      "answer": "ちゃくし",
      "meaning": "legitimate heir"
    },
    {
      "question": "人定質問",
      "answer": "じんていしつもん",
      "meaning": "establishing the identity of a defendant"
    },
    {
      "question": "県南",
      "answer": "けんなん",
      "meaning": "southern part of a prefecture"
    },
    {
      "question": "不溶性",
      "answer": "ふようせい",
      "meaning": "insolubility"
    },
    {
      "question": "蘭鋳",
      "answer": "らんちゅう",
      "meaning": "ranchu, variety of goldfish"
    },
    {
      "question": "壮士",
      "answer": "そうし",
      "meaning": "young man in his prime, swaggerer, ruffian"
    },
    {
      "question": "付属学校",
      "answer": "ふぞくがっこう",
      "meaning": "affiliated school"
    },
    {
      "question": "銀モール",
      "answer": "ぎんモール",
      "meaning": "silver lace, silver braid"
    },
    {
      "question": "嶮",
      "answer": "けん",
      "meaning": "steepness, steep place, harsh (look), sharp (tongue)"
    },
    {
      "question": "上げ膳",
      "answer": "あげぜん",
      "meaning": "placing a meal in front of one"
    },
    {
      "question": "繻子織り",
      "answer": "しゅすおり",
      "meaning": "satin weave"
    },
    {
      "question": "妙諦",
      "answer": "みょうてい,みょうたい",
      "meaning": "amazing truth, cardinal principle, key (to understanding)"
    },
    {
      "question": "山伝い",
      "answer": "やまづたい",
      "meaning": "(passing along) from mountain to mountain"
    },
    {
      "question": "塩煎餅",
      "answer": "しおせんべい",
      "meaning": "rice cracker seasoned with soy sauce, salty rice cracker"
    },
    {
      "question": "混載",
      "answer": "こんさい",
      "meaning": "mixed loading, consolidation"
    },
    {
      "question": "筆筒",
      "answer": "ふでづつ",
      "meaning": "brush case"
    },
    {
      "question": "曖昧宿",
      "answer": "あいまいやど",
      "meaning": "brothel fronting as a tea house, inn, restaurant, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "飛び箱",
      "answer": "とびばこ",
      "meaning": "vaulting horse, vaulting box, box horse"
    },
    {
      "question": "外挿",
      "answer": "がいそう",
      "meaning": "extrapolation"
    },
    {
      "question": "打感",
      "answer": "だかん",
      "meaning": "feeling of a golf club hitting a ball"
    },
    {
      "question": "中太",
      "answer": "なかぶと,ちゅうぶと",
      "meaning": "medium thickness, medium width"
    },
    {
      "question": "竹筏",
      "answer": "てっぱい",
      "meaning": "Taiwanese bamboo raft"
    },
    {
      "question": "初年兵",
      "answer": "しょねんへい",
      "meaning": "new or raw recruit"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄馬鹿",
      "answer": "うすばか",
      "meaning": "dimwit"
    },
    {
      "question": "参着",
      "answer": "さんちゃく",
      "meaning": "arrival, payment on sight"
    },
    {
      "question": "謝金",
      "answer": "しゃきん",
      "meaning": "reward, monetary expression of thanks"
    },
    {
      "question": "圧電効果",
      "answer": "あつでんこうか",
      "meaning": "piezoelectric effect"
    },
    {
      "question": "栄職",
      "answer": "えいしょく",
      "meaning": "honorable post, honourable post"
    },
    {
      "question": "御盆",
      "answer": "おぼん",
      "meaning": "O-Bon, Obon, Bon Festival, Lantern Festival, Festival of the Dead, tray"
    },
    {
      "question": "雑物",
      "answer": "ざつぶつ",
      "meaning": "miscellaneous things"
    },
    {
      "question": "凶変",
      "answer": "きょうへん",
      "meaning": "catastrophe, assassination, calamity, disaster"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷肉",
      "answer": "れいにく",
      "meaning": "cold meat"
    },
    {
      "question": "澄まし汁",
      "answer": "すましじる",
      "meaning": "clear soup"
    },
    {
      "question": "緩か",
      "answer": "ゆるか",
      "meaning": "loose, slack, gentle, easy, slow, lenient, liberal, lax"
    },
    {
      "question": "当初予算",
      "answer": "とうしょよさん",
      "meaning": "initial budget, original budget"
    },
    {
      "question": "雁皮紙",
      "answer": "がんぴし",
      "meaning": "traditional Japanese paper made from the fibre of plant species Diplomorpha sikokiana (high quality,"
    },
    {
      "question": "幅ったい",
      "answer": "はばったい",
      "meaning": "wide, presumptuous"
    },
    {
      "question": "上海語",
      "answer": "シャンハイご",
      "meaning": "Shanghainese, Shanghai dialect (of Wu Chinese)"
    },
    {
      "question": "書記局",
      "answer": "しょききょく",
      "meaning": "secretariat"
    },
    {
      "question": "建学",
      "answer": "けんがく",
      "meaning": "foundation of a school"
    },
    {
      "question": "特措法",
      "answer": "とくそほう",
      "meaning": "special measures law"
    },
    {
      "question": "離魂病",
      "answer": "りこんびょう",
      "meaning": "somnambulism"
    },
    {
      "question": "官地",
      "answer": "かんち",
      "meaning": "government land, public land"
    },
    {
      "question": "屋根屋",
      "answer": "やねや",
      "meaning": "roofer, thatcher"
    },
    {
      "question": "上顎骨",
      "answer": "じょうがくこつ",
      "meaning": "maxilla, upper jawbone"
    },
    {
      "question": "膝詰め",
      "answer": "ひざづめ",
      "meaning": "(sitting) knee-to-knee, face-to-face"
    },
    {
      "question": "ざら紙",
      "answer": "ざらがみ",
      "meaning": "pulp paper, rough (printing) paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "座敷着",
      "answer": "ざしきぎ",
      "meaning": "dress worn by a geisha to a zashiki party"
    },
    {
      "question": "婆抜き",
      "answer": "ばばぬき",
      "meaning": "old maid (card game), living without one's mother-in-law"
    },
    {
      "question": "六朝",
      "answer": "りくちょう,ろくちょう",
      "meaning": "Six Dynasties (of China: Eastern Wu, Eastern Jin, Song, Qi, Liang, Chen), calligraphic style of the"
    },
    {
      "question": "掛け売り",
      "answer": "かけうり",
      "meaning": "selling on credit"
    },
    {
      "question": "尻が青い",
      "answer": "けつがあおい,しりがあおい",
      "meaning": "wet behind the ears, inexperienced, immature"
    },
    {
      "question": "転地",
      "answer": "てんち",
      "meaning": "change of air, change of scenery"
    },
    {
      "question": "舌下錠",
      "answer": "ぜっかじょう",
      "meaning": "sublingual tablet"
    },
    {
      "question": "金筋",
      "answer": "きんすじ",
      "meaning": "gold stripes"
    },
    {
      "question": "絶念",
      "answer": "ぜつねん",
      "meaning": "giving up, abandoning (hope, plans)"
    },
    {
      "question": "恋風",
      "answer": "こいかぜ",
      "meaning": "love's zephyr"
    },
    {
      "question": "再掲",
      "answer": "さいけい",
      "meaning": "redisplaying, republishing, reproduction, reprint, repost"
    },
    {
      "question": "常滑焼",
      "answer": "とこなめやき",
      "meaning": "Tokoname ware"
    },
    {
      "question": "闇値",
      "answer": "やみね",
      "meaning": "black-market price"
    },
    {
      "question": "木骨",
      "answer": "もっこつ",
      "meaning": "wooden frame"
    },
    {
      "question": "不定詞",
      "answer": "ふていし",
      "meaning": "infinitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "冬木立",
      "answer": "ふゆこだち",
      "meaning": "barren trees in winter"
    },
    {
      "question": "正本",
      "answer": "しょうほん,せいほん",
      "meaning": "book of registration, text of a play, original, original text, authenticated facsimile, authenticate"
    },
    {
      "question": "神代文字",
      "answer": "じんだいもじ",
      "meaning": "ancient Japanese characters (regarded today as created at a much more recent date)"
    },
    {
      "question": "一炊の夢",
      "answer": "いっすいのゆめ",
      "meaning": "an empty dream"
    },
    {
      "question": "立髪",
      "answer": "たてがみ",
      "meaning": "long hair style popular in the Genroku era"
    },
    {
      "question": "梯子車",
      "answer": "はしごしゃ",
      "meaning": "hook-and-ladder truck, ladder truck"
    },
    {
      "question": "白葱",
      "answer": "しろねぎ",
      "meaning": "white spring onion, white scallion"
    },
    {
      "question": "専政",
      "answer": "せんせい",
      "meaning": "autocracy"
    },
    {
      "question": "賢才",
      "answer": "けんさい",
      "meaning": "man of ability, gifted man"
    },
    {
      "question": "磁束密度",
      "answer": "じそくみつど",
      "meaning": "magnetic flux density"
    },
    {
      "question": "桜肉",
      "answer": "さくらにく",
      "meaning": "horse meat"
    },
    {
      "question": "不参",
      "answer": "ふさん",
      "meaning": "absence, nonattendance, nonappearance"
    },
    {
      "question": "鳥の子紙",
      "answer": "とりのこがみ",
      "meaning": "eggshell-colored traditional Japanese paper made primarily of Diplomorpha sikokiana fibres (high-qua"
    },
    {
      "question": "学才",
      "answer": "がくさい",
      "meaning": "academic ability"
    },
    {
      "question": "山の日",
      "answer": "やまのひ",
      "meaning": "Mountain Day (national holiday; August 11)"
    },
    {
      "question": "耳下腺",
      "answer": "じかせん",
      "meaning": "parotid gland"
    },
    {
      "question": "監査法人",
      "answer": "かんさほうじん",
      "meaning": "auditor"
    },
    {
      "question": "柑子色",
      "answer": "こうじいろ",
      "meaning": "orange, saffron"
    },
    {
      "question": "酸性土壌",
      "answer": "さんせいどじょう",
      "meaning": "acid soil"
    },
    {
      "question": "深秋",
      "answer": "しんしゅう",
      "meaning": "deep autumn (when the autumn has reached its climax)"
    },
    {
      "question": "会主",
      "answer": "かいしゅ",
      "meaning": "sponsor of a meeting"
    },
    {
      "question": "山鼠",
      "answer": "やまね,やまねみず",
      "meaning": "Japanese dormouse (Glirulus japonicus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "一張",
      "answer": "いっちょう",
      "meaning": "one pair (set) of clothes"
    },
    {
      "question": "鰐皮",
      "answer": "わにがわ",
      "meaning": "crocodile or alligator skin (hide)"
    },
    {
      "question": "酷悪",
      "answer": "こくあく",
      "meaning": "inhuman, wicked, evil"
    },
    {
      "question": "発光植物",
      "answer": "はっこうしょくぶつ",
      "meaning": "luminous plant"
    },
    {
      "question": "懶惰",
      "answer": "らんだ,らいだ",
      "meaning": "lazy, idle, indolence, laziness, sloth, idleness"
    },
    {
      "question": "交通信号",
      "answer": "こうつうしんごう",
      "meaning": "traffic signal"
    },
    {
      "question": "早変り",
      "answer": "はやがわり",
      "meaning": "quick change, quick transformation, metamorphosis, turning suddenly into"
    },
    {
      "question": "黄河文明",
      "answer": "こうがぶんめい",
      "meaning": "Yellow River civilization, Huang civilization, cradle of Chinese civilization"
    },
    {
      "question": "打水",
      "answer": "うちみず",
      "meaning": "sprinkling water (to keep down dust, cool pavements, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "急性腹症",
      "answer": "きゅうせいふくしょう",
      "meaning": "acute abdomen, stomach problem requiring immediate surgery"
    },
    {
      "question": "慶州",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "黙約",
      "answer": "もくやく",
      "meaning": "tacit agreement, default"
    },
    {
      "question": "推賞",
      "answer": "すいしょう",
      "meaning": "admiration, praise"
    },
    {
      "question": "利茶",
      "answer": "ききちゃ",
      "meaning": "tea tasting, tea-tasting, tea-tasting contest"
    },
    {
      "question": "三教",
      "answer": "さんきょう,さんぎょう",
      "meaning": "Shinto, Buddhism and Confucianism, the three religions, Confucianism, Buddhism and Taoism, Buddhism,"
    },
    {
      "question": "霊的交感",
      "answer": "れいてきこうかん",
      "meaning": "spiritual sympathy, spiritual communion"
    },
    {
      "question": "風趣",
      "answer": "ふうしゅ",
      "meaning": "elegance"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪水",
      "answer": "ゆきみず",
      "meaning": "water from melted snow"
    },
    {
      "question": "修む",
      "answer": "おさむ",
      "meaning": "to study, to complete (a course), to cultivate, to master, to order (one's life), to repair (a fault"
    },
    {
      "question": "既設",
      "answer": "きせつ",
      "meaning": "established, existing"
    },
    {
      "question": "垂れ絹",
      "answer": "たれぎぬ",
      "meaning": "hanging silk, curtain, tapestry, veil"
    },
    {
      "question": "皓皓",
      "answer": "こうこう",
      "meaning": "bright (esp. of the moon), broad and empty"
    },
    {
      "question": "列火",
      "answer": "れっか",
      "meaning": "kanji 'fire' radical at bottom (radical 86)"
    },
    {
      "question": "塒を巻く",
      "answer": "とぐろをまく",
      "meaning": "to coil itself (e.g. a snake), to loaf around"
    },
    {
      "question": "皮膚癌",
      "answer": "ひふがん",
      "meaning": "skin cancer"
    },
    {
      "question": "修まる",
      "answer": "おさまる",
      "meaning": "to reform (oneself), to conduct oneself well"
    },
    {
      "question": "円熟味",
      "answer": "えんじゅくみ",
      "meaning": "mellowness"
    },
    {
      "question": "二足三文",
      "answer": "にそくさんもん",
      "meaning": "dirt cheap, very cheap"
    },
    {
      "question": "口渇",
      "answer": "こうかつ",
      "meaning": "thirst, dry mouth, -dipsia"
    },
    {
      "question": "同生",
      "answer": "どうせい",
      "meaning": "sibling"
    },
    {
      "question": "打っ棄る",
      "answer": "うっちゃる",
      "meaning": "to discard, to abandon, to neglect, to let be"
    },
    {
      "question": "人生行路",
      "answer": "じんせいこうろ",
      "meaning": "journey of life"
    },
    {
      "question": "抽象芸術",
      "answer": "ちゅうしょうげいじゅつ",
      "meaning": "abstract art"
    },
    {
      "question": "石帯",
      "answer": "せきたい",
      "meaning": "special leather belt used in ceremonial court dress, covered in black lacquer and decorated with sto"
    },
    {
      "question": "一毛",
      "answer": "いちもう",
      "meaning": "one-tenth of a rin"
    },
    {
      "question": "返り忠",
      "answer": "かえりちゅう",
      "meaning": "act of betrayal"
    },
    {
      "question": "主著",
      "answer": "しゅちょ",
      "meaning": "one's main (chief) (literary) work"
    },
    {
      "question": "一劃",
      "answer": "いっかく",
      "meaning": "one plot (of land), one block (i.e. one city block), one area, one lot, one brush stroke, one kanji"
    },
    {
      "question": "方解石",
      "answer": "ほうかいせき",
      "meaning": "calcite"
    },
    {
      "question": "雲助",
      "answer": "くもすけ",
      "meaning": "palanquin bearer, coolie, wandering robber"
    },
    {
      "question": "白鳥の歌",
      "answer": "はくちょうのうた",
      "meaning": "swan song"
    },
    {
      "question": "摺り込む",
      "answer": "すりこむ",
      "meaning": "to rub in (e.g. cream into the skin), to grind and mix (e.g. pepper into miso)"
    },
    {
      "question": "危殆",
      "answer": "きたい",
      "meaning": "danger, jeopardy, distress"
    },
    {
      "question": "除災",
      "answer": "じょさい",
      "meaning": "warding off calamities, getting rid of bad luck"
    },
    {
      "question": "限定戦争",
      "answer": "げんていせんそう",
      "meaning": "limited war"
    },
    {
      "question": "本地",
      "answer": "ほんじ,ほんち",
      "meaning": "true form of a buddha, land of origin"
    },
    {
      "question": "一番茶",
      "answer": "いちばんちゃ",
      "meaning": "first-grade tea (first picking)"
    },
    {
      "question": "水生動物",
      "answer": "すいせいどうぶつ",
      "meaning": "aquatic animal, aquatic fauna"
    },
    {
      "question": "動態保存",
      "answer": "どうたいほぞん",
      "meaning": "preservation of obsolete machinery in a functional condition (e.g. train engines)"
    },
    {
      "question": "根毛",
      "answer": "こんもう",
      "meaning": "root hair"
    },
    {
      "question": "壮者",
      "answer": "そうしゃ",
      "meaning": "person in his or her prime, man in his prime, woman in her prime"
    },
    {
      "question": "信義則",
      "answer": "しんぎそく",
      "meaning": "fair and equitable principle"
    },
    {
      "question": "服紗",
      "answer": "ふくさ",
      "meaning": "small silk wrapper, small cloth for wiping tea utensils, crepe wrapper"
    },
    {
      "question": "依願",
      "answer": "いがん",
      "meaning": "in accordance with one's request"
    },
    {
      "question": "頑陋",
      "answer": "がんろう",
      "meaning": "stubborn and mean, obstinate and bigoted"
    },
    {
      "question": "面窶れ",
      "answer": "おもやつれ",
      "meaning": "care-worn, haggard"
    },
    {
      "question": "内の奴",
      "answer": "うちのやつ",
      "meaning": "the wife, the missus"
    },
    {
      "question": "論壇",
      "answer": "ろんだん",
      "meaning": "rostrum, the world of criticism"
    },
    {
      "question": "嘉例",
      "answer": "かれい",
      "meaning": "happy precedent"
    },
    {
      "question": "正平",
      "answer": "しょうへい",
      "meaning": "Shōhei era (of the Southern Court) (1346.12.8-1370.7.24)"
    },
    {
      "question": "即妙",
      "answer": "そくみょう",
      "meaning": "ready wit"
    },
    {
      "question": "停滞前線",
      "answer": "ていたいぜんせん",
      "meaning": "stationary weather front"
    },
    {
      "question": "展性",
      "answer": "てんせい",
      "meaning": "malleability"
    },
    {
      "question": "場合の数",
      "answer": "ばあいのかず",
      "meaning": "number of possible outcomes, number of ways (e.g. of arranging something)"
    },
    {
      "question": "凜烈",
      "answer": "りんれつ",
      "meaning": "biting (cold), severe, intense, piercing"
    },
    {
      "question": "廓清",
      "answer": "かくせい",
      "meaning": "purification, cleaning up, purging"
    },
    {
      "question": "喃々",
      "answer": "なんなん",
      "meaning": "chatteringly, wittering on, prattling on, blathering on"
    },
    {
      "question": "男腹",
      "answer": "おとこばら",
      "meaning": "woman who has borne only male children"
    },
    {
      "question": "近眼鏡",
      "answer": "きんがんきょう",
      "meaning": "corrective lenses for myopia"
    },
    {
      "question": "粉茶",
      "answer": "こちゃ,こなちゃ",
      "meaning": "powdered (green) tea"
    },
    {
      "question": "孫請け",
      "answer": "まごうけ",
      "meaning": "sub-sub contractor"
    },
    {
      "question": "鋪",
      "answer": "ほ,しき",
      "meaning": "shop, store, counter for foldable things such as maps, etc., mine tunnel, mine shaft, mineshaft"
    },
    {
      "question": "謄本",
      "answer": "とうほん",
      "meaning": "certified copy, transcript, official copy of the family register"
    },
    {
      "question": "月の入り",
      "answer": "つきのいり",
      "meaning": "moonset, moondown"
    },
    {
      "question": "円転滑脱",
      "answer": "えんてんかつだつ",
      "meaning": "suave, tactful, smooth, versatile, adaptable"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍場",
      "answer": "いくさば",
      "meaning": "battlefield, battleground"
    },
    {
      "question": "犢",
      "answer": "こうし,こうじ",
      "meaning": "calf, small cow"
    },
    {
      "question": "強制保険",
      "answer": "きょうせいほけん",
      "meaning": "mandatory insurance (e.g. for motor vehicles)"
    },
    {
      "question": "入り日",
      "answer": "いりひ",
      "meaning": "setting sun, evening sun"
    },
    {
      "question": "前翅",
      "answer": "ぜんし",
      "meaning": "fore-wing (of insect)"
    },
    {
      "question": "一撮み",
      "answer": "ひとつまみ",
      "meaning": "pinch (of something), one piece, easy victory"
    },
    {
      "question": "所有格",
      "answer": "しょゆうかく",
      "meaning": "possessive case"
    },
    {
      "question": "竹蜻蛉",
      "answer": "たけとんぼ",
      "meaning": "small wooden Japanese toy that flies when spun between the palms of one's hands"
    },
    {
      "question": "面皰",
      "answer": "にきび,めんぽう",
      "meaning": "pimple, acne"
    },
    {
      "question": "南京袋",
      "answer": "ナンキンぶくろ",
      "meaning": "gunny sack"
    },
    {
      "question": "道路標示",
      "answer": "どうろひょうじ",
      "meaning": "traffic sign painted on the road"
    },
    {
      "question": "トルコ帽",
      "answer": "トルコぼう",
      "meaning": "fez, tarboosh"
    },
    {
      "question": "江戸弁",
      "answer": "えどべん",
      "meaning": "Edo dialect"
    },
    {
      "question": "天水桶",
      "answer": "てんすいおけ",
      "meaning": "rain barrel"
    },
    {
      "question": "露営",
      "answer": "ろえい",
      "meaning": "bivouac"
    },
    {
      "question": "奉還",
      "answer": "ほうかん",
      "meaning": "restoring to the emperor"
    },
    {
      "question": "私鋳銭",
      "answer": "しちゅうせん",
      "meaning": "private coinage"
    },
    {
      "question": "開山",
      "answer": "かいさん",
      "meaning": "founding a temple (on a hill-top)"
    },
    {
      "question": "台秤",
      "answer": "だいばかり",
      "meaning": "platform scales, weighing platform"
    },
    {
      "question": "怒り上戸",
      "answer": "おこりじょうご",
      "meaning": "quarrelsome drinker"
    },
    {
      "question": "油障子",
      "answer": "あぶらしょうじ",
      "meaning": "shoji with an oil-treated screen (for increased water resistance)"
    },
    {
      "question": "佳人薄命",
      "answer": "かじんはくめい",
      "meaning": "beauties die young, beauty and luck seldom go together"
    },
    {
      "question": "椿説",
      "answer": "ちんせつ",
      "meaning": "novel idea, strange theory"
    },
    {
      "question": "末期養子",
      "answer": "まつごようし",
      "meaning": "deathbed adoption of a successor (to prevent extinction of the family line), person adopted by someo"
    },
    {
      "question": "男出入り",
      "answer": "おとこでいり",
      "meaning": "woman with a turbulent love life, woman always having man trouble"
    },
    {
      "question": "下垂",
      "answer": "かすい",
      "meaning": "drooping, hanging down"
    },
    {
      "question": "偏奇",
      "answer": "へんき",
      "meaning": "eccentricity"
    },
    {
      "question": "百計",
      "answer": "ひゃっけい",
      "meaning": "all means"
    },
    {
      "question": "旦夕",
      "answer": "たんせき",
      "meaning": "on the brink of, morning and evening, day and night"
    },
    {
      "question": "用器",
      "answer": "ようき",
      "meaning": "tool, instrument"
    },
    {
      "question": "参院",
      "answer": "さんいん",
      "meaning": "House of Councillors (upper house of the National Diet of Japan)"
    },
    {
      "question": "兼学",
      "answer": "けんがく",
      "meaning": "concurrently studying the teachings of two or more different schools or sects"
    },
    {
      "question": "宮参り",
      "answer": "みやまいり",
      "meaning": "miyamairi, newborn child's first visit to a shrine (within about 30 days of being born), visiting a"
    },
    {
      "question": "哀楽",
      "answer": "あいらく",
      "meaning": "grief and pleasure"
    },
    {
      "question": "顕然",
      "answer": "けんぜん",
      "meaning": "clear, manifest"
    },
    {
      "question": "鬱金色",
      "answer": "うこんいろ",
      "meaning": "yellow, saffron (color, colour)"
    },
    {
      "question": "手焙り",
      "answer": "てあぶり",
      "meaning": "small brazier, hand-warmer"
    },
    {
      "question": "大計",
      "answer": "たいけい",
      "meaning": "grand-scale or long-range plan, farsighted policy"
    },
    {
      "question": "内閣改造",
      "answer": "ないかくかいぞう",
      "meaning": "cabinet reshuffle, cabinet shake-up"
    },
    {
      "question": "国務省",
      "answer": "こくむしょう",
      "meaning": "State Department"
    },
    {
      "question": "明り窓",
      "answer": "あかりまど",
      "meaning": "transom, skylight, dormer window"
    },
    {
      "question": "断想",
      "answer": "だんそう",
      "meaning": "fragmentary thoughts, random thoughts"
    },
    {
      "question": "時代祭",
      "answer": "じだいまつり",
      "meaning": "Festival of the Ages (held at Heian Jingu Shrine in Kyoto on October 22), Jidai Festival"
    },
    {
      "question": "熟し",
      "answer": "こなし",
      "meaning": "carriage (e.g. of one's body)"
    },
    {
      "question": "待降節",
      "answer": "たいこうせつ",
      "meaning": "Advent"
    },
    {
      "question": "目籠",
      "answer": "めかご",
      "meaning": "openwork bamboo basket"
    },
    {
      "question": "保税地域",
      "answer": "ほぜいちいき",
      "meaning": "bonded area (i.e. customs)"
    },
    {
      "question": "故山",
      "answer": "こざん",
      "meaning": "one's native place"
    },
    {
      "question": "電子投票",
      "answer": "でんしとうひょう",
      "meaning": "electronic voting, e-voting"
    },
    {
      "question": "霜夜",
      "answer": "しもよ",
      "meaning": "frosty night"
    },
    {
      "question": "公選法",
      "answer": "こうせんほう",
      "meaning": "Public Office Election Law"
    },
    {
      "question": "水蝕",
      "answer": "すいしょく",
      "meaning": "(water) erosion"
    },
    {
      "question": "大山猫",
      "answer": "おおやまねこ",
      "meaning": "lynx (esp. the Eurasian lynx, Lynx lynx)"
    },
    {
      "question": "生酔い",
      "answer": "なまよい",
      "meaning": "tipsy"
    },
    {
      "question": "一溜まり",
      "answer": "ひとたまり",
      "meaning": "holding out for a short while, putting up resistance for a while, briefly holding one's own"
    },
    {
      "question": "了然",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "円石",
      "answer": "えんせき",
      "meaning": "round stone, pebble, boulder, cobblestone, cobble, coccolith"
    },
    {
      "question": "裏日本",
      "answer": "うらにっぽん,うらにほん",
      "meaning": "Japan Sea coastal areas, Sea of Japan coastal areas"
    },
    {
      "question": "素敵滅法",
      "answer": "すてきめっぽう",
      "meaning": "very lovely, totally dreamy, very beautiful, really great, fantastic, superb, cool, capital"
    },
    {
      "question": "膠付け",
      "answer": "にかわづけ",
      "meaning": "glueing"
    },
    {
      "question": "散蒔く",
      "answer": "ばらまく",
      "meaning": "to scatter, to disseminate (e.g. a rumor), to spread (e.g. germs), to broadcast, to distribute widel"
    },
    {
      "question": "北々西",
      "answer": "ほくほくせい",
      "meaning": "north-northwest"
    },
    {
      "question": "射通す",
      "answer": "いとおす",
      "meaning": "to pierce, to penetrate"
    },
    {
      "question": "果敢無い",
      "answer": "はかない",
      "meaning": "fleeting, transient, short-lived, momentary, ephemeral, fickle, vain, empty (dream, etc.), mere (hop"
    },
    {
      "question": "官衙",
      "answer": "かんが",
      "meaning": "government office, government agency"
    },
    {
      "question": "振飛車",
      "answer": "ふりびしゃ",
      "meaning": "ranging rook opening, strategy of initially moving the rook sideways"
    },
    {
      "question": "名文句",
      "answer": "めいもんく",
      "meaning": "witty (happy, apt) remark, well-worded saying, epigram, aphorism"
    },
    {
      "question": "公開鍵",
      "answer": "こうかいかぎ",
      "meaning": "public key"
    },
    {
      "question": "本状",
      "answer": "ほんじょう",
      "meaning": "this document, this letter, this writing"
    },
    {
      "question": "一次関数",
      "answer": "いちじかんすう",
      "meaning": "linear function"
    },
    {
      "question": "黄酒",
      "answer": "おうしゅ,こうしゅ",
      "meaning": "huangjiu, undistilled Chinese alcohol made of fermented grains"
    },
    {
      "question": "紫雲",
      "answer": "しうん",
      "meaning": "purple clouds, clouds on which Amida Buddha rides to welcome the spirits of the dead"
    },
    {
      "question": "公益法人",
      "answer": "こうえきほうじん",
      "meaning": "public-service corporation, charitable corporation, juridical (legal) person working for the public"
    },
    {
      "question": "童画",
      "answer": "どうが",
      "meaning": "pictures drawn by child, pictures for children"
    },
    {
      "question": "病気見舞",
      "answer": "びょうきみまい",
      "meaning": "get-well card (gift, letter), visit to (inquiry after) a sick person"
    },
    {
      "question": "矢車",
      "answer": "やぐるま",
      "meaning": "arrow wheel (decorative windmill on the pole on which carp streamers are raised)"
    },
    {
      "question": "有功",
      "answer": "ゆうこう",
      "meaning": "merit"
    },
    {
      "question": "誰某",
      "answer": "だれそれ",
      "meaning": "a certain someone, Mr So-and-so"
    },
    {
      "question": "前借金",
      "answer": "ぜんしゃくきん,ぜんしゃっきん",
      "meaning": "loan, advance"
    },
    {
      "question": "優々",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "参宮",
      "answer": "さんぐう",
      "meaning": "pilgrimage (esp. to the Ise Grand Shrine)"
    },
    {
      "question": "隠し田",
      "answer": "かくしだ",
      "meaning": "unregistered rice field"
    },
    {
      "question": "詛い",
      "answer": "のろい",
      "meaning": "curse, spell, malediction"
    },
    {
      "question": "鮒鮨",
      "answer": "ふなずし",
      "meaning": "funazushi, old-style fermented crucian carp sushi"
    },
    {
      "question": "下作",
      "answer": "げさく,したさく",
      "meaning": "poor manufacture, poor quality, inferior goods"
    },
    {
      "question": "脆性",
      "answer": "ぜいせい",
      "meaning": "brittleness"
    },
    {
      "question": "債務超過",
      "answer": "さいむちょうか",
      "meaning": "insolvency"
    },
    {
      "question": "導水管",
      "answer": "どうすいかん",
      "meaning": "water pipe"
    },
    {
      "question": "睦ぶ",
      "answer": "むつぶ",
      "meaning": "to be harmonious, to get on well, to be intimate or close"
    },
    {
      "question": "灌腸",
      "answer": "かんちょう",
      "meaning": "(giving an) enema"
    },
    {
      "question": "安気",
      "answer": "あんき",
      "meaning": "ease, comfort, feeling at home"
    },
    {
      "question": "三尖弁",
      "answer": "さんせんべん",
      "meaning": "tricuspid valve"
    },
    {
      "question": "脳浮腫",
      "answer": "のうふしゅ",
      "meaning": "cerebral edema, cerebral oedema"
    },
    {
      "question": "卓袱",
      "answer": "しっぽく,ちゃぶ",
      "meaning": "Chinese-style low dining table, Japanese-Chinese cuisine, served family-style (large dishes, diners"
    },
    {
      "question": "海盆",
      "answer": "かいぼん",
      "meaning": "ocean basin"
    },
    {
      "question": "公刊",
      "answer": "こうかん",
      "meaning": "publication"
    },
    {
      "question": "娘心",
      "answer": "むすめごころ",
      "meaning": "girlish mind, girlish innocence"
    },
    {
      "question": "労働争議",
      "answer": "ろうどうそうぎ",
      "meaning": "labor dispute, labour dispute, industrial dispute, strike"
    },
    {
      "question": "負ぶい紐",
      "answer": "おぶいひも",
      "meaning": "baby backpack, back-mounted baby carrier, sling"
    },
    {
      "question": "旅役者",
      "answer": "たびやくしゃ",
      "meaning": "itinerant entertainer or troupe"
    },
    {
      "question": "災異",
      "answer": "さいい",
      "meaning": "natural disaster, calamity"
    },
    {
      "question": "嗟嘆",
      "answer": "さたん",
      "meaning": "lamentation, deploring, admiration, praise"
    },
    {
      "question": "蹈鞴",
      "answer": "たたら",
      "meaning": "foot-operated bellows, foot bellows"
    },
    {
      "question": "非命",
      "answer": "ひめい",
      "meaning": "unnatural or untimely death"
    },
    {
      "question": "洗浄器",
      "answer": "せんじょうき",
      "meaning": "washer, syringe"
    },
    {
      "question": "然に非ず",
      "answer": "さにあらず",
      "meaning": "not so"
    },
    {
      "question": "軟膜",
      "answer": "なんまく",
      "meaning": "pia mater (membranes surrounding the brain and spinal cord)"
    },
    {
      "question": "讖",
      "answer": "しん",
      "meaning": "foretelling, prophecy"
    },
    {
      "question": "横寝",
      "answer": "よこね",
      "meaning": "sleeping on one's side, lying on one's side"
    },
    {
      "question": "耽楽",
      "answer": "たんらく",
      "meaning": "indulging in pleasure, giving oneself up to enjoyment"
    },
    {
      "question": "秋冷",
      "answer": "しゅうれい",
      "meaning": "cool autumn weather, cool fall weather"
    },
    {
      "question": "撓垂れる",
      "answer": "しなだれる",
      "meaning": "to droop"
    },
    {
      "question": "別間",
      "answer": "べつま",
      "meaning": "separate room, special room"
    },
    {
      "question": "多事多難",
      "answer": "たじたなん",
      "meaning": "various difficulties"
    },
    {
      "question": "則天去私",
      "answer": "そくてんきょし",
      "meaning": "selfless devotion to justice"
    },
    {
      "question": "言い違い",
      "answer": "いいちがい",
      "meaning": "slip of the tongue, misstatement"
    },
    {
      "question": "結い目",
      "answer": "ゆいめ",
      "meaning": "knot"
    },
    {
      "question": "青黛",
      "answer": "せいたい",
      "meaning": "blue eyebrow pencil, blue eyebrows, deep blue, dark blue"
    },
    {
      "question": "不評判",
      "answer": "ふひょうばん",
      "meaning": "bad reputation, disgrace, unpopularity"
    },
    {
      "question": "淡彩",
      "answer": "たんさい",
      "meaning": "light colouring, light coloring"
    },
    {
      "question": "聴許",
      "answer": "ちょうきょ",
      "meaning": "permission"
    },
    {
      "question": "通俗小説",
      "answer": "つうぞくしょうせつ",
      "meaning": "popular novel"
    },
    {
      "question": "置き碁",
      "answer": "おきご",
      "meaning": "handicap go, game of go played with a handicap"
    },
    {
      "question": "割り木",
      "answer": "わりき",
      "meaning": "split firewood"
    },
    {
      "question": "神明裁判",
      "answer": "しんめいさいばん",
      "meaning": "trial by ordeal"
    },
    {
      "question": "巌頭",
      "answer": "がんとう",
      "meaning": "top of a massive rock"
    },
    {
      "question": "人馴れる",
      "answer": "ひとなれる",
      "meaning": "to become accustomed to people"
    },
    {
      "question": "脊髄神経",
      "answer": "せきずいしんけい",
      "meaning": "spinal nerves"
    },
    {
      "question": "常置",
      "answer": "じょうち",
      "meaning": "permanent, standing"
    },
    {
      "question": "糞戯け",
      "answer": "くそたわけ",
      "meaning": "idiot, shitbrain"
    },
    {
      "question": "保科正之",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "現ずる",
      "answer": "げんずる",
      "meaning": "to appear, to reveal, to show"
    },
    {
      "question": "天秤宮",
      "answer": "てんびんきゅう",
      "meaning": "Libra (7th zodiacal sign), the Scales"
    },
    {
      "question": "遺棄罪",
      "answer": "いきざい",
      "meaning": "abandonment"
    },
    {
      "question": "大切り",
      "answer": "おおぎり",
      "meaning": "large cut (e.g. of meat), last piece of the day's programme, last act of a play, comic dialogue as t"
    },
    {
      "question": "芳賀",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "司式",
      "answer": "ししき",
      "meaning": "officiating (a ceremony), presiding (over a service)"
    },
    {
      "question": "風船玉",
      "answer": "ふうせんだま",
      "meaning": "toy balloon"
    },
    {
      "question": "会規",
      "answer": "かいき",
      "meaning": "society by-laws"
    },
    {
      "question": "悟道",
      "answer": "ごどう",
      "meaning": "(the path of spiritual) enlightenment"
    },
    {
      "question": "冬鳥",
      "answer": "ふゆどり",
      "meaning": "winter bird (resident)"
    },
    {
      "question": "宗教教育",
      "answer": "しゅうきょうきょういく",
      "meaning": "religious education"
    },
    {
      "question": "太刀先",
      "answer": "たちさき",
      "meaning": "point of a sword, forceful debate"
    },
    {
      "question": "可汗",
      "answer": "かがん",
      "meaning": "khan"
    },
    {
      "question": "久三",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "繊巧",
      "answer": "せんこう",
      "meaning": "fine workmanship"
    },
    {
      "question": "膠質",
      "answer": "こうしつ,にかわしつ",
      "meaning": "colloid"
    },
    {
      "question": "東男",
      "answer": "あずまおとこ",
      "meaning": "man from eastern Japan (esp. Edo or elsewhere in the Kanto region)"
    },
    {
      "question": "合評",
      "answer": "がっぴょう",
      "meaning": "joint review, joint criticism"
    },
    {
      "question": "空事",
      "answer": "そらごと",
      "meaning": "fake, fabrication"
    },
    {
      "question": "月別",
      "answer": "つきべつ",
      "meaning": "by months"
    },
    {
      "question": "傭船",
      "answer": "ようせん",
      "meaning": "chartered ship, chartering or hiring a vessel"
    },
    {
      "question": "判決理由",
      "answer": "はんけつりゆう",
      "meaning": "ratio decidendi, reason for a verdict"
    },
    {
      "question": "風害",
      "answer": "ふうがい",
      "meaning": "wind damage, storm damage"
    },
    {
      "question": "本結び",
      "answer": "ほんむすび",
      "meaning": "square knot"
    },
    {
      "question": "報謝",
      "answer": "ほうしゃ",
      "meaning": "repaying a favor, repaying a favour"
    },
    {
      "question": "輾転",
      "answer": "てんてん",
      "meaning": "rolling about, tossing and turning (in bed), jactitation, jactation"
    },
    {
      "question": "脈搏",
      "answer": "みゃくはく",
      "meaning": "pulse, pulse rate, pulsation, stroke of pulse"
    },
    {
      "question": "電気通信",
      "answer": "でんきつうしん",
      "meaning": "telecommunications"
    },
    {
      "question": "色子",
      "answer": "いろこ",
      "meaning": "kabuki actor who is also a male prostitute"
    },
    {
      "question": "吐剤",
      "answer": "とざい",
      "meaning": "emetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "僕女",
      "answer": "ぼくおんな",
      "meaning": "woman who uses the usually male personal pronoun 'boku' to refer to herself"
    },
    {
      "question": "水圏",
      "answer": "すいけん",
      "meaning": "hydrosphere"
    },
    {
      "question": "偏頗",
      "answer": "へんぱ",
      "meaning": "favoritism, favouritism, discrimination"
    },
    {
      "question": "鬼百合",
      "answer": "おにゆり",
      "meaning": "tiger lily (Lilium lancifolium)"
    },
    {
      "question": "無水鍋",
      "answer": "むすいなべ",
      "meaning": "pan which can be used without water"
    },
    {
      "question": "金口",
      "answer": "きんぐち",
      "meaning": "gold-colored paper wrapped around the tip of a cigarette (coloured)"
    },
    {
      "question": "花材",
      "answer": "かざい",
      "meaning": "material used for flower arrangement"
    },
    {
      "question": "聴手",
      "answer": "ききて",
      "meaning": "hearer, listener, audience, interviewer, questioner"
    },
    {
      "question": "協業",
      "answer": "きょうぎょう",
      "meaning": "cooperative industry"
    },
    {
      "question": "青丹",
      "answer": "あおたん,あおに",
      "meaning": "5-point card with a blue tanzaku, blue ribbon card, scoring combination consisting of the three 5-po"
    },
    {
      "question": "解析学",
      "answer": "かいせきがく",
      "meaning": "analysis"
    },
    {
      "question": "因数",
      "answer": "いんすう",
      "meaning": "factor"
    },
    {
      "question": "演算子",
      "answer": "えんざんし",
      "meaning": "operator"
    },
    {
      "question": "粉吹き芋",
      "answer": "こふきいも",
      "meaning": "dish of potatoes first boiled, then spun around while fried in a bowl (making them look as if covere"
    },
    {
      "question": "満目",
      "answer": "まんもく",
      "meaning": "as far as the eye can see"
    },
    {
      "question": "剰余金",
      "answer": "じょうよきん",
      "meaning": "surplus, balance"
    },
    {
      "question": "マニ教",
      "answer": "マニきょう",
      "meaning": "Manichaeism"
    },
    {
      "question": "黄花",
      "answer": "こうか",
      "meaning": "chrysanthemum"
    },
    {
      "question": "話頭",
      "answer": "わとう",
      "meaning": "topic, subject"
    },
    {
      "question": "受洗",
      "answer": "じゅせん",
      "meaning": "being baptized, undergoing baptism"
    },
    {
      "question": "口上手",
      "answer": "くちじょうず",
      "meaning": "being good at conversation, conversationalist, good talker, smooth-talker"
    },
    {
      "question": "蒲鉾形",
      "answer": "かまぼこがた",
      "meaning": "semi-cylindrical"
    },
    {
      "question": "四維",
      "answer": "しい,しゆい",
      "meaning": "four ordinal directions, four cardinal principles of the state (propriety, justice, integrity, sense"
    },
    {
      "question": "帝威",
      "answer": "ていい",
      "meaning": "imperial majesty"
    },
    {
      "question": "袋帯",
      "answer": "ふくろおび",
      "meaning": "double-woven obi"
    },
    {
      "question": "霞網",
      "answer": "かすみあみ",
      "meaning": "fowling net"
    },
    {
      "question": "成文法",
      "answer": "せいぶんほう",
      "meaning": "written law, statutory law"
    },
    {
      "question": "身仕舞い",
      "answer": "みじまい",
      "meaning": "dressing oneself (e.g. to go out), outfitting oneself"
    },
    {
      "question": "漢族",
      "answer": "かんぞく",
      "meaning": "Han race, Han people"
    },
    {
      "question": "馬鹿舌",
      "answer": "ばかじた",
      "meaning": "poor taste (in food), unsophisticated palate"
    },
    {
      "question": "徳育",
      "answer": "とくいく",
      "meaning": "moral education"
    },
    {
      "question": "収攬",
      "answer": "しゅうらん",
      "meaning": "grasping, winning over"
    },
    {
      "question": "核子",
      "answer": "かくし",
      "meaning": "nucleon"
    },
    {
      "question": "済度",
      "answer": "さいど",
      "meaning": "redemption, salvation"
    },
    {
      "question": "月琴",
      "answer": "げっきん",
      "meaning": "yueqin (4-stringed Chinese lute)"
    },
    {
      "question": "内食",
      "answer": "ないしょく,うちしょく",
      "meaning": "home cooking, eating at home"
    },
    {
      "question": "世俗主義",
      "answer": "せぞくしゅぎ",
      "meaning": "secularism"
    },
    {
      "question": "入梅",
      "answer": "つゆいり,にゅうばい,ついり",
      "meaning": "entering the rainy season, beginning of the rainy season"
    },
    {
      "question": "聖寿",
      "answer": "せいじゅ",
      "meaning": "age or life of the emperor"
    },
    {
      "question": "育メン",
      "answer": "いくメン",
      "meaning": "man who enjoys child rearing"
    },
    {
      "question": "歳時記",
      "answer": "さいじき",
      "meaning": "almanac of seasonal words (for haiku poets)"
    },
    {
      "question": "師表",
      "answer": "しひょう",
      "meaning": "model, pattern, paragon, leader, teacher"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤札",
      "answer": "あかふだ",
      "meaning": "red tag (esp. one attached to sold goods or discounted products), (red) card in the isu suit (in mek"
    },
    {
      "question": "膀胱結石",
      "answer": "ぼうこうけっせき",
      "meaning": "bladder stones, cystoliths"
    },
    {
      "question": "災害保険",
      "answer": "さいがいほけん",
      "meaning": "disaster insurance"
    },
    {
      "question": "動脈血",
      "answer": "どうみゃくけつ,どうみゃっけつ",
      "meaning": "arterial blood"
    },
    {
      "question": "傑人",
      "answer": "けつじん",
      "meaning": "outstanding person"
    },
    {
      "question": "本願寺派",
      "answer": "ほんがんじは",
      "meaning": "Honganji sect (of Shin Buddhism)"
    },
    {
      "question": "送信所",
      "answer": "そうしんじょ",
      "meaning": "transmitting station (e.g. for TV)"
    },
    {
      "question": "消炎剤",
      "answer": "しょうえんざい",
      "meaning": "anti-inflammatory agent, antiphlogistic"
    },
    {
      "question": "電力系統",
      "answer": "でんりょくけいとう",
      "meaning": "electric power system, electric system, power system"
    },
    {
      "question": "二重拘束",
      "answer": "にじゅうこうそく",
      "meaning": "double bind"
    },
    {
      "question": "脳磁図",
      "answer": "のうじず",
      "meaning": "magnetoencephalogram"
    },
    {
      "question": "風俗画",
      "answer": "ふうぞくが",
      "meaning": "genre picture, painting depicting customs"
    },
    {
      "question": "炭車",
      "answer": "たんしゃ",
      "meaning": "coal wagon"
    },
    {
      "question": "内転筋",
      "answer": "ないてんきん",
      "meaning": "adductor muscle"
    },
    {
      "question": "憎悪犯罪",
      "answer": "ぞうおはんざい",
      "meaning": "hate crime"
    },
    {
      "question": "星間雲",
      "answer": "せいかんうん",
      "meaning": "interstellar cloud"
    },
    {
      "question": "才略",
      "answer": "さいりゃく",
      "meaning": "wise planning"
    },
    {
      "question": "任意団体",
      "answer": "にんいだんたい",
      "meaning": "private organization (neither controlled nor protected by law), private organisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "止り木",
      "answer": "とまりぎ",
      "meaning": "perch, barstool"
    },
    {
      "question": "固陋",
      "answer": "ころう",
      "meaning": "stubbornly sticking to old ways, dislike of new things, narrow-mindedness"
    },
    {
      "question": "雅文",
      "answer": "がぶん",
      "meaning": "elegant (literary) style"
    },
    {
      "question": "市制",
      "answer": "しせい",
      "meaning": "municipal organization, municipal organisation, municipality"
    },
    {
      "question": "着火点",
      "answer": "ちゃっかてん",
      "meaning": "ignition point"
    },
    {
      "question": "凡手",
      "answer": "ぼんしゅ",
      "meaning": "mediocre ability, person of ordinary skills, uninteresting (trivial, worthless) move (go, shogi, oth"
    },
    {
      "question": "明らめる",
      "answer": "あきらめる",
      "meaning": "to elucidate, to shed light on, to clarify"
    },
    {
      "question": "立野",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "化粧回し",
      "answer": "けしょうまわし",
      "meaning": "ornamental apron"
    },
    {
      "question": "枝垂れ",
      "answer": "しだれ",
      "meaning": "weeping form (e.g. tree)"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤短",
      "answer": "あかたん",
      "meaning": "5-point card with a red tanzaku, red ribbon card, the three 5-point cards with ribbons (high-scoring"
    },
    {
      "question": "連単",
      "answer": "れんたん",
      "meaning": "perfecta (bet), exacta, straight forecast"
    },
    {
      "question": "絹雲母",
      "answer": "きぬうんも",
      "meaning": "sericite"
    },
    {
      "question": "御作り",
      "answer": "おつくり",
      "meaning": "sashimi, make-up"
    },
    {
      "question": "熾盛",
      "answer": "しじょう,しせい",
      "meaning": "vigor (like leaping flames), liveliness"
    },
    {
      "question": "姓氏",
      "answer": "せいし",
      "meaning": "full name, family name"
    },
    {
      "question": "不遡及",
      "answer": "ふそきゅう",
      "meaning": "non-retroactivity"
    },
    {
      "question": "談じる",
      "answer": "だんじる",
      "meaning": "to talk, to discuss, to debate, to negotiate"
    },
    {
      "question": "微温的",
      "answer": "びおんてき",
      "meaning": "lukewarm, tepid, indifferent, halfhearted"
    },
    {
      "question": "掛算",
      "answer": "かけざん",
      "meaning": "multiplication"
    },
    {
      "question": "立命",
      "answer": "りつめい",
      "meaning": "peace of mind"
    },
    {
      "question": "銀泥",
      "answer": "ぎんでい,ぎんどろ",
      "meaning": "silver paint, white poplar (Populus alba)"
    },
    {
      "question": "返盃",
      "answer": "へんぱい",
      "meaning": "offering a cup (of sake) in return"
    },
    {
      "question": "破れ傘",
      "answer": "やぶれがさ",
      "meaning": "broken umbrella, torn umbrella, shredded umbrella plant (Syneilesis palmata)"
    },
    {
      "question": "橄欖",
      "answer": "かんらん",
      "meaning": "Chinese white olive (Canarium album), olive (Olea europea)"
    },
    {
      "question": "温泉療法",
      "answer": "おんせんりょうほう",
      "meaning": "hot-spring cure, onsen therapy, balneotherapy"
    },
    {
      "question": "木化",
      "answer": "もっか,もくか",
      "meaning": "lignification"
    },
    {
      "question": "友愛会",
      "answer": "ゆうあいかい",
      "meaning": "fraternal association, friendship society, fraternity"
    },
    {
      "question": "配偶子",
      "answer": "はいぐうし",
      "meaning": "gamete"
    },
    {
      "question": "鎮護国家",
      "answer": "ちんごこっか",
      "meaning": "spiritual protection of the state"
    },
    {
      "question": "武断政治",
      "answer": "ぶだんせいじ",
      "meaning": "military government"
    },
    {
      "question": "圧縮酸素",
      "answer": "あっしゅくさんそ",
      "meaning": "compressed oxygen"
    },
    {
      "question": "猿酒",
      "answer": "さるざけ,ましらざけ",
      "meaning": "monkey booze, sake-like liquid produced by the fermentation of fruits left by monkeys in tree caches"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛越",
      "answer": "ひえつ",
      "meaning": "jumping over (a hurdle), clearing (a fence), hurdling"
    },
    {
      "question": "散花",
      "answer": "さんげ",
      "meaning": "rite of scattering flowers, glorious death (in battle), heroic death"
    },
    {
      "question": "圏域",
      "answer": "けんいき",
      "meaning": "sphere (e.g. of knowledge, influence)"
    },
    {
      "question": "竜座",
      "answer": "りゅうざ",
      "meaning": "Draco (constellation), the Dragon"
    },
    {
      "question": "従業",
      "answer": "じゅうぎょう",
      "meaning": "employment"
    },
    {
      "question": "地口",
      "answer": "じぐち",
      "meaning": "pun, play on words"
    },
    {
      "question": "空心菜",
      "answer": "くうしんさい",
      "meaning": "Chinese water spinach (Ipomoea aquatica), ong choy, kang kong, water morning glory, water convolvulu"
    },
    {
      "question": "理非曲直",
      "answer": "りひきょくちょく",
      "meaning": "the rights and wrongs (of a case)"
    },
    {
      "question": "余響",
      "answer": "よきょう",
      "meaning": "echo, reverberation"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝押し",
      "answer": "ねおし",
      "meaning": "pressing clothes, etc. by placing them under the bedding while one sleeps"
    },
    {
      "question": "観照",
      "answer": "かんしょう",
      "meaning": "meditation, contemplation"
    },
    {
      "question": "良知",
      "answer": "りょうち",
      "meaning": "intuition"
    },
    {
      "question": "実証的",
      "answer": "じっしょうてき",
      "meaning": "empirical, positive"
    },
    {
      "question": "才色",
      "answer": "さいしょく",
      "meaning": "wit and beauty"
    },
    {
      "question": "耶蘇",
      "answer": "やそ",
      "meaning": "Christ"
    },
    {
      "question": "原泉",
      "answer": "げんせん",
      "meaning": "source (of a spring, etc.), source (of payment, energy, knowledge, etc.), origin, wellspring"
    },
    {
      "question": "全身浴",
      "answer": "ぜんしんよく",
      "meaning": "full-body bath, full-body bathing"
    },
    {
      "question": "牛頭天王",
      "answer": "ごずてんのう",
      "meaning": "Gozu Tenno (deity said to be the Indian god Gavagriva)"
    },
    {
      "question": "御見逸れ",
      "answer": "おみそれ",
      "meaning": "failing to recognize someone, underestimation"
    },
    {
      "question": "胃瘻",
      "answer": "いろう",
      "meaning": "gastric fistula, gastrosomy, gastrosoma"
    },
    {
      "question": "日捲り",
      "answer": "ひめくり",
      "meaning": "daily rip-off-a-page calendar, daily pad calendar"
    },
    {
      "question": "茸狩り",
      "answer": "きのこがり,たけがり",
      "meaning": "mushroom gathering"
    },
    {
      "question": "内妻",
      "answer": "ないさい",
      "meaning": "common-law wife"
    },
    {
      "question": "孤塁",
      "answer": "こるい",
      "meaning": "isolated stronghold"
    },
    {
      "question": "社会教育",
      "answer": "しゃかいきょういく",
      "meaning": "social education"
    },
    {
      "question": "同化政策",
      "answer": "どうかせいさく",
      "meaning": "assimilation policy"
    },
    {
      "question": "摂家",
      "answer": "せっけ",
      "meaning": "(line of) regents and advisers (advisors)"
    },
    {
      "question": "僻み根性",
      "answer": "ひがみこんじょう",
      "meaning": "prejudiced mind"
    },
    {
      "question": "震源域",
      "answer": "しんげんいき",
      "meaning": "hypocentral region"
    },
    {
      "question": "勇烈",
      "answer": "ゆうれつ",
      "meaning": "bravery, valor, valour, courage"
    },
    {
      "question": "給する",
      "answer": "きゅうする",
      "meaning": "to provide, to supply, to furnish"
    },
    {
      "question": "夏木立",
      "answer": "なつこだち",
      "meaning": "grove in summer"
    },
    {
      "question": "無常の風",
      "answer": "むじょうのかぜ",
      "meaning": "wind of impermanence (that ends people lives, like the wind scattering a flower's petals)"
    },
    {
      "question": "黄金分割",
      "answer": "おうごんぶんかつ",
      "meaning": "(artistic) golden section"
    },
    {
      "question": "慚恚",
      "answer": "ざんい",
      "meaning": "being ashamed and angry"
    },
    {
      "question": "荒漠",
      "answer": "こうばく",
      "meaning": "desolate (e.g. plains), ruined"
    },
    {
      "question": "註記",
      "answer": "ちゅうき",
      "meaning": "annotation, commentary, explanatory note"
    },
    {
      "question": "板唐戸",
      "answer": "いたからど",
      "meaning": "door made of one or several wooden planks and no door framework"
    },
    {
      "question": "諳んずる",
      "answer": "そらんずる",
      "meaning": "to memorize, to memorise, to recite from memory"
    },
    {
      "question": "遠眼",
      "answer": "えんがん",
      "meaning": "farsightedness, hyperopia, hypermetropia, far-sightedness"
    },
    {
      "question": "簫",
      "answer": "しょう",
      "meaning": "xiao (vertical Chinese bamboo flute)"
    },
    {
      "question": "炭窯",
      "answer": "すみがま",
      "meaning": "charcoal kiln, charcoal pile"
    },
    {
      "question": "岩座",
      "answer": "いわざ,いわくら",
      "meaning": "stone-like socle (used as the base for a Buddhist statue), dwelling place of a god (usu. in referenc"
    },
    {
      "question": "廟議",
      "answer": "びょうぎ",
      "meaning": "court council, privy council"
    },
    {
      "question": "長着",
      "answer": "ながぎ",
      "meaning": "long kimono, ankle-length traditional Japanese garment"
    },
    {
      "question": "私書",
      "answer": "ししょ",
      "meaning": "private document, personal letter"
    },
    {
      "question": "署する",
      "answer": "しょする",
      "meaning": "to sign (one's signature)"
    },
    {
      "question": "敗戦投手",
      "answer": "はいせんとうしゅ",
      "meaning": "losing pitcher"
    },
    {
      "question": "数直線",
      "answer": "すうちょくせん",
      "meaning": "number line (e.g. on a graph), real number line"
    },
    {
      "question": "広目天",
      "answer": "こうもくてん",
      "meaning": "Virupaksa (Buddhist deity)"
    },
    {
      "question": "態様",
      "answer": "たいよう",
      "meaning": "state, condition, situation, terms"
    },
    {
      "question": "皎皎",
      "answer": "こうこう,きょうきょう",
      "meaning": "bright (esp. of the moon), broad and empty"
    },
    {
      "question": "五月人形",
      "answer": "ごがつにんぎょう",
      "meaning": "Boys' May Festival dolls"
    },
    {
      "question": "鶯張り",
      "answer": "うぐいすばり",
      "meaning": "nightingale (flooring), method of laying floors to deliberately make a noise (like a nightingale's c"
    },
    {
      "question": "加熱器",
      "answer": "かねつき",
      "meaning": "heating apparatus, heater"
    },
    {
      "question": "正多面体",
      "answer": "せいためんたい",
      "meaning": "regular polyhedron"
    },
    {
      "question": "野焼",
      "answer": "のやき",
      "meaning": "burning off a field (in early spring)"
    },
    {
      "question": "脊梁",
      "answer": "せきりょう",
      "meaning": "backbone, mountain range"
    },
    {
      "question": "透間",
      "answer": "すきま",
      "meaning": "crevice, crack, gap, opening, clearance, spare moment, interval, break, pause, spare time, chink (in"
    },
    {
      "question": "武者人形",
      "answer": "むしゃにんぎょう",
      "meaning": "samurai doll"
    },
    {
      "question": "歯槽",
      "answer": "しそう",
      "meaning": "(dental) alveolus, (dental) alveoli, socket in the jaw containing the root of a tooth"
    },
    {
      "question": "古細菌",
      "answer": "こさいきん",
      "meaning": "archaea, archaebacteria"
    },
    {
      "question": "伐倒",
      "answer": "ばっとう",
      "meaning": "felling"
    },
    {
      "question": "呼水",
      "answer": "よびみず",
      "meaning": "pump-priming, rousing, stimulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "利害得失",
      "answer": "りがいとくしつ",
      "meaning": "advantages and disadvantages, pros and cons"
    },
    {
      "question": "専行",
      "answer": "せんこう",
      "meaning": "acting arbitrarily, arbitrary action"
    },
    {
      "question": "被く",
      "answer": "かずく,かづく",
      "meaning": "to wear on the head, to have cloth, clothing, etc. bestowed upon one by their lord or master, to wea"
    },
    {
      "question": "推断",
      "answer": "すいだん",
      "meaning": "inference, deduction"
    },
    {
      "question": "仏法僧",
      "answer": "ぶっぽうそう",
      "meaning": "Buddha, Dharma, Sangha, The Three Jewels, Buddha, the teachings of Buddha, and the community of monk"
    },
    {
      "question": "促音",
      "answer": "そくおん",
      "meaning": "geminate consonant (small 'tsu' in Japanese)"
    },
    {
      "question": "剛腹",
      "answer": "ごうふく",
      "meaning": "obstinacy, stubbornness"
    },
    {
      "question": "技能検定",
      "answer": "ぎのうけんてい",
      "meaning": "technical skills test, trade skill test"
    },
    {
      "question": "癈人",
      "answer": "はいじん",
      "meaning": "cripple, disabled person, invalid"
    },
    {
      "question": "刀創",
      "answer": "とうそう",
      "meaning": "sword wound, sword cut"
    },
    {
      "question": "今日的",
      "answer": "こんにちてき",
      "meaning": "modern, up-to-date"
    },
    {
      "question": "驚歎",
      "answer": "きょうたん",
      "meaning": "wonder, admiration, being struck with admiration"
    },
    {
      "question": "過給機",
      "answer": "かきゅうき",
      "meaning": "supercharger"
    },
    {
      "question": "案じ顔",
      "answer": "あんじがお",
      "meaning": "worried look"
    },
    {
      "question": "令兄",
      "answer": "れいけい",
      "meaning": "your elder brother"
    },
    {
      "question": "丁石",
      "answer": "ちょういし",
      "meaning": "roadside stone distance indicators placed at intervals of one chō (approx. 109 meters)"
    },
    {
      "question": "青華",
      "answer": "せいか",
      "meaning": "ceramics with a blue pattern on a white background"
    },
    {
      "question": "劇しい",
      "answer": "はげしい",
      "meaning": "violent, furious, tempestuous, extreme, intense, fierce, strong, fervent, vehement, incessant, relen"
    },
    {
      "question": "玩弄物",
      "answer": "がんろうぶつ",
      "meaning": "plaything"
    },
    {
      "question": "紙花",
      "answer": "かみばな",
      "meaning": "paper flowers, paper flowers for a funeral, paper handed out as a means of congratulations in a red"
    },
    {
      "question": "給気",
      "answer": "きゅうき",
      "meaning": "air supply, aeration"
    },
    {
      "question": "僕婢",
      "answer": "ぼくひ",
      "meaning": "male and female servants"
    },
    {
      "question": "代表理事",
      "answer": "だいひょうりじ",
      "meaning": "representative of a board of directors, spokesperson for a board of directors"
    },
    {
      "question": "偉観",
      "answer": "いかん",
      "meaning": "magnificent sight"
    },
    {
      "question": "震天動地",
      "answer": "しんてんどうち",
      "meaning": "earth-shaking"
    },
    {
      "question": "組積造",
      "answer": "そせきぞう",
      "meaning": "masonry, masonry structure, construction method using brick, stone, concrete blocks, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "食時",
      "answer": "しょくじ",
      "meaning": "meal time, mealtime"
    },
    {
      "question": "痲痺",
      "answer": "まひ",
      "meaning": "paralysis, palsy, numbness, stupor"
    },
    {
      "question": "愚女",
      "answer": "ぐじょ",
      "meaning": "daughter"
    },
    {
      "question": "力戦奮闘",
      "answer": "りきせんふんとう",
      "meaning": "fighting with all one's might, fighting up against, making strenuous efforts"
    },
    {
      "question": "独股",
      "answer": "とっこ,どっこ",
      "meaning": "single-pronged vajra, tokko, dokko, copper or iron implement, pointed at both ends, used in esoteric"
    },
    {
      "question": "不善",
      "answer": "ふぜん",
      "meaning": "evil, sin, vice, mischief"
    },
    {
      "question": "共白髪",
      "answer": "ともしらが",
      "meaning": "growing old together (as a couple), white hemp thread (as a betrothal gift, representing the hair of"
    },
    {
      "question": "終止形",
      "answer": "しゅうしけい",
      "meaning": "plain form (of a Japanese verb or adjective), dictionary form, predicative form"
    },
    {
      "question": "油に水",
      "answer": "あぶらにみず",
      "meaning": "incompatible, (going together) like oil and water"
    },
    {
      "question": "絹綿",
      "answer": "きぬわた",
      "meaning": "silk floss"
    },
    {
      "question": "迦羅",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "花笠",
      "answer": "はながさ",
      "meaning": "type of conical hat adorned with flowers (used in Japanese traditional performing arts), hanagasa"
    },
    {
      "question": "近親結婚",
      "answer": "きんしんけっこん",
      "meaning": "consanguineous marriage"
    },
    {
      "question": "岩蟹",
      "answer": "いわがに",
      "meaning": "striped shore crab (Pachygrapsus crassipes)"
    },
    {
      "question": "足浴",
      "answer": "そくよく",
      "meaning": "footbath (for improving blood circulation)"
    },
    {
      "question": "釣り舟",
      "answer": "つりぶね,つりふね",
      "meaning": "fishing boat, boat-shaped hanging flower vase"
    },
    {
      "question": "邪曲",
      "answer": "じゃきょく",
      "meaning": "wickedness"
    },
    {
      "question": "立所に",
      "answer": "たちどころに",
      "meaning": "at once, there and then, immediately"
    },
    {
      "question": "五賢帝",
      "answer": "ごけんてい",
      "meaning": "the Five Good Emperors (of the Roman Empire; Nerva, Trajan, Hadrian, Antoninus Pius, and Marcus Aure"
    },
    {
      "question": "後頭葉",
      "answer": "こうとうよう",
      "meaning": "occipital lobe"
    },
    {
      "question": "立ちっぱ",
      "answer": "たちっぱ",
      "meaning": "standing on one's feet for a long time"
    },
    {
      "question": "旗持",
      "answer": "はたもち",
      "meaning": "standard-bearer, flag-bearer"
    },
    {
      "question": "引算",
      "answer": "ひきざん",
      "meaning": "subtraction"
    },
    {
      "question": "陸前",
      "answer": "りくぜん",
      "meaning": "Rikuzen (former province located in parts of present-day Miyagi and Iwate prefectures)"
    },
    {
      "question": "力行",
      "answer": "りっこう,りょっこう",
      "meaning": "strenuous efforts, exertion"
    },
    {
      "question": "練鉄",
      "answer": "れんてつ",
      "meaning": "wrought iron"
    },
    {
      "question": "門札",
      "answer": "もんさつ,かどふだ",
      "meaning": "doorplate, nameplate, gate pass"
    },
    {
      "question": "朝三暮四",
      "answer": "ちょうさんぼし",
      "meaning": "being preoccupied with immediate (superficial) differences without realizing that there are no diffe"
    },
    {
      "question": "行雲流水",
      "answer": "こううんりゅうすい",
      "meaning": "(metaphorically) floating with the tide"
    },
    {
      "question": "閻浮提",
      "answer": "えんぶだい",
      "meaning": "Jambudvipa, continent of the terrestrial world"
    },
    {
      "question": "隠れ肥満",
      "answer": "かくれひまん",
      "meaning": "normal weight obesity, hidden obesity, being thin while having an unhealthily high body fat percenta"
    },
    {
      "question": "ラマ教",
      "answer": "ラマきょう",
      "meaning": "Lamaism"
    },
    {
      "question": "行政事務",
      "answer": "ぎょうせいじむ",
      "meaning": "administrative affairs"
    },
    {
      "question": "甲斐犬",
      "answer": "かいいぬ,かいけん",
      "meaning": "Kai, Kai ken, Japanese dog breed"
    },
    {
      "question": "手懸り",
      "answer": "てがかり",
      "meaning": "clue, lead, key, trail, scent, track, handhold, hold"
    },
    {
      "question": "洞門",
      "answer": "どうもん",
      "meaning": "cave entrance, tunnel"
    },
    {
      "question": "疣贅",
      "answer": "ゆうぜい",
      "meaning": "wart, verruca"
    },
    {
      "question": "抗敵",
      "answer": "こうてき",
      "meaning": "opposition, resistance"
    },
    {
      "question": "法律行為",
      "answer": "ほうりつこうい",
      "meaning": "legal action"
    },
    {
      "question": "和敬清寂",
      "answer": "わけいせいじゃく",
      "meaning": "harmony, respect, purity and tranquility, the four most important elements of the tea ceremony"
    },
    {
      "question": "地和",
      "answer": "チーホー",
      "meaning": "blessing of earth, winning with a self-drawn tile in the first turn"
    },
    {
      "question": "犬に論語",
      "answer": "いぬにろんご",
      "meaning": "wasting one's breath (trying to explain something), (reading) the Analects of Confucius to a dog"
    },
    {
      "question": "暗黙知",
      "answer": "あんもくち",
      "meaning": "tacit knowledge (knowledge management terminology)"
    },
    {
      "question": "淋漓",
      "answer": "りんり",
      "meaning": "dripping (with), brimming"
    },
    {
      "question": "将几",
      "answer": "しょうぎ",
      "meaning": "camp stool, folding stool"
    },
    {
      "question": "逼る",
      "answer": "せまる",
      "meaning": "to approach, to draw near, to be imminent, to press (someone for something), to urge, to compel"
    },
    {
      "question": "喇叭飲み",
      "answer": "らっぱのみ",
      "meaning": "drinking straight from a bottle"
    },
    {
      "question": "株価指数",
      "answer": "かぶかしすう",
      "meaning": "stock price index"
    },
    {
      "question": "脱殻",
      "answer": "ぬけがら",
      "meaning": "cast-off skin (snake, insect, etc.), husk, empty shell, exuvia, exuviae"
    },
    {
      "question": "其の内",
      "answer": "そのうち",
      "meaning": "before very long, soon, someday, one of these days, sooner or later, of the previously mentioned, of"
    },
    {
      "question": "溜まり水",
      "answer": "たまりみず",
      "meaning": "stagnant water"
    },
    {
      "question": "弾ずる",
      "answer": "だんずる",
      "meaning": "to play (a stringed instrument)"
    },
    {
      "question": "仮髪",
      "answer": "かはつ",
      "meaning": "hairpiece, false hair, wig"
    },
    {
      "question": "合葬",
      "answer": "がっそう,ごうそう",
      "meaning": "joint burial, group burial, burying together"
    },
    {
      "question": "腎臓病",
      "answer": "じんぞうびょう",
      "meaning": "kidney trouble or disease"
    },
    {
      "question": "水洟",
      "answer": "みずばな",
      "meaning": "runny nose, snivelling, sniveling"
    },
    {
      "question": "佩",
      "answer": "はい",
      "meaning": "ancient oriental belt decoration, counter for swords"
    },
    {
      "question": "完納",
      "answer": "かんのう",
      "meaning": "full payment or delivery"
    },
    {
      "question": "忽せ",
      "answer": "ゆるがせ,いるかせ",
      "meaning": "negligent, careless, easygoing, relaxed"
    },
    {
      "question": "無線操縦",
      "answer": "むせんそうじゅう",
      "meaning": "radio-controlled (plane)"
    },
    {
      "question": "単推し",
      "answer": "たんおし",
      "meaning": "(being a) fan of a single member of a music group (esp. idol group)"
    },
    {
      "question": "知能検査",
      "answer": "ちのうけんさ",
      "meaning": "intelligence test"
    },
    {
      "question": "利他主義",
      "answer": "りたしゅぎ",
      "meaning": "altruism"
    },
    {
      "question": "仙客",
      "answer": "せんかく",
      "meaning": "immortal mountain wizard (in Taoism), crane"
    },
    {
      "question": "諾する",
      "answer": "だくする",
      "meaning": "to consent to, to assent to"
    },
    {
      "question": "三景",
      "answer": "さんけい",
      "meaning": "three famous beauty spots"
    },
    {
      "question": "俗名",
      "answer": "ぞくみょう,ぞくめい",
      "meaning": "common name, popular name, secular name, bad reputation"
    },
    {
      "question": "潤目",
      "answer": "うるめ",
      "meaning": "round herring (Etrumeus teres)"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛地",
      "answer": "とびち",
      "meaning": "detached territory, enclave, exclave, scattered landholdings"
    },
    {
      "question": "感取",
      "answer": "かんしゅ",
      "meaning": "feeling, sensing, understanding intuitively"
    },
    {
      "question": "電子署名",
      "answer": "でんししょめい",
      "meaning": "e-signature, electronic signature"
    },
    {
      "question": "札止め",
      "answer": "ふだどめ",
      "meaning": "full house, sell-out, putting up a sign forbidding entry, passage, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "起請文",
      "answer": "きしょうもん",
      "meaning": "religious oath in writing, written vow to the gods"
    },
    {
      "question": "背が立つ",
      "answer": "せがたつ",
      "meaning": "to have one's feet reach the bottom (e.g. when standing in water)"
    },
    {
      "question": "戯事",
      "answer": "ざれごと,たわむれごと",
      "meaning": "wanton sporting"
    },
    {
      "question": "畏服",
      "answer": "いふく",
      "meaning": "awe"
    },
    {
      "question": "牛蒡抜き",
      "answer": "ごぼうぬき",
      "meaning": "pulling something out (in a stroke), plucking out, forcibly removing one after another (e.g. demonst"
    },
    {
      "question": "罷免権",
      "answer": "ひめんけん",
      "meaning": "authority to dismiss someone (from a position)"
    },
    {
      "question": "智慮",
      "answer": "ちりょ",
      "meaning": "foresight, wisdom, sagacity"
    },
    {
      "question": "御猪口",
      "answer": "おちょこ",
      "meaning": "sake cup"
    },
    {
      "question": "去なす",
      "answer": "いなす",
      "meaning": "to parry, to sidestep, to dodge"
    },
    {
      "question": "特別国会",
      "answer": "とくべつこっかい",
      "meaning": "special Diet session, special session of the Diet, Diet session required to be convoked within thirt"
    },
    {
      "question": "東郊",
      "answer": "とうこう",
      "meaning": "eastern suburbs"
    },
    {
      "question": "嘆美",
      "answer": "たんび",
      "meaning": "admiration, adoration, extolling"
    },
    {
      "question": "斬捨て",
      "answer": "きりすて",
      "meaning": "cutting a person down (without a second thought), sacrificing, throwing to the wolves, treating as s"
    },
    {
      "question": "遊休",
      "answer": "ゆうきゅう",
      "meaning": "idle, unused, fallow"
    },
    {
      "question": "勇往",
      "answer": "ゆうおう",
      "meaning": "spirited advance, energetically going forward"
    },
    {
      "question": "別席",
      "answer": "べっせき",
      "meaning": "different seat, special seat, separate room, temporary rank after merging of two separate rankings i"
    },
    {
      "question": "楽部",
      "answer": "がくぶ",
      "meaning": "Music Department (part of the Board of Ceremonies of the Imperial Household Agency)"
    },
    {
      "question": "日語",
      "answer": "にちご",
      "meaning": "Japanese (language)"
    },
    {
      "question": "馬鹿鳥",
      "answer": "ばかどり",
      "meaning": "albatross"
    },
    {
      "question": "摂関",
      "answer": "せっかん",
      "meaning": "regents and advisers (advisors)"
    },
    {
      "question": "阿弥陀仏",
      "answer": "あみだぶつ",
      "meaning": "Amitabha"
    },
    {
      "question": "海綿動物",
      "answer": "かいめんどうぶつ",
      "meaning": "(sea) sponges"
    },
    {
      "question": "万年茸",
      "answer": "まんねんたけ",
      "meaning": "bracket fungus (Ganoderma lucidum), reishi mushroom"
    },
    {
      "question": "承引",
      "answer": "しょういん",
      "meaning": "consent, acceptance, agreement"
    },
    {
      "question": "間歇",
      "answer": "かんけつ",
      "meaning": "intermittence, intermittent"
    },
    {
      "question": "褶曲",
      "answer": "しゅうきょく",
      "meaning": "bend, geologic fold"
    },
    {
      "question": "冥境",
      "answer": "めいきょう",
      "meaning": "shades of the dead"
    },
    {
      "question": "令法",
      "answer": "りょうぶ",
      "meaning": "Japanese clethra, tree clethra, clethra barbinervis"
    },
    {
      "question": "厭人",
      "answer": "えんじん",
      "meaning": "misanthropy"
    },
    {
      "question": "強圧",
      "answer": "きょうあつ",
      "meaning": "pressure, duress, stress"
    },
    {
      "question": "亡友",
      "answer": "ぼうゆう",
      "meaning": "deceased friend"
    },
    {
      "question": "抽象性",
      "answer": "ちゅうしょうせい",
      "meaning": "abstractness, abstraction"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤狐",
      "answer": "あかぎつね",
      "meaning": "red fox (Vulpes vulpes)"
    },
    {
      "question": "骨細",
      "answer": "ほねぼそ",
      "meaning": "small-boned, thin-boned, slender, slight"
    },
    {
      "question": "駆潜艇",
      "answer": "くせんてい",
      "meaning": "submarine chaser"
    },
    {
      "question": "無期刑",
      "answer": "むきけい",
      "meaning": "life imprisonment"
    },
    {
      "question": "観兵式",
      "answer": "かんぺいしき",
      "meaning": "military review, (military) parade"
    },
    {
      "question": "授産",
      "answer": "じゅさん",
      "meaning": "sheltered work programs, sheltered work programmes, providing with work, giving employment"
    },
    {
      "question": "乗換え",
      "answer": "のりかえ",
      "meaning": "transfer (trains, buses, etc.), change, connection, switch (to another ideology, party, system, meth"
    },
    {
      "question": "砺波",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "寸間",
      "answer": "すんかん",
      "meaning": "moment's leisure"
    },
    {
      "question": "早発",
      "answer": "そうはつ",
      "meaning": "departing early in the morning, departing earlier than scheduled, premature (e.g. of an disease), ea"
    },
    {
      "question": "記念物",
      "answer": "きねんぶつ",
      "meaning": "souvenir, memento"
    },
    {
      "question": "相続分",
      "answer": "そうぞくぶん",
      "meaning": "share in inheritance, inheritance share, portion of inheritance"
    },
    {
      "question": "胸を病む",
      "answer": "むねをやむ",
      "meaning": "to become consumptive"
    },
    {
      "question": "排出物",
      "answer": "はいしゅつぶつ",
      "meaning": "discharge, excreta"
    },
    {
      "question": "屑入れ",
      "answer": "くずいれ",
      "meaning": "wastebasket, dustbin"
    },
    {
      "question": "信販",
      "answer": "しんぱん",
      "meaning": "sales on credit"
    },
    {
      "question": "丸切り",
      "answer": "まるきり",
      "meaning": "completely, absolutely, totally, (not) at all"
    },
    {
      "question": "物情",
      "answer": "ぶつじょう",
      "meaning": "public feeling, state of things"
    },
    {
      "question": "竹に雀",
      "answer": "たけにすずめ",
      "meaning": "match made in heaven, perfect match, great coupling, sparrow and bamboo (a common motif in poetry an"
    },
    {
      "question": "未墾",
      "answer": "みこん",
      "meaning": "uncultivated, wild"
    },
    {
      "question": "初節句",
      "answer": "はつぜっく",
      "meaning": "baby's first annual festival"
    },
    {
      "question": "政治責任",
      "answer": "せいじせきにん",
      "meaning": "(one's) administrative responsibilities"
    },
    {
      "question": "八紘一宇",
      "answer": "はっこういちう",
      "meaning": "universal brotherhood, all eight corners of the world under one roof"
    },
    {
      "question": "花嫁学校",
      "answer": "はなよめがっこう",
      "meaning": "school for training bachelor girls in homemaking arts, (a type of) finishing school"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り運ぶ",
      "answer": "とりはこぶ",
      "meaning": "to proceed smoothly"
    },
    {
      "question": "漁礁",
      "answer": "ぎょしょう",
      "meaning": "fish reef, reef where fish live and breed"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕付け",
      "answer": "しつけ",
      "meaning": "tacking (in needlework), basting, planting (esp. rice seedlings), discipline, training, teaching man"
    },
    {
      "question": "冥闇",
      "answer": "めいあん",
      "meaning": "gloom, shade"
    },
    {
      "question": "帰り掛け",
      "answer": "かえりがけ",
      "meaning": "on the way back, when about to go back"
    },
    {
      "question": "政教",
      "answer": "せいきょう",
      "meaning": "religion and politics, church and state"
    },
    {
      "question": "不体裁",
      "answer": "ふていさい",
      "meaning": "bad form or manners, indecency, impropriety"
    },
    {
      "question": "心柱",
      "answer": "しんばしら",
      "meaning": "central pillar of a pagoda, shinbashira"
    },
    {
      "question": "地祇",
      "answer": "くにつかみ,ちぎ",
      "meaning": "gods of the land, earthly deities"
    },
    {
      "question": "雌蕊",
      "answer": "めしべ,しずい",
      "meaning": "pistil"
    },
    {
      "question": "矯飾",
      "answer": "きょうしょく",
      "meaning": "affectation, pretense, pretence"
    },
    {
      "question": "頓悟",
      "answer": "とんご",
      "meaning": "sudden enlightenment"
    },
    {
      "question": "鼓笛",
      "answer": "こてき",
      "meaning": "drum and fife"
    },
    {
      "question": "駅家",
      "answer": "えきか,うまや,えきや",
      "meaning": "posthouse, station, post station"
    },
    {
      "question": "苫屋",
      "answer": "とまや",
      "meaning": "rush-thatched house"
    },
    {
      "question": "賭弓",
      "answer": "のりゆみ",
      "meaning": "prize archery, imperial archery event held annually on the 18th day of the first lunar month (Heian"
    },
    {
      "question": "用言",
      "answer": "ようげん",
      "meaning": "declinable word, inflectable word"
    },
    {
      "question": "真鯖",
      "answer": "まさば",
      "meaning": "chub mackerel (Scomber japonicus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "鴉片",
      "answer": "あへん",
      "meaning": "opium"
    },
    {
      "question": "装蹄",
      "answer": "そうてい",
      "meaning": "shoeing a horse, horseshoeing"
    },
    {
      "question": "後らせる",
      "answer": "おくらせる",
      "meaning": "to delay, to postpone, to put off, to slow down, to hold up, to retard, to put back (a clock)"
    },
    {
      "question": "比定",
      "answer": "ひてい",
      "meaning": "hypothesis (formed by comparison with other similar objects), identification"
    },
    {
      "question": "突として",
      "answer": "とつとして",
      "meaning": "suddenly, all of a sudden"
    },
    {
      "question": "全家",
      "answer": "ぜんか",
      "meaning": "the whole family, the whole house"
    },
    {
      "question": "宗義",
      "answer": "しゅうぎ",
      "meaning": "denominational doctrine, doctrine of a sect"
    },
    {
      "question": "米味噌",
      "answer": "こめみそ",
      "meaning": "rice miso, miso fermented with malted rice"
    },
    {
      "question": "牛裂き",
      "answer": "うしざき",
      "meaning": "tying a person's limbs to two or four bulls and making them run in different directions (Warring Sta"
    },
    {
      "question": "五菜",
      "answer": "ごさい",
      "meaning": "the five vegetables (garlic chive, Japanese leek, green onion, wasabi and mame), (meal of) five dish"
    },
    {
      "question": "立者",
      "answer": "たてもの",
      "meaning": "leading actor, leading figure, leader"
    },
    {
      "question": "海蝕",
      "answer": "かいしょく",
      "meaning": "marine erosion"
    },
    {
      "question": "開花前線",
      "answer": "かいかぜんせん",
      "meaning": "(cherry) blossom front, flower front"
    },
    {
      "question": "謝す",
      "answer": "しゃす",
      "meaning": "to thank, to apologize, to apologise, to say farewell, to retreat, to retire, to refuse, to pay back"
    },
    {
      "question": "部別",
      "answer": "ぶべつ",
      "meaning": "sorting"
    },
    {
      "question": "行脚僧",
      "answer": "あんぎゃそう",
      "meaning": "itinerant monk, monk on a pilgrimage"
    },
    {
      "question": "棒紅",
      "answer": "ぼうべに",
      "meaning": "lipstick"
    },
    {
      "question": "刺し子",
      "answer": "さしこ",
      "meaning": "quilting, quilted coat, quilted clothes"
    },
    {
      "question": "家父長権",
      "answer": "かふちょうけん",
      "meaning": "rights of the head of a family"
    },
    {
      "question": "厭世主義",
      "answer": "えんせいしゅぎ",
      "meaning": "pessimism"
    },
    {
      "question": "御参り",
      "answer": "おまいり",
      "meaning": "visit (to a shrine, grave, etc.), worship"
    },
    {
      "question": "着生",
      "answer": "ちゃくせい",
      "meaning": "epiphytic, designating a non-parasitic plant that grows on other plants"
    },
    {
      "question": "直系卑属",
      "answer": "ちょっけいひぞく",
      "meaning": "lineal descendant"
    },
    {
      "question": "累犯",
      "answer": "るいはん",
      "meaning": "repeated offense, repeated offence"
    },
    {
      "question": "捨て金",
      "answer": "すてがね",
      "meaning": "wasted money"
    },
    {
      "question": "射創",
      "answer": "しゃそう",
      "meaning": "bullet wound, gunshot wound"
    },
    {
      "question": "押しピン",
      "answer": "おしピン",
      "meaning": "drawing pin, thumbtack, pushpin"
    },
    {
      "question": "外向",
      "answer": "がいこう",
      "meaning": "extroversion"
    },
    {
      "question": "緩行",
      "answer": "かんこう",
      "meaning": "going slowly"
    },
    {
      "question": "土牢",
      "answer": "つちろう",
      "meaning": "dungeon, underground prison"
    },
    {
      "question": "沮喪",
      "answer": "そそう",
      "meaning": "loss of spirit, dejection"
    },
    {
      "question": "土地収用",
      "answer": "とちしゅうよう",
      "meaning": "land expropriation"
    },
    {
      "question": "臥竜",
      "answer": "がりゅう,がりょう",
      "meaning": "unrecognized genius, exceptional person hidden among the masses, reclining dragon"
    },
    {
      "question": "都道",
      "answer": "とどう",
      "meaning": "Tokyo municipal road"
    },
    {
      "question": "荒布",
      "answer": "あらめ",
      "meaning": "arame (species of kelp, Eisenia bicyclis)"
    },
    {
      "question": "奇瑞",
      "answer": "きずい",
      "meaning": "auspicious (good) omen"
    },
    {
      "question": "遊猟",
      "answer": "ゆうりょう",
      "meaning": "hunting"
    },
    {
      "question": "伸し掛る",
      "answer": "のしかかる",
      "meaning": "to lean on, to weigh on, to bend over, to lean forward"
    },
    {
      "question": "復水器",
      "answer": "ふくすいき",
      "meaning": "condenser"
    },
    {
      "question": "賀状",
      "answer": "がじょう",
      "meaning": "New Year's card"
    },
    {
      "question": "突合",
      "answer": "とつごう",
      "meaning": "matching, checking, comparison (of data)"
    },
    {
      "question": "募らす",
      "answer": "つのらす",
      "meaning": "to exacerbate, to exasperate"
    },
    {
      "question": "昇叙",
      "answer": "しょうじょ",
      "meaning": "promotion, advancement"
    },
    {
      "question": "然りとて",
      "answer": "さりとて",
      "meaning": "however, having said that, but"
    },
    {
      "question": "文雅",
      "answer": "ぶんが",
      "meaning": "elegant or refined style"
    },
    {
      "question": "一処",
      "answer": "ひとところ",
      "meaning": "one place, the same place, one person"
    },
    {
      "question": "天眼鏡",
      "answer": "てんがんきょう",
      "meaning": "magnifying glass (esp. in physiognomy, palm reading, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "来車",
      "answer": "らいしゃ",
      "meaning": "your coming, your visiting me"
    },
    {
      "question": "迫持",
      "answer": "せりもち",
      "meaning": "arch"
    },
    {
      "question": "商慣習",
      "answer": "しょうかんしゅう",
      "meaning": "commercial practice"
    },
    {
      "question": "大乗仏教",
      "answer": "だいじょうぶっきょう",
      "meaning": "Mahayana Buddhism"
    },
    {
      "question": "精選",
      "answer": "せいせん",
      "meaning": "careful selection"
    },
    {
      "question": "虫送り",
      "answer": "むしおくり",
      "meaning": "torch procession to drive away crop-eating insects"
    },
    {
      "question": "小女子",
      "answer": "こうなご",
      "meaning": "young lancefish, young sand lance"
    },
    {
      "question": "船板",
      "answer": "ふないた",
      "meaning": "(ship or shipbuilding) timber or plank"
    },
    {
      "question": "直往邁進",
      "answer": "ちょくおうまいしん",
      "meaning": "push boldly forward"
    },
    {
      "question": "獅子鼻",
      "answer": "ししばな",
      "meaning": "pug nose"
    },
    {
      "question": "登記所",
      "answer": "とうきしょ",
      "meaning": "registry office"
    },
    {
      "question": "似我蜂",
      "answer": "じがばち",
      "meaning": "red-banded sand wasp (Ammophila sabulosa), thread-waisted wasp (any wasp of family Sphecidae, incl."
    },
    {
      "question": "同行二人",
      "answer": "どうぎょうににん",
      "meaning": "Kobo Daishi is always with me (written on the hats of Shikoku pilgrims)"
    },
    {
      "question": "罹患率",
      "answer": "りかんりつ",
      "meaning": "disease rate, infection rate, morbidity rate"
    },
    {
      "question": "銘々皿",
      "answer": "めいめいざら",
      "meaning": "small plates for individual helpings of food"
    },
    {
      "question": "触れ太鼓",
      "answer": "ふれだいこ",
      "meaning": "drumming in the streets to announce a tournament, announcing an event by walking around in the stree"
    },
    {
      "question": "検眼",
      "answer": "けんがん",
      "meaning": "eye examination, optometry"
    },
    {
      "question": "中水道",
      "answer": "ちゅうすいどう",
      "meaning": "gray-water system, grey-water system, recycled waste-water"
    },
    {
      "question": "切付ける",
      "answer": "きりつける",
      "meaning": "to cut at, to slash at"
    },
    {
      "question": "闇夜の礫",
      "answer": "やみよのつぶて",
      "meaning": "aimless attempt, crapshot, shot in the dark"
    },
    {
      "question": "偉物",
      "answer": "えらぶつ,えらもの",
      "meaning": "talented person, great man, great woman"
    },
    {
      "question": "骨牌",
      "answer": "かるた,こっぱい",
      "meaning": "karuta, traditional Japanese playing cards, playing cards, mahjong tiles made of animal bone"
    },
    {
      "question": "披見",
      "answer": "ひけん",
      "meaning": "reading, perusing"
    },
    {
      "question": "三選",
      "answer": "さんせん",
      "meaning": "third-term election"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛報",
      "answer": "ひほう",
      "meaning": "urgent report, urgent message"
    },
    {
      "question": "薫ずる",
      "answer": "くんずる",
      "meaning": "to be fragrant"
    },
    {
      "question": "京師",
      "answer": "けいし",
      "meaning": "capital, metropolis, old Kyoto"
    },
    {
      "question": "金準備",
      "answer": "きんじゅんび",
      "meaning": "gold reserve"
    },
    {
      "question": "鳶職",
      "answer": "とびしょく",
      "meaning": "construction worker (who works at heights), scaffolding builder, firefighter (Edo period)"
    },
    {
      "question": "大を成す",
      "answer": "だいをなす",
      "meaning": "to achieve greatness, to achieve success"
    },
    {
      "question": "拝賀",
      "answer": "はいが",
      "meaning": "congratulations"
    },
    {
      "question": "窮まり",
      "answer": "きわまり",
      "meaning": "extremity, end, bound, limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "切線",
      "answer": "せっせん",
      "meaning": "tangent line, tangential line"
    },
    {
      "question": "齷齪",
      "answer": "あくせく,あくさく",
      "meaning": "busily, sedulously, laboriously, feverishly, fussily, worrying (about little things)"
    },
    {
      "question": "炊ぐ",
      "answer": "かしぐ",
      "meaning": "to cook (e.g. rice)"
    },
    {
      "question": "総見",
      "answer": "そうけん",
      "meaning": "observing a performance in a large group"
    },
    {
      "question": "自己免疫",
      "answer": "じこめんえき",
      "meaning": "autoimmunity"
    },
    {
      "question": "上聞",
      "answer": "じょうぶん",
      "meaning": "an imperial hearing"
    },
    {
      "question": "裏芸",
      "answer": "うらげい",
      "meaning": "act or trick which a performer reserves for selected occasions"
    },
    {
      "question": "盛年",
      "answer": "せいねん",
      "meaning": "prime of life"
    },
    {
      "question": "喚呼",
      "answer": "かんこ",
      "meaning": "verbal check (esp. on railroads), verbal confirmation"
    },
    {
      "question": "連舞",
      "answer": "つれまい",
      "meaning": "dance done by two persons or more"
    },
    {
      "question": "閥族",
      "answer": "ばつぞく",
      "meaning": "clan, clique"
    },
    {
      "question": "治承",
      "answer": "じしょう,ちしょう",
      "meaning": "Jishō era (1177.8.4-1181.7.14), Chishō era"
    },
    {
      "question": "近回り",
      "answer": "ちかまわり",
      "meaning": "taking a shortcut, neighborhood, neighbourhood"
    },
    {
      "question": "短打",
      "answer": "たんだ",
      "meaning": "chopping, base hit, one-base hit, single"
    },
    {
      "question": "独酌",
      "answer": "どくしゃく",
      "meaning": "drinking alone, solitary drinking"
    },
    {
      "question": "唐門",
      "answer": "からもん",
      "meaning": "karamon, large gate with a karahafu gable (typically at a temple, shrine or castle)"
    },
    {
      "question": "毒人参",
      "answer": "どくにんじん",
      "meaning": "hemlock"
    },
    {
      "question": "糸蒟蒻",
      "answer": "いとこんにゃく,いとごんにゃく",
      "meaning": "konnyaku cut into fine threads, konjac noodles"
    },
    {
      "question": "中堂",
      "answer": "ちゅうどう",
      "meaning": "main temple building"
    },
    {
      "question": "喜多八",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "円環面",
      "answer": "えんかんめん",
      "meaning": "anchor ring, torus"
    },
    {
      "question": "字凧",
      "answer": "じだこ",
      "meaning": "kite with a (kanji or kana) character written on it"
    },
    {
      "question": "悉皆成仏",
      "answer": "しっかいじょうぶつ",
      "meaning": "all things have the Buddha nature"
    },
    {
      "question": "明眸皓歯",
      "answer": "めいぼうこうし",
      "meaning": "starry eyes and beautiful white teeth (said of beautiful women)"
    },
    {
      "question": "遁走曲",
      "answer": "とんそうきょく",
      "meaning": "fugue"
    },
    {
      "question": "瀬踏み",
      "answer": "せぶみ",
      "meaning": "sounding out, measuring the depths (of a river)"
    },
    {
      "question": "袖垣",
      "answer": "そでがき",
      "meaning": "low fence flanking a gate or entrance"
    },
    {
      "question": "海老芋",
      "answer": "えびいも",
      "meaning": "shrimp-shaped taro variety"
    },
    {
      "question": "御隠れ",
      "answer": "おかくれ",
      "meaning": "passing away, dying, death"
    },
    {
      "question": "止宿",
      "answer": "ししゅく",
      "meaning": "lodging, putting up"
    },
    {
      "question": "文尾",
      "answer": "ぶんび",
      "meaning": "end of a sentence, sentence final"
    },
    {
      "question": "自動織機",
      "answer": "じどうしょっき",
      "meaning": "automatic loom"
    },
    {
      "question": "同大",
      "answer": "どうだい",
      "meaning": "something of the same size, the said university"
    },
    {
      "question": "山漆",
      "answer": "やまうるし",
      "meaning": "Japanese sumac (Rhus trichocarpa)"
    },
    {
      "question": "越流",
      "answer": "えつりゅう",
      "meaning": "overflow"
    },
    {
      "question": "廻国",
      "answer": "かいこく",
      "meaning": "traveling throughout the country (travelling)"
    },
    {
      "question": "水銀柱",
      "answer": "すいぎんちゅう",
      "meaning": "column of mercury"
    },
    {
      "question": "合邦",
      "answer": "がっぽう",
      "meaning": "merger (of countries), union, confederation"
    },
    {
      "question": "都雅",
      "answer": "とが",
      "meaning": "graceful, sophisticated"
    },
    {
      "question": "秘密鍵",
      "answer": "ひみつかぎ",
      "meaning": "private key (cryptography), secret key"
    },
    {
      "question": "天譴",
      "answer": "てんけん",
      "meaning": "divine punishment"
    },
    {
      "question": "塩類",
      "answer": "えんるい",
      "meaning": "salts"
    },
    {
      "question": "左右相称",
      "answer": "さゆうそうしょう",
      "meaning": "symmetry"
    },
    {
      "question": "蚕豆",
      "answer": "そらまめ",
      "meaning": "broad bean (Vicia faba), horse bean, fava bean"
    },
    {
      "question": "征途",
      "answer": "せいと",
      "meaning": "(military or pleasure) expedition"
    },
    {
      "question": "鬱金香",
      "answer": "うっこんこう,うこんこう",
      "meaning": "tulip"
    },
    {
      "question": "八白",
      "answer": "はっぱく",
      "meaning": "eighth of nine traditional astrological signs (corresponding to Saturn and north-east)"
    },
    {
      "question": "歓天喜地",
      "answer": "かんてんきち",
      "meaning": "great joy, jubilation, exultation"
    },
    {
      "question": "戊戌",
      "answer": "ぼじゅつ",
      "meaning": "Earth Dog (35th year of the sexagenary cycle, e.g. 1958, 2018, 2078)"
    },
    {
      "question": "飲み倒す",
      "answer": "のみたおす",
      "meaning": "to skip out on one's bar bill, to drink oneself to ruin, to drink everything vigorously, to get wast"
    },
    {
      "question": "押込み",
      "answer": "おしこみ",
      "meaning": "burglary, burglar, closet"
    },
    {
      "question": "散佚",
      "answer": "さんいつ",
      "meaning": "being scattered and ultimately lost, dissipation"
    },
    {
      "question": "月産",
      "answer": "げっさん",
      "meaning": "monthly output (production)"
    },
    {
      "question": "屠腹",
      "answer": "とふく",
      "meaning": "harakiri, seppuku, disembowelment"
    },
    {
      "question": "謹呈",
      "answer": "きんてい",
      "meaning": "humbly presenting, respectfully presenting"
    },
    {
      "question": "乞食坊主",
      "answer": "こじきぼうず,こつじきぼうず",
      "meaning": "Buddhist monk"
    },
    {
      "question": "壁蝨",
      "answer": "だに",
      "meaning": "tick (Acari spp.), mite"
    },
    {
      "question": "首部",
      "answer": "しゅぶ",
      "meaning": "beginning part, initial part, nose cone (missile)"
    },
    {
      "question": "蛍草",
      "answer": "ほたるぐさ",
      "meaning": "dayflower"
    },
    {
      "question": "裂果",
      "answer": "れっか",
      "meaning": "dehiscent fruit"
    },
    {
      "question": "本街道",
      "answer": "ほんかいどう",
      "meaning": "main road"
    },
    {
      "question": "七赤",
      "answer": "しちせき",
      "meaning": "seventh of nine traditional astrological signs (corresponding to Venus and west)"
    },
    {
      "question": "短期国債",
      "answer": "たんきこくさい",
      "meaning": "treasury bill, TB"
    },
    {
      "question": "再従弟",
      "answer": "さいじゅうてい",
      "meaning": "younger second cousin"
    },
    {
      "question": "手織り機",
      "answer": "ておりばた",
      "meaning": "manually powered loom, hand loom"
    },
    {
      "question": "著作者",
      "answer": "ちょさくしゃ",
      "meaning": "writer, author"
    },
    {
      "question": "廃家",
      "answer": "はいか,はいけ",
      "meaning": "deserted house, ruined house, abolishing one's own family line in order to join another (under pre-1"
    },
    {
      "question": "和光同塵",
      "answer": "わこうどうじん",
      "meaning": "mingling with the world by hiding one's true talent or knowledge, living a quiet life by effacing on"
    },
    {
      "question": "乳房雲",
      "answer": "ちぶさぐも,にゅうぼううん",
      "meaning": "mammatus (cloud), mammatocumulus, festoon cloud"
    },
    {
      "question": "然し乍ら",
      "answer": "しかしながら",
      "meaning": "however, nevertheless"
    },
    {
      "question": "化粧紙",
      "answer": "けしょうがみ",
      "meaning": "cleaning tissue"
    },
    {
      "question": "傭人",
      "answer": "ようにん",
      "meaning": "employee"
    },
    {
      "question": "太閤検地",
      "answer": "たいこうけんち",
      "meaning": "Toyotomi Hideyoshi's nationwide land survey (1582 CE)"
    },
    {
      "question": "縄暖簾",
      "answer": "なわのれん",
      "meaning": "rope curtain"
    },
    {
      "question": "桟唐戸",
      "answer": "さんからど",
      "meaning": "panelled wooden door"
    },
    {
      "question": "珍本",
      "answer": "ちんぽん",
      "meaning": "rare book"
    },
    {
      "question": "扶余",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "登仙",
      "answer": "とうせん",
      "meaning": "becoming a saint, death of a high-ranking person"
    },
    {
      "question": "九寸五分",
      "answer": "くすんごぶ",
      "meaning": "dagger"
    },
    {
      "question": "親柱",
      "answer": "おやばしら",
      "meaning": "main pillar"
    },
    {
      "question": "菌根",
      "answer": "きんこん",
      "meaning": "mycorrhiza"
    },
    {
      "question": "当て外れ",
      "answer": "あてはずれ",
      "meaning": "disappointment, letdown"
    },
    {
      "question": "種を宿す",
      "answer": "たねをやどす",
      "meaning": "to be the mother of someone's child"
    },
    {
      "question": "虚実皮膜",
      "answer": "きょじつひまく",
      "meaning": "the difference between truth and fiction in art being very subtle, Art abides in a realm that is nei"
    },
    {
      "question": "刑事処分",
      "answer": "けいじしょぶん",
      "meaning": "legal penalty, punishment of a criminal"
    },
    {
      "question": "詩聖",
      "answer": "しせい",
      "meaning": "great poet"
    },
    {
      "question": "実化",
      "answer": "じっけ",
      "meaning": "noumenal Buddha (in comparison to phenomenal Buddha)"
    },
    {
      "question": "水張り",
      "answer": "みずばり",
      "meaning": "spreading a piece of wet washing or paper on a board"
    },
    {
      "question": "攻め合い",
      "answer": "せめあい",
      "meaning": "attacking each other, capturing race (e.g. in go), mutual attack"
    },
    {
      "question": "然う",
      "answer": "そう",
      "meaning": "in that way, thus, such, so, so?"
    },
    {
      "question": "二院",
      "answer": "にいん",
      "meaning": "the two houses of legislature"
    },
    {
      "question": "小戦",
      "answer": "しょうせん",
      "meaning": "brush, clash, encounter, skirmish"
    },
    {
      "question": "佚",
      "answer": "いつ",
      "meaning": "being comfortable, relaxing"
    },
    {
      "question": "群居",
      "answer": "ぐんきょ",
      "meaning": "gregariousness"
    },
    {
      "question": "楽焼き",
      "answer": "らくやき",
      "meaning": "raku ware, hand-moulded, lead glazed earthenware pottery fired at low temperatures, esp. used in tea"
    },
    {
      "question": "韓紅",
      "answer": "からくれない",
      "meaning": "crimson"
    },
    {
      "question": "斜眼",
      "answer": "しゃがん",
      "meaning": "sidelong glance, squint"
    },
    {
      "question": "御節",
      "answer": "おせち",
      "meaning": "osechi, food eaten during the New Year's Holidays"
    },
    {
      "question": "土釜",
      "answer": "どがま",
      "meaning": "earthen rice cooker"
    },
    {
      "question": "檜皮色",
      "answer": "ひわだいろ",
      "meaning": "dusky-red, color of cypress bark"
    },
    {
      "question": "寒桜",
      "answer": "かんざくら",
      "meaning": "Prunus kanzakura (species of winter-blooming cherry tree), Chinese primrose (Primula sinensis)"
    },
    {
      "question": "裏書人",
      "answer": "うらがきにん",
      "meaning": "endorser"
    },
    {
      "question": "通常国会",
      "answer": "つうじょうこっかい",
      "meaning": "ordinary session of the Diet"
    },
    {
      "question": "風解",
      "answer": "ふうかい",
      "meaning": "efflorescence, loss of crystallization water to the air"
    },
    {
      "question": "棟上げ",
      "answer": "むねあげ",
      "meaning": "ridgepole-raising, setting up of the framework of a house"
    },
    {
      "question": "心立て",
      "answer": "こころだて",
      "meaning": "disposition"
    },
    {
      "question": "清冷",
      "answer": "せいれい",
      "meaning": "clear and cold (water, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "左党",
      "answer": "さとう,ひだりとう",
      "meaning": "drinker, person who is fond of alcohol, left-wing party"
    },
    {
      "question": "人民委員",
      "answer": "じんみんいいん",
      "meaning": "(early Soviet era) People's Commissar"
    },
    {
      "question": "麪",
      "answer": "めん",
      "meaning": "noodles, flour"
    },
    {
      "question": "組入れる",
      "answer": "くみいれる",
      "meaning": "to incorporate, to work into, to insert"
    },
    {
      "question": "相称",
      "answer": "そうしょう",
      "meaning": "symmetry"
    },
    {
      "question": "牛鍋屋",
      "answer": "ぎゅうなべや",
      "meaning": "beef-hotpot restaurant"
    },
    {
      "question": "見変える",
      "answer": "みかえる",
      "meaning": "to forsake one thing for another"
    },
    {
      "question": "出女",
      "answer": "でおんな",
      "meaning": "unlicensed prostitute (Edo period)"
    },
    {
      "question": "醜状",
      "answer": "しゅうじょう",
      "meaning": "disgraceful state of affairs"
    },
    {
      "question": "待宵草",
      "answer": "まつよいぐさ",
      "meaning": "evening primrose (esp. Chilean evening primrose, Oenothera stricta)"
    },
    {
      "question": "国造",
      "answer": "くにのみやつこ,くにつこ,こくぞう",
      "meaning": "regional administrator (pre-Taika hereditary title)"
    },
    {
      "question": "毳",
      "answer": "むくげ,けば",
      "meaning": "shaggy hair, downy hair, fluff, fuzz, nap, hachures, hatching"
    },
    {
      "question": "手偏",
      "answer": "てへん",
      "meaning": "kanji 'hand' radical at left (radical 64)"
    },
    {
      "question": "複合競技",
      "answer": "ふくごうきょうぎ",
      "meaning": "combined competition (usu. in skiing)"
    },
    {
      "question": "地下銀行",
      "answer": "ちかぎんこう",
      "meaning": "clandestine bank, underground bank"
    },
    {
      "question": "立ち通し",
      "answer": "たちどおし",
      "meaning": "remain standing, keeping standing (all the way)"
    },
    {
      "question": "小乗",
      "answer": "しょうじょう",
      "meaning": "Hinayana (Buddhism), the Lesser Vehicle"
    },
    {
      "question": "聴音機",
      "answer": "ちょうおんき",
      "meaning": "listening instrument, sound detector, sound locator, acoustic locator, hydrophone"
    },
    {
      "question": "鰐口",
      "answer": "わにぐち",
      "meaning": "wide mouth, alligator, temple gong"
    },
    {
      "question": "調音",
      "answer": "ちょうおん",
      "meaning": "articulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "自適",
      "answer": "じてき",
      "meaning": "living free from worldly care, easy and comfortable living"
    },
    {
      "question": "弥栄",
      "answer": "いやさか,やさか",
      "meaning": "prosperity, prospering, flourishing, best of luck, all the best, hurray, hoorah"
    },
    {
      "question": "御迎え",
      "answer": "おむかえ",
      "meaning": "receiving, welcoming, going to meet, person sent to meet or pick up someone, final call, call of fat"
    },
    {
      "question": "背皮",
      "answer": "せがわ",
      "meaning": "back of a leatherbound book"
    },
    {
      "question": "諭旨",
      "answer": "ゆし",
      "meaning": "official suggestion, official advice, official instruction"
    },
    {
      "question": "手漉き",
      "answer": "てすき",
      "meaning": "handmade paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "宮人",
      "answer": "みやびと",
      "meaning": "(noble) courtier"
    },
    {
      "question": "心当て",
      "answer": "こころあて",
      "meaning": "a guess, anticipation"
    },
    {
      "question": "べた足",
      "answer": "べたあし",
      "meaning": "flatfoot, flat feet"
    },
    {
      "question": "襠",
      "answer": "まち",
      "meaning": "gusset"
    },
    {
      "question": "鸚哥",
      "answer": "いんこ",
      "meaning": "true parrot (esp. small parrots such as the parakeet, lory and conure)"
    },
    {
      "question": "手八丁",
      "answer": "てはっちょう",
      "meaning": "eloquence, cleverness in speaking"
    },
    {
      "question": "汎発",
      "answer": "はんぱつ",
      "meaning": "pandemic, widespread"
    },
    {
      "question": "再従兄",
      "answer": "さいじゅうけい",
      "meaning": "elder second cousin"
    },
    {
      "question": "珍物",
      "answer": "ちんぶつ",
      "meaning": "rare item (esp. food)"
    },
    {
      "question": "裸火",
      "answer": "はだかび",
      "meaning": "naked flame, naked light"
    },
    {
      "question": "係助詞",
      "answer": "かかりじょし,けいじょし",
      "meaning": "binding particle (e.g. 'ha', 'mo', 'koso', 'shika'), linking particle, connecting particle"
    },
    {
      "question": "言い及ぶ",
      "answer": "いいおよぶ",
      "meaning": "to refer to, to mention (e.g. theme)"
    },
    {
      "question": "雹害",
      "answer": "ひょうがい",
      "meaning": "hail damage"
    },
    {
      "question": "様を見ろ",
      "answer": "ざまをみろ",
      "meaning": "serves you right!, see what happens!"
    },
    {
      "question": "御造り",
      "answer": "おつくり",
      "meaning": "sashimi, make-up"
    },
    {
      "question": "三和音",
      "answer": "さんわおん",
      "meaning": "triad"
    },
    {
      "question": "御詠",
      "answer": "ぎょえい",
      "meaning": "poem written by the Emperor or a member of the imperial family"
    },
    {
      "question": "逆潮",
      "answer": "ぎゃくちょう,さかしお",
      "meaning": "weather tide, adverse current"
    },
    {
      "question": "部分集合",
      "answer": "ぶぶんしゅうごう",
      "meaning": "subset"
    },
    {
      "question": "親裁",
      "answer": "しんさい",
      "meaning": "matter personally decided by the emperor"
    },
    {
      "question": "店鋪",
      "answer": "てんぽ",
      "meaning": "shop, store"
    },
    {
      "question": "袋網",
      "answer": "ふくろあみ",
      "meaning": "tunnel net"
    },
    {
      "question": "神伝",
      "answer": "しんでん",
      "meaning": "teachings conveyed by the gods"
    },
    {
      "question": "喀痰検査",
      "answer": "かくたんけんさ",
      "meaning": "examination of somebody's sputum"
    },
    {
      "question": "電源開発",
      "answer": "でんげんかいはつ",
      "meaning": "development of electrical power resources"
    },
    {
      "question": "愚計",
      "answer": "ぐけい",
      "meaning": "foolish plan, (one's own) plan, one's modest proposal"
    },
    {
      "question": "家礼",
      "answer": "けらい",
      "meaning": "retainer, retinue, servant"
    },
    {
      "question": "天父",
      "answer": "てんぷ",
      "meaning": "Heavenly Father, God"
    },
    {
      "question": "卒寿",
      "answer": "そつじゅ",
      "meaning": "90th birthday"
    },
    {
      "question": "交付金",
      "answer": "こうふきん",
      "meaning": "subsidy, grant, bounty"
    },
    {
      "question": "無為自然",
      "answer": "むいしぜん",
      "meaning": "abandoning artifice and just being oneself, doing nothing and taking things as they come, unconditio"
    },
    {
      "question": "抜き書き",
      "answer": "ぬきがき",
      "meaning": "extract, excerpt"
    },
    {
      "question": "折込み",
      "answer": "おりこみ",
      "meaning": "insert (in a magazine, newspaper, etc.), foldout, insertion"
    },
    {
      "question": "堅塁",
      "answer": "けんるい",
      "meaning": "stronghold"
    },
    {
      "question": "持国天",
      "answer": "じこくてん",
      "meaning": "Dhrtarastra (Buddhist deity)"
    },
    {
      "question": "打ち欠く",
      "answer": "うちかく",
      "meaning": "to break off, to knock off, to create a false eye by sacrificing a stone (in go)"
    },
    {
      "question": "労使協調",
      "answer": "ろうしきょうちょう",
      "meaning": "labor-management cooperation, labour-management cooperation"
    },
    {
      "question": "恭敬",
      "answer": "きょうけい",
      "meaning": "respect, reverence, veneration"
    },
    {
      "question": "整容",
      "answer": "せいよう",
      "meaning": "straighten one's posture"
    },
    {
      "question": "仮泊",
      "answer": "かはく",
      "meaning": "emergency anchoring"
    },
    {
      "question": "一角獣座",
      "answer": "いっかくじゅうざ",
      "meaning": "Monoceros (constellation), the Unicorn"
    },
    {
      "question": "触書き",
      "answer": "ふれがき",
      "meaning": "Edo-period proclamation issued by the shogunate (or a daimyo, etc.) usu. to the general populace"
    },
    {
      "question": "同小",
      "answer": "どうしょう,おなしょう",
      "meaning": "the same elementary school, student at the same elementary school, graduate of the same elementary s"
    },
    {
      "question": "耐蝕",
      "answer": "たいしょく",
      "meaning": "corrosion-resistant"
    },
    {
      "question": "自存",
      "answer": "じそん",
      "meaning": "existing of or by itself, self-existence"
    },
    {
      "question": "分析化学",
      "answer": "ぶんせきかがく",
      "meaning": "analytical chemistry"
    },
    {
      "question": "珍名",
      "answer": "ちんめい",
      "meaning": "unusual name, strange name, unconventional name"
    },
    {
      "question": "松葉牡丹",
      "answer": "まつばぼたん",
      "meaning": "moss-rose purslane (Portulaca grandiflora)"
    },
    {
      "question": "旧懐",
      "answer": "きゅうかい",
      "meaning": "love of antiquity"
    },
    {
      "question": "詩仙",
      "answer": "しせん",
      "meaning": "great poet"
    },
    {
      "question": "買掛金",
      "answer": "かいかけきん",
      "meaning": "accounts payable"
    },
    {
      "question": "約言",
      "answer": "やくげん",
      "meaning": "summary, contraction, verbal agreement"
    },
    {
      "question": "凍害",
      "answer": "とうがい",
      "meaning": "frost damage"
    },
    {
      "question": "距骨",
      "answer": "きょこつ",
      "meaning": "talus, astragalus, anklebone"
    },
    {
      "question": "詩賦",
      "answer": "しふ",
      "meaning": "songs and poems, Chinese poetry"
    },
    {
      "question": "泥砂",
      "answer": "でいさ,でいしゃ",
      "meaning": "mud and sand"
    },
    {
      "question": "大連立",
      "answer": "だいれんりつ",
      "meaning": "grand coalition, grand alliance"
    },
    {
      "question": "表替え",
      "answer": "おもてがえ",
      "meaning": "refacing (tatami) mats"
    },
    {
      "question": "良貨",
      "answer": "りょうか",
      "meaning": "good money"
    },
    {
      "question": "毀れ",
      "answer": "こぼれ",
      "meaning": "nick, chip, scratch"
    },
    {
      "question": "収入役",
      "answer": "しゅうにゅうやく",
      "meaning": "government treasurer"
    },
    {
      "question": "耕土",
      "answer": "こうど",
      "meaning": "arable soil"
    },
    {
      "question": "尻からげ",
      "answer": "しりからげ",
      "meaning": "tucking up the hem of one's garments"
    },
    {
      "question": "亢奮",
      "answer": "こうふん",
      "meaning": "excitement, stimulation, agitation, arousal"
    },
    {
      "question": "露地栽培",
      "answer": "ろじさいばい",
      "meaning": "outdoor cultivation"
    },
    {
      "question": "煮出し汁",
      "answer": "にだしじる",
      "meaning": "(soup) stock, broth"
    },
    {
      "question": "荒事師",
      "answer": "あらごとし",
      "meaning": "actor who specializes in ruffian roles (specialises)"
    },
    {
      "question": "挿頭",
      "answer": "かざし",
      "meaning": "flower fastened in the hair"
    },
    {
      "question": "球茎",
      "answer": "きゅうけい",
      "meaning": "corm"
    },
    {
      "question": "豎子",
      "answer": "じゅし",
      "meaning": "child, young lad, stripling, greenhorn, inexperienced person"
    },
    {
      "question": "花嫁御寮",
      "answer": "はなよめごりょう",
      "meaning": "bride"
    },
    {
      "question": "無届",
      "answer": "むとどけ",
      "meaning": "without notice, without leave (e.g. absence), unregistered, unreported (e.g. marriage, business, etc"
    },
    {
      "question": "定性的",
      "answer": "ていせいてき",
      "meaning": "qualitative"
    },
    {
      "question": "夢を結ぶ",
      "answer": "ゆめをむすぶ",
      "meaning": "to sleep, to fall asleep"
    },
    {
      "question": "棋界",
      "answer": "きかい",
      "meaning": "world of go, world of shogi, go circles, shogi circles"
    },
    {
      "question": "否応無し",
      "answer": "いやおうなし",
      "meaning": "compulsory, unavoidable, necessary"
    },
    {
      "question": "点綴",
      "answer": "てんてい,てんてつ",
      "meaning": "a line (of mountains, islands, houses, etc.), bound together"
    },
    {
      "question": "糺問",
      "answer": "きゅうもん",
      "meaning": "inquiry, enquiry"
    },
    {
      "question": "元曲",
      "answer": "げんきょく",
      "meaning": "yuanqu (form of Chinese classical drama), Yuan drama"
    },
    {
      "question": "柳刃",
      "answer": "やなぎば",
      "meaning": "kitchen knife for sashimi"
    },
    {
      "question": "名古屋帯",
      "answer": "なごやおび",
      "meaning": "common variety of women's kimono sash"
    },
    {
      "question": "表具",
      "answer": "ひょうぐ",
      "meaning": "mounting (a picture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "人造石油",
      "answer": "じんぞうせきゆ",
      "meaning": "synthetic oil"
    },
    {
      "question": "同報",
      "answer": "どうほう",
      "meaning": "broadcast, multi-destination delivery"
    },
    {
      "question": "毒害",
      "answer": "どくがい",
      "meaning": "poison"
    },
    {
      "question": "共編",
      "answer": "きょうへん",
      "meaning": "joint editorship"
    },
    {
      "question": "決潰",
      "answer": "けっかい",
      "meaning": "burst (e.g. dam, embankment, levee), breach, collapse, washout, rupture"
    },
    {
      "question": "上っ調子",
      "answer": "うわっちょうし",
      "meaning": "flippant, frivolous, shallow"
    },
    {
      "question": "航海法",
      "answer": "こうかいほう",
      "meaning": "Navigation Acts, regulations of colonial trade in 17th century England"
    },
    {
      "question": "余得",
      "answer": "よとく",
      "meaning": "emoluments, additional profits"
    },
    {
      "question": "山鯨",
      "answer": "やまくじら",
      "meaning": "wild boar meat, mountain whale"
    },
    {
      "question": "空気調節",
      "answer": "くうきちょうせつ",
      "meaning": "air conditioning"
    },
    {
      "question": "朴の木",
      "answer": "ほおのき,ほうのき",
      "meaning": "magnolia (Magnolia obovata), Japanese big leaf magnolia"
    },
    {
      "question": "鯨飲馬食",
      "answer": "げいいんばしょく",
      "meaning": "drinking like a fish and eat like a horse, eating mountains of food and drink oceans of liquor"
    },
    {
      "question": "陪堂",
      "answer": "ほいとう,ほいと",
      "meaning": "being served food outside the meditation hall (at a Zen temple), serving food, food served, begging,"
    },
    {
      "question": "半醒半睡",
      "answer": "はんせいはんすい",
      "meaning": "half awake and half asleep"
    },
    {
      "question": "拱く",
      "answer": "こまぬく,こまねく",
      "meaning": "to fold (one's) arms, to stand by and do nothing, to look on passively"
    },
    {
      "question": "紺絣",
      "answer": "こんがすり",
      "meaning": "dark blue cloth with white splash patterns"
    },
    {
      "question": "陶片追放",
      "answer": "とうへんついほう",
      "meaning": "ostracism"
    },
    {
      "question": "険相",
      "answer": "けんそう",
      "meaning": "forbidding look, uncanny look"
    },
    {
      "question": "噴泉",
      "answer": "ふんせん",
      "meaning": "fountain, spring"
    },
    {
      "question": "サロマ湖",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "泥足",
      "answer": "どろあし",
      "meaning": "muddy feet"
    },
    {
      "question": "甜茶",
      "answer": "てんちゃ",
      "meaning": "tian cha, sweet tea, blackberry leaf tea, Chinese blackberry (Rubus suavissimus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "後らす",
      "answer": "おくらす",
      "meaning": "to delay, to postpone, to slow down, to retard"
    },
    {
      "question": "遊び事",
      "answer": "あそびごと",
      "meaning": "game, pastime, recreation, diversion"
    },
    {
      "question": "夫唱婦随",
      "answer": "ふしょうふずい",
      "meaning": "a wife should do her husband's bidding"
    },
    {
      "question": "軟調",
      "answer": "なんちょう",
      "meaning": "weak (market), bearish, soft (tone, focus) (photography)"
    },
    {
      "question": "焚き物",
      "answer": "たきもの",
      "meaning": "firewood"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝際",
      "answer": "ねぎわ",
      "meaning": "on the verge of sleep, just after falling asleep"
    },
    {
      "question": "ごね得",
      "answer": "ごねどく",
      "meaning": "getting what one wants by complaining or grumbling, profiting by holding out or taking a hard line,"
    },
    {
      "question": "苦艾",
      "answer": "にがよもぎ",
      "meaning": "wormwood (Artemisia absinthium), absinthium, absinthe wormwood, absinthe"
    },
    {
      "question": "万万",
      "answer": "まんまん,ばんばん",
      "meaning": "very much, fully, never"
    },
    {
      "question": "手入らず",
      "answer": "ていらず",
      "meaning": "requiring little trouble, untouched"
    },
    {
      "question": "御名御璽",
      "answer": "ぎょめいぎょじ",
      "meaning": "privy seal, imperial seal"
    },
    {
      "question": "塩茶",
      "answer": "しおちゃ",
      "meaning": "coarse tea in which a pinch of salt is added (said to help dissipate alcoholic intoxication)"
    },
    {
      "question": "無水",
      "answer": "むすい",
      "meaning": "anhydrous, absolute"
    },
    {
      "question": "形容句",
      "answer": "けいようく",
      "meaning": "phrase used as an adjective"
    },
    {
      "question": "大数",
      "answer": "たいすう",
      "meaning": "great number, very large number, round number, approximate figure"
    },
    {
      "question": "名号",
      "answer": "みょうごう,めいごう",
      "meaning": "Buddha's name (esp. when used in prayer), fame, renown"
    },
    {
      "question": "蹴込む",
      "answer": "けこむ",
      "meaning": "to kick in(to), to sustain a loss"
    },
    {
      "question": "遣い切る",
      "answer": "つかいきる",
      "meaning": "to use up, to exhaust, to wear out"
    },
    {
      "question": "前株",
      "answer": "まえかぶ",
      "meaning": "company name with the 'kabushiki kaisha' at the beginning"
    },
    {
      "question": "崎嶇",
      "answer": "きく",
      "meaning": "steep (mountain), precipitous, hard (life), difficult, troubled"
    },
    {
      "question": "有価",
      "answer": "ゆうか",
      "meaning": "valuable (object), negotiable (instrument)"
    },
    {
      "question": "猛打賞",
      "answer": "もうだしょう",
      "meaning": "hitting three or more times in a game (NPB)"
    },
    {
      "question": "椹",
      "answer": "さわら",
      "meaning": "sawara cypress (Chamaecyparis pisifera)"
    },
    {
      "question": "盛会",
      "answer": "せいかい",
      "meaning": "successful meeting"
    },
    {
      "question": "愛嬢",
      "answer": "あいじょう",
      "meaning": "one's beloved daughter"
    },
    {
      "question": "暗刻",
      "answer": "アンコー,アンコ",
      "meaning": "concealed pung, concealed three-of-a-kind"
    },
    {
      "question": "史蹟",
      "answer": "しせき",
      "meaning": "historic landmark, historic site, historic remains"
    },
    {
      "question": "実科",
      "answer": "じっか",
      "meaning": "practical course"
    },
    {
      "question": "船首楼",
      "answer": "せんしゅろう",
      "meaning": "forecastle, fo'c's'le"
    },
    {
      "question": "週内",
      "answer": "しゅうない",
      "meaning": "by the end of this week, within the week"
    },
    {
      "question": "追剝ぎ",
      "answer": "おいはぎ",
      "meaning": "highwayman, bandit, brigand, mugger, highway robbery, holdup, mugging"
    },
    {
      "question": "金盞花",
      "answer": "きんせんか",
      "meaning": "marigold, Calendula officinalis"
    },
    {
      "question": "持株",
      "answer": "もちかぶ",
      "meaning": "stock holdings, one's shares"
    },
    {
      "question": "雲足",
      "answer": "くもあし",
      "meaning": "cloud movements, overhanging clouds"
    },
    {
      "question": "工場閉鎖",
      "answer": "こうじょうへいさ",
      "meaning": "factory closure, factory shutdown, lockout (e.g. during industrial dispute)"
    },
    {
      "question": "石塁",
      "answer": "せきるい",
      "meaning": "stone fort"
    },
    {
      "question": "杉菜",
      "answer": "すぎな",
      "meaning": "field horsetail (Equisetum arvense), common horsetail"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝殿造り",
      "answer": "しんでんづくり",
      "meaning": "manner of Heian era palatial architecture"
    },
    {
      "question": "家司",
      "answer": "けいし,けし,いえづかさ",
      "meaning": "steward in charge of the affairs of nobles of the third rank and higher (from the middle of the Heia"
    },
    {
      "question": "知客",
      "answer": "しか",
      "meaning": "head monk in charge of the administrative section of a zendo (Zen)"
    },
    {
      "question": "本占地",
      "answer": "ほんしめじ",
      "meaning": "Lyophyllum shimeji (species of edible mushroom)"
    },
    {
      "question": "遊び紙",
      "answer": "あそびがみ",
      "meaning": "flyleaf"
    },
    {
      "question": "相知る",
      "answer": "あいしる",
      "meaning": "to know each other, to exchange vows, to love each other"
    },
    {
      "question": "別学",
      "answer": "べつがく",
      "meaning": "single-sex education"
    },
    {
      "question": "速写",
      "answer": "そくしゃ",
      "meaning": "snapshot"
    },
    {
      "question": "不寝の番",
      "answer": "ねずのばん",
      "meaning": "sleepless vigil"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪催い",
      "answer": "ゆきもよい",
      "meaning": "threatening to snow"
    },
    {
      "question": "食付く",
      "answer": "くいつく",
      "meaning": "to bite at, to snap at, to nibble, to get one's teeth into (metaphorically), to get to grips with, t"
    },
    {
      "question": "受け払い",
      "answer": "うけはらい",
      "meaning": "receipts and payments"
    },
    {
      "question": "差物",
      "answer": "さしもの",
      "meaning": "cabinetwork, joinery, hair ornament, hairpin, colours, banner, small banner worn by soldiers during"
    },
    {
      "question": "米穀",
      "answer": "べいこく",
      "meaning": "rice"
    },
    {
      "question": "紅差し指",
      "answer": "べにさしゆび",
      "meaning": "ring finger"
    },
    {
      "question": "風流韻事",
      "answer": "ふうりゅういんじ",
      "meaning": "elegant appreciation of nature through artistic pursuits such as poetry, painting and calligraphy"
    },
    {
      "question": "末女",
      "answer": "まつじょ",
      "meaning": "youngest daughter"
    },
    {
      "question": "菽",
      "answer": "まめ",
      "meaning": "legume (esp. edible legumes or their seeds, such as beans, peas, pulses, etc.), beans, peas, soya be"
    },
    {
      "question": "楊弓",
      "answer": "ようきゅう",
      "meaning": "small toy bow that can be shot while sitting, popular in the Edo period"
    },
    {
      "question": "律呂",
      "answer": "りつりょ",
      "meaning": "standard tones, Chinese system of musical sounds"
    },
    {
      "question": "天一神",
      "answer": "てんいちじん,なかがみ",
      "meaning": "Ten'ichijin, Nakagami, god of fortune in Onmyōdō who descends to the northeast on the 46th day of th"
    },
    {
      "question": "就床",
      "answer": "しゅうしょう",
      "meaning": "bedridden"
    },
    {
      "question": "屋久杉",
      "answer": "やくすぎ",
      "meaning": "Yakushima cedar (esp. one over 1000 years old)"
    },
    {
      "question": "盲縞",
      "answer": "めくらじま",
      "meaning": "plain blue cotton"
    },
    {
      "question": "大不敬",
      "answer": "だいふけい",
      "meaning": "great impropriety (esp. towards the imperial family), crime against the imperial family (or a shrine"
    },
    {
      "question": "広聴",
      "answer": "こうちょう",
      "meaning": "public consultation, public information"
    },
    {
      "question": "剪枝",
      "answer": "せんし",
      "meaning": "pruning"
    },
    {
      "question": "総量規制",
      "answer": "そうりょうきせい",
      "meaning": "total volume control, regulations on total allowable volumes of pollutants"
    },
    {
      "question": "論駁",
      "answer": "ろんばく",
      "meaning": "refutation, confutation"
    },
    {
      "question": "正数",
      "answer": "せいすう",
      "meaning": "positive number"
    },
    {
      "question": "来秋",
      "answer": "らいしゅう",
      "meaning": "next autumn, next fall"
    },
    {
      "question": "単結合",
      "answer": "たんけつごう",
      "meaning": "single bond"
    },
    {
      "question": "木殺し",
      "answer": "きごろし",
      "meaning": "pounding the edges of planks of wood to join them"
    },
    {
      "question": "おっ開く",
      "answer": "おっぴらく",
      "meaning": "to do something in public, to open"
    },
    {
      "question": "宙乗り",
      "answer": "ちゅうのり",
      "meaning": "midair stunt, aerial stunts"
    },
    {
      "question": "粗大塵",
      "answer": "そだいごみ",
      "meaning": "large-size refuse (e.g. furniture, electrical goods), oversized garbage, bulky rubbish, useless man"
    },
    {
      "question": "蕨餅",
      "answer": "わらびもち",
      "meaning": "bracken-starch dumpling, type of dumpling traditionally made using bracken starch"
    },
    {
      "question": "名石",
      "answer": "めいせき",
      "meaning": "famous jewel, exquisite stone"
    },
    {
      "question": "塩汁",
      "answer": "しおじる,しょっつる",
      "meaning": "salty broth, salt water, salted and fermented fish sauce from Akita"
    },
    {
      "question": "教戒",
      "answer": "きょうかい",
      "meaning": "counselling (often of imprisoned criminals by a chaplain, etc.), giving guidance, admonishment, scol"
    },
    {
      "question": "処処",
      "answer": "しょしょ",
      "meaning": "here and there, some parts (of something), several places"
    },
    {
      "question": "白瓜",
      "answer": "しろうり",
      "meaning": "melon cucumber"
    },
    {
      "question": "涼秋",
      "answer": "りょうしゅう",
      "meaning": "cool autumn, cool fall"
    },
    {
      "question": "花柱",
      "answer": "かちゅう",
      "meaning": "(flower's) style"
    },
    {
      "question": "立志式",
      "answer": "りっししき",
      "meaning": "coming-of-age ceremony for middle school students"
    },
    {
      "question": "奴頭",
      "answer": "やっこあたま",
      "meaning": "Edo-period hairstyle worn by samurai's attendants"
    },
    {
      "question": "平滑筋",
      "answer": "へいかつきん",
      "meaning": "smooth muscle"
    },
    {
      "question": "油溶性",
      "answer": "ゆようせい",
      "meaning": "oil solubility"
    },
    {
      "question": "牛屋",
      "answer": "うしや,ぎゅうや",
      "meaning": "cowshed, cow farmer, restaurant specializing in beef dishes, store (butcher, etc.) that sells beef"
    },
    {
      "question": "律師",
      "answer": "りっし",
      "meaning": "Buddhist priest"
    },
    {
      "question": "畳替え",
      "answer": "たたみがえ",
      "meaning": "renewing mats, refacing mats"
    },
    {
      "question": "板木",
      "answer": "はんぎ,ばんぎ",
      "meaning": "(printing) block, woodcut"
    },
    {
      "question": "回転角",
      "answer": "かいてんかく",
      "meaning": "angle of rotation"
    },
    {
      "question": "曲玉",
      "answer": "まがたま",
      "meaning": "comma-shaped jewels"
    },
    {
      "question": "永治",
      "answer": "えいじ",
      "meaning": "Eiji era (1141.7.10-1142.4.28)"
    },
    {
      "question": "介殻",
      "answer": "かいかく",
      "meaning": "sea shell"
    },
    {
      "question": "麻織物",
      "answer": "あさおりもの",
      "meaning": "hemp fabric"
    },
    {
      "question": "刻する",
      "answer": "こくする",
      "meaning": "to carve, to engrave, to publish, to author"
    },
    {
      "question": "腸線",
      "answer": "ちょうせん",
      "meaning": "catgut, sheepgut"
    },
    {
      "question": "変格",
      "answer": "へんかく",
      "meaning": "irregularity, irregular conjugation, translative"
    },
    {
      "question": "黥",
      "answer": "げい,いれずみ",
      "meaning": "tattoo (esp. a traditional Japanese one), tattooing"
    },
    {
      "question": "特立",
      "answer": "とくりつ",
      "meaning": "prominence, independence"
    },
    {
      "question": "本管",
      "answer": "ほんかん",
      "meaning": "main pipe"
    },
    {
      "question": "追い腹",
      "answer": "おいばら",
      "meaning": "following one's master into death by committing ritual suicide (seppuku)"
    },
    {
      "question": "御店",
      "answer": "おたな,おみせ",
      "meaning": "merchant's home (esp. used by apprentices, etc.), (your) rental home, store, shop"
    },
    {
      "question": "四緑",
      "answer": "しろく",
      "meaning": "fourth of nine traditional astrological signs (corresponding to Jupiter and south-east)"
    },
    {
      "question": "典麗",
      "answer": "てんれい",
      "meaning": "graceful"
    },
    {
      "question": "空籤",
      "answer": "からくじ",
      "meaning": "blank (ticket), unsuccessful lottery ticket"
    },
    {
      "question": "起臥",
      "answer": "きが",
      "meaning": "daily life, daily living, waking up and going to sleep"
    },
    {
      "question": "北郊",
      "answer": "ほっこう",
      "meaning": "northern suburbs"
    },
    {
      "question": "定積分",
      "answer": "ていせきぶん",
      "meaning": "definite integral"
    },
    {
      "question": "低脂肪乳",
      "answer": "ていしぼうにゅう",
      "meaning": "low-fat milk"
    },
    {
      "question": "浅学菲才",
      "answer": "せんがくひさい",
      "meaning": "one's lack of learning or ability, shallow learning and limited ability"
    },
    {
      "question": "輔す",
      "answer": "ふす",
      "meaning": "to appoint, to designate"
    },
    {
      "question": "煩多",
      "answer": "はんた",
      "meaning": "multiplicity of troubles, so many as to be troublesome"
    },
    {
      "question": "示偏",
      "answer": "しめすへん",
      "meaning": "kanji 'show' radical at left (radical 113)"
    },
    {
      "question": "塩花",
      "answer": "しおばな",
      "meaning": "purifying salt, pile of salt placed by the door of a shop or restaurant, whitecap"
    },
    {
      "question": "左義長",
      "answer": "さぎちょう",
      "meaning": "burning of New Year's gate decorations (usu. on the 15th day of the New Year)"
    },
    {
      "question": "時めく",
      "answer": "ときめく",
      "meaning": "to be prosperous, to prosper, to flourish, to enjoy great prosperity"
    },
    {
      "question": "迂曲",
      "answer": "うきょく",
      "meaning": "meandering, winding"
    },
    {
      "question": "丹毒",
      "answer": "たんどく",
      "meaning": "erysipelas"
    },
    {
      "question": "破れ鍋",
      "answer": "われなべ",
      "meaning": "cracked pot"
    },
    {
      "question": "他色",
      "answer": "たしょく",
      "meaning": "discolouration of a mineral due to impurities (discoloration)"
    },
    {
      "question": "猿梨",
      "answer": "さるなし",
      "meaning": "hardy kiwi (Actinidia arguta), kiwi berry, tara vine, bower vine"
    },
    {
      "question": "神慮",
      "answer": "しんりょ",
      "meaning": "divine will"
    },
    {
      "question": "楽焼",
      "answer": "らくやき",
      "meaning": "raku ware, hand-moulded, lead glazed earthenware pottery fired at low temperatures, esp. used in tea"
    },
    {
      "question": "家書",
      "answer": "かしょ",
      "meaning": "letter from home"
    },
    {
      "question": "同役",
      "answer": "どうやく",
      "meaning": "colleague"
    },
    {
      "question": "清ます",
      "answer": "すます",
      "meaning": "to clear, to make clear, to be unruffled, to look unconcerned, to feign indifference, to look demure"
    },
    {
      "question": "芳信",
      "answer": "ほうしん",
      "meaning": "letter, news that flowers have bloomed"
    },
    {
      "question": "染め糸",
      "answer": "そめいと",
      "meaning": "dyed thread or yarn"
    },
    {
      "question": "電番",
      "answer": "でんばん",
      "meaning": "telephone number, directory number"
    },
    {
      "question": "蟒草",
      "answer": "うわばみそう",
      "meaning": "Elatostema umbellatum var. majus (variety of plant related to the nettles)"
    },
    {
      "question": "外政",
      "answer": "がいせい",
      "meaning": "foreign policy, diplomatic affairs"
    },
    {
      "question": "利上げ",
      "answer": "りあげ",
      "meaning": "increase in interest rates"
    },
    {
      "question": "無定形",
      "answer": "むていけい",
      "meaning": "amorphous, shapeless"
    },
    {
      "question": "鋳掛け屋",
      "answer": "いかけや",
      "meaning": "a tinker, tinkerer"
    },
    {
      "question": "重商主義",
      "answer": "じゅうしょうしゅぎ",
      "meaning": "mercantilism"
    },
    {
      "question": "クロム鋼",
      "answer": "クロムこう",
      "meaning": "chrome steel, chromium steel"
    },
    {
      "question": "回視",
      "answer": "かいし",
      "meaning": "looking back (at the past), looking around, surveying"
    },
    {
      "question": "産児制限",
      "answer": "さんじせいげん",
      "meaning": "birth control"
    },
    {
      "question": "廃頽",
      "answer": "はいたい",
      "meaning": "decay, decadence"
    },
    {
      "question": "有声音",
      "answer": "ゆうせいおん",
      "meaning": "voiced sound"
    },
    {
      "question": "五番目物",
      "answer": "ごばんめもの",
      "meaning": "last of the traditional set of five noh plays"
    },
    {
      "question": "散ずる",
      "answer": "さんずる",
      "meaning": "to scatter, to disperse, to spend on, to squander (e.g. one's fortune), to chase away (e.g. one's wo"
    },
    {
      "question": "糸状虫",
      "answer": "しじょうちゅう",
      "meaning": "filaria, heartworm"
    },
    {
      "question": "劈開",
      "answer": "へきかい",
      "meaning": "cleavage (in gems)"
    },
    {
      "question": "乾燥材",
      "answer": "かんそうざい",
      "meaning": "seasoned lumber"
    },
    {
      "question": "痔疾",
      "answer": "じしつ",
      "meaning": "hemorrhoids"
    },
    {
      "question": "内接",
      "answer": "ないせつ",
      "meaning": "inscribed (circle)"
    },
    {
      "question": "駆虫薬",
      "answer": "くちゅうやく",
      "meaning": "anthelmintic, vermifuge, vermicide, insect repellent"
    },
    {
      "question": "尺寸",
      "answer": "しゃくすん,せきすん",
      "meaning": "(something) tiny, trifle"
    },
    {
      "question": "無腰",
      "answer": "むごし",
      "meaning": "unarmed"
    },
    {
      "question": "外方",
      "answer": "そっぽ,とざま",
      "meaning": "the other way, outside daimyo, non-Tokugawa daimyo, outsider, one not included in the favored (favou"
    },
    {
      "question": "駐英",
      "answer": "ちゅうえい",
      "meaning": "stationed in the United Kingdom, resident in the United Kingdom"
    },
    {
      "question": "柳川鍋",
      "answer": "やながわなべ",
      "meaning": "loach stew, loaches boiled in soy sauce with stewed eggs and slivered burdock root"
    },
    {
      "question": "官権",
      "answer": "かんけん",
      "meaning": "governmental authority"
    },
    {
      "question": "刀圭家",
      "answer": "とうけいか",
      "meaning": "doctor"
    },
    {
      "question": "二枚蹴り",
      "answer": "にまいげり",
      "meaning": "ankle-kicking twist down"
    },
    {
      "question": "栄養物",
      "answer": "えいようぶつ",
      "meaning": "nutritive material"
    },
    {
      "question": "万善",
      "answer": "まんぜん",
      "meaning": "all good works, all good deeds"
    },
    {
      "question": "弥久",
      "answer": "びきゅう",
      "meaning": "extending over a long time"
    },
    {
      "question": "速記者",
      "answer": "そっきしゃ",
      "meaning": "stenographer, writer of shorthand"
    },
    {
      "question": "染め返す",
      "answer": "そめかえす",
      "meaning": "to dye again"
    },
    {
      "question": "暴民",
      "answer": "ぼうみん",
      "meaning": "a mob"
    },
    {
      "question": "孤立死",
      "answer": "こりつし",
      "meaning": "dying alone (esp. of someone who lives alone and dies of natural causes at home without anyone knowi"
    },
    {
      "question": "継統",
      "answer": "けいとう",
      "meaning": "accession to the throne"
    },
    {
      "question": "駄本",
      "answer": "だほん",
      "meaning": "worthless book, meritless book"
    },
    {
      "question": "被治者",
      "answer": "ひちしゃ",
      "meaning": "the ruled, the governed"
    },
    {
      "question": "灰神楽",
      "answer": "はいかぐら",
      "meaning": "cloud of ashes (caused by pouring water on a fire)"
    },
    {
      "question": "膝蓋腱",
      "answer": "しつがいけん",
      "meaning": "patellar tendon"
    },
    {
      "question": "全天候",
      "answer": "ぜんてんこう",
      "meaning": "all-weather, weather-proof"
    },
    {
      "question": "畜類",
      "answer": "ちくるい",
      "meaning": "livestock, domestic animals"
    },
    {
      "question": "聴す",
      "answer": "ゆるす",
      "meaning": "to permit, to allow, to approve, to consent to, to forgive, to pardon, to excuse, to tolerate, to ex"
    },
    {
      "question": "章節",
      "answer": "しょうせつ",
      "meaning": "chapters and sections, chapter and verse"
    },
    {
      "question": "表現型",
      "answer": "ひょうげんがた",
      "meaning": "phenotype"
    },
    {
      "question": "見晴し台",
      "answer": "みはらしだい",
      "meaning": "lookout platform, viewing platform, observation tower, viewpoint, overlook"
    },
    {
      "question": "家常",
      "answer": "かじょう",
      "meaning": "family custom"
    },
    {
      "question": "解氷",
      "answer": "かいひょう",
      "meaning": "a thaw"
    },
    {
      "question": "接ぎ目",
      "answer": "はぎめ",
      "meaning": "seam, joint"
    },
    {
      "question": "驕傲",
      "answer": "きょうごう",
      "meaning": "pride, arrogance"
    },
    {
      "question": "稲科",
      "answer": "いねか",
      "meaning": "Poaceae, Gramineae, family comprising the true grasses"
    },
    {
      "question": "太平天国",
      "answer": "たいへいてんごく",
      "meaning": "Taiping Heavenly Kingdom (1851-1864)"
    },
    {
      "question": "生命権",
      "answer": "せいめいけん",
      "meaning": "right to life"
    },
    {
      "question": "御水",
      "answer": "おみず",
      "meaning": "water, (drinking) water, (glass of) water, night entertainment business, nightlife worker, hostess,"
    },
    {
      "question": "酷刑",
      "answer": "こっけい",
      "meaning": "severe punishment"
    },
    {
      "question": "陽当り",
      "answer": "ひあたり",
      "meaning": "exposure to the sun, sunny place"
    },
    {
      "question": "休院",
      "answer": "きゅういん",
      "meaning": "temporary closure of a hospital (clinic, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "粗面",
      "answer": "そめん",
      "meaning": "rough surface"
    },
    {
      "question": "飲助",
      "answer": "のみすけ",
      "meaning": "tippler, drunkard, heavy drinker"
    },
    {
      "question": "松籟",
      "answer": "しょうらい",
      "meaning": "(sound of) wind through pine trees, soughing of wind through pine trees, (metaphorically) sound of a"
    },
    {
      "question": "求不得苦",
      "answer": "ぐふとくく",
      "meaning": "the pain of not getting what one seeks"
    },
    {
      "question": "京方",
      "answer": "きょうがた",
      "meaning": "the direction of Kyoto, Kansai area, citizens of Kyoto, nobles"
    },
    {
      "question": "小意気",
      "answer": "こいき",
      "meaning": "stylish, smart, chic, tasteful, snappy, dapper, conceited, cheeky"
    },
    {
      "question": "山懐",
      "answer": "やまふところ",
      "meaning": "heart of a mountain"
    },
    {
      "question": "差込み",
      "answer": "さしこみ",
      "meaning": "insertion, plug, (electrical) outlet, power point, spasm of pain, griping pain, (fit of) convulsions"
    },
    {
      "question": "心延え",
      "answer": "こころばえ",
      "meaning": "concern, sympathy, solicitude, consideration (for others), nature, disposition, temperament"
    },
    {
      "question": "御涙頂戴",
      "answer": "おなみだちょうだい",
      "meaning": "tearjerker, sob story, maudlin tale"
    },
    {
      "question": "天金",
      "answer": "てんきん",
      "meaning": "gilt top (book)"
    },
    {
      "question": "里道",
      "answer": "りどう,さとみち",
      "meaning": "non-legal public road (sometimes no longer physically existing)"
    },
    {
      "question": "奉祝",
      "answer": "ほうしゅく",
      "meaning": "celebration"
    },
    {
      "question": "似非科学",
      "answer": "えせかがく",
      "meaning": "pseudoscience"
    },
    {
      "question": "準抗告",
      "answer": "じゅんこうこく",
      "meaning": "jun-kokoku appeal, quasi-appeal, quasi-complaint"
    },
    {
      "question": "昏れる",
      "answer": "くれる",
      "meaning": "to get dark, to grow dark, to end (of a day, year, season, etc.), to come to an end, to close, to be"
    },
    {
      "question": "畜犬",
      "answer": "ちくけん,ちっけん",
      "meaning": "pet dog, keeping a dog"
    },
    {
      "question": "解像力",
      "answer": "かいぞうりょく",
      "meaning": "resolving power (of a lens)"
    },
    {
      "question": "追分",
      "answer": "おいわけ",
      "meaning": "forked road"
    },
    {
      "question": "坐像",
      "answer": "ざぞう",
      "meaning": "seated figure (e.g. of Buddha), sedentary statue, sedentary image"
    },
    {
      "question": "猥褻罪",
      "answer": "わいせつざい",
      "meaning": "criminal indecency"
    },
    {
      "question": "仁政",
      "answer": "じんせい",
      "meaning": "benevolent rule"
    },
    {
      "question": "油性塗料",
      "answer": "ゆせいとりょう",
      "meaning": "oil-based paint"
    },
    {
      "question": "徳用品",
      "answer": "とくようひん",
      "meaning": "economical product, economy-sized goods"
    },
    {
      "question": "尾輪",
      "answer": "びりん",
      "meaning": "tail wheel (aircraft)"
    },
    {
      "question": "除虫菊",
      "answer": "じょちゅうぎく",
      "meaning": "Dalmatian chrysanthemum (Tanacetum cinerariifolium), Dalmatian pyrethrum, Dalmatian pellitory"
    },
    {
      "question": "集合論",
      "answer": "しゅうごうろん",
      "meaning": "set theory"
    },
    {
      "question": "一元論",
      "answer": "いちげんろん",
      "meaning": "monism"
    },
    {
      "question": "素人下宿",
      "answer": "しろうとげしゅく",
      "meaning": "boarding house"
    },
    {
      "question": "四十雀",
      "answer": "しじゅうから,しじゅうがら",
      "meaning": "Japanese tit (Parus minor), Oriental tit"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝部屋",
      "answer": "ねべや",
      "meaning": "bedroom, sleeping room"
    },
    {
      "question": "厳存",
      "answer": "げんそん",
      "meaning": "real existence"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪汁",
      "answer": "ゆきしる,ゆきじる",
      "meaning": "snow water, melt water"
    },
    {
      "question": "選挙人",
      "answer": "せんきょにん",
      "meaning": "voter, constituent, elector, presidential elector (US), member of the Electoral College"
    },
    {
      "question": "官展",
      "answer": "かんてん",
      "meaning": "exhibition sponsored by the government"
    },
    {
      "question": "松虫",
      "answer": "まつむし",
      "meaning": "pine cricket (Xenogryllus marmoratus), bell cricket (Meloimorpha japonicus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "非同盟",
      "answer": "ひどうめい",
      "meaning": "non-alignment, nonalignment"
    },
    {
      "question": "握り鮨",
      "answer": "にぎりずし",
      "meaning": "nigirizushi, hand-formed sushi with a topping of seafood, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "厚相",
      "answer": "こうしょう",
      "meaning": "Welfare Minister"
    },
    {
      "question": "目貼り",
      "answer": "めばり",
      "meaning": "weather strip, weather stripping, sealing up (a window)"
    },
    {
      "question": "万延",
      "answer": "まんえん",
      "meaning": "Man'en era (1860.3.18-1861.2.19)"
    },
    {
      "question": "乱菊",
      "answer": "らんぎく",
      "meaning": "pattern made from chrysanthemums with disordered petals, esp. used on family crests"
    },
    {
      "question": "内助",
      "answer": "ないじょ",
      "meaning": "wife's help"
    },
    {
      "question": "経学",
      "answer": "けいがく",
      "meaning": "Confucianism"
    },
    {
      "question": "閃閃",
      "answer": "せんせん",
      "meaning": "sparkling, glistening, glittering, fluttering, flickering"
    },
    {
      "question": "黄蝶",
      "answer": "きちょう",
      "meaning": "large grass yellow (species of butterfly, Eurema hecabe), common grass yellow, yellow butterfly"
    },
    {
      "question": "痩せ男",
      "answer": "やせおとこ",
      "meaning": "skinny man, shabby-looking man, noh mask representing a male ghost"
    },
    {
      "question": "無言の行",
      "answer": "むごんのぎょう",
      "meaning": "ascetic practice of silence"
    },
    {
      "question": "同族会社",
      "answer": "どうぞくがいしゃ,どうぞくかいしゃ",
      "meaning": "family corporation, family company, affiliated concern"
    },
    {
      "question": "統計力学",
      "answer": "とうけいりきがく",
      "meaning": "statistical mechanics"
    },
    {
      "question": "渦雷",
      "answer": "からい",
      "meaning": "cyclonic thunder-storm"
    },
    {
      "question": "家郷",
      "answer": "かきょう",
      "meaning": "one's homeland, one's old home"
    },
    {
      "question": "植村直己",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "謂れ無い",
      "answer": "いわれない",
      "meaning": "unjustified, unwarranted, unfounded, baseless, groundless"
    },
    {
      "question": "俄仕込み",
      "answer": "にわかじこみ",
      "meaning": "hasty preparation"
    },
    {
      "question": "余日",
      "answer": "よじつ",
      "meaning": "remaining time, days left"
    },
    {
      "question": "四段活用",
      "answer": "よだんかつよう",
      "meaning": "yodan verb conjugation, verb conjugation of classical Japanese"
    },
    {
      "question": "骨組織",
      "answer": "こつそしき",
      "meaning": "bony tissue"
    },
    {
      "question": "香香",
      "answer": "こうこう",
      "meaning": "pickled vegetables"
    },
    {
      "question": "俘囚",
      "answer": "ふしゅう",
      "meaning": "prisoner, captive, prisoner of war, Emishi allied with the Japanese during the Nara and Heian period"
    },
    {
      "question": "其の儀",
      "answer": "そのぎ",
      "meaning": "that matter, those matters"
    },
    {
      "question": "損気",
      "answer": "そんき",
      "meaning": "disadvantage"
    },
    {
      "question": "借銭",
      "answer": "しゃくせん",
      "meaning": "debt"
    },
    {
      "question": "豆科",
      "answer": "まめか",
      "meaning": "Fabaceae, pea family of plants"
    },
    {
      "question": "上つ方",
      "answer": "うえつがた",
      "meaning": "nobles, the upper class"
    },
    {
      "question": "呉須",
      "answer": "ごす",
      "meaning": "gosu porcelain, asbolite"
    },
    {
      "question": "側鎖",
      "answer": "そくさ",
      "meaning": "chemical side chain"
    },
    {
      "question": "印地打ち",
      "answer": "いんじうち",
      "meaning": "big rock fight for children on the fifth day of the fifth month (adults also participated during the"
    },
    {
      "question": "刀背打ち",
      "answer": "みねうち,むねうち",
      "meaning": "striking with the back of the sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "音場",
      "answer": "おんじょう,おんば",
      "meaning": "sound field"
    },
    {
      "question": "南京条約",
      "answer": "ナンキンじょうやく",
      "meaning": "Treaty of Nanking (1842)"
    },
    {
      "question": "津液",
      "answer": "しんえき",
      "meaning": "saliva, spit, spittle, fluid (in Chinese medicine, esp. a colourless bodily fluid, e.g. tears)"
    },
    {
      "question": "掛橋",
      "answer": "かけはし",
      "meaning": "suspension bridge, viaduct, temporary bridge, mediation, go-between"
    },
    {
      "question": "直諫",
      "answer": "ちょっかん",
      "meaning": "personal admonition, remonstration"
    },
    {
      "question": "足摺り",
      "answer": "あしずり",
      "meaning": "stamping or scraping one's feet"
    },
    {
      "question": "広闊",
      "answer": "こうかつ",
      "meaning": "spaciousness, extensiveness, expansiveness, vastness"
    },
    {
      "question": "ボトル缶",
      "answer": "ボトルかん",
      "meaning": "aluminium can shaped like a bottle (aluminum), metal bottle"
    },
    {
      "question": "帝座",
      "answer": "ていざ",
      "meaning": "imperial throne"
    },
    {
      "question": "賦する",
      "answer": "ふする",
      "meaning": "to allocate, to compose (poetry, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "渋紙",
      "answer": "しぶがみ",
      "meaning": "paper treated with astringent persimmon juice"
    },
    {
      "question": "化性",
      "answer": "かせい",
      "meaning": "voltinism"
    },
    {
      "question": "排他制御",
      "answer": "はいたせいぎょ",
      "meaning": "exclusive control"
    },
    {
      "question": "全面安",
      "answer": "ぜんめんやす",
      "meaning": "across-the-board fall in prices"
    },
    {
      "question": "地割",
      "answer": "じわり",
      "meaning": "allotment (of land), parcelling out"
    },
    {
      "question": "公舎",
      "answer": "こうしゃ",
      "meaning": "official residence"
    },
    {
      "question": "労働省",
      "answer": "ろうどうしょう",
      "meaning": "Ministry of Labour (now Ministry of Health, Labour and Welfare)"
    },
    {
      "question": "貸し金",
      "answer": "かしきん",
      "meaning": "loan, advance"
    },
    {
      "question": "揺籃期",
      "answer": "ようらんき",
      "meaning": "infancy, in cradle"
    },
    {
      "question": "味噌餡",
      "answer": "みそあん",
      "meaning": "sweet paste of white beans and miso"
    },
    {
      "question": "借料",
      "answer": "しゃくりょう",
      "meaning": "rent money"
    },
    {
      "question": "金比羅",
      "answer": "こんぴら",
      "meaning": "guardian deity of seafaring, Kumbhira"
    },
    {
      "question": "新釈",
      "answer": "しんしゃく",
      "meaning": "new interpretation"
    },
    {
      "question": "細胞学",
      "answer": "さいぼうがく",
      "meaning": "cytology"
    },
    {
      "question": "歌い回し",
      "answer": "うたいまわし",
      "meaning": "manner of singing"
    },
    {
      "question": "薫育",
      "answer": "くんいく",
      "meaning": "moral influence, moral education"
    },
    {
      "question": "蓴菜",
      "answer": "じゅんさい",
      "meaning": "water shield (Brasenia schreberi)"
    },
    {
      "question": "丁々",
      "answer": "ちょうちょう,とうとう",
      "meaning": "clashing of swords, felling of trees, ringing of an ax"
    },
    {
      "question": "良性腫瘍",
      "answer": "りょうせいしゅよう",
      "meaning": "benign tumor, benign tumour"
    },
    {
      "question": "株屋",
      "answer": "かぶや",
      "meaning": "stockbroker"
    },
    {
      "question": "吏員",
      "answer": "りいん",
      "meaning": "official"
    },
    {
      "question": "花生け",
      "answer": "はないけ",
      "meaning": "(flower) vase"
    },
    {
      "question": "三つ鱗",
      "answer": "みつうろこ",
      "meaning": "mitsuuroko emblem (three triangles in a triangular pattern; Hōjō clan symbol)"
    },
    {
      "question": "子葉",
      "answer": "しよう",
      "meaning": "cotyledon, seed leaf"
    },
    {
      "question": "尊信",
      "answer": "そんしん",
      "meaning": "reverence"
    },
    {
      "question": "新選",
      "answer": "しんせん",
      "meaning": "newly compiled, selected or edited"
    },
    {
      "question": "美文字",
      "answer": "びもじ",
      "meaning": "beautifully written (Chinese) character"
    },
    {
      "question": "綺談",
      "answer": "きだん",
      "meaning": "romantic story, colorful story, colourful story, highly embellished story"
    },
    {
      "question": "定則",
      "answer": "ていそく",
      "meaning": "law, established rule"
    },
    {
      "question": "舵棒",
      "answer": "かじぼう",
      "meaning": "shafts (of rickshaws or similar vehicles), thills, tiller, yoke"
    },
    {
      "question": "入貢",
      "answer": "にゅうこう",
      "meaning": "paying tribute"
    },
    {
      "question": "学びの園",
      "answer": "まなびのその",
      "meaning": "educational institution"
    },
    {
      "question": "株式配当",
      "answer": "かぶしきはいとう",
      "meaning": "stock dividend"
    },
    {
      "question": "航路標識",
      "answer": "こうろひょうしき",
      "meaning": "sea mark, seamark, beacon"
    },
    {
      "question": "有徳",
      "answer": "うとく,ゆうとく",
      "meaning": "virtuous, rich"
    },
    {
      "question": "倹約令",
      "answer": "けんやくれい",
      "meaning": "laws regulating expenditures, sumptuary edicts, thrift ordinance"
    },
    {
      "question": "定植",
      "answer": "ていしょく",
      "meaning": "planting out (e.g. seedlings), planting, setting"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄倖",
      "answer": "はっこう",
      "meaning": "unhappiness, sad fate, misfortune"
    },
    {
      "question": "慣用語",
      "answer": "かんようご",
      "meaning": "idiom"
    },
    {
      "question": "心機",
      "answer": "しんき",
      "meaning": "mental state, attitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "泉門",
      "answer": "せんもん",
      "meaning": "soft spot (in the skull of an infant), fontanelle, fontanel, gates of Hades, entrance to the underwo"
    },
    {
      "question": "刻銘",
      "answer": "こくめい",
      "meaning": "inscription on stone monuments, metal receptacles, etc., exergue, inscribing"
    },
    {
      "question": "木膚",
      "answer": "きはだ,こはだ",
      "meaning": "bark (of a tree)"
    },
    {
      "question": "前掲",
      "answer": "ぜんけい",
      "meaning": "above-mentioned, given above, previously shown"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪解",
      "answer": "ゆきげ",
      "meaning": "snow melting, water from melting snow"
    },
    {
      "question": "泉石",
      "answer": "せんせき",
      "meaning": "springs and rocks"
    },
    {
      "question": "降り募る",
      "answer": "ふりつのる",
      "meaning": "to rain harder"
    },
    {
      "question": "銭苔",
      "answer": "ぜにごけ",
      "meaning": "liverwort"
    },
    {
      "question": "出勤簿",
      "answer": "しゅっきんぼ",
      "meaning": "employee's attendance record"
    },
    {
      "question": "接続語",
      "answer": "せつぞくご",
      "meaning": "connective"
    },
    {
      "question": "啓蒙的",
      "answer": "けいもうてき",
      "meaning": "enlightening"
    },
    {
      "question": "短評",
      "answer": "たんぴょう",
      "meaning": "brief comment or criticism"
    },
    {
      "question": "馬食",
      "answer": "ばしょく",
      "meaning": "heavy eating"
    },
    {
      "question": "下意",
      "answer": "かい",
      "meaning": "the feelings of the people"
    },
    {
      "question": "昨冬",
      "answer": "さくとう",
      "meaning": "last winter"
    },
    {
      "question": "人工地震",
      "answer": "じんこうじしん",
      "meaning": "artificial earthquake"
    },
    {
      "question": "飲ん兵衛",
      "answer": "のんべえ",
      "meaning": "heavy drinker, tippler"
    },
    {
      "question": "鰻丼",
      "answer": "うなどん,うなぎどんぶり",
      "meaning": "bowl of eel and rice (donburi)"
    },
    {
      "question": "論理演算",
      "answer": "ろんりえんざん",
      "meaning": "logic operation, logical operation"
    },
    {
      "question": "力足",
      "answer": "ちからあし",
      "meaning": "strong legs"
    },
    {
      "question": "不犯",
      "answer": "ふぼん",
      "meaning": "strict observance of the Buddhist commandment that all priests should be celibate"
    },
    {
      "question": "菜漬け",
      "answer": "なづけ",
      "meaning": "greens pickled in salt (mizuna, mustard leaves, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "盛儀",
      "answer": "せいぎ",
      "meaning": "grand ceremony"
    },
    {
      "question": "南京豆",
      "answer": "ナンキンまめ",
      "meaning": "peanut (Arachis hypogaea)"
    },
    {
      "question": "若布",
      "answer": "わかめ",
      "meaning": "wakame (species of edible brown seaweed, Undaria pinnatifida)"
    },
    {
      "question": "踏切番",
      "answer": "ふみきりばん",
      "meaning": "gatekeeper, crossing guard"
    },
    {
      "question": "杜松",
      "answer": "ねず",
      "meaning": "temple juniper (Juniperus rigida), needle juniper"
    },
    {
      "question": "不退",
      "answer": "ふたい",
      "meaning": "determination"
    },
    {
      "question": "頽唐",
      "answer": "たいとう",
      "meaning": "decadence, decline"
    },
    {
      "question": "水団",
      "answer": "すいとん",
      "meaning": "flour dumplings in soup"
    },
    {
      "question": "窒化",
      "answer": "ちっか",
      "meaning": "nitridization, nitriding, nitride (of)"
    },
    {
      "question": "懸崖",
      "answer": "けんがい",
      "meaning": "overhanging cliff"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒穂",
      "answer": "くろほ,くろぼ",
      "meaning": "smut"
    },
    {
      "question": "稲刈",
      "answer": "いねかり",
      "meaning": "rice reaping, rice harvesting"
    },
    {
      "question": "蒸気浴",
      "answer": "じょうきよく",
      "meaning": "vapor bath, vapour bath, steam bath"
    },
    {
      "question": "物理化学",
      "answer": "ぶつりかがく",
      "meaning": "physical chemistry"
    },
    {
      "question": "来観",
      "answer": "らいかん",
      "meaning": "inspection visit"
    },
    {
      "question": "内輪差",
      "answer": "ないりんさ",
      "meaning": "difference between track followed by front and back inner wheels when turning"
    },
    {
      "question": "毀傷",
      "answer": "きしょう",
      "meaning": "injury, damage"
    },
    {
      "question": "顱頂",
      "answer": "ろちょう",
      "meaning": "top of the head, vertex, parietal"
    },
    {
      "question": "自刎",
      "answer": "じふん",
      "meaning": "committing suicide by slitting one's throat"
    },
    {
      "question": "鶴亀鶴亀",
      "answer": "つるかめつるかめ",
      "meaning": "knock on wood, touch wood"
    },
    {
      "question": "油滴",
      "answer": "ゆてき",
      "meaning": "drop of oil"
    },
    {
      "question": "快投",
      "answer": "かいとう",
      "meaning": "good pitch"
    },
    {
      "question": "友交",
      "answer": "ゆうこう",
      "meaning": "friendship, amity, companionship"
    },
    {
      "question": "ペトリ皿",
      "answer": "ペトリざら",
      "meaning": "Petri dish"
    },
    {
      "question": "変改",
      "answer": "へんかい",
      "meaning": "revise (rules)"
    },
    {
      "question": "大勲位",
      "answer": "だいくんい",
      "meaning": "supreme order (i.e. of the chrysanthemum), highest possible order of merit"
    },
    {
      "question": "衆院",
      "answer": "しゅういん",
      "meaning": "House of Representatives (lower house of the National Diet of Japan)"
    },
    {
      "question": "諸子百家",
      "answer": "しょしひゃっか",
      "meaning": "Hundred Schools of Thought, general term for the large number of scholars and controversialists, and"
    },
    {
      "question": "旧事",
      "answer": "きゅうじ,くじ",
      "meaning": "past events, bygones"
    },
    {
      "question": "混成競技",
      "answer": "こんせいきょうぎ",
      "meaning": "combined competitions"
    },
    {
      "question": "斎食",
      "answer": "さいじき",
      "meaning": "morning meal (for priests, monks, etc.), food offering at a Buddhist ceremony"
    },
    {
      "question": "遵行",
      "answer": "じゅんこう",
      "meaning": "obedience, observance, adherence"
    },
    {
      "question": "始新世",
      "answer": "ししんせい",
      "meaning": "Eocene epoch"
    },
    {
      "question": "創痍",
      "answer": "そうい",
      "meaning": "wound, scar"
    },
    {
      "question": "畳水練",
      "answer": "たたみすいれん",
      "meaning": "useless book learning, knowing the theory but not being able to put it into practice, swim practice"
    },
    {
      "question": "人代名詞",
      "answer": "じんだいめいし",
      "meaning": "personal pronoun"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄荷油",
      "answer": "はっかゆ",
      "meaning": "mint oil, peppermint oil"
    },
    {
      "question": "選り出す",
      "answer": "よりだす,えりだす",
      "meaning": "to select, to pick out"
    },
    {
      "question": "手細工",
      "answer": "てざいく",
      "meaning": "handiwork, handicraft, homemade"
    },
    {
      "question": "仏寺",
      "answer": "ぶつじ",
      "meaning": "Buddhist temple"
    },
    {
      "question": "三角貿易",
      "answer": "さんかくぼうえき",
      "meaning": "trilateral trade"
    },
    {
      "question": "家族手当",
      "answer": "かぞくてあて",
      "meaning": "a family allowance"
    },
    {
      "question": "肺葉",
      "answer": "はいよう",
      "meaning": "pulmonary lobe, lobe of the lung"
    },
    {
      "question": "新柄",
      "answer": "しんがら",
      "meaning": "new pattern"
    },
    {
      "question": "渦紋",
      "answer": "かもん",
      "meaning": "whirlpool design"
    },
    {
      "question": "詰め碁",
      "answer": "つめご",
      "meaning": "composed go problem"
    },
    {
      "question": "海陸",
      "answer": "かいりく",
      "meaning": "land and sea"
    },
    {
      "question": "空空",
      "answer": "くうくう",
      "meaning": "empty, vacant, void"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭付き",
      "answer": "かしらつき,あたまつき",
      "meaning": "hairstyle, shape of one's head, fish served whole"
    },
    {
      "question": "局外中立",
      "answer": "きょくがいちゅうりつ",
      "meaning": "neutrality"
    },
    {
      "question": "林野",
      "answer": "りんや",
      "meaning": "forests and fields"
    },
    {
      "question": "総角",
      "answer": "あげまき,チョンガー",
      "meaning": "old-fashioned boys' hairstyle, Meiji period women's hairstyle, constricted tagelus (Sinonovacula con"
    },
    {
      "question": "勘亭流",
      "answer": "かんていりゅう",
      "meaning": "Kantei style of calligraphy"
    },
    {
      "question": "蹴手繰り",
      "answer": "けたぐり",
      "meaning": "pulling inside ankle sweep"
    },
    {
      "question": "複合語",
      "answer": "ふくごうご",
      "meaning": "compound word, compound term"
    },
    {
      "question": "権力政治",
      "answer": "けんりょくせいじ",
      "meaning": "power politics"
    },
    {
      "question": "官本",
      "answer": "かんぽん",
      "meaning": "official publication, government publication, book belonging to a government office"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪投げ",
      "answer": "ゆきなげ",
      "meaning": "snowball fight"
    },
    {
      "question": "俗謡",
      "answer": "ぞくよう",
      "meaning": "popular song, ballad, folk song, ditty"
    },
    {
      "question": "邦家",
      "answer": "ほうか",
      "meaning": "country, one's own country"
    },
    {
      "question": "荒唐",
      "answer": "こうとう",
      "meaning": "absurd, nonsensical, ridiculous, idiotic, laughable, ludicrous, preposterous"
    },
    {
      "question": "上白",
      "answer": "じょうはく",
      "meaning": "first-class rice"
    },
    {
      "question": "小忠実",
      "answer": "こまめ",
      "meaning": "diligent, earnest, attentive to detail, brisk (working, moving), frequent (e.g. checking)"
    },
    {
      "question": "内無双",
      "answer": "うちむそう",
      "meaning": "inner-thigh-propping twist down"
    },
    {
      "question": "隠見",
      "answer": "いんけん",
      "meaning": "appearance and disappearance"
    },
    {
      "question": "竹箸",
      "answer": "たけばし",
      "meaning": "bamboo chopsticks"
    },
    {
      "question": "小児病",
      "answer": "しょうにびょう",
      "meaning": "childhood diseases"
    },
    {
      "question": "久慈川",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "感性論",
      "answer": "かんせいろん",
      "meaning": "aesthetics, esthetics"
    },
    {
      "question": "按察使",
      "answer": "あぜち,あんさつし",
      "meaning": "travelling inspector of the provincial governments (Nara and Heian-period position)"
    },
    {
      "question": "公権",
      "answer": "こうけん",
      "meaning": "civil rights"
    },
    {
      "question": "寄せ太鼓",
      "answer": "よせだいこ",
      "meaning": "drums sounded in the morning to draw the crowds to a match"
    },
    {
      "question": "俗話",
      "answer": "ぞくわ",
      "meaning": "small talk, gossip, spoken language, colloquial expression"
    },
    {
      "question": "客離れ",
      "answer": "きゃくばなれ",
      "meaning": "customers losing interest in product or shop"
    },
    {
      "question": "動作環境",
      "answer": "どうさかんきょう",
      "meaning": "operating environment"
    },
    {
      "question": "互換機",
      "answer": "ごかんき",
      "meaning": "compatible machine"
    },
    {
      "question": "巻積雲",
      "answer": "けんせきうん",
      "meaning": "cirrocumulus"
    },
    {
      "question": "訪米",
      "answer": "ほうべい",
      "meaning": "visit to America"
    },
    {
      "question": "辛味噌",
      "answer": "からみそ",
      "meaning": "high-salt miso, salty miso"
    },
    {
      "question": "賞玩",
      "answer": "しょうがん,しょうかん",
      "meaning": "appreciation, admiration, enjoyment"
    },
    {
      "question": "和英",
      "answer": "わえい",
      "meaning": "Japanese-English, Japanese-English dictionary"
    },
    {
      "question": "大辛",
      "answer": "おおから,おおがら",
      "meaning": "very spicy"
    },
    {
      "question": "時花",
      "answer": "じか",
      "meaning": "flowers of the season"
    },
    {
      "question": "土壇",
      "answer": "どだん",
      "meaning": "dirt mound, dirt walls on the inside of the sunken hearth in a tea room, platform made of dirt used"
    },
    {
      "question": "率土",
      "answer": "そっと",
      "meaning": "face of the earth"
    },
    {
      "question": "髪結い床",
      "answer": "かみゆいどこ",
      "meaning": "Edo-era barbershop"
    },
    {
      "question": "鳴戸",
      "answer": "なると",
      "meaning": "strait with a roaring tidal ebb and flow, whirlpool, maelstrom, kamaboko with a spiral whirlpool-lik"
    },
    {
      "question": "紅灯",
      "answer": "こうとう",
      "meaning": "red light"
    },
    {
      "question": "窯出し",
      "answer": "かまだし",
      "meaning": "removing pots from kiln"
    },
    {
      "question": "好学",
      "answer": "こうがく",
      "meaning": "love of learning"
    },
    {
      "question": "書き抜く",
      "answer": "かきぬく",
      "meaning": "to extract (e.g. a passage from a book), to make an excerpt"
    },
    {
      "question": "名親",
      "answer": "なおや",
      "meaning": "godparent"
    },
    {
      "question": "煮麺",
      "answer": "にゅうめん",
      "meaning": "soup of sōmen noodles and various ingredients in a soy sauce broth"
    },
    {
      "question": "漢和",
      "answer": "かんわ",
      "meaning": "China and Japan, Chinese and Japanese (languages), dictionary with Japanese definitions of kanji and"
    },
    {
      "question": "流会",
      "answer": "りゅうかい",
      "meaning": "cancelling a meeting, adjournment of a meeting (due to lack of attendance)"
    },
    {
      "question": "臥竜鳳雛",
      "answer": "がりょうほうすう",
      "meaning": "gifted young person who shows much promise, unrecognized genius, great person whose talent is hidden"
    },
    {
      "question": "卵細胞",
      "answer": "らんさいぼう",
      "meaning": "ovum, egg cell"
    },
    {
      "question": "萎黄病",
      "answer": "いおうびょう",
      "meaning": "chlorosis, greensickness"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜夜中",
      "answer": "よるよなか",
      "meaning": "midnight"
    },
    {
      "question": "憖",
      "answer": "なまじ",
      "meaning": "thoughtlessly, rashly, unwisely, half-heartedly, halfway, half-done, incomplete"
    },
    {
      "question": "楽座",
      "answer": "らくざ",
      "meaning": "free markets and open guilds, way of sitting on the ground with the sole of both feet pressed togeth"
    },
    {
      "question": "流説",
      "answer": "りゅうせつ,るせつ",
      "meaning": "groundless rumor, groundless rumour, false report"
    },
    {
      "question": "分離課税",
      "answer": "ぶんりかぜい",
      "meaning": "separate taxation"
    },
    {
      "question": "落球",
      "answer": "らっきゅう",
      "meaning": "failing to catch a ball, dropping a ball, flubbing a catch"
    },
    {
      "question": "三重殺",
      "answer": "さんじゅうさつ",
      "meaning": "triple play"
    },
    {
      "question": "言わでも",
      "answer": "いわでも",
      "meaning": "goes without saying, needn't be said, should rather be left unsaid"
    },
    {
      "question": "陰陽家",
      "answer": "いんようか,おんようけ,おんみょうけ",
      "meaning": "diviner (esp. of the Yin and Yang system), sorcerer, exorcist, medium"
    },
    {
      "question": "陰腹",
      "answer": "かげばら",
      "meaning": "secretly slitting one's belly (and only eventually revealing one's mortal wound) (in kabuki, bunraku"
    },
    {
      "question": "率先躬行",
      "answer": "そっせんきゅうこう",
      "meaning": "taking a lead in (doing), setting an example of (doing)"
    },
    {
      "question": "骨芽細胞",
      "answer": "こつがさいぼう",
      "meaning": "osteoblast"
    },
    {
      "question": "金剛心",
      "answer": "こんごうしん",
      "meaning": "extreme religious piety, unshakable faith"
    },
    {
      "question": "朱鳥",
      "answer": "しゅちょう,すちょう,あかみとり",
      "meaning": "Shuchō era (686.7.20-686.12.?), Suchō era, Akamitori era"
    },
    {
      "question": "早産児",
      "answer": "そうざんじ",
      "meaning": "premature baby"
    },
    {
      "question": "兇弾",
      "answer": "きょうだん",
      "meaning": "assassin's bullet"
    },
    {
      "question": "中華蕎麦",
      "answer": "ちゅうかそば",
      "meaning": "Chinese noodles (esp. ramen)"
    },
    {
      "question": "三具足",
      "answer": "みつぐそく",
      "meaning": "three implements for worship (incense burner, flower vase and candle-stand)"
    },
    {
      "question": "塵灰",
      "answer": "じんかい",
      "meaning": "dust and ash"
    },
    {
      "question": "氷輪",
      "answer": "ひょうりん",
      "meaning": "the moon"
    },
    {
      "question": "瘡",
      "answer": "くさ,かさ",
      "meaning": "eczema, pustule, scab, syphilis, pox"
    },
    {
      "question": "弁髪",
      "answer": "べんぱつ",
      "meaning": "pigtail, queue, cue"
    },
    {
      "question": "分子量",
      "answer": "ぶんしりょう",
      "meaning": "molecular weight"
    },
    {
      "question": "好誼",
      "answer": "こうぎ",
      "meaning": "warm friendship"
    },
    {
      "question": "手織",
      "answer": "ており",
      "meaning": "handwoven, handspun, weaving by hand"
    },
    {
      "question": "贖宥状",
      "answer": "しょくゆうじょう",
      "meaning": "indulgence (religious)"
    },
    {
      "question": "厳刑",
      "answer": "げんけい",
      "meaning": "severe punishment"
    },
    {
      "question": "僧伽",
      "answer": "そうぎゃ",
      "meaning": "sangha (the Buddhist community)"
    },
    {
      "question": "小車",
      "answer": "こぐるま,おぐるま",
      "meaning": "small cart, small carriage, wheeled palanquin (with a castle-shaped box), Inula japonica"
    },
    {
      "question": "諧和",
      "answer": "かいわ,かいか",
      "meaning": "gentle mutual affection, harmony"
    },
    {
      "question": "聯邦",
      "answer": "れんぽう",
      "meaning": "commonwealth, federation of states, confederation, union"
    },
    {
      "question": "老軀",
      "answer": "ろうく",
      "meaning": "one's old bones, aged body"
    },
    {
      "question": "泡雪",
      "answer": "あわゆき",
      "meaning": "light snowfall"
    },
    {
      "question": "棚牡丹",
      "answer": "たなぼた",
      "meaning": "godsend, windfall"
    },
    {
      "question": "養護学校",
      "answer": "ようごがっこう",
      "meaning": "school for the handicapped, special school"
    },
    {
      "question": "喉頭蓋",
      "answer": "こうとうがい",
      "meaning": "epiglottis"
    },
    {
      "question": "合式",
      "answer": "ごうしき",
      "meaning": "formal, regular, valid, categorical"
    },
    {
      "question": "校規",
      "answer": "こうき",
      "meaning": "school regulations"
    },
    {
      "question": "末々",
      "answer": "すえずえ",
      "meaning": "distant future, descendants, lower classes, common people"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦々兢々",
      "answer": "せんせんきょうきょう",
      "meaning": "trembling with fear, filled with trepidation"
    },
    {
      "question": "六腑",
      "answer": "ろっぷ",
      "meaning": "the six internal organs (large intestine, small intestine, gallbladder, stomach, san jiao, urinary b"
    },
    {
      "question": "平筆",
      "answer": "ひらふで",
      "meaning": "flat brush"
    },
    {
      "question": "整流管",
      "answer": "せいりゅうかん",
      "meaning": "rectifier tube, diode"
    },
    {
      "question": "正音",
      "answer": "せいおん",
      "meaning": "correct Chinese (on) pronunciation of a character"
    },
    {
      "question": "年女",
      "answer": "としおんな",
      "meaning": "Woman of the Year, referring to a woman born in a year with the same Chinese zodiac sign as the curr"
    },
    {
      "question": "仲仕",
      "answer": "なかし",
      "meaning": "longshoreman, baggageman"
    },
    {
      "question": "田楽豆腐",
      "answer": "でんがくどうふ",
      "meaning": "skewered pieces of tofu baked and coated with miso"
    },
    {
      "question": "低地帯",
      "answer": "ていちたい",
      "meaning": "low-lying region, lowland, basal zone"
    },
    {
      "question": "緋の袴",
      "answer": "ひのはかま",
      "meaning": "red hakama (worn by miko or noblewomen at court)"
    },
    {
      "question": "受託者",
      "answer": "じゅたくしゃ",
      "meaning": "trustee, assignee, consignee"
    },
    {
      "question": "鱗翅目",
      "answer": "りんしもく",
      "meaning": "Lepidoptera"
    },
    {
      "question": "鳥はむ",
      "answer": "とりはむ",
      "meaning": "chicken ham"
    },
    {
      "question": "緑閃石",
      "answer": "りょくせんせき",
      "meaning": "actinolite"
    },
    {
      "question": "附言",
      "answer": "ふげん",
      "meaning": "saying in addition, postscript, additional remarks"
    },
    {
      "question": "角化",
      "answer": "かくか",
      "meaning": "keratinization, cornification"
    },
    {
      "question": "越境入学",
      "answer": "えっきょうにゅうがく",
      "meaning": "gaining admission into a school in a school district other than one's own"
    },
    {
      "question": "登庸",
      "answer": "とうよう",
      "meaning": "appointment, assignment, promotion"
    },
    {
      "question": "裸出",
      "answer": "らしゅつ",
      "meaning": "exposure"
    },
    {
      "question": "同工異曲",
      "answer": "どうこういきょく",
      "meaning": "equal workmanship but different style"
    },
    {
      "question": "運動学",
      "answer": "うんどうがく",
      "meaning": "kinematics, kinesiology"
    },
    {
      "question": "気腫",
      "answer": "きしゅ",
      "meaning": "emphysema"
    },
    {
      "question": "阿菊虫",
      "answer": "おきくむし",
      "meaning": "chrysalis of a swallowtail butterfly (esp. of species Atrophaneura alcinous)"
    },
    {
      "question": "直履き",
      "answer": "じかばき",
      "meaning": "wearing next to the skin (e.g. shoes without socks, trousers without underwear)"
    },
    {
      "question": "賜与",
      "answer": "しよ",
      "meaning": "giving a gift (to a subordinate)"
    },
    {
      "question": "吟味役",
      "answer": "ぎんみやく",
      "meaning": "auditor (Edo period), examiner, inquisitor, investigator, winner (of the most rounds, i.e. a full ga"
    },
    {
      "question": "来孫",
      "answer": "らいそん",
      "meaning": "fifth-generation descendant, great-great-great-grandchild"
    },
    {
      "question": "延滞利息",
      "answer": "えんたいりそく",
      "meaning": "default interest"
    },
    {
      "question": "筋向かい",
      "answer": "すじむかい",
      "meaning": "diagonally opposite"
    },
    {
      "question": "鮮緑",
      "answer": "せんりょく",
      "meaning": "bright green"
    },
    {
      "question": "雲脂",
      "answer": "ふけ",
      "meaning": "dandruff"
    },
    {
      "question": "笠雲",
      "answer": "かさぐも",
      "meaning": "cap cloud (cloud shaped like an Asian bamboo hat that forms at the peak of a tall mountain)"
    },
    {
      "question": "押し麦",
      "answer": "おしむぎ",
      "meaning": "rolled barley, rolled oats"
    },
    {
      "question": "配収",
      "answer": "はいしゅう",
      "meaning": "distribution revenue (e.g. films), distribution income"
    },
    {
      "question": "怨み節",
      "answer": "うらみぶし",
      "meaning": "song with lyrics about resentment and a sorrowful tune, resentful complaint"
    },
    {
      "question": "中心角",
      "answer": "ちゅうしんかく",
      "meaning": "central angle"
    },
    {
      "question": "斜坑",
      "answer": "しゃこう",
      "meaning": "inclined shaft"
    },
    {
      "question": "人口学",
      "answer": "じんこうがく",
      "meaning": "demography"
    },
    {
      "question": "円頂",
      "answer": "えんちょう",
      "meaning": "dome, cupola"
    },
    {
      "question": "在米",
      "answer": "ざいべい,ざいまい,ありまい",
      "meaning": "being in the United States, staying in the United States, residing in the United States, rice stocks"
    },
    {
      "question": "慶安",
      "answer": "けいあん",
      "meaning": "agency for employing servants and arranging marriages (Edo period), mediator, go-between, flattery,"
    },
    {
      "question": "十死一生",
      "answer": "じっしいっしょう",
      "meaning": "narrow escape from the jaws of death, there being barely a chance of escaping death"
    },
    {
      "question": "画本",
      "answer": "がほん",
      "meaning": "picture copybook"
    },
    {
      "question": "利刃",
      "answer": "りじん",
      "meaning": "sharp sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉢物",
      "answer": "はちもの",
      "meaning": "food served in bowls, potted plant, bonsai"
    },
    {
      "question": "雛妓",
      "answer": "すうぎ",
      "meaning": "child geisha, geisha apprentice"
    },
    {
      "question": "嵩高い",
      "answer": "かさだかい",
      "meaning": "bulky, unwieldy, haughty, high-handed"
    },
    {
      "question": "本然",
      "answer": "ほんぜん,ほんねん",
      "meaning": "natural, inborn, inherent, innate"
    },
    {
      "question": "易学",
      "answer": "えきがく",
      "meaning": "study of divination"
    },
    {
      "question": "再校",
      "answer": "さいこう",
      "meaning": "second proof, second revision"
    },
    {
      "question": "微生物学",
      "answer": "びせいぶつがく",
      "meaning": "microbiology"
    },
    {
      "question": "大愚",
      "answer": "たいぐ",
      "meaning": "great folly or fool"
    },
    {
      "question": "蛸足配線",
      "answer": "たこあしはいせん",
      "meaning": "overloading an electrical circuit, piggybacked electrical outlet, 'octopus outlet'"
    },
    {
      "question": "隙目",
      "answer": "すきめ",
      "meaning": "gap, opening, crevice, crack"
    },
    {
      "question": "徳治主義",
      "answer": "とくちしゅぎ",
      "meaning": "principle of virtuous government, virtue as the principle of good government"
    },
    {
      "question": "雲煙",
      "answer": "うんえん",
      "meaning": "clouds and smoke, landscape"
    },
    {
      "question": "典籍",
      "answer": "てんせき,てんじゃく",
      "meaning": "books, writings"
    },
    {
      "question": "証票",
      "answer": "しょうひょう",
      "meaning": "certificate, voucher, chit"
    },
    {
      "question": "副甲状腺",
      "answer": "ふくこうじょうせん",
      "meaning": "parathyroid"
    },
    {
      "question": "円鑿",
      "answer": "まるのみ",
      "meaning": "gouge, scorper, scauper"
    },
    {
      "question": "画派",
      "answer": "がは",
      "meaning": "school of painting"
    },
    {
      "question": "敬仰",
      "answer": "けいこう,けいぎょう",
      "meaning": "adoration, admiration, reverence"
    },
    {
      "question": "夏場所",
      "answer": "なつばしょ",
      "meaning": "summer (May) tournament, held in Tokyo"
    },
    {
      "question": "鯖を読む",
      "answer": "さばをよむ",
      "meaning": "to manipulate figures to one's advantage, to count wrongly on purpose, to inflate or deflate one's a"
    },
    {
      "question": "人文主義",
      "answer": "じんぶんしゅぎ",
      "meaning": "humanism"
    },
    {
      "question": "煮売り屋",
      "answer": "にうりや",
      "meaning": "store selling boiled vegetables, fish, and beans"
    },
    {
      "question": "連れ小便",
      "answer": "つれしょうべん",
      "meaning": "going off to urinate together"
    },
    {
      "question": "調髪",
      "answer": "ちょうはつ",
      "meaning": "haircut, barbering"
    },
    {
      "question": "寛寛",
      "answer": "かんかん",
      "meaning": "looking cool and collect, with an air of perfect composure"
    },
    {
      "question": "窮理",
      "answer": "きゅうり",
      "meaning": "study of natural laws, branch of neo-Confusianist scholarship"
    },
    {
      "question": "食酢",
      "answer": "しょくず,しょくす",
      "meaning": "vinegar, table vinegar"
    },
    {
      "question": "聖公会",
      "answer": "せいこうかい",
      "meaning": "Anglican or Episcopal Church"
    },
    {
      "question": "原水",
      "answer": "げんすい",
      "meaning": "raw water"
    },
    {
      "question": "其の手",
      "answer": "そのて",
      "meaning": "that kind of, that way, that move, that trick, that game"
    },
    {
      "question": "雁が音",
      "answer": "かりがね",
      "meaning": "call of a wild goose, wild goose (esp. a lesser white-fronted goose, Anser erythropus), tea made fro"
    },
    {
      "question": "燃ゆる水",
      "answer": "もゆるみず",
      "meaning": "petroleum"
    },
    {
      "question": "課税標準",
      "answer": "かぜいひょうじゅん",
      "meaning": "base of taxation"
    },
    {
      "question": "訂する",
      "answer": "ていする",
      "meaning": "to correct"
    },
    {
      "question": "姦淫罪",
      "answer": "かんいんざい",
      "meaning": "sex crimes"
    },
    {
      "question": "皺襞",
      "answer": "しゅうへき",
      "meaning": "folds (e.g. on a mountain)"
    },
    {
      "question": "丈余",
      "answer": "じょうよ",
      "meaning": "over ten feet"
    },
    {
      "question": "多毛類",
      "answer": "たもうるい",
      "meaning": "bristle worm, polychaete"
    },
    {
      "question": "筆を擱く",
      "answer": "ふでをおく",
      "meaning": "to stop writing, to put down one's pen, to close (a letter)"
    },
    {
      "question": "ミサ曲",
      "answer": "ミサきょく",
      "meaning": "mass, setting of the ordinary of the mass (Kyrie, Credo, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "揚げ代",
      "answer": "あげだい",
      "meaning": "fee paid for the services of a geisha or prostitute"
    },
    {
      "question": "冬官",
      "answer": "とうかん",
      "meaning": "Ministry of Works (Zhou-dynasty China)"
    },
    {
      "question": "釣り球",
      "answer": "つりだま",
      "meaning": "bait pitch, sucker pitch, pitch that lures a batter to swing"
    },
    {
      "question": "賃銀",
      "answer": "ちんぎん",
      "meaning": "wages, pay"
    },
    {
      "question": "二部合唱",
      "answer": "にぶがっしょう",
      "meaning": "two-part chorus, vocal duet"
    },
    {
      "question": "緒に就く",
      "answer": "しょにつく,ちょにつく",
      "meaning": "to be started, to get underway"
    },
    {
      "question": "貸間",
      "answer": "かしま",
      "meaning": "room to let, room for rent"
    },
    {
      "question": "一時所得",
      "answer": "いちじしょとく",
      "meaning": "occasional income"
    },
    {
      "question": "際疾い",
      "answer": "きわどい",
      "meaning": "risky, dangerous, hazardous, perilous, close (e.g. game), narrow (e.g. victory), suggestive, borderi"
    },
    {
      "question": "嘸かし",
      "answer": "さぞかし",
      "meaning": "certainly, surely"
    },
    {
      "question": "折り本",
      "answer": "おりほん",
      "meaning": "folding book, folded sections of a book"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤魚",
      "answer": "あかうお,あこう",
      "meaning": "Pacific ocean perch (Sebastes alutus), comb goby (Ctenotrypauchen microcephalus), Matsubara's red ro"
    },
    {
      "question": "書院造り",
      "answer": "しょいんづくり",
      "meaning": "traditional style of Japanese residential architecture"
    },
    {
      "question": "銘文",
      "answer": "めいぶん",
      "meaning": "inscription"
    },
    {
      "question": "直路",
      "answer": "すぐみち,ちょくろ",
      "meaning": "straight road, short cut"
    },
    {
      "question": "芯地",
      "answer": "しんじ",
      "meaning": "padding, lining, foundation"
    },
    {
      "question": "前脳",
      "answer": "ぜんのう",
      "meaning": "forebrain, prosencephalon"
    },
    {
      "question": "裏移り",
      "answer": "うらうつり",
      "meaning": "set-off, offset, unwanted transfer of ink from a freshly printed sheet to an adjacent sheet in a pil"
    },
    {
      "question": "鰯雲",
      "answer": "いわしぐも",
      "meaning": "cirro-cumulus, mackerel sky"
    },
    {
      "question": "招宴",
      "answer": "しょうえん",
      "meaning": "banquet, invitation to a party, party"
    },
    {
      "question": "生新しい",
      "answer": "なまあたらしい",
      "meaning": "very fresh"
    },
    {
      "question": "縮刷",
      "answer": "しゅくさつ",
      "meaning": "reduced-size printing, printing in a compact format"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷水浴",
      "answer": "れいすいよく",
      "meaning": "cold bath, cold shower"
    },
    {
      "question": "燻蒸剤",
      "answer": "くんじょうざい",
      "meaning": "fumigant"
    },
    {
      "question": "心障",
      "answer": "しんしょう",
      "meaning": "mental disorder"
    },
    {
      "question": "力編",
      "answer": "りきへん",
      "meaning": "painstaking piece of work, work of great effort, tour de force, outstanding work"
    },
    {
      "question": "席割り",
      "answer": "せきわり",
      "meaning": "seat allocation, fee paid to an performer (at a vaudeville hall), appearance fee"
    },
    {
      "question": "裾模様",
      "answer": "すそもよう",
      "meaning": "kimono with design on the skirt"
    },
    {
      "question": "正治",
      "answer": "しょうじ",
      "meaning": "Shōji era (1199.4.27-1201.2.13)"
    },
    {
      "question": "其の道",
      "answer": "そのみち",
      "meaning": "that road (path, street, way, etc.), that line (of business), that profession, that trade, love affa"
    },
    {
      "question": "文芸欄",
      "answer": "ぶんげいらん",
      "meaning": "literary (and the arts) column"
    },
    {
      "question": "盗汗",
      "answer": "ねあせ,とうかん",
      "meaning": "perspiration given off during sleep, sweating while sleeping, night sweats"
    },
    {
      "question": "癲狂院",
      "answer": "てんきょういん",
      "meaning": "asylum, bedlam"
    },
    {
      "question": "現然",
      "answer": "げんぜん",
      "meaning": "clearly visible"
    },
    {
      "question": "嬰児殺し",
      "answer": "えいじごろし",
      "meaning": "infanticide"
    },
    {
      "question": "華鬘",
      "answer": "けまん",
      "meaning": "Buddhist decoration engraved with various motifs, often made from gilt copper (e.g. for adorning the"
    },
    {
      "question": "雲鑼",
      "answer": "うんら",
      "meaning": "yunluo (10 small gongs mounted in a wooden frame)"
    },
    {
      "question": "劫掠",
      "answer": "きょうりゃく,ごうりゃく",
      "meaning": "pillage, plunder"
    },
    {
      "question": "送呈",
      "answer": "そうてい",
      "meaning": "sending a book as a present"
    },
    {
      "question": "一膳飯屋",
      "answer": "いちぜんめしや",
      "meaning": "simple and inexpensive restaurant, diner"
    },
    {
      "question": "嗄声",
      "answer": "させい,かせい",
      "meaning": "hoarseness, hoarse voice"
    },
    {
      "question": "端綱",
      "answer": "はづな",
      "meaning": "halter"
    },
    {
      "question": "操行",
      "answer": "そうこう",
      "meaning": "conduct, deportment"
    },
    {
      "question": "色校正",
      "answer": "いろこうせい",
      "meaning": "checking the colors on a colored proof (colour)"
    },
    {
      "question": "高踏",
      "answer": "こうとう",
      "meaning": "highbrow, aloof, transcendent"
    },
    {
      "question": "草鞋虫",
      "answer": "わらじむし",
      "meaning": "wood louse, wood lice, slater"
    },
    {
      "question": "媒染",
      "answer": "ばいせん",
      "meaning": "color fixing, colour fixing, mordantizing"
    },
    {
      "question": "盛土",
      "answer": "もりど,もりつち",
      "meaning": "embankment (for road, railway, etc.), raising the ground level, fill"
    },
    {
      "question": "建久",
      "answer": "けんきゅう",
      "meaning": "Kenkyū era (1190.4.11-1199.4.27)"
    },
    {
      "question": "デボン紀",
      "answer": "デボンき",
      "meaning": "Devonian period"
    },
    {
      "question": "曲学阿世",
      "answer": "きょくがくあせい",
      "meaning": "prostitution of learning, twisting the truth and truckling to the times"
    },
    {
      "question": "師管",
      "answer": "しかん",
      "meaning": "sieve tube"
    },
    {
      "question": "花結び",
      "answer": "はなむすび",
      "meaning": "rosette"
    },
    {
      "question": "升酒",
      "answer": "ますざけ",
      "meaning": "alcohol (esp. sake) served in a small wooden box, alcohol (esp. sake) sold in a small wooden box"
    },
    {
      "question": "道央",
      "answer": "どうおう",
      "meaning": "central Hokkaido"
    },
    {
      "question": "事件記者",
      "answer": "じけんきしゃ",
      "meaning": "police reporter"
    },
    {
      "question": "庶事",
      "answer": "しょじ",
      "meaning": "various matters, everything"
    },
    {
      "question": "閑日月",
      "answer": "かんじつげつ",
      "meaning": "leisure"
    },
    {
      "question": "五障",
      "answer": "ごしょう",
      "meaning": "five hindrances (that prevent a woman from becoming a Buddha, a Brahmā, a Shakra, a devil king, or a"
    },
    {
      "question": "百貨",
      "answer": "ひゃっか",
      "meaning": "all kinds of goods"
    },
    {
      "question": "踵骨",
      "answer": "しょうこつ",
      "meaning": "calcaneus, calcaneum, heel bone"
    },
    {
      "question": "建玉",
      "answer": "たてぎょく",
      "meaning": "position (in finance: amount of a security either owned or owed by an investor or dealer), open inte"
    },
    {
      "question": "照尺",
      "answer": "しょうしゃく",
      "meaning": "sight (of a firearm)"
    },
    {
      "question": "月給取り",
      "answer": "げっきゅうとり",
      "meaning": "salaried employee"
    },
    {
      "question": "男伊達",
      "answer": "おとこだて",
      "meaning": "chivalrous man who helps the weak and fights the strong, knight in shining armor, ruffians who act u"
    },
    {
      "question": "大豆油",
      "answer": "だいずゆ,だいずあぶら",
      "meaning": "soybean oil"
    },
    {
      "question": "恐惶謹言",
      "answer": "きょうこうきんげん",
      "meaning": "Very truly yours (a complimentary close used in a letter written in an old epistolary style)"
    },
    {
      "question": "変格活用",
      "answer": "へんかくかつよう",
      "meaning": "irregular conjugation (declension, inflection), irregular verb"
    },
    {
      "question": "未済",
      "answer": "みさい",
      "meaning": "executory, unpaid"
    },
    {
      "question": "跡切れ",
      "answer": "とぎれ",
      "meaning": "break, pause, interruption, intermission"
    },
    {
      "question": "可也",
      "answer": "かなり",
      "meaning": "considerably, fairly, quite"
    },
    {
      "question": "飲み手",
      "answer": "のみて",
      "meaning": "heavy drinker"
    },
    {
      "question": "翁草",
      "answer": "おきなぐさ",
      "meaning": "nodding anemone (Anemone cernua), chrysanthemum, pine"
    },
    {
      "question": "方鉛鉱",
      "answer": "ほうえんこう",
      "meaning": "galena"
    },
    {
      "question": "猿面冠者",
      "answer": "さるめんかんじゃ,さるめんかじゃ",
      "meaning": "young person with a monkey-like face (nickname for Toyotomi Hideyoshi)"
    },
    {
      "question": "弓筈",
      "answer": "ゆみはず,ゆはず",
      "meaning": "nock (of a bow)"
    },
    {
      "question": "船積み",
      "answer": "ふなづみ",
      "meaning": "lading, shipment"
    },
    {
      "question": "矯正視力",
      "answer": "きょうせいしりょく",
      "meaning": "corrected eyesight"
    },
    {
      "question": "併吞",
      "answer": "へいどん",
      "meaning": "annexation, merger, swallowing up"
    },
    {
      "question": "黄鐘調",
      "answer": "おうしきちょう,おうしきじょう",
      "meaning": "ōshiki mode (one of the six main gagaku modes)"
    },
    {
      "question": "渦電流",
      "answer": "うずでんりゅう",
      "meaning": "eddy current (elec.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "鴻基",
      "answer": "こうき",
      "meaning": "foundation of a great project, base of a great enterprise"
    },
    {
      "question": "教育勅語",
      "answer": "きょういくちょくご",
      "meaning": "Imperial Rescript on Education (1890)"
    },
    {
      "question": "日増し",
      "answer": "ひまし",
      "meaning": "increasing daily, increasing day by day, foodstuffs left out for many days"
    },
    {
      "question": "不行儀",
      "answer": "ふぎょうぎ",
      "meaning": "bad manners, rudeness"
    },
    {
      "question": "豊麗線",
      "answer": "ほうれいせん",
      "meaning": "nasolabial fold, smile line, laugh line"
    },
    {
      "question": "地方財政",
      "answer": "ちほうざいせい",
      "meaning": "local government finance"
    },
    {
      "question": "活字文化",
      "answer": "かつじぶんか",
      "meaning": "culture of the printed word, book culture"
    },
    {
      "question": "花笠音頭",
      "answer": "はながさおんど",
      "meaning": "traditional ballad sung wearing hanagasa (esp. Yamagata Pref.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "酪酸",
      "answer": "らくさん",
      "meaning": "butyric acid"
    },
    {
      "question": "元禄袖",
      "answer": "げんろくそで",
      "meaning": "short and round sleeves of a kimono"
    },
    {
      "question": "土崩瓦解",
      "answer": "どほうがかい",
      "meaning": "complete collapse, (something) going to pieces (breaking up beyond repair)"
    },
    {
      "question": "勝運",
      "answer": "しょううん",
      "meaning": "luck at winning"
    },
    {
      "question": "麝香猫",
      "answer": "じゃこうねこ",
      "meaning": "civet cat"
    },
    {
      "question": "片肌",
      "answer": "かたはだ",
      "meaning": "bare shoulder"
    },
    {
      "question": "随想録",
      "answer": "ずいそうろく",
      "meaning": "essays, collection of miscellaneous thoughts"
    },
    {
      "question": "道床",
      "answer": "どうしょう",
      "meaning": "roadbed"
    },
    {
      "question": "再生繊維",
      "answer": "さいせいせんい",
      "meaning": "regenerated fiber, regenerated fibre"
    },
    {
      "question": "悼辞",
      "answer": "とうじ",
      "meaning": "funeral address, message of condolence, words of condolence"
    },
    {
      "question": "懲悪",
      "answer": "ちょうあく",
      "meaning": "chastisement for evildoing, punishment"
    },
    {
      "question": "嗽",
      "answer": "うがい",
      "meaning": "gargling, rinsing one's mouth"
    },
    {
      "question": "咏",
      "answer": "えい",
      "meaning": "recitation (of a poem), chanting, singing, composition (of a poem), composed poem"
    },
    {
      "question": "馳駆",
      "answer": "ちく",
      "meaning": "dashing around on a horse, running around, exerting oneself (for another)"
    },
    {
      "question": "餡ころ餅",
      "answer": "あんころもち",
      "meaning": "mochi wrapped with sweet bean jam"
    },
    {
      "question": "抑鬱",
      "answer": "よくうつ",
      "meaning": "dejection, depression"
    },
    {
      "question": "愛翫",
      "answer": "あいがん",
      "meaning": "caring for (esp. a pet or a small object), cherishing, being fond of, prizing, treasuring"
    },
    {
      "question": "慶弔",
      "answer": "けいちょう",
      "meaning": "congratulations and condolences"
    },
    {
      "question": "読み人",
      "answer": "よみびと",
      "meaning": "(poetic) author"
    },
    {
      "question": "発馬",
      "answer": "はつば",
      "meaning": "start (of a horse race)"
    },
    {
      "question": "手回り",
      "answer": "てまわり",
      "meaning": "at hand, personal effects or belongings"
    },
    {
      "question": "南極海",
      "answer": "なんきょくかい",
      "meaning": "Antarctic Ocean"
    },
    {
      "question": "尻窄まり",
      "answer": "しりすぼまり",
      "meaning": "attenuating, fizzling out"
    },
    {
      "question": "故殺",
      "answer": "こさつ",
      "meaning": "(voluntary) manslaughter, killing with intent"
    },
    {
      "question": "月利",
      "answer": "げつり",
      "meaning": "monthly interest"
    },
    {
      "question": "安危",
      "answer": "あんき",
      "meaning": "fate, safety, welfare"
    },
    {
      "question": "絶え入る",
      "answer": "たえいる",
      "meaning": "to expire"
    },
    {
      "question": "造作無い",
      "answer": "ぞうさない",
      "meaning": "no trouble, easy, simple"
    },
    {
      "question": "張り札",
      "answer": "はりふだ",
      "meaning": "poster, notice, harifuda (type of playing cards numbered 1-6; used for playing tehonbiki)"
    },
    {
      "question": "粉もん",
      "answer": "こなもん",
      "meaning": "food made from flour (esp. dishes like okonomiyaki and takoyaki)"
    },
    {
      "question": "水烏賊",
      "answer": "みずいか",
      "meaning": "bigfin reef squid, oval squid (Sepioteuthis lessoniana)"
    },
    {
      "question": "産業資本",
      "answer": "さんぎょうしほん",
      "meaning": "industrial capital"
    },
    {
      "question": "不易流行",
      "answer": "ふえきりゅうこう",
      "meaning": "the principle of fluidity and immutability in haiku, Haiku is both 'fluid and transitory' and 'etern"
    },
    {
      "question": "僧体",
      "answer": "そうたい",
      "meaning": "appearance of a Buddhist priest"
    },
    {
      "question": "冴え返る",
      "answer": "さえかえる",
      "meaning": "to be very clear, to be keenly cold, to be cold and clear"
    },
    {
      "question": "映倫",
      "answer": "えいりん",
      "meaning": "Eirin, Film Classification and Rating Organization"
    },
    {
      "question": "空巣狙い",
      "answer": "あきすねらい",
      "meaning": "burglary (of an empty house), burglar (who targets empty houses), sneak thief, prowler"
    },
    {
      "question": "時法",
      "answer": "じほう",
      "meaning": "time convention, way of dividing day into hours, hour system"
    },
    {
      "question": "サゴ椰子",
      "answer": "サゴやし",
      "meaning": "sago palm (Metroxylon sagu)"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒色人種",
      "answer": "こくしょくじんしゅ",
      "meaning": "black race"
    },
    {
      "question": "食細胞",
      "answer": "しょくさいぼう",
      "meaning": "phagocyte"
    },
    {
      "question": "迷夢",
      "answer": "めいむ",
      "meaning": "illusion, fallacy, delusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "髄質",
      "answer": "ずいしつ",
      "meaning": "medulla"
    },
    {
      "question": "核戦力",
      "answer": "かくせんりょく",
      "meaning": "nuclear force"
    },
    {
      "question": "宣耀殿",
      "answer": "せんようでん,せんにょうでん",
      "meaning": "ladies' pavilion (of the inner Heian Palace)"
    },
    {
      "question": "立ち暗み",
      "answer": "たちくらみ",
      "meaning": "dizziness (from standing up too fast), orthostatic syncope, lightheadedness, vertigo"
    },
    {
      "question": "利生",
      "answer": "りしょう",
      "meaning": "blessings bestowed by the Buddha on all living creatures"
    },
    {
      "question": "不料簡",
      "answer": "ふりょうけん",
      "meaning": "indiscretion, bad idea, thoughtlessness, indiscreetness"
    },
    {
      "question": "邏卒",
      "answer": "らそつ",
      "meaning": "serviceman on patrol, policeman (early Meiji era)"
    },
    {
      "question": "敷板",
      "answer": "しきいた",
      "meaning": "floorboard, plank"
    },
    {
      "question": "常任委員",
      "answer": "じょうにんいいん",
      "meaning": "member of a standing committee"
    },
    {
      "question": "添乗",
      "answer": "てんじょう",
      "meaning": "accompanying (on a trip), escorting (a tour group)"
    },
    {
      "question": "甘葛",
      "answer": "あまずら",
      "meaning": "ivy (esp. Boston ivy, Parthenocissus tricuspidata), jiaogulan (species of herbaceous vine; Gynostemm"
    },
    {
      "question": "四書五経",
      "answer": "ししょごきょう",
      "meaning": "the Four Books and Five Classics of Confucianism, the Nine Chinese Classics"
    },
    {
      "question": "静思",
      "answer": "せいし",
      "meaning": "meditation"
    },
    {
      "question": "死亡届け",
      "answer": "しぼうとどけ",
      "meaning": "report of death, notification of a death"
    },
    {
      "question": "円貨",
      "answer": "えんか",
      "meaning": "yen currency"
    },
    {
      "question": "海狸",
      "answer": "かいり,うみだぬき",
      "meaning": "beaver"
    },
    {
      "question": "見越し",
      "answer": "みこし",
      "meaning": "anticipation, expectation, looking over (e.g. a fence)"
    },
    {
      "question": "希望退職",
      "answer": "きぼうたいしょく",
      "meaning": "voluntary retirement"
    },
    {
      "question": "寄居虫",
      "answer": "やどかり,ごうな,かみな",
      "meaning": "hermit crab"
    },
    {
      "question": "下刻",
      "answer": "げこく,かこく",
      "meaning": "final third of a two-hour period, downcutting, downward erosion, vertical erosion"
    },
    {
      "question": "生馬",
      "answer": "いけま",
      "meaning": "Cynanchum caudatum (species of swallowwort)"
    },
    {
      "question": "電鈴",
      "answer": "でんれい",
      "meaning": "electric bell"
    },
    {
      "question": "端ミシン",
      "answer": "たんミシン",
      "meaning": "machined edge, edge-stitched seam"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪風",
      "answer": "あくふう",
      "meaning": "vice, bad manners, evil customs, storm, raging winds"
    },
    {
      "question": "自然増",
      "answer": "しぜんぞう",
      "meaning": "natural increase"
    },
    {
      "question": "不安心",
      "answer": "ふあんしん",
      "meaning": "uneasiness, uncertainty, anxiety, apprehension, restlessness, insecurity, suspense, fear"
    },
    {
      "question": "二分音符",
      "answer": "にぶおんぷ,にぶんおんぷ",
      "meaning": "half note, minim"
    },
    {
      "question": "達て",
      "answer": "たって",
      "meaning": "strongly hoping or requesting (of something that is difficult to be brought to fruition)"
    },
    {
      "question": "自治行政",
      "answer": "じちぎょうせい",
      "meaning": "self-government"
    },
    {
      "question": "換る",
      "answer": "かわる",
      "meaning": "to succeed, to relieve, to replace, to take the place of, to substitute for, to take over for, to re"
    },
    {
      "question": "竜骨座",
      "answer": "りゅうこつざ",
      "meaning": "Carina (constellation), the Keel"
    },
    {
      "question": "内国債",
      "answer": "ないこくさい",
      "meaning": "internal debt or loans"
    },
    {
      "question": "角袖",
      "answer": "かくそで",
      "meaning": "square sleeves"
    },
    {
      "question": "吟唱",
      "answer": "ぎんしょう",
      "meaning": "recital, recitation, chant(ing)"
    },
    {
      "question": "切干し",
      "answer": "きりぼし",
      "meaning": "dried daikon strips"
    },
    {
      "question": "世間智",
      "answer": "せけんち",
      "meaning": "worldly wisdom, knowledge of the ways of the world"
    },
    {
      "question": "現業",
      "answer": "げんぎょう",
      "meaning": "on-site work, work-site operations"
    },
    {
      "question": "各月",
      "answer": "かくげつ",
      "meaning": "every month"
    },
    {
      "question": "近代音楽",
      "answer": "きんだいおんがく",
      "meaning": "modern music, contemporary music"
    },
    {
      "question": "法会",
      "answer": "ほうえ",
      "meaning": "Buddhist service (e.g. memorial service)"
    },
    {
      "question": "重馬場",
      "answer": "おもばば",
      "meaning": "muddy track (in horse racing), dead track"
    },
    {
      "question": "蘚苔",
      "answer": "せんたい",
      "meaning": "moss, bryophyte"
    },
    {
      "question": "咬傷",
      "answer": "こうしょう",
      "meaning": "biting wound, bite"
    },
    {
      "question": "無駄食い",
      "answer": "むだぐい",
      "meaning": "eating between meals, wasteful eating habits, waste of resources, living idly, loafing one's way thr"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪見障子",
      "answer": "ゆきみしょうじ",
      "meaning": "shoji with glass window behind a sliding bottom half"
    },
    {
      "question": "正貨",
      "answer": "せいか",
      "meaning": "specie, metallic currency"
    },
    {
      "question": "次亜",
      "answer": "じあ",
      "meaning": "hypo- (indicating the lowest oxidation state)"
    },
    {
      "question": "小鯨",
      "answer": "こくじら",
      "meaning": "gray whale"
    },
    {
      "question": "活版所",
      "answer": "かっぱんじょ,かっぱんしょ",
      "meaning": "printer's, print shop"
    },
    {
      "question": "芬芬",
      "answer": "ふんぷん",
      "meaning": "(of a smell, esp. a good smell) strong"
    },
    {
      "question": "嗅神経",
      "answer": "きゅうしんけい",
      "meaning": "olfactory nerve"
    },
    {
      "question": "帽子掛",
      "answer": "ぼうしかけ",
      "meaning": "hat rack, hat stand, hat peg"
    },
    {
      "question": "中夏",
      "answer": "ちゅうか",
      "meaning": "midsummer, China, Chinese, capital (city, town)"
    },
    {
      "question": "歩測",
      "answer": "ほそく",
      "meaning": "pacing off (a measurement or distance)"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤出し",
      "answer": "あかだし",
      "meaning": "soup made with red miso paste, red miso soup"
    },
    {
      "question": "失敬千万",
      "answer": "しっけいせんばん",
      "meaning": "extremely rude (impertinent, impolite)"
    },
    {
      "question": "折柄",
      "answer": "おりから,おりがら",
      "meaning": "just then, at that time, right then, at that moment, appropriate moment"
    },
    {
      "question": "持家",
      "answer": "もちいえ,もちや",
      "meaning": "one's (own) house"
    },
    {
      "question": "揚水機",
      "answer": "ようすいき",
      "meaning": "water pump"
    },
    {
      "question": "特需景気",
      "answer": "とくじゅけいき",
      "meaning": "economic boom due to special procurements, esp. in wartime"
    },
    {
      "question": "後発品",
      "answer": "こうはつひん",
      "meaning": "generic (drug), me-too (drug)"
    },
    {
      "question": "ゼロ歳児",
      "answer": "ゼロさいじ",
      "meaning": "child under a year old"
    },
    {
      "question": "予て",
      "answer": "かねて",
      "meaning": "previously, already, for some time, for quite a while"
    },
    {
      "question": "債鬼",
      "answer": "さいき",
      "meaning": "cruel creditor, bill collector"
    },
    {
      "question": "分有",
      "answer": "ぶんゆう",
      "meaning": "partial ownership, possession in portions"
    },
    {
      "question": "誘電加熱",
      "answer": "ゆうでんかねつ",
      "meaning": "dielectric heating"
    },
    {
      "question": "縦横家",
      "answer": "じゅうおうか,しょうおうか",
      "meaning": "School of Diplomacy, one of the Schools of Thought during the Warring States period in China"
    },
    {
      "question": "処女峰",
      "answer": "しょじょほう",
      "meaning": "untrodden peak"
    },
    {
      "question": "女旱",
      "answer": "おんなひでり",
      "meaning": "scarcity of eligible women, difficulty for a man to find a woman, woman shortage"
    },
    {
      "question": "低潮",
      "answer": "ていちょう",
      "meaning": "low tide, low water"
    },
    {
      "question": "口塞ぎ",
      "answer": "くちふさぎ",
      "meaning": "prohibition of speaking, imposition of silence, tiny morsel"
    },
    {
      "question": "船荷証券",
      "answer": "ふなにしょうけん",
      "meaning": "bill of lading, BL"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪液質",
      "answer": "あくえきしつ",
      "meaning": "cachexia, cachexy, wasting syndrome"
    },
    {
      "question": "明け番",
      "answer": "あけばん",
      "meaning": "day off, off duty"
    },
    {
      "question": "掛け詞",
      "answer": "かけことば",
      "meaning": "kakekotoba, pivot word, play on words (esp. in poetry), pun"
    },
    {
      "question": "慣性系",
      "answer": "かんせいけい",
      "meaning": "inertial system, inertial frame of reference"
    },
    {
      "question": "胞子体",
      "answer": "ほうしたい",
      "meaning": "sporophyte"
    },
    {
      "question": "尋ね者",
      "answer": "たずねもの",
      "meaning": "wanted person"
    },
    {
      "question": "重力計",
      "answer": "じゅうりょくけい",
      "meaning": "gravimeter"
    },
    {
      "question": "此の人",
      "answer": "このひと",
      "meaning": "this person"
    },
    {
      "question": "わん公",
      "answer": "わんこう",
      "meaning": "dog"
    },
    {
      "question": "式部職",
      "answer": "しきぶしょく",
      "meaning": "Board of Ceremonies (part of the Imperial Household Agency)"
    },
    {
      "question": "胎芽",
      "answer": "たいが",
      "meaning": "embryo, bulbil"
    },
    {
      "question": "労務者",
      "answer": "ろうむしゃ",
      "meaning": "laborer, labourer, workman"
    },
    {
      "question": "為種",
      "answer": "しぐさ",
      "meaning": "gesture, movement, action, behavior, behaviour, bearing, mannerism, acting, performance"
    },
    {
      "question": "衰滅",
      "answer": "すいめつ",
      "meaning": "decline, downfall, ruin(ation)"
    },
    {
      "question": "風鎮",
      "answer": "ふうちん",
      "meaning": "hanging-scroll weight"
    },
    {
      "question": "営業費",
      "answer": "えいぎょうひ",
      "meaning": "operating expenses, operating cost"
    },
    {
      "question": "素的",
      "answer": "すてき",
      "meaning": "lovely, wonderful, nice, great, fantastic, superb, cool"
    },
    {
      "question": "伝法灌頂",
      "answer": "でんぼうかんじょう",
      "meaning": "consecration ritual for the conferral of the status of Acharya (in esoteric Buddhism)"
    },
    {
      "question": "夏帽子",
      "answer": "なつぼうし",
      "meaning": "summer hat, straw hat"
    },
    {
      "question": "巻尾",
      "answer": "かんび",
      "meaning": "end of a book"
    },
    {
      "question": "護摩の灰",
      "answer": "ごまのはい",
      "meaning": "thief posing as fellow traveller (traveler)"
    },
    {
      "question": "濡れ事",
      "answer": "ぬれごと",
      "meaning": "love affair, romance, love scene (in kabuki)"
    },
    {
      "question": "振り合い",
      "answer": "ふりあい",
      "meaning": "consideration, comparison, balancing, circumstances, condition"
    },
    {
      "question": "固有運動",
      "answer": "こゆううんどう",
      "meaning": "proper motion"
    },
    {
      "question": "仮出獄",
      "answer": "かりしゅつごく",
      "meaning": "parole, release on bail"
    },
    {
      "question": "地方風",
      "answer": "ちほうふう",
      "meaning": "local wind"
    },
    {
      "question": "枯れ葉剤",
      "answer": "かれはざい",
      "meaning": "defoliant"
    },
    {
      "question": "米西戦争",
      "answer": "べいせいせんそう",
      "meaning": "Spanish-American War"
    },
    {
      "question": "塗布剤",
      "answer": "とふざい",
      "meaning": "liniment, ointment, salve"
    },
    {
      "question": "湿性",
      "answer": "しっせい",
      "meaning": "wet (pleurisy)"
    },
    {
      "question": "小心翼翼",
      "answer": "しょうしんよくよく",
      "meaning": "very timid, very nervous, faint-hearted"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪盲",
      "answer": "せつもう",
      "meaning": "snow blindness"
    },
    {
      "question": "研削",
      "answer": "けんさく",
      "meaning": "grinding"
    },
    {
      "question": "複勝",
      "answer": "ふくしょう",
      "meaning": "placing bets"
    },
    {
      "question": "明くる年",
      "answer": "あくるとし",
      "meaning": "next year, following year"
    },
    {
      "question": "前轍",
      "answer": "ぜんてつ",
      "meaning": "wheel tracks left by vehicles that have passed before"
    },
    {
      "question": "珪藻",
      "answer": "けいそう",
      "meaning": "diatom"
    },
    {
      "question": "輸入超過",
      "answer": "ゆにゅうちょうか",
      "meaning": "excess of imports"
    },
    {
      "question": "嗾す",
      "answer": "そそのかす",
      "meaning": "to instigate, to tempt, to entice, to incite"
    },
    {
      "question": "同名異人",
      "answer": "どうめいいじん",
      "meaning": "namesake, person with the same name"
    },
    {
      "question": "私慾",
      "answer": "しよく",
      "meaning": "self-interest, selfish desire"
    },
    {
      "question": "劇烈",
      "answer": "げきれつ",
      "meaning": "violence, vehemence, fury, fervour, fervor, severity, fierceness, keenness"
    },
    {
      "question": "可搬性",
      "answer": "かはんせい",
      "meaning": "portability"
    },
    {
      "question": "屠畜場",
      "answer": "とちくじょう",
      "meaning": "abattoir, slaughterhouse"
    },
    {
      "question": "歌道",
      "answer": "かどう",
      "meaning": "versification, tanka poetry"
    },
    {
      "question": "出藍",
      "answer": "しゅつらん",
      "meaning": "pupil excelling his master"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭血腫",
      "answer": "とうけっしゅ,ずけっしゅ",
      "meaning": "cephalhematoma"
    },
    {
      "question": "馬軍",
      "answer": "うまいくさ",
      "meaning": "cavalry, cavalry battle"
    },
    {
      "question": "夏眠",
      "answer": "かみん",
      "meaning": "estivation"
    },
    {
      "question": "法律問題",
      "answer": "ほうりつもんだい",
      "meaning": "legal problem"
    },
    {
      "question": "ゴト師",
      "answer": "ゴトし",
      "meaning": "pachinko swindler, pachinko scammer"
    },
    {
      "question": "幣帛",
      "answer": "へいはく",
      "meaning": "offering of cloth (rope, paper, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "冶金学",
      "answer": "やきんがく",
      "meaning": "metallurgy (the science)"
    },
    {
      "question": "唐風",
      "answer": "とうふう,からふう",
      "meaning": "Chinese style"
    },
    {
      "question": "指事",
      "answer": "しじ",
      "meaning": "indicative (kanji whose shape is based on logical representation of an abstract idea)"
    },
    {
      "question": "役僧",
      "answer": "やくそう",
      "meaning": "priest in charge of a temple's clerical duties"
    },
    {
      "question": "種油",
      "answer": "たねあぶら",
      "meaning": "rapeseed oil, canola oil"
    },
    {
      "question": "法体",
      "answer": "ほったい,ほうたい",
      "meaning": "clerical appearance, appearance of a priest, teachings of Buddha, condition of the universe at creat"
    },
    {
      "question": "下図",
      "answer": "かず,したず",
      "meaning": "the figure below, the lower chart (diagram, illustration, etc.), rough sketch"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜間中学",
      "answer": "やかんちゅうがく",
      "meaning": "evening middle school"
    },
    {
      "question": "不正咬合",
      "answer": "ふせいこうごう",
      "meaning": "malocclusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "融氷",
      "answer": "ゆうひょう",
      "meaning": "melting ice"
    },
    {
      "question": "底堅い",
      "answer": "そこがたい",
      "meaning": "stable (market) after having bottomed out"
    },
    {
      "question": "聴者",
      "answer": "ちょうしゃ",
      "meaning": "listener, person with normal hearing (i.e. not deaf), hearing person"
    },
    {
      "question": "飢民",
      "answer": "きみん",
      "meaning": "starving people"
    },
    {
      "question": "納受",
      "answer": "のうじゅ",
      "meaning": "acceptance, reception"
    },
    {
      "question": "浴用",
      "answer": "よくよう",
      "meaning": "for bath use"
    },
    {
      "question": "町年寄",
      "answer": "まちどしより",
      "meaning": "town elder (Edo period), town leader, alderman"
    },
    {
      "question": "駁",
      "answer": "ぶち,ふち",
      "meaning": "spots, speckles, mottles"
    },
    {
      "question": "磁束",
      "answer": "じそく",
      "meaning": "magnetic flux"
    },
    {
      "question": "原色版",
      "answer": "げんしょくばん",
      "meaning": "tricolor printing, tricolour printing"
    },
    {
      "question": "按分",
      "answer": "あんぶん",
      "meaning": "proportional division, proportional distribution"
    },
    {
      "question": "祝い歌",
      "answer": "いわいうた",
      "meaning": "festive poem or song, congratulatory form (of waka)"
    },
    {
      "question": "献残屋",
      "answer": "けんざんや",
      "meaning": "person who sells left-over gifts received by the shogun or daimyo, etc. (Edo period)"
    },
    {
      "question": "砂糖楓",
      "answer": "さとうかえで",
      "meaning": "sugar maple (Acer saccharum), rock maple"
    },
    {
      "question": "心柄",
      "answer": "こころがら",
      "meaning": "state of mind"
    },
    {
      "question": "深長",
      "answer": "しんちょう",
      "meaning": "profound"
    },
    {
      "question": "純綿",
      "answer": "じゅんめん",
      "meaning": "pure cotton, all-cotton"
    },
    {
      "question": "四夷",
      "answer": "しい",
      "meaning": "Four Barbarians, derogative name for various ancient non-Chinese peoples bordering ancient China"
    },
    {
      "question": "卵塊",
      "answer": "らんかい",
      "meaning": "egg sack (frog, spider, etc.), egg mass"
    },
    {
      "question": "紫衣",
      "answer": "しえ,しい",
      "meaning": "purple vestment (traditionally awarded by the imperial household), high-ranking priest's purple robe"
    },
    {
      "question": "菊月",
      "answer": "きくづき",
      "meaning": "ninth month in the lunar calendar"
    },
    {
      "question": "諸派",
      "answer": "しょは",
      "meaning": "various parties or factions, minor parties"
    },
    {
      "question": "帰航",
      "answer": "きこう",
      "meaning": "homeward voyage or flight"
    },
    {
      "question": "除毛",
      "answer": "じょもう",
      "meaning": "(non-permanent) hair removal, depilation"
    },
    {
      "question": "小著",
      "answer": "しょうちょ",
      "meaning": "small book, my book"
    },
    {
      "question": "現勢",
      "answer": "げんせい",
      "meaning": "current state, present or actual strength"
    },
    {
      "question": "領土保全",
      "answer": "りょうどほぜん",
      "meaning": "maintenance of territorial integrity"
    },
    {
      "question": "来演",
      "answer": "らいえん",
      "meaning": "coming to perform"
    },
    {
      "question": "圧痕",
      "answer": "あっこん",
      "meaning": "impression, indentation"
    },
    {
      "question": "軟白",
      "answer": "なんぱく",
      "meaning": "blanching (cultivation method), whitening (of vegetables, etc.) by depriving of light"
    },
    {
      "question": "発光塗料",
      "answer": "はっこうとりょう",
      "meaning": "luminous paint"
    },
    {
      "question": "室内干し",
      "answer": "しつないぼし",
      "meaning": "indoor drying, hanging clothes to dry indoors"
    },
    {
      "question": "卸し金",
      "answer": "おろしがね",
      "meaning": "grater (esp. the variety used in Japanese cooking to grate foods very finely)"
    },
    {
      "question": "常座",
      "answer": "じょうざ",
      "meaning": "upstage right (on a noh stage)"
    },
    {
      "question": "屈斜路湖",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "五常",
      "answer": "ごじょう",
      "meaning": "the five cardinal Confucian virtues (justice, politeness, wisdom, fidelity and benevolence)"
    },
    {
      "question": "五言絶句",
      "answer": "ごごんぜっく",
      "meaning": "poem of four lines, each of five (Chinese) characters"
    },
    {
      "question": "早桶",
      "answer": "はやおけ",
      "meaning": "roughly made casket, quickly made casket"
    },
    {
      "question": "合目的",
      "answer": "ごうもくてき",
      "meaning": "purposive, appropriate"
    },
    {
      "question": "故無い",
      "answer": "ゆえない",
      "meaning": "without a reason"
    },
    {
      "question": "黄檗",
      "answer": "きはだ,きわだ,おうばく",
      "meaning": "Amur cork tree (Phellodendron amurense), Obaku school of Zen Buddhism"
    },
    {
      "question": "総ルビ",
      "answer": "そうルビ",
      "meaning": "having furigana on all kanji in a document"
    },
    {
      "question": "手根骨",
      "answer": "しゅこんこつ",
      "meaning": "carpal (any of the bones of the carpus in the wrist)"
    },
    {
      "question": "統制経済",
      "answer": "とうせいけいざい",
      "meaning": "controlled economy"
    },
    {
      "question": "盲動",
      "answer": "もうどう",
      "meaning": "rash act, reckless act"
    },
    {
      "question": "舞踊劇",
      "answer": "ぶようげき",
      "meaning": "dance drama"
    },
    {
      "question": "膣痙攣",
      "answer": "ちつけいれん",
      "meaning": "vaginismus, vaginal spasm"
    },
    {
      "question": "僻村",
      "answer": "へきそん",
      "meaning": "remote village"
    },
    {
      "question": "切窓",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "民力",
      "answer": "みんりょく",
      "meaning": "national manpower"
    },
    {
      "question": "上がり場",
      "answer": "あがりば",
      "meaning": "landing, landing place"
    },
    {
      "question": "入れ代り",
      "answer": "いれかわり",
      "meaning": "substitution, replacement, shifting, change"
    },
    {
      "question": "留め立て",
      "answer": "とめだて",
      "meaning": "restraining (someone), restraint"
    },
    {
      "question": "臭素",
      "answer": "しゅうそ",
      "meaning": "bromine (Br)"
    },
    {
      "question": "過電圧",
      "answer": "かでんあつ",
      "meaning": "overpotential, over-voltage"
    },
    {
      "question": "確然",
      "answer": "かくぜん",
      "meaning": "definite, positive"
    },
    {
      "question": "二次コン",
      "answer": "にじコン",
      "meaning": "two-dimensional complex, people more interested in two-dimensional (i.e. anime or manga) girls than"
    },
    {
      "question": "座右",
      "answer": "ざゆう,ざう",
      "meaning": "(by) one's side, nearby location, place close to one's person, area by one's hand, you"
    },
    {
      "question": "三宝",
      "answer": "さんぼう,さんぽう",
      "meaning": "the Three Jewels, the Triple Gem, Triratna, the Three Treasures, Buddha, Dharma, Sangha, Buddha, the"
    },
    {
      "question": "墾田",
      "answer": "こんでん",
      "meaning": "new rice field"
    },
    {
      "question": "強風域",
      "answer": "きょうふういき",
      "meaning": "strong wind area (15mps or more), strong wind zone"
    },
    {
      "question": "立ち腐れ",
      "answer": "たちぐされ",
      "meaning": "dilapidation"
    },
    {
      "question": "鼻高",
      "answer": "はなたか",
      "meaning": "high nose, person with a high nose, pride"
    },
    {
      "question": "告辞",
      "answer": "こくじ",
      "meaning": "farewell address"
    },
    {
      "question": "尊命",
      "answer": "そんめい",
      "meaning": "your order"
    },
    {
      "question": "鯣烏賊",
      "answer": "するめいか",
      "meaning": "Japanese common squid, Pacific flying squid (Todarodes pacificus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "尻上り",
      "answer": "しりあがり",
      "meaning": "rising intonation, upward inflection, rising (sales, tendency, etc.), getting better, improvement, f"
    },
    {
      "question": "渋抜き",
      "answer": "しぶぬき",
      "meaning": "removing the astringent taste (from persimmons)"
    },
    {
      "question": "苔類",
      "answer": "こけるい,たいるい",
      "meaning": "bryophyte (any of three groups of non-vascular land plants, incl. mosses, hornworts and liverworts),"
    },
    {
      "question": "私論",
      "answer": "しろん",
      "meaning": "one's personal opinion or views"
    },
    {
      "question": "怫然",
      "answer": "ふつぜん",
      "meaning": "indignant, wrathful"
    },
    {
      "question": "復辟",
      "answer": "ふくへき",
      "meaning": "restoration (of an abdicated ruler)"
    },
    {
      "question": "売出し",
      "answer": "うりだし",
      "meaning": "(bargain) sale"
    },
    {
      "question": "二つ割り",
      "answer": "ふたつわり",
      "meaning": "half, cutting in two"
    },
    {
      "question": "退座",
      "answer": "たいざ",
      "meaning": "leaving one's seat"
    },
    {
      "question": "臆断",
      "answer": "おくだん",
      "meaning": "jumping to hasty conclusions, conjecture"
    },
    {
      "question": "迷子石",
      "answer": "まいごいし",
      "meaning": "glacial erratic, erratic boulder"
    },
    {
      "question": "芸域",
      "answer": "げいいき",
      "meaning": "range of skills"
    },
    {
      "question": "傾慕",
      "answer": "けいぼ",
      "meaning": "yearning, wholehearted long, deep adoration"
    },
    {
      "question": "膵炎",
      "answer": "すいえん",
      "meaning": "pancreatitis"
    },
    {
      "question": "兜率",
      "answer": "とそつ",
      "meaning": "Tusita (heaven, pure land)"
    },
    {
      "question": "見出し語",
      "answer": "みだしご",
      "meaning": "headword (in a dictionary), entry word"
    },
    {
      "question": "属地",
      "answer": "ぞくち",
      "meaning": "territorial"
    },
    {
      "question": "鯖節",
      "answer": "さばぶし",
      "meaning": "dried, smoked mackerel, shavings from dried, smoked mackerel"
    },
    {
      "question": "聖楽",
      "answer": "せいがく",
      "meaning": "church music, sacred music"
    },
    {
      "question": "檐",
      "answer": "のき",
      "meaning": "eaves, narrow aisle surrounding the core of a temple building"
    },
    {
      "question": "野茨",
      "answer": "のいばら",
      "meaning": "multiflora rose (Rosa multiflora), baby rose, Japanese rose"
    },
    {
      "question": "中細",
      "answer": "ちゅうぼそ,なかぼそ",
      "meaning": "medium-fine (thickness of string, noodles, pencil lead, etc.), medium pointed (e.g. pen), being narr"
    },
    {
      "question": "国禁",
      "answer": "こっきん",
      "meaning": "state prohibition"
    },
    {
      "question": "語り尽す",
      "answer": "かたりつくす",
      "meaning": "to say everything one wants to say, to exhaust a topic"
    },
    {
      "question": "心像",
      "answer": "しんぞう",
      "meaning": "mental image"
    },
    {
      "question": "奄美諸島",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "租庸調",
      "answer": "そようちょう",
      "meaning": "corvee, taxes in kind or service (ritsuryo system)"
    },
    {
      "question": "狐拳",
      "answer": "きつねけん",
      "meaning": "game similar to rock, paper, scissors, with the hand gestures fox, hunter and village headman"
    },
    {
      "question": "麦打ち",
      "answer": "むぎうち",
      "meaning": "wheat threshing"
    },
    {
      "question": "府下",
      "answer": "ふか",
      "meaning": "suburban districts (of a metropolis), within an urban-prefecture"
    },
    {
      "question": "暈し",
      "answer": "ぼかし",
      "meaning": "shading off, gradation, bokashi composting, fermented composting"
    },
    {
      "question": "御召し",
      "answer": "おめし",
      "meaning": "summoning, calling, riding, wearing, dressing, clothing, (high-quality) silk crepe (fabric)"
    },
    {
      "question": "一六勝負",
      "answer": "いちろくしょうぶ",
      "meaning": "gambling, speculation"
    },
    {
      "question": "壁間",
      "answer": "へきかん",
      "meaning": "portion of wall between two pillars, surface of a wall"
    },
    {
      "question": "夏時",
      "answer": "かじ,なつどき",
      "meaning": "summertime"
    },
    {
      "question": "斧鉞",
      "answer": "ふえつ",
      "meaning": "axe"
    },
    {
      "question": "糖衣錠",
      "answer": "とういじょう",
      "meaning": "sugar-coated pill"
    },
    {
      "question": "元朝",
      "answer": "がんちょう,げんちょう",
      "meaning": "New Year's morning, Yuan dynasty (China, 1271-1368), Yüan dynasty, Mongol dynasty"
    },
    {
      "question": "特撰",
      "answer": "とくせん",
      "meaning": "special selection, special approval, special prize, highest honours"
    },
    {
      "question": "髪冠",
      "answer": "かみかんむり",
      "meaning": "kanji 'hair' radical at top"
    },
    {
      "question": "蒸し鍋",
      "answer": "むしなべ",
      "meaning": "steamer, casserole dish"
    },
    {
      "question": "野馬",
      "answer": "のうま",
      "meaning": "wild horse"
    },
    {
      "question": "コプト語",
      "answer": "コプトご",
      "meaning": "Coptic (language)"
    },
    {
      "question": "塗り立て",
      "answer": "ぬりたて",
      "meaning": "freshly painted"
    },
    {
      "question": "蜜源植物",
      "answer": "みつげんしょくぶつ",
      "meaning": "bee plant, honey plant"
    },
    {
      "question": "日天子",
      "answer": "にってんし",
      "meaning": "Surya (Hindu sun god also revered as one of the twelve devas in Shingon Buddhism), sun"
    },
    {
      "question": "浜焼き",
      "answer": "はまやき",
      "meaning": "freshly caught seafood broiled at a beach"
    },
    {
      "question": "心に適う",
      "answer": "こころにかなう",
      "meaning": "to be pleased with, to be to one's liking"
    },
    {
      "question": "屎尿",
      "answer": "しにょう",
      "meaning": "excreta, raw sewage, human waste, night soil"
    },
    {
      "question": "心添え",
      "answer": "こころぞえ",
      "meaning": "advice, suggestion"
    },
    {
      "question": "城楼",
      "answer": "じょうろう",
      "meaning": "watchtower of a castle"
    },
    {
      "question": "牴触",
      "answer": "ていしょく",
      "meaning": "infringement (of a law, treaty, etc.), contravention, running afoul, conflict (with a theory, claim,"
    },
    {
      "question": "遣い込む",
      "answer": "つかいこむ",
      "meaning": "to embezzle, to misappropriate, to peculate, to accustom oneself to using, to use for a long time"
    },
    {
      "question": "位官",
      "answer": "いかん",
      "meaning": "rank and official position"
    },
    {
      "question": "十年一昔",
      "answer": "じゅうねんひとむかし",
      "meaning": "the pace of change makes ten years back seem like ancient history"
    },
    {
      "question": "虎刈り",
      "answer": "とらがり",
      "meaning": "unevenly cropped (hair), badly cropped"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜逃げ屋",
      "answer": "よにげや",
      "meaning": "fly-by-night arranger, person who helps others flee creditors"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤魚鯛",
      "answer": "あこうだい",
      "meaning": "Matsubara's red rockfish (Sebastes matsubarae), red rockfish, red scorpionfish"
    },
    {
      "question": "一時逃れ",
      "answer": "いちじのがれ,いっときのがれ",
      "meaning": "quibbling, temporizing, temporising"
    },
    {
      "question": "無価",
      "answer": "むか",
      "meaning": "priceless"
    },
    {
      "question": "銃丸",
      "answer": "じゅうがん",
      "meaning": "bullet"
    },
    {
      "question": "嫌煙権",
      "answer": "けんえんけん",
      "meaning": "non-smokers' rights, right for nonsmokers to not be exposed to smoking in public space"
    },
    {
      "question": "出札",
      "answer": "しゅっさつ",
      "meaning": "issuing tickets"
    },
    {
      "question": "杉箸",
      "answer": "すぎばし",
      "meaning": "chopsticks made of cedar"
    },
    {
      "question": "薨御",
      "answer": "こうぎょ",
      "meaning": "death of important person (e.g. prince, princess, cabinet minister)"
    },
    {
      "question": "四姓",
      "answer": "しせい",
      "meaning": "the four great families of the age (esp. the Minamoto clan, the Taira clan, the Fujiwara clan and th"
    },
    {
      "question": "世離れる",
      "answer": "よばなれる",
      "meaning": "to become unworldly, to stop keeping up with social norms, to be out of touch with reality"
    },
    {
      "question": "田舎めく",
      "answer": "いなかめく",
      "meaning": "to appear rustic, to become countrified"
    },
    {
      "question": "提子",
      "answer": "ひさげ",
      "meaning": "ceremonial sake decanter with a spout and semicircular handle"
    },
    {
      "question": "染め模様",
      "answer": "そめもよう",
      "meaning": "dyed pattern"
    },
    {
      "question": "編針",
      "answer": "あみばり",
      "meaning": "knitting needle"
    },
    {
      "question": "御金",
      "answer": "おかね",
      "meaning": "money"
    },
    {
      "question": "安定多数",
      "answer": "あんていたすう",
      "meaning": "stable majority"
    },
    {
      "question": "驕児",
      "answer": "きょうじ",
      "meaning": "spoiled child, spoilt child"
    },
    {
      "question": "天恩",
      "answer": "てんおん",
      "meaning": "blessings of heaven, favour of emperor, favor of emperor, divination's luckiest day, blessings of na"
    },
    {
      "question": "家譜",
      "answer": "かふ",
      "meaning": "pedigree, genealogy"
    },
    {
      "question": "一斑",
      "answer": "いっぱん",
      "meaning": "spot (glimpse, outline), sighting"
    },
    {
      "question": "押手",
      "answer": "おして,おしで",
      "meaning": "seal, stamp, depressing the string of a zither with one's left hand, (in archery) left hand, obstina"
    },
    {
      "question": "折畳み",
      "answer": "おりたたみ",
      "meaning": "folding, collapsible, telescopic"
    },
    {
      "question": "長鳴き",
      "answer": "ながなき",
      "meaning": "long crowing (warbling)"
    },
    {
      "question": "臨時国会",
      "answer": "りんじこっかい",
      "meaning": "extraordinary Diet session, extraordinary session of the Diet, session of the Diet convoked by the C"
    },
    {
      "question": "撮り鉄",
      "answer": "とりてつ",
      "meaning": "railway enthusiast who enjoys taking pictures of trains"
    },
    {
      "question": "難義",
      "answer": "なんぎ",
      "meaning": "abstruseness, abstruse word"
    },
    {
      "question": "旺ん",
      "answer": "さかん",
      "meaning": "prosperous, flourishing, thriving, successful, popular, widespread, active, lively, energetic, vigor"
    },
    {
      "question": "芸道",
      "answer": "げいどう",
      "meaning": "performing arts, accomplishment (in performing arts)"
    },
    {
      "question": "絵草紙屋",
      "answer": "えぞうしや",
      "meaning": "shop selling picture books, wood prints, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "自主権",
      "answer": "じしゅけん",
      "meaning": "autonomy"
    },
    {
      "question": "出場所",
      "answer": "でばしょ",
      "meaning": "one's time (e.g. to go on stage), one's turn, source, origin, place of production"
    },
    {
      "question": "蝨",
      "answer": "しらみ",
      "meaning": "louse (esp. a sucking louse), lice"
    },
    {
      "question": "急啓",
      "answer": "きゅうけい",
      "meaning": "Dear Sir or Madam"
    },
    {
      "question": "春寒",
      "answer": "しゅんかん",
      "meaning": "cold weather in early spring"
    },
    {
      "question": "輪タク",
      "answer": "りんタク",
      "meaning": "trishaw, pedicab"
    },
    {
      "question": "正覚",
      "answer": "しょうがく",
      "meaning": "perfect enlightenment"
    },
    {
      "question": "扠",
      "answer": "さて",
      "meaning": "well, now, then"
    },
    {
      "question": "綴じ糸",
      "answer": "とじいと",
      "meaning": "binding thread, basting thread"
    },
    {
      "question": "市部",
      "answer": "しぶ",
      "meaning": "urban areas"
    },
    {
      "question": "渡り初め",
      "answer": "わたりぞめ",
      "meaning": "bridge-opening ceremony, first crossing of a bridge"
    },
    {
      "question": "川開き",
      "answer": "かわびらき",
      "meaning": "festival marking the start of boating season"
    },
    {
      "question": "溝渠",
      "answer": "こうきょ",
      "meaning": "ditch, sewer, canal"
    },
    {
      "question": "御目見",
      "answer": "おめみえ",
      "meaning": "(the privilege to have) an audience (with one's lord, a dignitary, etc.), interview (with one's supe"
    },
    {
      "question": "義太夫節",
      "answer": "ぎだゆうぶし",
      "meaning": "gidayū ballad drama (narrative accompanied by a shamisen used in the bunraku puppet theater)"
    },
    {
      "question": "衣装道楽",
      "answer": "いしょうどうらく",
      "meaning": "love of fine clothing, weakness for fine clothes, being extravagant in clothing"
    },
    {
      "question": "空っ穴",
      "answer": "からっけつ",
      "meaning": "flat broke, stone broke, penniless"
    },
    {
      "question": "遍照",
      "answer": "へんじょう,へんしょう",
      "meaning": "universal illumination (esp. in Buddhism, by the dharma-body)"
    },
    {
      "question": "陽極",
      "answer": "ようきょく",
      "meaning": "anode, plus terminal, positive pole"
    },
    {
      "question": "鶏鳴",
      "answer": "けいめい",
      "meaning": "crowing of a cock, crowing of a rooster, cockcrow, dawn, daybreak, hour of the Ox (around 2am)"
    },
    {
      "question": "民事事件",
      "answer": "みんじじけん",
      "meaning": "civil case"
    },
    {
      "question": "跡付ける",
      "answer": "あとづける",
      "meaning": "to trace, to inquire into"
    },
    {
      "question": "衝立障子",
      "answer": "ついたてそうじ,ついたてしょうじ",
      "meaning": "partitioning screen"
    },
    {
      "question": "近国",
      "answer": "きんごく",
      "meaning": "neighboring country, neighbouring country, provinces close to Kyoto (under ritsuryo system)"
    },
    {
      "question": "偏流",
      "answer": "へんりゅう",
      "meaning": "drift"
    },
    {
      "question": "汗止め",
      "answer": "あせどめ",
      "meaning": "an antisudorific (agent or material)"
    },
    {
      "question": "肘枕",
      "answer": "ひじまくら",
      "meaning": "using one's elbows as a pillow"
    },
    {
      "question": "非望",
      "answer": "ひぼう",
      "meaning": "inordinate ambition"
    },
    {
      "question": "歓喜天",
      "answer": "かんぎてん",
      "meaning": "Nandikesvara (Ganesh in the Buddhist pantheon)"
    },
    {
      "question": "受信人",
      "answer": "じゅしんにん",
      "meaning": "addressee"
    },
    {
      "question": "一刀彫り",
      "answer": "いっとうぼり",
      "meaning": "one-knife carving"
    },
    {
      "question": "従軍記章",
      "answer": "じゅうぐんきしょう",
      "meaning": "service medal, war medal"
    },
    {
      "question": "気変わり",
      "answer": "きがわり",
      "meaning": "changing one's mind"
    },
    {
      "question": "樹蔭",
      "answer": "こかげ,じゅいん",
      "meaning": "shade of tree, bower"
    },
    {
      "question": "悔やみ状",
      "answer": "くやみじょう",
      "meaning": "letter of condolence, condolence message"
    },
    {
      "question": "心理主義",
      "answer": "しんりしゅぎ",
      "meaning": "psychologism"
    },
    {
      "question": "犬追物",
      "answer": "いぬおうもの",
      "meaning": "dog-hunting event of Kamakura period"
    },
    {
      "question": "自然権",
      "answer": "しぜんけん",
      "meaning": "natural right, right under natural law"
    },
    {
      "question": "不乾性油",
      "answer": "ふかんせいゆ",
      "meaning": "non-drying oil"
    },
    {
      "question": "校正刷",
      "answer": "こうせいずり",
      "meaning": "galley proofs, proof sheet, printer's proof"
    },
    {
      "question": "草魚",
      "answer": "そうぎょ",
      "meaning": "grass carp (Ctenopharyngodon idellus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "莞",
      "answer": "ふとい",
      "meaning": "softstem bulrush (Scirpus tabernaemontani)"
    },
    {
      "question": "木深い",
      "answer": "こぶかい",
      "meaning": "deep in the woods"
    },
    {
      "question": "縮緬雑魚",
      "answer": "ちりめんじゃこ,ちりめんざこ",
      "meaning": "dried young sardines"
    },
    {
      "question": "北海道犬",
      "answer": "ほっかいどうけん,ほっかいどういぬ",
      "meaning": "Hokkaido dog, dog breed native to Hokkaido"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤脚",
      "answer": "せっきゃく,しゃっきゃく",
      "meaning": "bare feet"
    },
    {
      "question": "納得尽く",
      "answer": "なっとくずく",
      "meaning": "having consent (e.g. to do something), having (someone's) assent"
    },
    {
      "question": "奉安",
      "answer": "ほうあん",
      "meaning": "enshrining"
    },
    {
      "question": "大政",
      "answer": "たいせい",
      "meaning": "sovereign power, the reins of government"
    },
    {
      "question": "鯰髭",
      "answer": "なまずひげ",
      "meaning": "drooping moustache"
    },
    {
      "question": "請じる",
      "answer": "しょうじる",
      "meaning": "to invite, to show (someone) in"
    },
    {
      "question": "傘寿",
      "answer": "さんじゅ",
      "meaning": "80th birthday"
    },
    {
      "question": "取次店",
      "answer": "とりつぎてん",
      "meaning": "agency, distributor"
    },
    {
      "question": "炭殻",
      "answer": "たんがら",
      "meaning": "(coal) cinders"
    },
    {
      "question": "筑波嶺",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "輻湊",
      "answer": "ふくそう",
      "meaning": "congestion (e.g. traffic), overcrowding, convergence (esp. optical)"
    },
    {
      "question": "雌雄異株",
      "answer": "しゆういしゅ",
      "meaning": "dioecy, dioecism"
    },
    {
      "question": "啓蒙思想",
      "answer": "けいもうしそう",
      "meaning": "the philosophy of the European Enlightenment"
    },
    {
      "question": "相対主義",
      "answer": "そうたいしゅぎ",
      "meaning": "relativism"
    },
    {
      "question": "蚊蜻蛉",
      "answer": "かとんぼ",
      "meaning": "crane fly, daddy longlegs (insect of family Tipulidae), a tall, gangly person, string bean"
    },
    {
      "question": "コール天",
      "answer": "コールてん",
      "meaning": "corduroy, corded velveteen"
    },
    {
      "question": "悲しい哉",
      "answer": "かなしいかな",
      "meaning": "sad to say, how sad, alas"
    },
    {
      "question": "吃水線",
      "answer": "きっすいせん",
      "meaning": "waterline (ship)"
    },
    {
      "question": "日割",
      "answer": "ひわり",
      "meaning": "daily rate, (day-by-day) schedule, program"
    },
    {
      "question": "仏印進駐",
      "answer": "ふついんしんちゅう",
      "meaning": "Japanese invasion of French Indochina (1940)"
    },
    {
      "question": "借り家",
      "answer": "かりや,かりいえ",
      "meaning": "house for rent, rented house, renting a house"
    },
    {
      "question": "専決",
      "answer": "せんけつ",
      "meaning": "deciding or acting on one's own"
    },
    {
      "question": "門脈",
      "answer": "もんみゃく",
      "meaning": "portal vein"
    },
    {
      "question": "装飾花",
      "answer": "そうしょくか",
      "meaning": "ornamental flower, decorative sterile floret (of a composite flower)"
    },
    {
      "question": "献辞",
      "answer": "けんじ",
      "meaning": "dedication"
    },
    {
      "question": "群れ立つ",
      "answer": "むれだつ,むれたつ",
      "meaning": "to stand all around (e.g. bamboo, pines, pampas grass)"
    },
    {
      "question": "商利",
      "answer": "しょうり",
      "meaning": "commercial profit"
    },
    {
      "question": "永楽銭",
      "answer": "えいらくせん",
      "meaning": "Chinese coinage produced during the reign of the Yongle Emperor (used in Japan from the Muromachi pe"
    },
    {
      "question": "鰮",
      "answer": "いわし",
      "meaning": "pilchard (esp. Japanese pilchard, Sardinops melanostictus), sardine"
    },
    {
      "question": "混用",
      "answer": "こんよう",
      "meaning": "using together, mixing (usage)"
    },
    {
      "question": "洪水神話",
      "answer": "こうずいしんわ",
      "meaning": "flood myth"
    },
    {
      "question": "豊沃",
      "answer": "ほうよく",
      "meaning": "fertility"
    },
    {
      "question": "深編み笠",
      "answer": "ふかあみがさ",
      "meaning": "type of conical hat that covers the whole head (used by Komuso monks)"
    },
    {
      "question": "捕縄",
      "answer": "とりなわ,ほじょう",
      "meaning": "policeman's rope (used for restraining criminals)"
    },
    {
      "question": "春蘭",
      "answer": "しゅんらん",
      "meaning": "noble orchid (Cymbidium goeringii)"
    },
    {
      "question": "凄技",
      "answer": "すごわざ",
      "meaning": "amazing trick, amazing skill"
    },
    {
      "question": "寛文",
      "answer": "かんぶん",
      "meaning": "Kanbun era (1661.4.25-1673.9.21)"
    },
    {
      "question": "萌動",
      "answer": "ほうどう",
      "meaning": "sprouting, budding"
    },
    {
      "question": "未定稿",
      "answer": "みていこう",
      "meaning": "unfinished manuscript"
    },
    {
      "question": "抜山蓋世",
      "answer": "ばつざんがいせい",
      "meaning": "great strength and energy (of a mighty hero), Herculean strength and vitality"
    },
    {
      "question": "等脚台形",
      "answer": "とうきゃくだいけい",
      "meaning": "isosceles trapezoid, isosceles trapezium"
    },
    {
      "question": "長途",
      "answer": "ちょうと",
      "meaning": "long way"
    },
    {
      "question": "双胴船",
      "answer": "そうどうせん",
      "meaning": "double-hull boat, catamaran"
    },
    {
      "question": "袖山",
      "answer": "そでやま",
      "meaning": "top crease of a sleeve (of traditional Japanese clothing), sleeve cap (of Western clothing)"
    },
    {
      "question": "撚り糸",
      "answer": "よりいと",
      "meaning": "twisting (thread, etc.), twisted yarn, twisted thread, twine"
    },
    {
      "question": "嫩葉",
      "answer": "わかば,どんよう",
      "meaning": "new leaves, young leaves, fresh verdure"
    },
    {
      "question": "含み置く",
      "answer": "ふくみおく",
      "meaning": "to understand, to keep in mind"
    },
    {
      "question": "適期",
      "answer": "てっき,てきき",
      "meaning": "proper time (e.g. for harvesting rice), appropriate time, right time"
    },
    {
      "question": "戸車",
      "answer": "とぐるま",
      "meaning": "sash roller, door roller, roller for a sliding door"
    },
    {
      "question": "右傾",
      "answer": "うけい",
      "meaning": "leaning to the right, turning rightist, being on the (political) right"
    },
    {
      "question": "太鼓持",
      "answer": "たいこもち",
      "meaning": "professional jester, professional entertainer, comedian, buffoon, flatterer, sycophant, brown-noser"
    },
    {
      "question": "療養病床",
      "answer": "りょうようびょうしょう",
      "meaning": "long term care bed, long term care beds, chronic stage bed, chronic stage beds"
    },
    {
      "question": "御産",
      "answer": "おさん",
      "meaning": "(giving) birth, childbirth, delivery, confinement"
    },
    {
      "question": "液肥",
      "answer": "えきひ",
      "meaning": "liquid fertilizer, liquid fertiliser"
    },
    {
      "question": "託かる",
      "answer": "ことづかる",
      "meaning": "to be entrusted with, to be asked to"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒身",
      "answer": "くろみ",
      "meaning": "meat of a fish (e.g. tuna) that is dark red with blood, usu. coming from the parts close to the spin"
    },
    {
      "question": "倒懸",
      "answer": "とうけん",
      "meaning": "hanging (someone) upside down"
    },
    {
      "question": "府道",
      "answer": "ふどう",
      "meaning": "prefectural road"
    },
    {
      "question": "綴じ目",
      "answer": "とじめ",
      "meaning": "seam"
    },
    {
      "question": "外交家",
      "answer": "がいこうか",
      "meaning": "diplomat, diplomatic person"
    },
    {
      "question": "梯形",
      "answer": "ていけい",
      "meaning": "trapezoid, trapezium"
    },
    {
      "question": "葭",
      "answer": "あし,よし",
      "meaning": "common reed (Phragmites australis)"
    },
    {
      "question": "オレっ娘",
      "answer": "オレっこ",
      "meaning": "young woman who uses the first person pronoun 'ore'"
    },
    {
      "question": "書き入れ",
      "answer": "かきいれ",
      "meaning": "entry, (marginal) notes"
    },
    {
      "question": "叮嚀",
      "answer": "ていねい",
      "meaning": "polite, courteous, civil, careful, close, thorough, conscientious"
    },
    {
      "question": "神社神道",
      "answer": "じんじゃしんとう",
      "meaning": "Shrine Shintō, form of Shintō that focuses on worship in shrines, in contrast to folk and sectarian"
    },
    {
      "question": "猛勉",
      "answer": "もうべん",
      "meaning": "studying hard, cramming"
    },
    {
      "question": "接続水域",
      "answer": "せつぞくすいいき",
      "meaning": "contiguous zone"
    },
    {
      "question": "芳烈",
      "answer": "ほうれつ",
      "meaning": "aromatic, heroic deed, outstanding achievement"
    },
    {
      "question": "渓水",
      "answer": "けいすい",
      "meaning": "mountain stream, the water of a mountain stream"
    },
    {
      "question": "点光源",
      "answer": "てんこうげん",
      "meaning": "positional light source"
    },
    {
      "question": "分掌",
      "answer": "ぶんしょう",
      "meaning": "division of duties"
    },
    {
      "question": "宿曜道",
      "answer": "すくようどう",
      "meaning": "form of astrology based on the Xiuyaojing (brought to Japan in the Heian period)"
    },
    {
      "question": "集魚灯",
      "answer": "しゅうぎょとう",
      "meaning": "fish-luring lights"
    },
    {
      "question": "風鳥座",
      "answer": "ふうちょうざ",
      "meaning": "Apus (constellation), the Bird-of-Paradise"
    },
    {
      "question": "小豆飯",
      "answer": "あずきめし",
      "meaning": "rice boiled with adzuki beans"
    },
    {
      "question": "垢擦り",
      "answer": "あかすり",
      "meaning": "scrubbing, getting grime off"
    },
    {
      "question": "准看護婦",
      "answer": "じゅんかんごふ",
      "meaning": "practical nurse"
    },
    {
      "question": "乾果",
      "answer": "かんか",
      "meaning": "dry fruit (e.g. nuts, legumes, follicles), dried fruit"
    },
    {
      "question": "百錬",
      "answer": "ひゃくれん",
      "meaning": "well-tempered, well drilled, well trained"
    },
    {
      "question": "根石",
      "answer": "ねいし",
      "meaning": "base-stone, plinth stone, stone that serves as a pedestal for a pillar"
    },
    {
      "question": "句法",
      "answer": "くほう",
      "meaning": "conventions to be followed in composing Japanese poetry, phraseology, diction, rules of grammar and"
    },
    {
      "question": "金座",
      "answer": "きんざ",
      "meaning": "Edo-period gold mint"
    },
    {
      "question": "塩辛声",
      "answer": "しおからごえ",
      "meaning": "hoarse voice"
    },
    {
      "question": "折り鞄",
      "answer": "おりかばん",
      "meaning": "briefcase, portfolio"
    },
    {
      "question": "荼枳尼",
      "answer": "だきに",
      "meaning": "Dakini (fairy-goddess)"
    },
    {
      "question": "留木",
      "answer": "とめぎ",
      "meaning": "fragrant wood, wooden peg, toggle"
    },
    {
      "question": "言い送る",
      "answer": "いいおくる",
      "meaning": "to send a message, to write to"
    },
    {
      "question": "口授",
      "answer": "くうじゅ,こうじゅ,くじゅ",
      "meaning": "oral instruction or teaching or method"
    },
    {
      "question": "往信",
      "answer": "おうしん",
      "meaning": "first half of a reply card"
    },
    {
      "question": "一顰一笑",
      "answer": "いっぴんいっしょう,いちびんいっしょう",
      "meaning": "one's mood, one's caprice, a smile or a frown"
    },
    {
      "question": "減員",
      "answer": "げんいん",
      "meaning": "reduction of staff"
    },
    {
      "question": "補欠選手",
      "answer": "ほけつせんしゅ",
      "meaning": "spare player, substitute, sub, benchwarmer"
    },
    {
      "question": "拓殖",
      "answer": "たくしょく",
      "meaning": "colonization, colonisation, development, settlement, exploitation"
    },
    {
      "question": "四生",
      "answer": "ししょう",
      "meaning": "the four ways of birth (from a womb, an egg, moisture or spontaneously), catur-yoni"
    },
    {
      "question": "亜麻糸",
      "answer": "あまいと",
      "meaning": "flax yarn"
    },
    {
      "question": "雅致",
      "answer": "がち",
      "meaning": "artistry, good taste, elegance, grace"
    },
    {
      "question": "帛紗",
      "answer": "ふくさ",
      "meaning": "small silk wrapper, small cloth for wiping tea utensils, crepe wrapper"
    },
    {
      "question": "脱肛",
      "answer": "だっこう",
      "meaning": "anal prolapse"
    },
    {
      "question": "下血",
      "answer": "げけつ",
      "meaning": "bloody bowel discharge"
    },
    {
      "question": "遅鈍",
      "answer": "ちどん",
      "meaning": "dullness, stupidity"
    },
    {
      "question": "種々相",
      "answer": "しゅじゅそう",
      "meaning": "various phases"
    },
    {
      "question": "有り合せ",
      "answer": "ありあわせ",
      "meaning": "on hand, readily available"
    },
    {
      "question": "混ぜ御飯",
      "answer": "まぜごはん",
      "meaning": "cooked rice with added ingredients (meat, vegetables, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "敷き革",
      "answer": "しきがわ",
      "meaning": "fur rug, fur cushion, insole, inner sole"
    },
    {
      "question": "饗す",
      "answer": "きょうす",
      "meaning": "to treat, to feast, to provide dinner for"
    },
    {
      "question": "酒興",
      "answer": "しゅきょう",
      "meaning": "merrymaking"
    },
    {
      "question": "収入印紙",
      "answer": "しゅうにゅういんし",
      "meaning": "revenue stamp"
    },
    {
      "question": "閉鎖音",
      "answer": "へいさおん",
      "meaning": "stop, stop consonant, occlusive"
    },
    {
      "question": "鎧窓",
      "answer": "よろいまど",
      "meaning": "louvered window"
    },
    {
      "question": "暗語",
      "answer": "あんご",
      "meaning": "secret language, code word, argot"
    },
    {
      "question": "回転窓",
      "answer": "かいてんまど",
      "meaning": "pivoted window"
    },
    {
      "question": "君主国",
      "answer": "くんしゅこく",
      "meaning": "monarchy"
    },
    {
      "question": "繭紬",
      "answer": "けんちゅう",
      "meaning": "pongee (unbleached silk)"
    },
    {
      "question": "主調",
      "answer": "しゅちょう",
      "meaning": "keynote, predominant element, main point"
    },
    {
      "question": "遷座",
      "answer": "せんざ",
      "meaning": "relocation of a shrine, transfer of an object of worship"
    },
    {
      "question": "野猪",
      "answer": "やちょ",
      "meaning": "wild boar"
    },
    {
      "question": "具す",
      "answer": "ぐす",
      "meaning": "to accompany, to follow, to assemble (necessary items), to prepare"
    },
    {
      "question": "繁劇",
      "answer": "はんげき",
      "meaning": "extreme busyness"
    },
    {
      "question": "帰宅難民",
      "answer": "きたくなんみん",
      "meaning": "person stranded due to mass transit disruptions after an earthquake, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "脱原発",
      "answer": "だつげんぱつ",
      "meaning": "abandoning nuclear power generation"
    },
    {
      "question": "謙徳公",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "敏活",
      "answer": "びんかつ",
      "meaning": "quickness, alacrity"
    },
    {
      "question": "建増し",
      "answer": "たてまし",
      "meaning": "building addition or extension, an annex"
    },
    {
      "question": "縹",
      "answer": "はなだ",
      "meaning": "light indigo"
    },
    {
      "question": "一幕物",
      "answer": "ひとまくもの",
      "meaning": "(a) one-act play"
    },
    {
      "question": "一揃",
      "answer": "ピンぞろ",
      "meaning": "snake eyes (dice), double ones"
    },
    {
      "question": "一斤染め",
      "answer": "いっこんぞめ,いっきんぞめ",
      "meaning": "light pink, pale pink"
    },
    {
      "question": "細粒",
      "answer": "さいりゅう",
      "meaning": "fine grain, fine granule, microsphere"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り持ち",
      "answer": "とりもち",
      "meaning": "mediation, intermediation, procuration, go-between, facilitating a rendezvous between lovers, entert"
    },
    {
      "question": "心霊術",
      "answer": "しんれいじゅつ",
      "meaning": "spiritualism, spiritualistic ability, ability to cause psychic phenomena"
    },
    {
      "question": "書証",
      "answer": "しょしょう",
      "meaning": "documentary evidence"
    },
    {
      "question": "綾絹",
      "answer": "あやぎぬ",
      "meaning": "twilled silk fabric"
    },
    {
      "question": "上刻",
      "answer": "じょうこく",
      "meaning": "first third of a two-hour period"
    },
    {
      "question": "尽忠",
      "answer": "じんちゅう",
      "meaning": "loyalty"
    },
    {
      "question": "天目山",
      "answer": "てんもくざん",
      "meaning": "line between victory and defeat"
    },
    {
      "question": "更更",
      "answer": "さらさら",
      "meaning": "(not) at all, (not) in the least, (none) whatsoever"
    },
    {
      "question": "一言一行",
      "answer": "いちげんいっこう",
      "meaning": "every word and act, just a word or an act"
    },
    {
      "question": "犀角",
      "answer": "さいかく",
      "meaning": "rhinoceros horn"
    },
    {
      "question": "鑽る",
      "answer": "きる",
      "meaning": "to start a fire (with wood-wood friction or by striking metal against stone)"
    },
    {
      "question": "つるっ禿",
      "answer": "つるっぱげ",
      "meaning": "shiny, bald head, person with a shiny, bald head"
    },
    {
      "question": "舌苔",
      "answer": "ぜったい",
      "meaning": "fur (on one's tongue)"
    },
    {
      "question": "自記",
      "answer": "じき",
      "meaning": "writing oneself, self-recording"
    },
    {
      "question": "善女",
      "answer": "ぜんにょ",
      "meaning": "pious woman"
    },
    {
      "question": "配本",
      "answer": "はいほん",
      "meaning": "distribution of books"
    },
    {
      "question": "駆虫",
      "answer": "くちゅう",
      "meaning": "exterminating insects, pest control, deinsectization"
    },
    {
      "question": "圧雪",
      "answer": "あっせつ",
      "meaning": "compacted snow"
    },
    {
      "question": "在留邦人",
      "answer": "ざいりゅうほうじん",
      "meaning": "Japanese residents in another country, Japanese expatriates"
    },
    {
      "question": "儼",
      "answer": "げん",
      "meaning": "strict, stern"
    },
    {
      "question": "特保",
      "answer": "とくほ",
      "meaning": "food for specified health uses (e.g. cholesterol reduction), designated health food"
    },
    {
      "question": "女人結界",
      "answer": "にょにんけっかい",
      "meaning": "prohibition against women entering a sacred area"
    },
    {
      "question": "凱旋将軍",
      "answer": "がいせんしょうぐん",
      "meaning": "triumphant general"
    },
    {
      "question": "生さぬ仲",
      "answer": "なさぬなか",
      "meaning": "with no blood relation"
    },
    {
      "question": "象皮病",
      "answer": "ぞうひびょう",
      "meaning": "elephantiasis"
    },
    {
      "question": "拝辞",
      "answer": "はいじ",
      "meaning": "resigning, declining"
    },
    {
      "question": "失心",
      "answer": "しっしん",
      "meaning": "faint, trance, swoon, stupefaction"
    },
    {
      "question": "思惑違い",
      "answer": "おもわくちがい",
      "meaning": "miscalculation, disappointment"
    },
    {
      "question": "志操堅固",
      "answer": "しそうけんご",
      "meaning": "being faithful to one's principles, being of firm purpose and deep commitment, constancy, true blue"
    },
    {
      "question": "司法裁判",
      "answer": "しほうさいばん",
      "meaning": "judicial trial"
    },
    {
      "question": "心淋しい",
      "answer": "うらさびしい,うらさみしい",
      "meaning": "lonesome, lonely, forlorn"
    },
    {
      "question": "文展",
      "answer": "ぶんてん",
      "meaning": "Bunten exhibition, art exhibition sponsored by the Ministry of Education (antecedent of the Nitten e"
    },
    {
      "question": "十六羅漢",
      "answer": "じゅうろくらかん",
      "meaning": "the sixteen arhats"
    },
    {
      "question": "締め込み",
      "answer": "しめこみ",
      "meaning": "wrestler's belt"
    },
    {
      "question": "本諸子",
      "answer": "ほんもろこ",
      "meaning": "willow gudgeon (species of fish, Gnathopogon caerulescens)"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒黴",
      "answer": "くろかび",
      "meaning": "black mold (Aspergillus niger), black mould"
    },
    {
      "question": "特配",
      "answer": "とくはい",
      "meaning": "special ration, special bonus or dividend"
    },
    {
      "question": "新玉",
      "answer": "あらたま",
      "meaning": "unpolished and uncut gem"
    },
    {
      "question": "時代精神",
      "answer": "じだいせいしん",
      "meaning": "spirit of the age, zeitgeist"
    },
    {
      "question": "安定成長",
      "answer": "あんていせいちょう",
      "meaning": "stable growth"
    },
    {
      "question": "上層雲",
      "answer": "じょうそううん",
      "meaning": "upper clouds"
    },
    {
      "question": "帆檣",
      "answer": "はんしょう",
      "meaning": "mast"
    },
    {
      "question": "対治",
      "answer": "たいじ",
      "meaning": "extermination (e.g. of pests, demons, bandits), elimination, eradication, destruction, suppression,"
    },
    {
      "question": "富士額",
      "answer": "ふじびたい",
      "meaning": "widow's peak, hairline that grows to a point in the middle of the forehead"
    },
    {
      "question": "涙液",
      "answer": "るいえき",
      "meaning": "lacrimal fluid, tears"
    },
    {
      "question": "宇宙医学",
      "answer": "うちゅういがく",
      "meaning": "space medicine"
    },
    {
      "question": "甘心",
      "answer": "かんしん",
      "meaning": "satisfaction"
    },
    {
      "question": "油条",
      "answer": "ユウティアオ,ヨウティヤオ",
      "meaning": "youtiao, deep-fried dough, Chinese cruller, Chinese fried churro"
    },
    {
      "question": "禅定",
      "answer": "ぜんじょう",
      "meaning": "dhyana-samadhi (meditative concentration), ascetic practice atop a sacred mountain (in Shugendō), mo"
    },
    {
      "question": "八天狗",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "萌え立つ",
      "answer": "もえたつ",
      "meaning": "to burst into leaf, to sprout"
    },
    {
      "question": "網代笠",
      "answer": "あじろがさ",
      "meaning": "conical wicker hat"
    },
    {
      "question": "密儀",
      "answer": "みつぎ",
      "meaning": "secret rites, secrets"
    },
    {
      "question": "説伏",
      "answer": "せっぷく",
      "meaning": "persuasion"
    },
    {
      "question": "寄合い",
      "answer": "よりあい",
      "meaning": "meeting, gathering, village assembly, two wrestlers approaching each other"
    },
    {
      "question": "局地戦争",
      "answer": "きょくちせんそう",
      "meaning": "local war, limited war"
    },
    {
      "question": "語頭",
      "answer": "ごとう",
      "meaning": "first part of a word"
    },
    {
      "question": "貞観",
      "answer": "じょうがん",
      "meaning": "Jōgan era (859.4.15-877.4.16)"
    },
    {
      "question": "真冬日",
      "answer": "まふゆび",
      "meaning": "day on which the temperature fails to reach 0 degrees Centigrade"
    },
    {
      "question": "凡策",
      "answer": "ぼんさく",
      "meaning": "mediocre policy, commonplace policy, worthless policy"
    },
    {
      "question": "悲泣",
      "answer": "ひきゅう",
      "meaning": "tears of grief, crying with sadness"
    },
    {
      "question": "結解",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "勁草",
      "answer": "けいそう",
      "meaning": "wind-resistant blade of grass, resistant idea (metaphorically)"
    },
    {
      "question": "アート紙",
      "answer": "アートし",
      "meaning": "coated paper, art paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "高黍",
      "answer": "たかきび",
      "meaning": "sorghum (Sorghum bicolor), Indian millet"
    },
    {
      "question": "聴視",
      "answer": "ちょうし",
      "meaning": "listening and watching"
    },
    {
      "question": "旧蹟",
      "answer": "ふるあと,きゅうせき",
      "meaning": "historic spot, historic remains, ruins"
    },
    {
      "question": "下土",
      "answer": "かど,かと",
      "meaning": "lower world, this world, the earth"
    },
    {
      "question": "協和音",
      "answer": "きょうわおん",
      "meaning": "consonance"
    },
    {
      "question": "指紋押捺",
      "answer": "しもんおうなつ",
      "meaning": "fingerprinting"
    },
    {
      "question": "朽壊",
      "answer": "きゅうかい",
      "meaning": "rotting and crumbling"
    },
    {
      "question": "洋刀",
      "answer": "ようとう",
      "meaning": "sabre, saber"
    },
    {
      "question": "誘電体",
      "answer": "ゆうでんたい",
      "meaning": "dielectric"
    },
    {
      "question": "当り屋",
      "answer": "あたりや",
      "meaning": "lucky person, someone who made a lot of money (e.g. gambling or on the stock market), skilled batter"
    },
    {
      "question": "出前持",
      "answer": "でまえもち",
      "meaning": "delivery person (of food)"
    },
    {
      "question": "右顧左眄",
      "answer": "うこさべん",
      "meaning": "inability to make up one's mind due to worrying about how others will think, hesitation, wavering, v"
    },
    {
      "question": "町役人",
      "answer": "まちやくにん,ちょうやくにん",
      "meaning": "Edo-period official of the chōnin social class, town official"
    },
    {
      "question": "歩卒",
      "answer": "ほそつ",
      "meaning": "footmen, foot soldier"
    },
    {
      "question": "油注し",
      "answer": "あぶらさし",
      "meaning": "oilcan"
    },
    {
      "question": "代数学",
      "answer": "だいすうがく",
      "meaning": "algebra"
    },
    {
      "question": "卜骨",
      "answer": "ぼっこつ",
      "meaning": "fortune-telling using animal bones"
    },
    {
      "question": "巣籠もり",
      "answer": "すごもり",
      "meaning": "nesting, hibernation, shutting oneself in at home, staying at home"
    },
    {
      "question": "御用納め",
      "answer": "ごようおさめ",
      "meaning": "year-end office closing (usu. Dec. 28)"
    },
    {
      "question": "産褥期",
      "answer": "さんじょくき",
      "meaning": "postpartum period, postnatal period, puerperal period, puerperium"
    },
    {
      "question": "骨化",
      "answer": "こっか",
      "meaning": "ossification"
    },
    {
      "question": "恒産",
      "answer": "こうさん",
      "meaning": "fixed property, real property, fixed occupation"
    },
    {
      "question": "吐薬",
      "answer": "はきぐすり",
      "meaning": "emetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪声",
      "answer": "あくせい",
      "meaning": "bad voice, evil speaking"
    },
    {
      "question": "意気銷沈",
      "answer": "いきしょうちん",
      "meaning": "depressed in spirits, dispirited, disheartened, rejection"
    },
    {
      "question": "極量",
      "answer": "きょくりょう",
      "meaning": "maximum dose"
    },
    {
      "question": "放送大学",
      "answer": "ほうそうだいがく",
      "meaning": "continuing education courses offered via radio or television, open university"
    },
    {
      "question": "社歴",
      "answer": "しゃれき",
      "meaning": "history of a company"
    },
    {
      "question": "聖蹟",
      "answer": "せいせき",
      "meaning": "holy site"
    },
    {
      "question": "旗国主義",
      "answer": "きこくしゅぎ",
      "meaning": "flag state principle"
    },
    {
      "question": "民衆的",
      "answer": "みんしゅうてき",
      "meaning": "popular"
    },
    {
      "question": "沸き上る",
      "answer": "わきあがる",
      "meaning": "to boil up, to come to the boil, to seethe, to arise, to break out, to get excited, to be in uproar"
    },
    {
      "question": "六十進法",
      "answer": "ろくじっしんほう",
      "meaning": "sexagesimal, base 60"
    },
    {
      "question": "符節",
      "answer": "ふせつ",
      "meaning": "tally, check"
    },
    {
      "question": "疾っくに",
      "answer": "とっくに",
      "meaning": "long ago, already, a long time ago"
    },
    {
      "question": "胡麻擂り",
      "answer": "ごますり",
      "meaning": "sycophant, apple-polisher, flatterer, brown-noser, ass-kisser, sesame seed grinding"
    },
    {
      "question": "厚誼",
      "answer": "こうぎ",
      "meaning": "kindnesses, friendship, cordialities"
    },
    {
      "question": "湯湯婆",
      "answer": "ゆたんぽ",
      "meaning": "hot-water bottle"
    },
    {
      "question": "皺伸ばし",
      "answer": "しわのばし",
      "meaning": "smoothing out wrinkles, (with reference to the elderly) recreation"
    },
    {
      "question": "里神楽",
      "answer": "さとかぐら",
      "meaning": "kagura performance held somewhere other than the imperial palace"
    },
    {
      "question": "鼬鼠",
      "answer": "いたち",
      "meaning": "weasel (esp. the Japanese weasel, Mustela itatsi), mustelid (any other member of the weasel family,"
    },
    {
      "question": "寄り切り",
      "answer": "よりきり",
      "meaning": "driving opponent out of the ring while gripping his belt"
    },
    {
      "question": "正書法",
      "answer": "せいしょほう",
      "meaning": "orthography"
    },
    {
      "question": "新患",
      "answer": "しんかん",
      "meaning": "new patient"
    },
    {
      "question": "有髪",
      "answer": "うはつ",
      "meaning": "untonsured (monk or priest or nun)"
    },
    {
      "question": "死馬",
      "answer": "しば",
      "meaning": "dead horse"
    },
    {
      "question": "配電線",
      "answer": "はいでんせん",
      "meaning": "power line"
    },
    {
      "question": "攩網",
      "answer": "たもあみ",
      "meaning": "hand net, dip net, scoop net"
    },
    {
      "question": "釈義",
      "answer": "しゃくぎ",
      "meaning": "exegesis, explanation of a text, commentary on a text"
    },
    {
      "question": "情緒纏綿",
      "answer": "じょうしょてんめん,じょうちょてんめん",
      "meaning": "tender sentiments, being overcome with emotions, having a tender feeling (for a person)"
    },
    {
      "question": "厚表紙",
      "answer": "あつびょうし",
      "meaning": "thick book cover, book with thick binding"
    },
    {
      "question": "風致",
      "answer": "ふうち",
      "meaning": "taste, elegance, scenic beauty"
    },
    {
      "question": "知恵競べ",
      "answer": "ちえくらべ",
      "meaning": "battle of wits, contest of wits"
    },
    {
      "question": "降神術",
      "answer": "こうしんじゅつ",
      "meaning": "spiritualism"
    },
    {
      "question": "黄銅鉱",
      "answer": "おうどうこう",
      "meaning": "copper pyrites, fool's gold, chalcopyrite"
    },
    {
      "question": "論理和",
      "answer": "ろんりわ",
      "meaning": "disjunction, logical sum, logical add, OR operation"
    },
    {
      "question": "巻き替え",
      "answer": "まきかえ",
      "meaning": "winding a replacement thread, wire, etc., changing from an overarm to an underarm grip on one's oppo"
    },
    {
      "question": "七曲がり",
      "answer": "ななまがり",
      "meaning": "tortuous or spiral (path)"
    },
    {
      "question": "類題",
      "answer": "るいだい",
      "meaning": "similar question, (classification by) similarity of theme"
    },
    {
      "question": "林地",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "膵臓癌",
      "answer": "すいぞうがん",
      "meaning": "pancreatic cancer"
    },
    {
      "question": "船級",
      "answer": "せんきゅう",
      "meaning": "ship's classification"
    },
    {
      "question": "動物質",
      "answer": "どうぶつしつ",
      "meaning": "animal matter"
    },
    {
      "question": "棘魚",
      "answer": "とげうお",
      "meaning": "stickleback (Gasterosteidae spp.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "六神通",
      "answer": "ろくじんずう,ろくじんつう",
      "meaning": "six supernormal powers"
    },
    {
      "question": "無患子",
      "answer": "むくろじ",
      "meaning": "Indian soapberry (Sapindus mukorossi), Chinese soapberry, washnut, soapnut tree"
    },
    {
      "question": "硝煙弾雨",
      "answer": "しょうえんだんう",
      "meaning": "smoke of powder and hail of bullets, (in) the thick of the raging battle"
    },
    {
      "question": "償金",
      "answer": "しょうきん",
      "meaning": "reparation, redemption"
    },
    {
      "question": "謎謎",
      "answer": "なぞなぞ",
      "meaning": "riddle, puzzle, enigma"
    },
    {
      "question": "七十二候",
      "answer": "しちじゅうにこう",
      "meaning": "the 72 'climates' of the year based on the 24 solar seasons further divided into three"
    },
    {
      "question": "損料",
      "answer": "そんりょう",
      "meaning": "rental fee"
    },
    {
      "question": "迂愚",
      "answer": "うぐ",
      "meaning": "stupid, ignorant"
    },
    {
      "question": "転業",
      "answer": "てんぎょう,てんごう",
      "meaning": "change of occupation, prank, joke"
    },
    {
      "question": "扁平足",
      "answer": "へんぺいそく",
      "meaning": "flatfoot, flat feet, splayfoot"
    },
    {
      "question": "五七調",
      "answer": "ごしちちょう",
      "meaning": "five and seven-syllable meter"
    },
    {
      "question": "籌",
      "answer": "はかりごと,ちゅう",
      "meaning": "plan, strategy, wooden skewer used for counting"
    },
    {
      "question": "跡始末",
      "answer": "あとしまつ",
      "meaning": "settlement (of affairs), remedial measures, cleaning up afterwards"
    },
    {
      "question": "端境期",
      "answer": "はざかいき",
      "meaning": "between-crops season, off-crops season"
    },
    {
      "question": "高枕",
      "answer": "たかまくら",
      "meaning": "high pillow"
    },
    {
      "question": "共通因数",
      "answer": "きょうつういんすう",
      "meaning": "common factor"
    },
    {
      "question": "喉自慢",
      "answer": "のどじまん",
      "meaning": "singing contest, person proud of their voice"
    },
    {
      "question": "メガ盛",
      "answer": "メガもり",
      "meaning": "mega-sized portion, mega-sized serving, mega meal"
    },
    {
      "question": "越南",
      "answer": "えつなん",
      "meaning": "Vietnam"
    },
    {
      "question": "事相",
      "answer": "じそう",
      "meaning": "aspect, phase, phenomenon"
    },
    {
      "question": "優先座席",
      "answer": "ゆうせんざせき",
      "meaning": "priority seating"
    },
    {
      "question": "天慶",
      "answer": "てんぎょう,てんきょう,てんけい",
      "meaning": "Tengyō era (938.5.22-947.4.22), Tenkei era"
    },
    {
      "question": "三毛作",
      "answer": "さんもうさく",
      "meaning": "three crops a year"
    },
    {
      "question": "即効薬",
      "answer": "そっこうやく",
      "meaning": "quick-acting remedy, fast-acting medicine"
    },
    {
      "question": "引ん剝く",
      "answer": "ひんむく",
      "meaning": "to strip, to peel, to tear off"
    },
    {
      "question": "香を聞く",
      "answer": "こうをきく",
      "meaning": "to smell incense"
    },
    {
      "question": "前栽",
      "answer": "せんざい",
      "meaning": "garden, trees and flowers in a garden"
    },
    {
      "question": "ガラス絵",
      "answer": "ガラスえ",
      "meaning": "picture painted on glass, stained glass"
    },
    {
      "question": "外耳炎",
      "answer": "がいじえん",
      "meaning": "otitis externa, inflammation of the outer ear"
    },
    {
      "question": "耐乏",
      "answer": "たいぼう",
      "meaning": "austerity, voluntary privation"
    },
    {
      "question": "来信",
      "answer": "らいしん",
      "meaning": "letter received"
    },
    {
      "question": "年が年中",
      "answer": "ねんがねんじゅう",
      "meaning": "all year round, year after year"
    },
    {
      "question": "男山",
      "answer": "おとこやま",
      "meaning": "rugged mountain (of the more rugged mountain of a pair of mountains)"
    },
    {
      "question": "炭焼き窯",
      "answer": "すみやきがま",
      "meaning": "charcoal kiln"
    },
    {
      "question": "通貫",
      "answer": "つうかん",
      "meaning": "piercing through, penetrating, perforating, persisting, sticking (e.g. to beliefs)"
    },
    {
      "question": "海深",
      "answer": "かいしん",
      "meaning": "depth of the sea"
    },
    {
      "question": "実葛",
      "answer": "さねかずら",
      "meaning": "scarlet kadsura (Kadsura japonica)"
    },
    {
      "question": "安臥",
      "answer": "あんが",
      "meaning": "quiet rest"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷や汁",
      "answer": "ひやじる",
      "meaning": "cold soup (usu. miso)"
    },
    {
      "question": "シーク教",
      "answer": "シークきょう",
      "meaning": "Sikhism"
    },
    {
      "question": "太白星",
      "answer": "たいはくせい",
      "meaning": "Venus (planet)"
    },
    {
      "question": "廻状",
      "answer": "かいじょう",
      "meaning": "circular, circulating letter"
    },
    {
      "question": "音吐",
      "answer": "おんと",
      "meaning": "voice"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍犬",
      "answer": "ぐんけん",
      "meaning": "war dog"
    },
    {
      "question": "政策秘書",
      "answer": "せいさくひしょ",
      "meaning": "policy secretary"
    },
    {
      "question": "足骨",
      "answer": "そっこつ,あしぼね",
      "meaning": "bones of the feet, the strength of one's feet"
    },
    {
      "question": "中夜",
      "answer": "ちゅうや",
      "meaning": "midnight period, midnight service, winter solstice"
    },
    {
      "question": "前付け",
      "answer": "まえづけ",
      "meaning": "front matter (of a book), preliminaries"
    },
    {
      "question": "色温度",
      "answer": "いろおんど",
      "meaning": "color temperature"
    },
    {
      "question": "共同正犯",
      "answer": "きょうどうせいはん",
      "meaning": "crime committed together by two or more people (in which each is known as a co-principal)"
    },
    {
      "question": "昔時",
      "answer": "せきじ",
      "meaning": "old times, former times"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉗む",
      "answer": "つぐむ",
      "meaning": "to shut one's mouth, to hold one's tongue, to keep silent"
    },
    {
      "question": "残花",
      "answer": "ざんか",
      "meaning": "(last) flower remaining in bloom"
    },
    {
      "question": "血液透析",
      "answer": "けつえきとうせき",
      "meaning": "hemodialysis, haemodialysis"
    },
    {
      "question": "差控える",
      "answer": "さしひかえる",
      "meaning": "to be moderate in, to be temperate in, to not do too much of, to refrain (from doing), to withhold ("
    },
    {
      "question": "肉叢",
      "answer": "ししむら",
      "meaning": "piece of meat, lump of meat, the body, the flesh"
    },
    {
      "question": "切れ物",
      "answer": "きれもの",
      "meaning": "edged tool, cutlery, shrewd businessman"
    },
    {
      "question": "規矩準縄",
      "answer": "きくじゅんじょう",
      "meaning": "rules and standards, norms, criteria"
    },
    {
      "question": "口気",
      "answer": "こうき",
      "meaning": "bad breath, intimation"
    },
    {
      "question": "形式名詞",
      "answer": "けいしきめいし",
      "meaning": "formal noun, dummy noun, expletive noun"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒檜",
      "answer": "くろべ,くろび",
      "meaning": "Japanese arborvitae (Thuja standishii)"
    },
    {
      "question": "氷滑り",
      "answer": "こおりすべり",
      "meaning": "ice skating"
    },
    {
      "question": "逆転写",
      "answer": "ぎゃくてんしゃ",
      "meaning": "reverse transcription"
    },
    {
      "question": "初句",
      "answer": "しょく",
      "meaning": "first five syllables (of a tanka), first line (of a poem)"
    },
    {
      "question": "定足数",
      "answer": "ていそくすう",
      "meaning": "quorum"
    },
    {
      "question": "挽き切る",
      "answer": "ひききる",
      "meaning": "to saw off, to interrupt, to suspend, to discontinue"
    },
    {
      "question": "測量図",
      "answer": "そくりょうず",
      "meaning": "survey map"
    },
    {
      "question": "詞藻",
      "answer": "しそう",
      "meaning": "florid expression, poetical talent"
    },
    {
      "question": "小糠",
      "answer": "こぬか",
      "meaning": "rice bran"
    },
    {
      "question": "狂妄",
      "answer": "きょうぼう,きょうもう",
      "meaning": "eccentric, wild, off-kilter, mad"
    },
    {
      "question": "先験的",
      "answer": "せんけんてき",
      "meaning": "transcendental"
    },
    {
      "question": "ビヤ樽",
      "answer": "ビヤだる",
      "meaning": "beer barrel"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜顔",
      "answer": "よるがお",
      "meaning": "moonflower (Ipomoea alba)"
    },
    {
      "question": "高血糖",
      "answer": "こうけっとう",
      "meaning": "hyperglycemia, hyperglycaemia"
    },
    {
      "question": "物情騒然",
      "answer": "ぶつじょうそうぜん",
      "meaning": "unrest prevailing, turmoil reigning"
    },
    {
      "question": "木戸番",
      "answer": "きどばん",
      "meaning": "doorman, gatekeeper"
    },
    {
      "question": "色砂",
      "answer": "いろすな",
      "meaning": "coloured sand (used for coating interior plaster walls)"
    },
    {
      "question": "旧称",
      "answer": "きゅうしょう",
      "meaning": "old name, former title"
    },
    {
      "question": "磚",
      "answer": "せん",
      "meaning": "brick (used in Chinese-style buildings)"
    },
    {
      "question": "細小",
      "answer": "さいしょう,いさら,いささ",
      "meaning": "minute, minuscule, small, little"
    },
    {
      "question": "威武",
      "answer": "いぶ",
      "meaning": "authority and force"
    },
    {
      "question": "一望千里",
      "answer": "いちぼうせんり",
      "meaning": "sweeping view of the eye, boundless expanse"
    },
    {
      "question": "表戸",
      "answer": "おもてど",
      "meaning": "front door"
    },
    {
      "question": "交易条件",
      "answer": "こうえきじょうけん",
      "meaning": "terms of trade"
    },
    {
      "question": "口言葉",
      "answer": "くちことば",
      "meaning": "spoken language, spoken words, language"
    },
    {
      "question": "暮し向き",
      "answer": "くらしむき",
      "meaning": "life circumstances, lifestyle, (family) finances"
    },
    {
      "question": "内炎",
      "answer": "ないえん",
      "meaning": "inner flame"
    },
    {
      "question": "無理無体",
      "answer": "むりむたい",
      "meaning": "by force"
    },
    {
      "question": "文人墨客",
      "answer": "ぶんじんぼっかく,ぶんじんぼっきゃく",
      "meaning": "writers and artists, persons who take delight in such refined pursuits as poetry, literature, painti"
    },
    {
      "question": "鱶の鰭",
      "answer": "ふかのひれ",
      "meaning": "shark fin"
    },
    {
      "question": "目明き",
      "answer": "めあき",
      "meaning": "one who can see, educated or sensible person"
    },
    {
      "question": "下国",
      "answer": "げこく",
      "meaning": "province of the lowest rank (ritsuryo system), leaving for the provinces"
    },
    {
      "question": "弱音器",
      "answer": "じゃくおんき",
      "meaning": "damper, mute (on musical instruments)"
    },
    {
      "question": "物化",
      "answer": "ぶっか,ものか",
      "meaning": "changing, becoming, death, objectification, objectifying"
    },
    {
      "question": "諮詢",
      "answer": "しじゅん",
      "meaning": "question, enquiry, inquiry, consultation, advice-seeking"
    },
    {
      "question": "内奏",
      "answer": "ないそう",
      "meaning": "secret report to the emperor"
    },
    {
      "question": "塩基性",
      "answer": "えんきせい",
      "meaning": "basicity, alkalinity, basic, alkaline"
    },
    {
      "question": "遠謀深慮",
      "answer": "えんぼうしんりょ",
      "meaning": "deep design and forethought, farsighted and deeply-laid plan"
    },
    {
      "question": "錨地",
      "answer": "びょうち",
      "meaning": "(point of) anchorage"
    },
    {
      "question": "卵胎生",
      "answer": "らんたいせい",
      "meaning": "ovoviviparity"
    },
    {
      "question": "余っ程",
      "answer": "よっぽど",
      "meaning": "very, greatly, much, considerably, to a large extent, quite, just about to, almost, very nearly"
    },
    {
      "question": "段組み",
      "answer": "だんぐみ",
      "meaning": "multicolumn layout, column setting"
    },
    {
      "question": "出軍",
      "answer": "しゅつぐん",
      "meaning": "expedition"
    },
    {
      "question": "金紗",
      "answer": "きんしゃ",
      "meaning": "silk crepe"
    },
    {
      "question": "繽紛",
      "answer": "ひんぷん",
      "meaning": "jumbled, in disarray, scattered randomly about (small items)"
    },
    {
      "question": "私感",
      "answer": "しかん",
      "meaning": "personal impression"
    },
    {
      "question": "処決",
      "answer": "しょけつ",
      "meaning": "settlement, decision"
    },
    {
      "question": "正編",
      "answer": "せいへん",
      "meaning": "main part of a book"
    },
    {
      "question": "暗箱",
      "answer": "あんばこ",
      "meaning": "camera obscura, black box"
    },
    {
      "question": "振仮名",
      "answer": "ふりがな",
      "meaning": "furigana, kana over or beside kanji to indicate pronunciation"
    },
    {
      "question": "流眄",
      "answer": "ながしめ",
      "meaning": "sidelong glance, flirtatious glance"
    },
    {
      "question": "蒸汽",
      "answer": "じょうき",
      "meaning": "steam, vapour, vapor, steamboat, steam locomotive"
    },
    {
      "question": "杮落とし",
      "answer": "こけらおとし",
      "meaning": "opening of a new theater (theatre)"
    },
    {
      "question": "中間選挙",
      "answer": "ちゅうかんせんきょ",
      "meaning": "midterm election, interim election"
    },
    {
      "question": "詳説",
      "answer": "しょうせつ",
      "meaning": "detailed explanation"
    },
    {
      "question": "不断着",
      "answer": "ふだんぎ",
      "meaning": "everyday clothes, ordinary clothes, casual wear, informal dress"
    },
    {
      "question": "瞽女",
      "answer": "ごぜ",
      "meaning": "blind female beggar who sings or plays shamisen"
    },
    {
      "question": "種板",
      "answer": "たねいた",
      "meaning": "(photographic) negative"
    },
    {
      "question": "女山",
      "answer": "おんなやま",
      "meaning": "gently sloping mountain (of the less rugged mountain of a pair of mountains)"
    },
    {
      "question": "追送",
      "answer": "ついそう",
      "meaning": "sending an additional part later"
    },
    {
      "question": "恋は闇",
      "answer": "こいはやみ",
      "meaning": "love is blind"
    },
    {
      "question": "猜む",
      "answer": "そねむ",
      "meaning": "to be jealous of, to envy, to begrudge"
    },
    {
      "question": "随える",
      "answer": "したがえる",
      "meaning": "to be accompanied by, to be attended by, to take along (someone), to conquer, to subjugate, to subdu"
    },
    {
      "question": "宗論",
      "answer": "しゅうろん",
      "meaning": "doctrinal dispute (within or between religious schools)"
    },
    {
      "question": "言継ぐ",
      "answer": "いいつぐ",
      "meaning": "to transmit by word of mouth"
    },
    {
      "question": "魂柱",
      "answer": "こんちゅう",
      "meaning": "sound post (e.g. of a violin)"
    },
    {
      "question": "宥恕",
      "answer": "ゆうじょ",
      "meaning": "forgiveness, generosity"
    },
    {
      "question": "亀虫",
      "answer": "かめむし",
      "meaning": "shield bug, stink bug"
    },
    {
      "question": "補語",
      "answer": "ほご",
      "meaning": "complement"
    },
    {
      "question": "甲高",
      "answer": "こうだか",
      "meaning": "high-pitched, high in the instep"
    },
    {
      "question": "事大主義",
      "answer": "じだいしゅぎ",
      "meaning": "worship of the powerful"
    },
    {
      "question": "復航",
      "answer": "ふっこう",
      "meaning": "return flight or voyage"
    },
    {
      "question": "篷",
      "answer": "とま",
      "meaning": "woven mat (of sedge, hay, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "墨家",
      "answer": "ぼっか,ぼくか",
      "meaning": "mohist, follower of mohism"
    },
    {
      "question": "元徳",
      "answer": "げんとく",
      "meaning": "Gentoku era (1329.8.29-1331.8.9)"
    },
    {
      "question": "光電管",
      "answer": "こうでんかん",
      "meaning": "photoelectric tube"
    },
    {
      "question": "奇偶",
      "answer": "きぐう",
      "meaning": "odd and even numbers"
    },
    {
      "question": "刎頸の友",
      "answer": "ふんけいのとも",
      "meaning": "inseparable friend, sworn friend"
    },
    {
      "question": "塩尻",
      "answer": "しおじり",
      "meaning": "cone-shaped"
    },
    {
      "question": "島伝い",
      "answer": "しまづたい",
      "meaning": "from island to island, island-hopping"
    },
    {
      "question": "赭顔",
      "answer": "しゃがん",
      "meaning": "ruddy face"
    },
    {
      "question": "鞏固",
      "answer": "きょうこ",
      "meaning": "firm, strong, solid, stable"
    },
    {
      "question": "花樹",
      "answer": "かじゅ",
      "meaning": "flowering tree"
    },
    {
      "question": "地方税",
      "answer": "ちほうぜい",
      "meaning": "local tax, council tax"
    },
    {
      "question": "徒事",
      "answer": "ただごと,あだごと",
      "meaning": "trivial matter"
    },
    {
      "question": "咽頭炎",
      "answer": "いんとうえん",
      "meaning": "pharyngitis, sore throat"
    },
    {
      "question": "神迎え",
      "answer": "かみむかえ",
      "meaning": "rite welcoming back the gods from Izumo Shrine (on the last day of the tenth lunar month)"
    },
    {
      "question": "氷冠",
      "answer": "ひょうかん",
      "meaning": "ice cap"
    },
    {
      "question": "降順",
      "answer": "こうじゅん",
      "meaning": "descending order"
    },
    {
      "question": "未開社会",
      "answer": "みかいしゃかい",
      "meaning": "a primitive society"
    },
    {
      "question": "給水管",
      "answer": "きゅうすいかん",
      "meaning": "water pipe"
    },
    {
      "question": "鋤焼き",
      "answer": "すきやき",
      "meaning": "sukiyaki, thin slices of beef, cooked with various vegetables in a table-top cast-iron pan"
    },
    {
      "question": "明達",
      "answer": "めいたつ",
      "meaning": "wisdom"
    },
    {
      "question": "当今",
      "answer": "とうこん",
      "meaning": "nowadays, these days, at present"
    },
    {
      "question": "綿羊",
      "answer": "めんよう",
      "meaning": "sheep"
    },
    {
      "question": "湯文字",
      "answer": "ゆもじ,いもじ",
      "meaning": "woman's loincloth (worn as a kimono underskirt), single-layer absorbent bathrobe (worn during or aft"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛切り",
      "answer": "とびきり",
      "meaning": "best, extra-fine, superfine, unequalled, exceptionally, extraordinarily, by far, jumping and slashin"
    },
    {
      "question": "多事",
      "answer": "たじ",
      "meaning": "eventfulness"
    },
    {
      "question": "十干",
      "answer": "じっかん",
      "meaning": "the 10 calendar signs"
    },
    {
      "question": "金員",
      "answer": "きんいん",
      "meaning": "(amount of) money"
    },
    {
      "question": "不可侵権",
      "answer": "ふかしんけん",
      "meaning": "inviolable right"
    },
    {
      "question": "魂祭",
      "answer": "たままつり",
      "meaning": "ceremony honouring the spirits of ancestors (esp. the Bon festival)"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝待月",
      "answer": "ねまちづき",
      "meaning": "waning gibbous moon, moon of the 19th day of the lunar month"
    },
    {
      "question": "窶す",
      "answer": "やつす",
      "meaning": "to be absorbed in, to lose oneself to, to disguise oneself as, to adorn oneself"
    },
    {
      "question": "特許法",
      "answer": "とっきょほう",
      "meaning": "Patent Act"
    },
    {
      "question": "フン族",
      "answer": "フンぞく",
      "meaning": "the Huns"
    },
    {
      "question": "調音器官",
      "answer": "ちょうおんきかん",
      "meaning": "articulatory organ (i.e. the tongue, teeth, lips, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "製版",
      "answer": "せいはん",
      "meaning": "plate-making (printing)"
    },
    {
      "question": "羽裏",
      "answer": "はうら",
      "meaning": "underside of a bird's wing, lining of a haori"
    },
    {
      "question": "遖",
      "answer": "あっぱれ",
      "meaning": "splendid, praiseworthy, admirable, brilliant, well done!, bravo!"
    },
    {
      "question": "青楼",
      "answer": "せいろう",
      "meaning": "officially sanctioned brothel (Edo-period)"
    },
    {
      "question": "犬走り",
      "answer": "いぬばしり",
      "meaning": "scarcement, berm, ledge"
    },
    {
      "question": "宝瓶宮",
      "answer": "ほうへいきゅう",
      "meaning": "Aquarius (11th zodiacal sign), the Water Bearer, the Water Carrier"
    },
    {
      "question": "細々しい",
      "answer": "こまごましい",
      "meaning": "minute, very fine, very small, annoying, complicated, very detailed, elaborate"
    },
    {
      "question": "迚も",
      "answer": "とても,とっても",
      "meaning": "very, awfully, exceedingly, (not) at all, by no means, simply (cannot)"
    },
    {
      "question": "味噌っ歯",
      "answer": "みそっぱ",
      "meaning": "decayed (baby) tooth"
    },
    {
      "question": "五十三次",
      "answer": "ごじゅうさんつぎ",
      "meaning": "fifty-three stations on the Tōkaidō (Edo-Kyoto highway in Edo-period Japan)"
    },
    {
      "question": "川船",
      "answer": "かわぶね",
      "meaning": "riverboat, rivercraft"
    },
    {
      "question": "窓掛",
      "answer": "まどかけ",
      "meaning": "curtains"
    },
    {
      "question": "近村",
      "answer": "きんそん",
      "meaning": "neighboring villages"
    },
    {
      "question": "大谷派",
      "answer": "おおたには",
      "meaning": "Otani sect (of Shin Buddhism)"
    },
    {
      "question": "控訴棄却",
      "answer": "こうそききゃく",
      "meaning": "dismissal of an intermediate appeal"
    },
    {
      "question": "復活当選",
      "answer": "ふっかつとうせん",
      "meaning": "failing to win an electoral seat in a single-member constituency, but winning a seat in a proportion"
    },
    {
      "question": "公序",
      "answer": "こうじょ",
      "meaning": "public order, public policy"
    },
    {
      "question": "百病",
      "answer": "ひゃくびょう",
      "meaning": "all kinds of illnesses"
    },
    {
      "question": "破廉恥罪",
      "answer": "はれんちざい",
      "meaning": "infamous crime or offense (offence)"
    },
    {
      "question": "配糖体",
      "answer": "はいとうたい",
      "meaning": "glycoside"
    },
    {
      "question": "三つ角",
      "answer": "みつかど",
      "meaning": "three corners"
    },
    {
      "question": "花鋏",
      "answer": "はなばさみ",
      "meaning": "florist's scissors, flower scissors"
    },
    {
      "question": "続け字",
      "answer": "つづけじ",
      "meaning": "cursive handwriting, connected characters, running characters"
    },
    {
      "question": "肇国",
      "answer": "ちょうこく",
      "meaning": "founding of a state"
    },
    {
      "question": "筆記帳",
      "answer": "ひっきちょう",
      "meaning": "notebook"
    },
    {
      "question": "咬筋",
      "answer": "こうきん",
      "meaning": "masseter muscle"
    },
    {
      "question": "炒り煮",
      "answer": "いりに",
      "meaning": "simmering after frying"
    },
    {
      "question": "硬音",
      "answer": "こうおん",
      "meaning": "fortis"
    },
    {
      "question": "添田",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "南家",
      "answer": "ナンチャ",
      "meaning": "south player"
    },
    {
      "question": "鑵",
      "answer": "かん",
      "meaning": "can, tin, canned food"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜盗蛾",
      "answer": "よとうが",
      "meaning": "cabbage armyworm"
    },
    {
      "question": "跳馬",
      "answer": "ちょうば",
      "meaning": "long horse (for vaulting)"
    },
    {
      "question": "古学",
      "answer": "こがく",
      "meaning": "classical studies"
    },
    {
      "question": "御寮人",
      "answer": "ごりょうにん",
      "meaning": "mistress, madam"
    },
    {
      "question": "木戸銭",
      "answer": "きどせん",
      "meaning": "gate money, admission fee"
    },
    {
      "question": "浅紅",
      "answer": "せんこう",
      "meaning": "light red"
    },
    {
      "question": "単層",
      "answer": "たんそう",
      "meaning": "monolayer, single layer, single story (storey)"
    },
    {
      "question": "平々",
      "answer": "へいへい",
      "meaning": "level, ordinary"
    },
    {
      "question": "糯米",
      "answer": "もちごめ",
      "meaning": "glutinous rice"
    },
    {
      "question": "畳み皺",
      "answer": "たたみじわ",
      "meaning": "crease (from folding)"
    },
    {
      "question": "丸公",
      "answer": "まるこう",
      "meaning": "official price"
    },
    {
      "question": "郵便為替",
      "answer": "ゆうびんかわせ",
      "meaning": "postal money order"
    },
    {
      "question": "目高",
      "answer": "めだか",
      "meaning": "Japanese rice fish (Oryzias latipes), killifish, Japanese medaka"
    },
    {
      "question": "来阪",
      "answer": "らいはん",
      "meaning": "coming to Osaka"
    },
    {
      "question": "酸性度",
      "answer": "さんせいど",
      "meaning": "(degree of) acidity"
    },
    {
      "question": "下萌え",
      "answer": "したもえ",
      "meaning": "sprout of a plant shooting from under the soil"
    },
    {
      "question": "舌ピアス",
      "answer": "したピアス",
      "meaning": "tongue piercing, tongue stud"
    },
    {
      "question": "奉納相撲",
      "answer": "ほうのうずもう",
      "meaning": "ritual matches held at a shrine"
    },
    {
      "question": "王法",
      "answer": "おうほう",
      "meaning": "royal decree"
    },
    {
      "question": "曲物",
      "answer": "まげもの,わげもの,くせもの",
      "meaning": "circular box, article for pawning, ruffian, villain, knave, thief, suspicious fellow, peculiar perso"
    },
    {
      "question": "春疾風",
      "answer": "はるはやて",
      "meaning": "strong spring storm"
    },
    {
      "question": "才徳",
      "answer": "さいとく",
      "meaning": "intelligence and virtue"
    },
    {
      "question": "七宝焼",
      "answer": "しっぽうやき",
      "meaning": "cloisonne ware"
    },
    {
      "question": "小正月",
      "answer": "こしょうがつ",
      "meaning": "Little New Year (festival held on January 15), 14th-16th days of the first month of the year, Koshog"
    },
    {
      "question": "筋向い",
      "answer": "すじむかい",
      "meaning": "diagonally opposite"
    },
    {
      "question": "徒輩",
      "answer": "とはい",
      "meaning": "set, company, companions, fellows"
    },
    {
      "question": "胙",
      "answer": "ひもろぎ",
      "meaning": "offerings of food (to the gods)"
    },
    {
      "question": "仙椎",
      "answer": "せんつい",
      "meaning": "sacral vertebra"
    },
    {
      "question": "獅子宮",
      "answer": "ししきゅう",
      "meaning": "Leo (5th zodiacal sign), the Lion"
    },
    {
      "question": "面対称",
      "answer": "めんたいしょう",
      "meaning": "plane symmetry, symmetry with respect to a plane"
    },
    {
      "question": "造山運動",
      "answer": "ぞうざんうんどう",
      "meaning": "mountain-making movements, mountain building, orogenesis"
    },
    {
      "question": "床山",
      "answer": "とこやま",
      "meaning": "hairdresser (for sumo wrestlers and actors), wigmaker (for actors), hairdressing room (Edo period Ka"
    },
    {
      "question": "塊根",
      "answer": "かいこん",
      "meaning": "tuberous root"
    },
    {
      "question": "造立",
      "answer": "ぞうりゅう,ぞうりつ",
      "meaning": "erecting (temple, Buddhist statue, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "私通",
      "answer": "しつう",
      "meaning": "adultery, illicit intercourse"
    },
    {
      "question": "粉体",
      "answer": "ふんたい",
      "meaning": "powder"
    },
    {
      "question": "打っ飛ぶ",
      "answer": "ぶっとぶ",
      "meaning": "to fly (with great force), to blast (e.g. into the sky), to lack common sense, to be extremely surpr"
    },
    {
      "question": "靴下留め",
      "answer": "くつしたどめ",
      "meaning": "garters, suspenders"
    },
    {
      "question": "矯激",
      "answer": "きょうげき",
      "meaning": "radical, extreme, eccentric"
    },
    {
      "question": "隕石孔",
      "answer": "いんせきこう",
      "meaning": "meteorite crater"
    },
    {
      "question": "等色",
      "answer": "とうしょく",
      "meaning": "isochromatic"
    },
    {
      "question": "端女郎",
      "answer": "はしじょろう",
      "meaning": "low class licensed prostitute (Edo period)"
    },
    {
      "question": "井然",
      "answer": "せいぜん",
      "meaning": "orderly, regular, systematic, well-organized, well-organised, trim, tidy, accurate"
    },
    {
      "question": "当月",
      "answer": "とうげつ",
      "meaning": "this month"
    },
    {
      "question": "拙策",
      "answer": "せっさく",
      "meaning": "poor policy, poor plan, unwise measure, (one's own) plan"
    },
    {
      "question": "春興",
      "answer": "しゅんきょう",
      "meaning": "enjoyment of spring, interest in spring"
    },
    {
      "question": "幽暗",
      "answer": "ゆうあん",
      "meaning": "gloom, darkness, seclusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "臨在",
      "answer": "りんざい",
      "meaning": "presence"
    },
    {
      "question": "茶利",
      "answer": "ちゃり",
      "meaning": "funny word or gesture, funny part (in a puppet show, kabuki, etc.), a woman's temple hair"
    },
    {
      "question": "解版",
      "answer": "かいはん",
      "meaning": "(in printing) distribution of type"
    },
    {
      "question": "聞き置く",
      "answer": "ききおく",
      "meaning": "to listen"
    },
    {
      "question": "棒磁石",
      "answer": "ぼうじしゃく",
      "meaning": "bar magnet"
    },
    {
      "question": "間然",
      "answer": "かんぜん",
      "meaning": "being liable to criticism"
    },
    {
      "question": "天主教",
      "answer": "てんしゅきょう",
      "meaning": "(Roman) Catholicism"
    },
    {
      "question": "土用波",
      "answer": "どようなみ",
      "meaning": "high waves which rise during the dog days of summer"
    },
    {
      "question": "摩羅",
      "answer": "まら",
      "meaning": "obstacle to Buddhist practice, penis"
    },
    {
      "question": "御預け",
      "answer": "おあずけ",
      "meaning": "making a person, pet, etc. wait (before being permitted to do something), postponement, putting on h"
    },
    {
      "question": "秋分点",
      "answer": "しゅうぶんてん",
      "meaning": "autumn equinoctal point"
    },
    {
      "question": "懸垂線",
      "answer": "けんすいせん",
      "meaning": "catenary"
    },
    {
      "question": "起龕",
      "answer": "きがん",
      "meaning": "ceremonial removal of the coffin from the house (lay person) or temple (priest) (Zen Buddhism)"
    },
    {
      "question": "縮瞳",
      "answer": "しゅくどう",
      "meaning": "miosis, myosis, (excessive) constriction of the pupil"
    },
    {
      "question": "被選挙人",
      "answer": "ひせんきょにん",
      "meaning": "person eligible for elective office"
    },
    {
      "question": "糞垂れ",
      "answer": "くそたれ",
      "meaning": "shithead, bastard"
    },
    {
      "question": "験し",
      "answer": "ためし",
      "meaning": "trial, test"
    },
    {
      "question": "閉業",
      "answer": "へいぎょう",
      "meaning": "closing of a business or enterprise"
    },
    {
      "question": "追贈",
      "answer": "ついぞう",
      "meaning": "conferring court rank posthumously"
    },
    {
      "question": "迫り上る",
      "answer": "せりあがる",
      "meaning": "to gradually rise"
    },
    {
      "question": "寄人",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "温度感覚",
      "answer": "おんどかんかく",
      "meaning": "temperature sense"
    },
    {
      "question": "排気弁",
      "answer": "はいきべん",
      "meaning": "exhaust valve"
    },
    {
      "question": "認許",
      "answer": "にんきょ",
      "meaning": "consent, recognition, approval, certification"
    },
    {
      "question": "局方",
      "answer": "きょくほう",
      "meaning": "Japanese Pharmacopeia"
    },
    {
      "question": "掃蕩",
      "answer": "そうとう",
      "meaning": "cleaning up, sweeping up, mopping up"
    },
    {
      "question": "建売り",
      "answer": "たてうり",
      "meaning": "constructing and selling a ready-built house"
    },
    {
      "question": "山岳会",
      "answer": "さんがくかい",
      "meaning": "mountaineering club, climbing club"
    },
    {
      "question": "盲爆",
      "answer": "もうばく",
      "meaning": "blind (unscrupulous, indiscriminate) bombing"
    },
    {
      "question": "曲筆",
      "answer": "きょくひつ",
      "meaning": "misrepresentation, falsification"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉄道馬車",
      "answer": "てつどうばしゃ",
      "meaning": "horse-drawn streetcar"
    },
    {
      "question": "水和",
      "answer": "すいわ",
      "meaning": "hydration"
    },
    {
      "question": "稼ぎ高",
      "answer": "かせぎだか",
      "meaning": "earnings"
    },
    {
      "question": "八町",
      "answer": "はまち",
      "meaning": "hamachi, young Japanese amberjack, young yellowtail"
    },
    {
      "question": "文献学",
      "answer": "ぶんけんがく",
      "meaning": "philology"
    },
    {
      "question": "妨碍",
      "answer": "ぼうがい",
      "meaning": "disturbance, obstruction, hindrance, jamming, interference"
    },
    {
      "question": "鍼術",
      "answer": "しんじゅつ",
      "meaning": "acupuncture"
    },
    {
      "question": "券面",
      "answer": "けんめん",
      "meaning": "face (of a bond, bill, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "教法",
      "answer": "きょうほう",
      "meaning": "teachings of Buddha, teaching method, way of teaching"
    },
    {
      "question": "力価",
      "answer": "りきか",
      "meaning": "titer, titre, potency"
    },
    {
      "question": "悲喜交交",
      "answer": "ひきこもごも",
      "meaning": "bittersweet, having mingled feelings of joy and sorrow, joy and sorrow alternating in one's heart"
    },
    {
      "question": "好い事",
      "answer": "よいこと,いいこと",
      "meaning": "good thing, nice thing, good excuse, good grounds, good opportunity, interjection used to impress an"
    },
    {
      "question": "耳垂れ",
      "answer": "みみだれ",
      "meaning": "ear discharge"
    },
    {
      "question": "外眼筋",
      "answer": "がいがんきん",
      "meaning": "extraocular muscle, external eye muscle"
    },
    {
      "question": "巡演",
      "answer": "じゅんえん",
      "meaning": "performance tour"
    },
    {
      "question": "引目",
      "answer": "ひきめ",
      "meaning": "large, perforated, turnip-shaped arrowhead cover made of Japanese bigleaf magnolia or paulownia, har"
    },
    {
      "question": "設け",
      "answer": "もうけ",
      "meaning": "preparation, provision, establishment"
    },
    {
      "question": "チャイ語",
      "answer": "チャイご",
      "meaning": "Chinese language (esp. as a college class)"
    },
    {
      "question": "香華",
      "answer": "こうげ",
      "meaning": "flowers and incense (given as a Buddhist offering)"
    },
    {
      "question": "遠音",
      "answer": "とおね",
      "meaning": "distant sound"
    },
    {
      "question": "校友会",
      "answer": "こうゆうかい",
      "meaning": "alumni association"
    },
    {
      "question": "卵塔場",
      "answer": "らんとうば",
      "meaning": "cemetery"
    },
    {
      "question": "総理府",
      "answer": "そうりふ",
      "meaning": "Prime Minister's office, PMO"
    },
    {
      "question": "掛け矢",
      "answer": "かけや",
      "meaning": "mallet"
    },
    {
      "question": "仏の座",
      "answer": "ほとけのざ",
      "meaning": "henbit deadnettle (Lamium amplexicaule), henbit, Japanese nipplewort (Lapsanastrum apogonoides)"
    },
    {
      "question": "免訴",
      "answer": "めんそ",
      "meaning": "acquittal, dismissal (of a case)"
    },
    {
      "question": "円タク",
      "answer": "えんタク",
      "meaning": "one-yen taxi (in the Taisho and Showa periods), taxi"
    },
    {
      "question": "部民",
      "answer": "べみん,ぶみん",
      "meaning": "people belonging to a hereditary occupation group (Yamato period)"
    },
    {
      "question": "抗血清",
      "answer": "こうけっせい",
      "meaning": "antiserum"
    },
    {
      "question": "敬天愛人",
      "answer": "けいてんあいじん",
      "meaning": "revere heaven, love people"
    },
    {
      "question": "英主",
      "answer": "えいしゅ",
      "meaning": "great ruler"
    },
    {
      "question": "銃傷",
      "answer": "じゅうしょう",
      "meaning": "gunshot wound"
    },
    {
      "question": "之繞",
      "answer": "しんにょう,しんにゅう",
      "meaning": "kanji 'road' or 'advance' radical (radical 162)"
    },
    {
      "question": "撥ねかす",
      "answer": "はねかす",
      "meaning": "to splash, to splatter"
    },
    {
      "question": "葬具",
      "answer": "そうぐ",
      "meaning": "funeral accessories, funeral items, funeral paraphernalia"
    },
    {
      "question": "春官",
      "answer": "しゅんかん",
      "meaning": "Ministry of Rites (Zhou-dynasty China)"
    },
    {
      "question": "羅針儀",
      "answer": "らしんぎ",
      "meaning": "compass"
    },
    {
      "question": "漸々",
      "answer": "ぜんぜん",
      "meaning": "gradually, by degrees, the sight of a tall soaring rock, crying, weeping"
    },
    {
      "question": "狩猟豹",
      "answer": "しゅりょうひょう",
      "meaning": "cheetah"
    },
    {
      "question": "冥助",
      "answer": "みょうじょ",
      "meaning": "divine protection, divine blessing, providence"
    },
    {
      "question": "規矩",
      "answer": "きく",
      "meaning": "rule, standard, compass and ruler"
    },
    {
      "question": "板絵",
      "answer": "いたえ",
      "meaning": "artwork on wood, canvas, metal sheet, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "造林",
      "answer": "ぞうりん",
      "meaning": "forestation, afforestation, reforestation"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷媒",
      "answer": "れいばい",
      "meaning": "refrigerant, coolant"
    },
    {
      "question": "光明真言",
      "answer": "こうみょうしんごん",
      "meaning": "Mantra of Light"
    },
    {
      "question": "腹面",
      "answer": "ふくめん",
      "meaning": "ventral surface"
    },
    {
      "question": "石竹",
      "answer": "せきちく",
      "meaning": "China pink (species of flower, Dianthus chinensis)"
    },
    {
      "question": "入れ智慧",
      "answer": "いれぢえ",
      "meaning": "putting an idea into someone's head, suggestion, hint"
    },
    {
      "question": "薩英戦争",
      "answer": "さつえいせんそう",
      "meaning": "Anglo-Satsuma War (1863)"
    },
    {
      "question": "局外者",
      "answer": "きょくがいしゃ",
      "meaning": "outsider"
    },
    {
      "question": "産官学",
      "answer": "さんかんがく",
      "meaning": "industry, government and academia"
    },
    {
      "question": "隠田",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "塩基対",
      "answer": "えんきつい",
      "meaning": "base pair"
    },
    {
      "question": "食養生",
      "answer": "しょくようじょう",
      "meaning": "taking nourishing food, eating a balanced diet"
    },
    {
      "question": "中売り",
      "answer": "なかうり",
      "meaning": "ambulatory vending of snacks in a theater or stadium (theatre)"
    },
    {
      "question": "立法機関",
      "answer": "りっぽうきかん",
      "meaning": "legislature, legislative body"
    },
    {
      "question": "関税障壁",
      "answer": "かんぜいしょうへき",
      "meaning": "tariff barrier"
    },
    {
      "question": "金権政治",
      "answer": "きんけんせいじ",
      "meaning": "money politics (i.e. corruption of politics by money)"
    },
    {
      "question": "地峡",
      "answer": "ちきょう",
      "meaning": "isthmus"
    },
    {
      "question": "熱水鉱床",
      "answer": "ねっすいこうしょう",
      "meaning": "hydrothermal deposit"
    },
    {
      "question": "賦存量",
      "answer": "ふそんりょう",
      "meaning": "abundance"
    },
    {
      "question": "陰陰",
      "answer": "いんいん",
      "meaning": "dark and desolate, forlorn"
    },
    {
      "question": "手車",
      "answer": "てぐるま",
      "meaning": "handcart, wheelbarrow"
    },
    {
      "question": "美挙",
      "answer": "びきょ",
      "meaning": "praiseworthy undertaking, commendable act"
    },
    {
      "question": "無気肺",
      "answer": "むきはい",
      "meaning": "atelectasis"
    },
    {
      "question": "空世辞",
      "answer": "からせじ",
      "meaning": "flattery, lip service"
    },
    {
      "question": "公徳心",
      "answer": "こうとくしん",
      "meaning": "public spirit"
    },
    {
      "question": "諢名",
      "answer": "あだな,こんめい",
      "meaning": "nickname"
    },
    {
      "question": "総嘗め",
      "answer": "そうなめ",
      "meaning": "sweeping over (e.g. of a natural disaster), engulfing, sweeping victory, clean sweep"
    },
    {
      "question": "内孫",
      "answer": "ないそん,うちまご",
      "meaning": "child of one's heir"
    },
    {
      "question": "医生",
      "answer": "いせい",
      "meaning": "bio-medical, biomedical, medical student"
    },
    {
      "question": "類同",
      "answer": "るいどう",
      "meaning": "similar, of the same type"
    },
    {
      "question": "海事",
      "answer": "かいじ",
      "meaning": "maritime affairs"
    },
    {
      "question": "公的年金",
      "answer": "こうてきねんきん",
      "meaning": "public pension"
    },
    {
      "question": "潜竜",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "小春日",
      "answer": "こはるび",
      "meaning": "mild late autumn day (around November), mild late fall day"
    },
    {
      "question": "緊急避妊",
      "answer": "きんきゅうひにん",
      "meaning": "emergency contraception"
    },
    {
      "question": "巨大分子",
      "answer": "きょだいぶんし",
      "meaning": "macromolecule"
    },
    {
      "question": "拐帯",
      "answer": "かいたい",
      "meaning": "absconding with money"
    },
    {
      "question": "内枠",
      "answer": "うちわく",
      "meaning": "inner frame, within given limits"
    },
    {
      "question": "急派",
      "answer": "きゅうは",
      "meaning": "dispatch, despatch"
    },
    {
      "question": "箒木",
      "answer": "ほうきぎ",
      "meaning": "common kochia (Bassia scoparia), burning bush, summer cypress"
    },
    {
      "question": "方案",
      "answer": "ほうあん",
      "meaning": "plan, device, scheme, program, thoughts or suggestions about a law"
    },
    {
      "question": "一分銀",
      "answer": "いちぶぎん",
      "meaning": "ichibugin, Edo-period rectangular silver coin worth one quarter ryō"
    },
    {
      "question": "瞽",
      "answer": "めくら",
      "meaning": "blindness, blind person, illiteracy, illiterate person, ignorance, ignoramus"
    },
    {
      "question": "因習的",
      "answer": "いんしゅうてき",
      "meaning": "conventional"
    },
    {
      "question": "衢",
      "answer": "ちまた",
      "meaning": "the public, the street (e.g. 'word on the street'), street, district, quarters, location (e.g. of a"
    },
    {
      "question": "点火薬",
      "answer": "てんかやく",
      "meaning": "priming powders"
    },
    {
      "question": "専門語",
      "answer": "せんもんご",
      "meaning": "(specialist) terminology"
    },
    {
      "question": "出養生",
      "answer": "でようじょう",
      "meaning": "travelling somewhere to improve one's health, travelling somewhere to recuperate"
    },
    {
      "question": "破産法",
      "answer": "はさんほう",
      "meaning": "Bankruptcy Act"
    },
    {
      "question": "小差",
      "answer": "しょうさ",
      "meaning": "slight difference, narrow margin"
    },
    {
      "question": "桟道",
      "answer": "さんどう",
      "meaning": "plank road, corduroy"
    },
    {
      "question": "置き土",
      "answer": "おきつち",
      "meaning": "earth taken from elsewhere and placed atop"
    },
    {
      "question": "閻魔堂",
      "answer": "えんまどう",
      "meaning": "temple hall dedicated to Yama"
    },
    {
      "question": "忍苦",
      "answer": "にんく",
      "meaning": "endurance, stoicism"
    },
    {
      "question": "煉る",
      "answer": "ねる",
      "meaning": "to knead, to thicken into a paste (stirring over a flame), to polish (a plan, etc.), to refine, to e"
    },
    {
      "question": "黄熟",
      "answer": "こうじゅく,おうじゅく",
      "meaning": "ripening and turning yellow"
    },
    {
      "question": "円規",
      "answer": "えんき",
      "meaning": "pair of compasses"
    },
    {
      "question": "妊娠中絶",
      "answer": "にんしんちゅうぜつ",
      "meaning": "abortion, pregnancy termination"
    },
    {
      "question": "練丹",
      "answer": "れんたん",
      "meaning": "elixir of life (prepared from cinnabar in ancient China)"
    },
    {
      "question": "幽艶",
      "answer": "ゆうえん",
      "meaning": "modest and beautiful, profound and elegant"
    },
    {
      "question": "胆石症",
      "answer": "たんせきしょう",
      "meaning": "gallstones, cholelithiasis"
    },
    {
      "question": "検する",
      "answer": "けんする",
      "meaning": "to inspect, to supervise"
    },
    {
      "question": "入朝",
      "answer": "にゅうちょう",
      "meaning": "visiting Japan, arrival in Japan"
    },
    {
      "question": "分納",
      "answer": "ぶんのう",
      "meaning": "installment payment or delivery, instalment payment or delivery"
    },
    {
      "question": "銀牌",
      "answer": "ぎんぱい",
      "meaning": "silver medal, silver badge"
    },
    {
      "question": "緋の衣",
      "answer": "ひのころも",
      "meaning": "scarlet robe"
    },
    {
      "question": "盛り花",
      "answer": "もりばな",
      "meaning": "flower arrangement in a built-up style, placing salt by the entrance to one's establishment to bring"
    },
    {
      "question": "造出",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "苛立てる",
      "answer": "いらだてる",
      "meaning": "to irritate, to exasperate"
    },
    {
      "question": "索莫",
      "answer": "さくばく",
      "meaning": "dreary, bleak, desolate"
    },
    {
      "question": "絵書き",
      "answer": "えかき",
      "meaning": "painter, artist, drawing pictures, doodling, painting"
    },
    {
      "question": "黄連",
      "answer": "おうれん",
      "meaning": "goldthread (Coptis japonica)"
    },
    {
      "question": "近事",
      "answer": "きんじ",
      "meaning": "recent events"
    },
    {
      "question": "配流",
      "answer": "はいる",
      "meaning": "exile, banishment"
    },
    {
      "question": "痩せ地",
      "answer": "やせち",
      "meaning": "barren soil"
    },
    {
      "question": "生齧り",
      "answer": "なまかじり",
      "meaning": "superficial knowledge, smattering, dabbler, dilettante, dipping into"
    },
    {
      "question": "秘密選挙",
      "answer": "ひみつせんきょ",
      "meaning": "secret ballot"
    },
    {
      "question": "揖斐川",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "青貝",
      "answer": "あおがい",
      "meaning": "limpet"
    },
    {
      "question": "献茶",
      "answer": "けんちゃ",
      "meaning": "tea offering to the gods"
    },
    {
      "question": "閻魔の庁",
      "answer": "えんまのちょう",
      "meaning": "judgment seat of Yama (judgement)"
    },
    {
      "question": "嵩高",
      "answer": "かさだか,すうこう",
      "meaning": "bulky, unwieldy, haughty, high-handed, lofty (of a mountain), tall"
    },
    {
      "question": "成島",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "実質賃金",
      "answer": "じっしつちんぎん",
      "meaning": "real wages"
    },
    {
      "question": "文芸学",
      "answer": "ぶんげいがく",
      "meaning": "study or science of literature, a liberal arts department"
    },
    {
      "question": "話柄",
      "answer": "わへい",
      "meaning": "topic, subject"
    },
    {
      "question": "人絹",
      "answer": "じんけん",
      "meaning": "rayon, artificial silk"
    },
    {
      "question": "高麗芝",
      "answer": "こうらいしば",
      "meaning": "Korean lawn grass"
    },
    {
      "question": "配属将校",
      "answer": "はいぞくしょうこう",
      "meaning": "commissioned officer attached to a school"
    },
    {
      "question": "普通郵便",
      "answer": "ふつうゆうびん",
      "meaning": "ordinary mail (post)"
    },
    {
      "question": "生け造り",
      "answer": "いけづくり",
      "meaning": "sashimi prepared from live fish, arranged in its original shape, fresh sashimi"
    },
    {
      "question": "内用薬",
      "answer": "ないようやく",
      "meaning": "medicine taken internally"
    },
    {
      "question": "苟且",
      "answer": "かりそめ,こうしょ",
      "meaning": "temporary, transient, trifling, slight, negligent"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉱滓",
      "answer": "こうさい,こうし",
      "meaning": "slag"
    },
    {
      "question": "反射能",
      "answer": "はんしゃのう",
      "meaning": "reflective power, albedo"
    },
    {
      "question": "作業仮説",
      "answer": "さぎょうかせつ",
      "meaning": "working hypothesis"
    },
    {
      "question": "科学革命",
      "answer": "かがくかくめい",
      "meaning": "scientific revolution"
    },
    {
      "question": "トルコ語",
      "answer": "トルコご",
      "meaning": "Turkish (language)"
    },
    {
      "question": "寸尺",
      "answer": "すんしゃく",
      "meaning": "length, measure, short length"
    },
    {
      "question": "聖恩",
      "answer": "せいおん",
      "meaning": "imperial blessings or favor (favour)"
    },
    {
      "question": "別アカ",
      "answer": "べつアカ",
      "meaning": "alternate account, separate account, alt account, alt"
    },
    {
      "question": "尖り帽子",
      "answer": "とんがりぼうし",
      "meaning": "pointy hat"
    },
    {
      "question": "許状",
      "answer": "きょじょう",
      "meaning": "licence, license, certificate, permit, (letter of) pardon"
    },
    {
      "question": "言い甲斐",
      "answer": "いいがい",
      "meaning": "worth mentioning"
    },
    {
      "question": "太巻",
      "answer": "ふとまき",
      "meaning": "futomaki, thick roll of makizushi, rolling something thickly, something rolled thickly (a cigar, etc"
    },
    {
      "question": "極冠",
      "answer": "きょっかん",
      "meaning": "polar cap"
    },
    {
      "question": "単葉",
      "answer": "たんよう",
      "meaning": "simple leaf, monoplane"
    },
    {
      "question": "御仕着せ",
      "answer": "おしきせ",
      "meaning": "uniforms supplied to employees, an allotment"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤道半径",
      "answer": "せきどうはんけい",
      "meaning": "equatorial radius"
    },
    {
      "question": "太皇太后",
      "answer": "たいこうたいごう",
      "meaning": "Grand Empress Dowager"
    },
    {
      "question": "主人顔",
      "answer": "しゅじんがお",
      "meaning": "propriety air"
    },
    {
      "question": "激職",
      "answer": "げきしょく",
      "meaning": "busy job, exhausting work"
    },
    {
      "question": "上床",
      "answer": "あげどこ",
      "meaning": "raised seedbed"
    },
    {
      "question": "小便袋",
      "answer": "しょうべんぶくろ",
      "meaning": "rubber bag for collecting urine, urinary bladder"
    },
    {
      "question": "禅院",
      "answer": "ぜんいん",
      "meaning": "Zen temple"
    },
    {
      "question": "門違い",
      "answer": "かどちがい",
      "meaning": "barking up the wrong tree, calling at the wrong house"
    },
    {
      "question": "分光器",
      "answer": "ぶんこうき",
      "meaning": "spectroscope, spectrograph"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪を欺く",
      "answer": "ゆきをあざむく",
      "meaning": "to be as white as snow"
    },
    {
      "question": "二者選一",
      "answer": "にしゃせんいつ",
      "meaning": "choosing between two things, two choices"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉋掛け",
      "answer": "かんなかけ",
      "meaning": "planing (wood)"
    },
    {
      "question": "営農",
      "answer": "えいのう",
      "meaning": "farming, agriculture"
    },
    {
      "question": "分祀",
      "answer": "ぶんし",
      "meaning": "separation of worship, movement of an enshrined deity to another shrine"
    },
    {
      "question": "口尻",
      "answer": "くちじり",
      "meaning": "commissures (of the lips), lip corners, mouth corners"
    },
    {
      "question": "瀬取り",
      "answer": "せどり",
      "meaning": "ship-to-ship cargo transfer, off-shore delivery (into smaller boats)"
    },
    {
      "question": "哀歓",
      "answer": "あいかん",
      "meaning": "joys and sorrows, happiness and sadness"
    },
    {
      "question": "殻斗",
      "answer": "かくと",
      "meaning": "cupule, acorn cup"
    },
    {
      "question": "好い仲",
      "answer": "いいなか",
      "meaning": "love for one another"
    },
    {
      "question": "一瀉千里",
      "answer": "いっしゃせんり",
      "meaning": "one swift effort, rush through one's work, fast-talking, writing, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "精進日",
      "answer": "しょうじんび",
      "meaning": "day of abstinence"
    },
    {
      "question": "壮途",
      "answer": "そうと",
      "meaning": "ambitious undertaking"
    },
    {
      "question": "冲する",
      "answer": "ちゅうする",
      "meaning": "to rise up into the air, to ascend into the sky"
    },
    {
      "question": "暮夜",
      "answer": "ぼや",
      "meaning": "night, evening"
    },
    {
      "question": "直接証拠",
      "answer": "ちょくせつしょうこ",
      "meaning": "direct evidence"
    },
    {
      "question": "総攬",
      "answer": "そうらん",
      "meaning": "control, superintendence"
    },
    {
      "question": "先先週",
      "answer": "せんせんしゅう",
      "meaning": "week before last"
    },
    {
      "question": "轡虫",
      "answer": "くつわむし",
      "meaning": "Mecopoda nipponensis (species of katydid)"
    },
    {
      "question": "碌々",
      "answer": "ろくろく",
      "meaning": "hardly, barely, inadequately (with negative grammatical constructions)"
    },
    {
      "question": "植物質",
      "answer": "しょくぶつしつ",
      "meaning": "vegetable matter"
    },
    {
      "question": "付けペン",
      "answer": "つけペン",
      "meaning": "dip pen, nib pen"
    },
    {
      "question": "皇典",
      "answer": "こうてん",
      "meaning": "Japanese classics"
    },
    {
      "question": "下げ髪",
      "answer": "さげがみ",
      "meaning": "pigtail, ponytail, hair (hanging down the back)"
    },
    {
      "question": "金剛鈴",
      "answer": "こんごうれい",
      "meaning": "vajra bell"
    },
    {
      "question": "石榴石",
      "answer": "ざくろいし",
      "meaning": "garnet"
    },
    {
      "question": "佳品",
      "answer": "かひん",
      "meaning": "choice article, item of excellent quality, masterpiece"
    },
    {
      "question": "五節句",
      "answer": "ごせっく",
      "meaning": "the five festivals (January 7, March 3, May 5, July 7 and September 9)"
    },
    {
      "question": "幼形成熟",
      "answer": "ようけいせいじゅく",
      "meaning": "neoteny"
    },
    {
      "question": "華夷",
      "answer": "かい",
      "meaning": "China and foreign countries (from the perspective of China), civilized land and uncivilized land"
    },
    {
      "question": "売約",
      "answer": "ばいやく",
      "meaning": "sales contract"
    },
    {
      "question": "蹲う",
      "answer": "つくばう",
      "meaning": "to crouch, to squat"
    },
    {
      "question": "西周",
      "answer": "せいしゅう",
      "meaning": "Western Zhou dynasty (China, c 1046-771 BCE), Western Chou dynasty"
    },
    {
      "question": "個々別々",
      "answer": "ここべつべつ",
      "meaning": "each one separately"
    },
    {
      "question": "商業資本",
      "answer": "しょうぎょうしほん",
      "meaning": "trading capital"
    },
    {
      "question": "芝刈",
      "answer": "しばかり",
      "meaning": "lawn mowing"
    },
    {
      "question": "地塗り",
      "answer": "じぬり",
      "meaning": "undercoating, underpainting, first coating"
    },
    {
      "question": "持戒",
      "answer": "じかい",
      "meaning": "strictly adhering to Buddhist precepts"
    },
    {
      "question": "新漬",
      "answer": "しんづけ",
      "meaning": "freshly pickled vegetables"
    },
    {
      "question": "追申",
      "answer": "ついしん",
      "meaning": "postscript, post scriptum, PS, P.S."
    },
    {
      "question": "切愛",
      "answer": "せつあい",
      "meaning": "deep love"
    },
    {
      "question": "花豆",
      "answer": "はなまめ",
      "meaning": "scarlet runner bean (Phaseolus coccineus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "顕微鏡座",
      "answer": "けんびきょうざ",
      "meaning": "Microscopium (constellation), the Microscope"
    },
    {
      "question": "接尾辞",
      "answer": "せつびじ",
      "meaning": "suffix"
    },
    {
      "question": "湯波",
      "answer": "ゆば",
      "meaning": "tofu skin, dried beancurd, delicacy made from the skin of gently boiled soybean milk"
    },
    {
      "question": "仏眼",
      "answer": "ぶつげん",
      "meaning": "the Buddha eye"
    },
    {
      "question": "町筋",
      "answer": "まちすじ",
      "meaning": "street"
    },
    {
      "question": "懸巣",
      "answer": "かけす",
      "meaning": "Eurasian jay (Garrulus glandarius)"
    },
    {
      "question": "咫",
      "answer": "あた,た",
      "meaning": "distance between outstretched thumb and middle finger (approx. 18 cm)"
    },
    {
      "question": "北海油田",
      "answer": "ほっかいゆでん",
      "meaning": "North Sea oil fields"
    },
    {
      "question": "二本差",
      "answer": "にほんざし",
      "meaning": "two-sworded (samurai)"
    },
    {
      "question": "丸八",
      "answer": "まるはち",
      "meaning": "Cyathea mertensiana (species of tree fern)"
    },
    {
      "question": "絵手紙",
      "answer": "えてがみ",
      "meaning": "letter made from a picture one has drawn"
    },
    {
      "question": "弘治",
      "answer": "こうじ",
      "meaning": "Kōji era (1555.10.23-1558.2.28)"
    },
    {
      "question": "銀河座標",
      "answer": "ぎんがざひょう",
      "meaning": "galactic coordinates"
    },
    {
      "question": "異腹",
      "answer": "いふく",
      "meaning": "child of a different mother"
    },
    {
      "question": "割烹店",
      "answer": "かっぽうてん",
      "meaning": "(Japanese) restaurant"
    },
    {
      "question": "塩煮",
      "answer": "しおに",
      "meaning": "boiling in salted water (e.g. fish)"
    },
    {
      "question": "京阪神",
      "answer": "けいはんしん",
      "meaning": "Kyoto-Osaka-Kobe"
    },
    {
      "question": "誕生仏",
      "answer": "たんじょうぶつ",
      "meaning": "statue of the birth of Buddha (right hand pointing at the heavens, left hand pointing at the earth)"
    },
    {
      "question": "復業",
      "answer": "ふくぎょう",
      "meaning": "returning to work"
    },
    {
      "question": "形態素",
      "answer": "けいたいそ",
      "meaning": "morpheme"
    },
    {
      "question": "荒地野菊",
      "answer": "あれちのぎく",
      "meaning": "flax-leaf fleabane (Conyza bonariensis), hairy fleabane, Argentine fleabane"
    },
    {
      "question": "片々",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "苛虐",
      "answer": "かぎゃく",
      "meaning": "cruel treatment"
    },
    {
      "question": "丁年",
      "answer": "ていねん",
      "meaning": "adulthood (i.e. age 20 in Japan), one's majority"
    },
    {
      "question": "愚暗",
      "answer": "ぐあん",
      "meaning": "imbecility"
    },
    {
      "question": "牧牛",
      "answer": "ぼくぎゅう",
      "meaning": "pasturing cattle"
    },
    {
      "question": "裏毛",
      "answer": "うらけ,うらげ",
      "meaning": "fleece lining"
    },
    {
      "question": "旧居",
      "answer": "きゅうきょ",
      "meaning": "former residence"
    },
    {
      "question": "御門違い",
      "answer": "おかどちがい",
      "meaning": "barking up the wrong tree, calling at the wrong house"
    },
    {
      "question": "才量",
      "answer": "さいりょう",
      "meaning": "wisdom and magnanimity, witty intelligence and large-mindedness, measurement, volume and weight"
    },
    {
      "question": "石油危機",
      "answer": "せきゆきき",
      "meaning": "oil crisis"
    },
    {
      "question": "存生",
      "answer": "ぞんじょう",
      "meaning": "being alive"
    },
    {
      "question": "啼声",
      "answer": "なきごえ",
      "meaning": "cry (esp. animal), roar, chirp, tweet, bark, whine, meow"
    },
    {
      "question": "縄編み",
      "answer": "なわあみ",
      "meaning": "cable stitch"
    },
    {
      "question": "波止",
      "answer": "はと",
      "meaning": "breakwater, seawall, bulwark, mole, narrow stone structure for breaking incoming waves and loading g"
    },
    {
      "question": "皮癬",
      "answer": "ひぜん",
      "meaning": "scabies, sarcoptic mange, the itch"
    },
    {
      "question": "例月",
      "answer": "れいげつ",
      "meaning": "every month"
    },
    {
      "question": "圧抑",
      "answer": "あつよく",
      "meaning": "check, restraint, oppression, suppression"
    },
    {
      "question": "在朝",
      "answer": "ざいちょう",
      "meaning": "working within the imperial court, being under government employ, resident in Korea, situated in Kor"
    },
    {
      "question": "文化勲章",
      "answer": "ぶんかくんしょう",
      "meaning": "Order of Culture, Order of Cultural Merit"
    },
    {
      "question": "導関数",
      "answer": "どうかんすう",
      "meaning": "derivative, derived function"
    },
    {
      "question": "概数",
      "answer": "がいすう",
      "meaning": "approximate figure, rough figure, round numbers"
    },
    {
      "question": "院主",
      "answer": "いんじゅ",
      "meaning": "head of a temple"
    },
    {
      "question": "幹竹",
      "answer": "からたけ",
      "meaning": "Japanese timber bamboo (Phyllostachys bambsoides), giant timber bamboo, madake, Henon bamboo (Phyllo"
    },
    {
      "question": "商品化権",
      "answer": "しょうひんかけん",
      "meaning": "merchandising right"
    },
    {
      "question": "游ぐ",
      "answer": "およぐ",
      "meaning": "to swim"
    },
    {
      "question": "松根油",
      "answer": "しょうこんゆ",
      "meaning": "pine oil"
    },
    {
      "question": "酒盗",
      "answer": "しゅとう",
      "meaning": "dish of pickled skipjack tuna entrails sometimes mixed with sake, honey, mirin and onions (specialty"
    },
    {
      "question": "金仏",
      "answer": "かなぶつ,かなぼとけ",
      "meaning": "metal statue of Buddha (usu. bronze), cold-hearted person, cold-blooded person"
    },
    {
      "question": "カナル型",
      "answer": "カナルがた",
      "meaning": "canalphones, in-ear headphones"
    },
    {
      "question": "余憤",
      "answer": "よふん",
      "meaning": "pent-up anger, rage"
    },
    {
      "question": "表店",
      "answer": "おもてだな",
      "meaning": "house on a main street"
    },
    {
      "question": "猛爆",
      "answer": "もうばく",
      "meaning": "heavy bombing, intensive bombing"
    },
    {
      "question": "迷い星",
      "answer": "まよいぼし",
      "meaning": "planet"
    },
    {
      "question": "式次",
      "answer": "しきじ",
      "meaning": "program of a ceremony, programme of a ceremony"
    },
    {
      "question": "知音",
      "answer": "ちいん",
      "meaning": "exceptionally close friend"
    },
    {
      "question": "硫化鉄",
      "answer": "りゅうかてつ",
      "meaning": "iron sulfide, iron sulphide"
    },
    {
      "question": "勧進元",
      "answer": "かんじんもと",
      "meaning": "backer, promoter"
    },
    {
      "question": "牛後",
      "answer": "ぎゅうご",
      "meaning": "rump of a cow"
    },
    {
      "question": "劇化",
      "answer": "げきか",
      "meaning": "dramatization, dramatisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "変通",
      "answer": "へんつう",
      "meaning": "resourcefulness, adaptability"
    },
    {
      "question": "湯取り",
      "answer": "ゆとり",
      "meaning": "clothing to absorb dampness after bathing, yukata, twice-boiled rice (for sick persons), scoop for r"
    },
    {
      "question": "細胞診",
      "answer": "さいぼうしん",
      "meaning": "cytodiagnosis"
    },
    {
      "question": "在方",
      "answer": "ざいかた",
      "meaning": "rural area"
    },
    {
      "question": "明明白白",
      "answer": "めいめいはくはく",
      "meaning": "clearly evident, quite obvious, as clear as day, beyond any doubt, strikingly apparent"
    },
    {
      "question": "特融",
      "answer": "とくゆう",
      "meaning": "special loan"
    },
    {
      "question": "豚饅",
      "answer": "ぶたまん",
      "meaning": "steamed bun with minced pork filling"
    },
    {
      "question": "美妙",
      "answer": "びみょう",
      "meaning": "elegant, exquisite"
    },
    {
      "question": "外股",
      "answer": "そとまた,そともも",
      "meaning": "(walking with) one's toes turned out, duckfooted, outer thigh"
    },
    {
      "question": "上図",
      "answer": "じょうず",
      "meaning": "the above figure (chart, diagram, illustration, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "半裁",
      "answer": "はんさい",
      "meaning": "cutting in half"
    },
    {
      "question": "再拝",
      "answer": "さいはい",
      "meaning": "bowing twice, worshipping again, Yours sincerely, Yours truly, Sincerely yours"
    },
    {
      "question": "洋辛子",
      "answer": "ようがらし",
      "meaning": "mustard"
    },
    {
      "question": "波斯",
      "answer": "ペルシャ,ペルシア,ハルシャ",
      "meaning": "Persia"
    },
    {
      "question": "妙趣",
      "answer": "みょうしゅ",
      "meaning": "exquisite beauty or charms"
    },
    {
      "question": "景気変動",
      "answer": "けいきへんどう",
      "meaning": "business fluctuations"
    },
    {
      "question": "縒り糸",
      "answer": "よりいと",
      "meaning": "twisting (thread, etc.), twisted yarn, twisted thread, twine"
    },
    {
      "question": "皆皆様",
      "answer": "みなみなさま",
      "meaning": "Ladies and Gentlemen!, all of you, everyone"
    },
    {
      "question": "小商人",
      "answer": "こあきんど",
      "meaning": "small businessman, petty trader"
    },
    {
      "question": "黄変",
      "answer": "おうへん",
      "meaning": "turning yellow"
    },
    {
      "question": "伝奇的",
      "answer": "でんきてき",
      "meaning": "legendary"
    },
    {
      "question": "特殊教育",
      "answer": "とくしゅきょういく",
      "meaning": "special education, special needs education"
    },
    {
      "question": "熱容量",
      "answer": "ねつようりょう",
      "meaning": "heat capacity"
    },
    {
      "question": "目的税",
      "answer": "もくてきぜい",
      "meaning": "earmarked tax, special-purpose tax"
    },
    {
      "question": "嚊",
      "answer": "かかあ,かか",
      "meaning": "wife"
    },
    {
      "question": "通牒",
      "answer": "つうちょう",
      "meaning": "notice, notification, memorandum, circular"
    },
    {
      "question": "御師",
      "answer": "おし,おんし",
      "meaning": "low-ranking priest"
    },
    {
      "question": "遊魚",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "悪計",
      "answer": "あっけい,あくけい",
      "meaning": "plot, trick, evil scheme"
    },
    {
      "question": "偽言",
      "answer": "ぎげん",
      "meaning": "falsehood"
    },
    {
      "question": "蛋民",
      "answer": "たんみん",
      "meaning": "Tanka people (of southern China)"
    },
    {
      "question": "家屋税",
      "answer": "かおくぜい",
      "meaning": "house tax"
    },
    {
      "question": "道話",
      "answer": "どうわ",
      "meaning": "exemplum"
    },
    {
      "question": "乾燥血漿",
      "answer": "かんそうけっしょう",
      "meaning": "dried plasma"
    },
    {
      "question": "狂言方",
      "answer": "きょうげんかた",
      "meaning": "kyogen performer, low-ranked house playwright (of kabuki)"
    },
    {
      "question": "過渡",
      "answer": "かと",
      "meaning": "crossing, ferry, transient, changing old to new"
    },
    {
      "question": "生物濃縮",
      "answer": "せいぶつのうしゅく",
      "meaning": "biological concentration"
    },
    {
      "question": "波数",
      "answer": "はすう",
      "meaning": "wave number, wavenumber"
    },
    {
      "question": "棟割長屋",
      "answer": "むねわりながや",
      "meaning": "terraced or partitioned housing structure"
    },
    {
      "question": "蒲色",
      "answer": "かばいろ",
      "meaning": "reddish yellow"
    },
    {
      "question": "窗",
      "answer": "まど",
      "meaning": "window"
    },
    {
      "question": "読譜",
      "answer": "どくふ",
      "meaning": "reading music"
    },
    {
      "question": "桜湯",
      "answer": "さくらゆ",
      "meaning": "drink made of boiled water poured over preserved cherry leaves and blossoms"
    },
    {
      "question": "総合課税",
      "answer": "そうごうかぜい",
      "meaning": "tax on aggregate income"
    },
    {
      "question": "粗放",
      "answer": "そほう",
      "meaning": "rough, careless, reckless, slovenly"
    },
    {
      "question": "公会",
      "answer": "こうかい",
      "meaning": "public meeting"
    },
    {
      "question": "爪繰る",
      "answer": "つまぐる",
      "meaning": "to finger, to roll between the thumb and the fingers"
    },
    {
      "question": "振子時計",
      "answer": "ふりこどけい",
      "meaning": "pendulum clock"
    },
    {
      "question": "管理会計",
      "answer": "かんりかいけい",
      "meaning": "managerial accounting"
    },
    {
      "question": "入角",
      "answer": "いりすみ",
      "meaning": "internal angle of two walls, planes, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "榧",
      "answer": "かや,かえ",
      "meaning": "kaya (Torreya nucifera), Japanese nutmeg tree"
    },
    {
      "question": "盞",
      "answer": "さかずき,さかづき,うき",
      "meaning": "sake cup, cup for alcoholic beverages"
    },
    {
      "question": "釣合い",
      "answer": "つりあい",
      "meaning": "balance, equilibrium"
    },
    {
      "question": "精舎",
      "answer": "しょうじゃ",
      "meaning": "temple, monastery, convent"
    },
    {
      "question": "浮身",
      "answer": "うきみ",
      "meaning": "floating on one's back"
    },
    {
      "question": "女持ち",
      "answer": "おんなもち",
      "meaning": "for women, women's article"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛跡",
      "answer": "ひせき",
      "meaning": "track, flight path"
    },
    {
      "question": "竜血樹",
      "answer": "りゅうけつじゅ",
      "meaning": "dragon tree (Dracaena draco)"
    },
    {
      "question": "合字",
      "answer": "ごうじ",
      "meaning": "ligature (writing, typography)"
    },
    {
      "question": "事前運動",
      "answer": "じぜんうんどう",
      "meaning": "pre-election campaigning"
    },
    {
      "question": "延べ金",
      "answer": "のべがね",
      "meaning": "sheet metal, dagger, sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "定立",
      "answer": "ていりつ",
      "meaning": "thesis"
    },
    {
      "question": "豆腐に鎹",
      "answer": "とうふにかすがい",
      "meaning": "having no effect, waste of effort"
    },
    {
      "question": "幅員",
      "answer": "ふくいん",
      "meaning": "breadth, extent"
    },
    {
      "question": "星合",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "同党",
      "answer": "どうとう",
      "meaning": "the same political party"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍艦巻",
      "answer": "ぐんかんまき",
      "meaning": "battleship sushi, gunkan maki, sushi made by wrapping a strip of nori around a rice ball with a topp"
    },
    {
      "question": "人外境",
      "answer": "じんがいきょう",
      "meaning": "uninhabited area"
    },
    {
      "question": "菱餅",
      "answer": "ひしもち",
      "meaning": "rhombus-shaped mochi"
    },
    {
      "question": "地方区",
      "answer": "ちほうく",
      "meaning": "prefectural constituency"
    },
    {
      "question": "月面車",
      "answer": "げつめんしゃ",
      "meaning": "lunar rover, Moon rover"
    },
    {
      "question": "附設",
      "answer": "ふせつ",
      "meaning": "annex, affiliated structure or institute"
    },
    {
      "question": "読札",
      "answer": "よみふだ",
      "meaning": "cards with words or phrases written on them, used in Japanese karuta games"
    },
    {
      "question": "陰極",
      "answer": "いんきょく",
      "meaning": "cathode"
    },
    {
      "question": "確報",
      "answer": "かくほう",
      "meaning": "definite report, confirmed data"
    },
    {
      "question": "仮綴じ",
      "answer": "かりとじ",
      "meaning": "temporary (paper) binding"
    },
    {
      "question": "完飲",
      "answer": "かんいん",
      "meaning": "drinking everything (in one's glass, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "頑愚",
      "answer": "がんぐ",
      "meaning": "obstinate and foolish"
    },
    {
      "question": "所書き",
      "answer": "ところがき",
      "meaning": "address"
    },
    {
      "question": "赫然",
      "answer": "かくぜん",
      "meaning": "violent and angry, shining, glittering, sparkling"
    },
    {
      "question": "遥拝",
      "answer": "ようはい",
      "meaning": "worshipping from afar"
    },
    {
      "question": "郵政大臣",
      "answer": "ゆうせいだいじん",
      "meaning": "Minister of Posts and Telecommunications"
    },
    {
      "question": "陣門",
      "answer": "じんもん",
      "meaning": "surrender to the enemy"
    },
    {
      "question": "五月晴",
      "answer": "さつきばれ",
      "meaning": "fine weather during the rainy season"
    },
    {
      "question": "組換え",
      "answer": "くみかえ",
      "meaning": "rearrangement (of classes), recomposition, recombination, reclassification"
    },
    {
      "question": "撥面",
      "answer": "ばちめん",
      "meaning": "pick-guard (protective patch on a biwa, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "鸛",
      "answer": "こうのとり,こう",
      "meaning": "stork (esp. the Oriental stork, Ciconia boyciana)"
    },
    {
      "question": "閉脚",
      "answer": "へいきゃく",
      "meaning": "closing the legs, keeping the legs together (in gymnastics)"
    },
    {
      "question": "勘定科目",
      "answer": "かんじょうかもく",
      "meaning": "account name, account title"
    },
    {
      "question": "嵌め込み",
      "answer": "はめこみ",
      "meaning": "insertion, inlaying, immersion"
    },
    {
      "question": "高架鉄道",
      "answer": "こうかてつどう",
      "meaning": "elevated railroad, elevated railway"
    },
    {
      "question": "誼み",
      "answer": "よしみ",
      "meaning": "friendship, friendly relations, connection, relation, intimacy"
    },
    {
      "question": "新蕎麦",
      "answer": "しんそば,あらそば",
      "meaning": "soba made from freshly harvested buckwheat"
    },
    {
      "question": "不急",
      "answer": "ふきゅう",
      "meaning": "in no hurry, nonessential (industry)"
    },
    {
      "question": "大陸法",
      "answer": "たいりくほう",
      "meaning": "civil law, continental law"
    },
    {
      "question": "綸言",
      "answer": "りんげん",
      "meaning": "imperial words"
    },
    {
      "question": "小子",
      "answer": "しょうし",
      "meaning": "little child, male between 4 and 16 years old (ritsuryo period), pupil, disciple, follower, I, me, m"
    },
    {
      "question": "良風",
      "answer": "りょうふう",
      "meaning": "good custom"
    },
    {
      "question": "無煙炭",
      "answer": "むえんたん",
      "meaning": "anthracite, smokeless coal"
    },
    {
      "question": "細胞周期",
      "answer": "さいぼうしゅうき",
      "meaning": "cell cycle"
    },
    {
      "question": "丹塗",
      "answer": "にぬり",
      "meaning": "painting red, vermillion lacquering"
    },
    {
      "question": "納経",
      "answer": "のうきょう",
      "meaning": "presenting a hand-copied sutra to a temple (or money, etc. in its place)"
    },
    {
      "question": "七五三縄",
      "answer": "しめなわ",
      "meaning": "rope used to cordon off consecrated areas or as a talisman against evil"
    },
    {
      "question": "新書判",
      "answer": "しんしょばん",
      "meaning": "paperback pocket edition (approx. 17x11 cm)"
    },
    {
      "question": "還元糖",
      "answer": "かんげんとう",
      "meaning": "reducing sugar"
    },
    {
      "question": "綿津見",
      "answer": "かいじん,わたつみ,わだつみ",
      "meaning": "sea god, Poseidon, Neptune, sea, ocean"
    },
    {
      "question": "奨励金",
      "answer": "しょうれいきん",
      "meaning": "subsidy, incentive, bounty"
    },
    {
      "question": "共食",
      "answer": "きょうしょく",
      "meaning": "communal eating of food that has been offered to a god, sacrificial meal, eating together (with fami"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り所",
      "answer": "とりどころ",
      "meaning": "merit, worth"
    },
    {
      "question": "百行",
      "answer": "ひゃっこう",
      "meaning": "all acts"
    },
    {
      "question": "海燕",
      "answer": "うみつばめ",
      "meaning": "storm petrel (any bird of family Hydrobatidae)"
    },
    {
      "question": "熊掌",
      "answer": "ゆうしょう",
      "meaning": "bear's palm (meat treasured in Ancient China)"
    },
    {
      "question": "世界語",
      "answer": "せかいご",
      "meaning": "international language, world language, global lingua franca, constructed international auxiliary la"
    },
    {
      "question": "乾式",
      "answer": "かんしき",
      "meaning": "dry process"
    },
    {
      "question": "学術用語",
      "answer": "がくじゅつようご",
      "meaning": "technical term"
    },
    {
      "question": "蘇婆訶",
      "answer": "そわか,そばか",
      "meaning": "svāhā, well said, so be it"
    },
    {
      "question": "霊猫",
      "answer": "れいびょう",
      "meaning": "civet cat"
    },
    {
      "question": "小知",
      "answer": "しょうち",
      "meaning": "superficial knowledge, shallow wisdom, small fief"
    },
    {
      "question": "瓊矛",
      "answer": "ぬほこ",
      "meaning": "jeweled spear (jewelled)"
    },
    {
      "question": "切刃",
      "answer": "せっぱ",
      "meaning": "thin washer on either side of the guard (tsuba) of a sword, (up to) the hilt, wits' end"
    },
    {
      "question": "木舞",
      "answer": "こまい",
      "meaning": "laths, bamboo lathing"
    },
    {
      "question": "実験科学",
      "answer": "じっけんかがく",
      "meaning": "empirical science"
    },
    {
      "question": "公知",
      "answer": "こうち",
      "meaning": "well-known"
    },
    {
      "question": "柳暗花明",
      "answer": "りゅうあんかめい",
      "meaning": "beautiful scenery of spring, red-light district"
    },
    {
      "question": "平家造り",
      "answer": "ひらやづくり",
      "meaning": "single story house"
    },
    {
      "question": "花曇",
      "answer": "はなぐもり",
      "meaning": "hazy weather in spring"
    },
    {
      "question": "電気伝導",
      "answer": "でんきでんどう",
      "meaning": "electrical conduction"
    },
    {
      "question": "無教育",
      "answer": "むきょういく",
      "meaning": "uneducated"
    },
    {
      "question": "月光菩薩",
      "answer": "がっこうぼさつ",
      "meaning": "Candraprabha (bodhisattva)"
    },
    {
      "question": "所思",
      "answer": "しょし",
      "meaning": "thoughts, opinions"
    },
    {
      "question": "火脚",
      "answer": "ひあし",
      "meaning": "spreading of a fire"
    },
    {
      "question": "履行不能",
      "answer": "りこうふのう",
      "meaning": "unenforceability, impossibility of performance"
    },
    {
      "question": "変域",
      "answer": "へんいき",
      "meaning": "domain, range"
    },
    {
      "question": "運動具",
      "answer": "うんどうぐ",
      "meaning": "sporting goods"
    },
    {
      "question": "全音",
      "answer": "ぜんおん",
      "meaning": "whole tone"
    },
    {
      "question": "過飽和",
      "answer": "かほうわ",
      "meaning": "supersaturation"
    },
    {
      "question": "入れ代る",
      "answer": "いれかわる",
      "meaning": "to change places, to relieve one another, to replace someone"
    },
    {
      "question": "淫風",
      "answer": "いんぷう",
      "meaning": "lewd manners, immorality"
    },
    {
      "question": "急設",
      "answer": "きゅうせつ",
      "meaning": "hurried construction, speedy laying"
    },
    {
      "question": "大和絵",
      "answer": "やまとえ",
      "meaning": "Yamato-e (classical Japan decorative paintings)"
    },
    {
      "question": "造木",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "獄囚",
      "answer": "ごくしゅう",
      "meaning": "prisoner"
    },
    {
      "question": "神璽",
      "answer": "しんじ",
      "meaning": "Imperial regalia (esp. the jewel Yasakani no Magatama), emperor's seal"
    },
    {
      "question": "善根",
      "answer": "ぜんこん",
      "meaning": "good deeds, charity"
    },
    {
      "question": "後周",
      "answer": "こうしゅう,ごしゅう",
      "meaning": "Later Zhou dynasty (China, 951-960), Later Chou dynasty"
    },
    {
      "question": "私製",
      "answer": "しせい",
      "meaning": "privately-made (esp. postcard, mailing card, etc.), commercially-made, non-government, unofficial"
    },
    {
      "question": "仲秋",
      "answer": "ちゅうしゅう,ちゅうじゅう,なかあき",
      "meaning": "15th day of the 8th lunar month, eighth month of the lunar calendar"
    },
    {
      "question": "按ずる",
      "answer": "あんずる",
      "meaning": "to investigate, to consider, to plan, to pat, to rub, to take a sword in one's hand"
    },
    {
      "question": "此の手",
      "answer": "このて",
      "meaning": "this way (of doing), this method, this sort (of thing), this type"
    },
    {
      "question": "俚諺",
      "answer": "りげん",
      "meaning": "proverb, saying"
    },
    {
      "question": "出御",
      "answer": "しゅつぎょ",
      "meaning": "emperor's arrival (at his office, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "板門店",
      "answer": "パンムンジョム,はんもんてん",
      "meaning": "Panmunjon (Korea), Joint Security Area (Korean Demilitarized Zone)"
    },
    {
      "question": "凸面",
      "answer": "とつめん",
      "meaning": "convex surface, convex"
    },
    {
      "question": "総目録",
      "answer": "そうもくろく",
      "meaning": "index"
    },
    {
      "question": "慷慨",
      "answer": "こうがい",
      "meaning": "righteous indignation, patriotic lamentation, deploration"
    },
    {
      "question": "甲状腺腫",
      "answer": "こうじょうせんしゅ",
      "meaning": "goiter, goitre"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉄傘",
      "answer": "てっさん",
      "meaning": "steel or iron dome"
    },
    {
      "question": "一荒れ",
      "answer": "ひとあれ",
      "meaning": "squall, burst of anger"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉄敷",
      "answer": "かなしき",
      "meaning": "anvil"
    },
    {
      "question": "産業政策",
      "answer": "さんぎょうせいさく",
      "meaning": "industrial policy"
    },
    {
      "question": "動滑車",
      "answer": "どうかっしゃ",
      "meaning": "movable pulley"
    },
    {
      "question": "杏林",
      "answer": "きょうりん",
      "meaning": "apricot grove"
    },
    {
      "question": "御領",
      "answer": "ごりょう",
      "meaning": "land under the control of the imperial household or the shogunate"
    },
    {
      "question": "印面",
      "answer": "いんめん",
      "meaning": "face of a seal"
    },
    {
      "question": "地目",
      "answer": "ちもく",
      "meaning": "land classification"
    },
    {
      "question": "衝天",
      "answer": "しょうてん",
      "meaning": "(being in) high spirits"
    },
    {
      "question": "成田屋",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "怏々",
      "answer": "おうおう",
      "meaning": "discontented, unhappy"
    },
    {
      "question": "金繰り",
      "answer": "かねぐり",
      "meaning": "financing, raising funds"
    },
    {
      "question": "譲り渡し",
      "answer": "ゆずりわたし",
      "meaning": "transfer, assignment, conveyance"
    },
    {
      "question": "岩松",
      "answer": "いわまつ,がんしょう",
      "meaning": "Selaginella tamariscina (species of spikemoss), pine tree growing on a rock"
    },
    {
      "question": "御疲れ様",
      "answer": "おつかれさま",
      "meaning": "thank you, many thanks, much appreciated, that's enough for today"
    },
    {
      "question": "日本脳炎",
      "answer": "にほんのうえん",
      "meaning": "Japanese encephalitis"
    },
    {
      "question": "霜害",
      "answer": "そうがい",
      "meaning": "frost damage"
    },
    {
      "question": "暑中",
      "answer": "しょちゅう",
      "meaning": "height of summer, high summer, hottest part of the summer"
    },
    {
      "question": "施政方針",
      "answer": "しせいほうしん",
      "meaning": "administrative policy"
    },
    {
      "question": "頓首",
      "answer": "とんしゅ,とんじゅ",
      "meaning": "respectfully yours, kowtowing, kowtow"
    },
    {
      "question": "弓張り月",
      "answer": "ゆみはりづき",
      "meaning": "crescent moon"
    },
    {
      "question": "佐竹義重",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "私意",
      "answer": "しい",
      "meaning": "personal opinion, selfishness"
    },
    {
      "question": "無常迅速",
      "answer": "むじょうじんそく",
      "meaning": "the (fast) pace at which life passes, and thus the nearness of death, promptitude of the changes of"
    },
    {
      "question": "化学作用",
      "answer": "かがくさよう",
      "meaning": "chemical action"
    },
    {
      "question": "銀塩",
      "answer": "ぎんえん",
      "meaning": "silver halide, silver salt"
    },
    {
      "question": "医方",
      "answer": "いほう",
      "meaning": "healing method"
    },
    {
      "question": "回り舞台",
      "answer": "まわりぶたい",
      "meaning": "revolving stage"
    },
    {
      "question": "先棒",
      "answer": "さきぼう",
      "meaning": "front palanquin bearer, flunky, cat's-paw, tool"
    },
    {
      "question": "柘",
      "answer": "はりぐわ,つみ",
      "meaning": "storehousebush (Cudrania tricuspidata), mandarin melon berry, silkworm thorn, cudrang, Chinese mulbe"
    },
    {
      "question": "冗漫",
      "answer": "じょうまん",
      "meaning": "verbosity"
    },
    {
      "question": "人才",
      "answer": "じんさい",
      "meaning": "capable person, talented person"
    },
    {
      "question": "事理",
      "answer": "じり",
      "meaning": "reason, facts, propriety, sense"
    },
    {
      "question": "相客",
      "answer": "あいきゃく",
      "meaning": "fellow guest, fellow lodger, fellow passenger"
    },
    {
      "question": "養鯉",
      "answer": "ようり",
      "meaning": "carp breeding"
    },
    {
      "question": "貨物駅",
      "answer": "かもつえき",
      "meaning": "freight depot"
    },
    {
      "question": "三国人",
      "answer": "さんごくじん,さんこくじん",
      "meaning": "national of a third country, foreigner resident in Japan (esp. Chinese and Korean)"
    },
    {
      "question": "趣意書",
      "answer": "しゅいしょ",
      "meaning": "prospectus"
    },
    {
      "question": "自今",
      "answer": "じこん",
      "meaning": "from now on, hereafter"
    },
    {
      "question": "巻き簀",
      "answer": "まきす",
      "meaning": "bamboo mat used in food preparation (esp. to roll sushi), sushi mat"
    },
    {
      "question": "上底",
      "answer": "あげぞこ,あげそこ",
      "meaning": "false bottom, fake bottom, raised bottom, platform (shoes), kick (of a bottle), exaggeration, overst"
    },
    {
      "question": "太太",
      "answer": "タイタイ",
      "meaning": "wife"
    },
    {
      "question": "押え",
      "answer": "おさえ",
      "meaning": "weight (e.g. paperweight), pressing down, keeping control, exercising authority, having self-control"
    },
    {
      "question": "塗抹",
      "answer": "とまつ",
      "meaning": "smear, daub, coating over"
    },
    {
      "question": "天理教",
      "answer": "てんりきょう",
      "meaning": "the Tenri sect"
    },
    {
      "question": "檜葉",
      "answer": "ひば",
      "meaning": "hinoki leaf, hiba false arborvitae (species of cypress, Thujopsis dolabrata), small ornamental false"
    },
    {
      "question": "豪然",
      "answer": "ごうぜん",
      "meaning": "full of strength, haughty, pompous"
    },
    {
      "question": "慶長の役",
      "answer": "けいちょうのえき",
      "meaning": "second Japanese invasion of Korea (1597), Keichō campaign (1597-98)"
    },
    {
      "question": "意気阻喪",
      "answer": "いきそそう",
      "meaning": "depressed in spirits, rejection, disheartened, lacking nerve"
    },
    {
      "question": "油圧器",
      "answer": "ゆあつき",
      "meaning": "hydraulic equipment"
    },
    {
      "question": "宿志",
      "answer": "しゅくし",
      "meaning": "longstanding desire"
    },
    {
      "question": "惟る",
      "answer": "おもいみる,おもんみる",
      "meaning": "to reflect carefully"
    },
    {
      "question": "遁辞",
      "answer": "とんじ",
      "meaning": "excuse, evasive answer, subterfuge"
    },
    {
      "question": "浮遊生物",
      "answer": "ふゆうせいぶつ",
      "meaning": "plankton"
    },
    {
      "question": "探り箸",
      "answer": "さぐりばし",
      "meaning": "using one's chopsticks to find a food one likes by rummaging in one's dish, pot, etc. (a breach of e"
    },
    {
      "question": "端武者",
      "answer": "はむしゃ",
      "meaning": "common soldier"
    },
    {
      "question": "防鳥",
      "answer": "ぼうちょう",
      "meaning": "birdproofing, protection from birds"
    },
    {
      "question": "絡繹",
      "answer": "らくえき",
      "meaning": "constant stream of traffic, incessant traffic"
    },
    {
      "question": "練り羊羹",
      "answer": "ねりようかん",
      "meaning": "neri yōkan, firm adzuki-bean jelly"
    },
    {
      "question": "追っ付く",
      "answer": "おっつく",
      "meaning": "to catch up (with), to draw level, to pull even, to reach, to be compensated, to make up for one's l"
    },
    {
      "question": "刷り物",
      "answer": "すりもの",
      "meaning": "printed matter"
    },
    {
      "question": "突先",
      "answer": "とっさき",
      "meaning": "tip"
    },
    {
      "question": "言詞",
      "answer": "げんし",
      "meaning": "words, speech, expression"
    },
    {
      "question": "河豚中毒",
      "answer": "ふぐちゅうどく",
      "meaning": "pufferfish poisoning"
    },
    {
      "question": "偕老同穴",
      "answer": "かいろうどうけつ",
      "meaning": "happy life partnership, living faithfully together till death, Venus's flower basket (Euplectella as"
    },
    {
      "question": "洗濯挟み",
      "answer": "せんたくばさみ",
      "meaning": "clothespin, clothes peg"
    },
    {
      "question": "脆化",
      "answer": "ぜいか",
      "meaning": "embrittlement"
    },
    {
      "question": "文名",
      "answer": "ぶんめい",
      "meaning": "literary fame"
    },
    {
      "question": "高麗茶碗",
      "answer": "こうらいぢゃわん",
      "meaning": "Koryo-dynasty tea bowl"
    },
    {
      "question": "門院",
      "answer": "もんいん",
      "meaning": "empress dowager"
    },
    {
      "question": "酢橘",
      "answer": "すだち",
      "meaning": "sudachi (species of Japanese citrus, Citrus sudachi)"
    },
    {
      "question": "出前持ち",
      "answer": "でまえもち",
      "meaning": "delivery person (of food)"
    },
    {
      "question": "大和芋",
      "answer": "やまといも",
      "meaning": "Chinese yam (variety of Dioscorea opposita), Japanese yam (variety of Dioscorea japonica)"
    },
    {
      "question": "経営資源",
      "answer": "けいえいしげん",
      "meaning": "management resource, management resources"
    },
    {
      "question": "農科",
      "answer": "のうか",
      "meaning": "agricultural course, agricultural department"
    },
    {
      "question": "紫微垣",
      "answer": "しびえん",
      "meaning": "Purple Forbidden Enclosure (group of constellations in the northern sky associated with the emperor)"
    },
    {
      "question": "潜熱",
      "answer": "せんねつ",
      "meaning": "latent heat"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪嶺",
      "answer": "せつれい",
      "meaning": "snow-capped peak"
    },
    {
      "question": "誦経",
      "answer": "じゅきょう,ずきょう",
      "meaning": "chanting or reading the sutras"
    },
    {
      "question": "秋場所",
      "answer": "あきばしょ",
      "meaning": "autumn (fall) (September) tournament, held in Tokyo"
    },
    {
      "question": "焉んぞ",
      "answer": "いずくんぞ",
      "meaning": "how, why"
    },
    {
      "question": "武家奉公",
      "answer": "ぶけぼうこう",
      "meaning": "service with a samurai family, serving in a samurai household (as a valet, chambermaid, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "ピコ秒",
      "answer": "ピコびょう",
      "meaning": "picosecond"
    },
    {
      "question": "烏兎",
      "answer": "うと",
      "meaning": "sun and moon, time, the years, the months"
    },
    {
      "question": "不愍",
      "answer": "ふびん",
      "meaning": "poor, pitiful, piteous, pitiable"
    },
    {
      "question": "験者",
      "answer": "けんざ,けんじゃ",
      "meaning": "mountaineering ascetic, practitioner of mountain asceticism"
    },
    {
      "question": "慮り",
      "answer": "おもんぱかり,おもんばかり",
      "meaning": "thought, consideration, fears"
    },
    {
      "question": "多極",
      "answer": "たきょく",
      "meaning": "multipolar"
    },
    {
      "question": "複勝式",
      "answer": "ふくしょうしき",
      "meaning": "place bet (in horse racing, etc.), show bet, bet that predicts a top 2 or top 3 finish (depending on"
    },
    {
      "question": "墨付き",
      "answer": "すみつき",
      "meaning": "certificate, certified document, authorization, authorisation, (the) thumbs up, seal of approval, pa"
    },
    {
      "question": "死児",
      "answer": "しじ",
      "meaning": "dead child, stillborn child"
    },
    {
      "question": "青鮫",
      "answer": "あおざめ",
      "meaning": "shortfin mako shark (Isurus oxyrinchus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "鐙革",
      "answer": "あぶみがわ",
      "meaning": "stirrup straps, stirrup leather"
    },
    {
      "question": "原注",
      "answer": "げんちゅう",
      "meaning": "the original notes"
    },
    {
      "question": "古稀",
      "answer": "こき",
      "meaning": "70th birthday, ancient Greek (language)"
    },
    {
      "question": "便衣",
      "answer": "べんい",
      "meaning": "everyday clothes (in China), ordinary clothes"
    },
    {
      "question": "圃場",
      "answer": "ほじょう",
      "meaning": "cultivated land (field, garden, orchard, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "杉戸",
      "answer": "すぎど",
      "meaning": "door made of cedar"
    },
    {
      "question": "性格俳優",
      "answer": "せいかくはいゆう",
      "meaning": "character actor, character actress"
    },
    {
      "question": "角打ち",
      "answer": "かくうち",
      "meaning": "combined liquor store and bar, combined off-license and pub (licence), drinking alcohol while standi"
    },
    {
      "question": "不軌",
      "answer": "ふき",
      "meaning": "lawlessness, violation of customs"
    },
    {
      "question": "冀う",
      "answer": "こいねがう",
      "meaning": "to beg, to request, to beseech, to implore, to entreat"
    },
    {
      "question": "摩尼",
      "answer": "まに",
      "meaning": "jewel, pearl, gemstone, Cintamani stone, wish-fulfilling jewel"
    },
    {
      "question": "乳酸発酵",
      "answer": "にゅうさんはっこう",
      "meaning": "lactic fermentation, lactic acid fermentation"
    },
    {
      "question": "劇作",
      "answer": "げきさく",
      "meaning": "play writing"
    },
    {
      "question": "吹き物",
      "answer": "ふきもの",
      "meaning": "wind instrument (esp. in gagaku)"
    },
    {
      "question": "二百十日",
      "answer": "にひゃくとおか",
      "meaning": "210th day (from the first day of spring according to the lunar calendar), the storm day"
    },
    {
      "question": "廻向",
      "answer": "えこう",
      "meaning": "memorial service, prayers for the repose of the soul, transfer of merit"
    },
    {
      "question": "面魂",
      "answer": "つらだましい",
      "meaning": "fierce or defiant look, determined expression, plucky countenance"
    },
    {
      "question": "信託会社",
      "answer": "しんたくがいしゃ",
      "meaning": "trust company"
    },
    {
      "question": "羽後",
      "answer": "うご",
      "meaning": "Ugo (former province located in parts of present-day Akita Prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "監視哨",
      "answer": "かんししょう",
      "meaning": "observation post"
    },
    {
      "question": "練絹",
      "answer": "ねりぎぬ",
      "meaning": "glossy silk cloth, degummed silk cloth"
    },
    {
      "question": "節句働き",
      "answer": "せっくばたらき",
      "meaning": "working on a day off (to make up for lost time, or to make an impression)"
    },
    {
      "question": "地蜘蛛",
      "answer": "じぐも",
      "meaning": "Atypus karschi (Asian species of mygalomorph spider)"
    },
    {
      "question": "海底谷",
      "answer": "かいていこく,かいていだに",
      "meaning": "submarine valley, submarine canyon"
    },
    {
      "question": "原板",
      "answer": "げんぱん,げんばん",
      "meaning": "negative (of a picture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "下関条約",
      "answer": "しものせきじょうやく",
      "meaning": "Treaty of Shimonoseki"
    },
    {
      "question": "断裁機",
      "answer": "だんさいき",
      "meaning": "cutting machine, paper cutter, guillotine"
    },
    {
      "question": "平均余命",
      "answer": "へいきんよめい",
      "meaning": "life expectancy"
    },
    {
      "question": "力役",
      "answer": "りきえき,りょくえき,りきやく",
      "meaning": "physical labor, physical labour, physical work, forced labor imposed by the government (e.g. under t"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜働き",
      "answer": "よばたらき",
      "meaning": "night work"
    },
    {
      "question": "万古",
      "answer": "ばんこ",
      "meaning": "perpetuity, eternity"
    },
    {
      "question": "運動失調",
      "answer": "うんどうしっちょう",
      "meaning": "ataxia, loss of coordination of the muscles, failure of muscular coordination"
    },
    {
      "question": "剽軽者",
      "answer": "ひょうきんもの",
      "meaning": "comical person"
    },
    {
      "question": "酷税",
      "answer": "こくぜい",
      "meaning": "heavy taxation"
    },
    {
      "question": "外為法",
      "answer": "がいためほう",
      "meaning": "Foreign Exchange and Foreign Trade Act"
    },
    {
      "question": "狗尾草",
      "answer": "えのころぐさ",
      "meaning": "green foxtail (Setaria viridis), green bristlegrass"
    },
    {
      "question": "付番",
      "answer": "ふばん",
      "meaning": "rank suffix"
    },
    {
      "question": "労農",
      "answer": "ろうのう",
      "meaning": "workers and farmers"
    },
    {
      "question": "提灯鮟鱇",
      "answer": "ちょうちんあんこう",
      "meaning": "football fish (any fish of family Himantolophidae, esp. the Atlantic footballfish, Himantolophus gro"
    },
    {
      "question": "一発回答",
      "answer": "いっぱつかいとう",
      "meaning": "first and final offer in labor-management negotiations"
    },
    {
      "question": "後山",
      "answer": "あとやま",
      "meaning": "pusher (in a mine)"
    },
    {
      "question": "弔慰金",
      "answer": "ちょういきん",
      "meaning": "condolence money"
    },
    {
      "question": "道破",
      "answer": "どうは",
      "meaning": "declaration"
    },
    {
      "question": "増分",
      "answer": "ぞうぶん",
      "meaning": "increment, change"
    },
    {
      "question": "被保険者",
      "answer": "ひほけんしゃ",
      "meaning": "insured person"
    },
    {
      "question": "上声",
      "answer": "じょうしょう",
      "meaning": "rising tone (in Chinese), (of a Japanese accent) having a high, flat tone"
    },
    {
      "question": "落剝",
      "answer": "らくはく",
      "meaning": "coming off, peeling off"
    },
    {
      "question": "災害補償",
      "answer": "さいがいほしょう",
      "meaning": "accident compensation"
    },
    {
      "question": "国家主義",
      "answer": "こっかしゅぎ",
      "meaning": "nationalism, statism"
    },
    {
      "question": "側臥",
      "answer": "そくが",
      "meaning": "lying down on one's side"
    },
    {
      "question": "緘黙",
      "answer": "かんもく",
      "meaning": "keeping silent"
    },
    {
      "question": "湯風呂",
      "answer": "ゆぶろ",
      "meaning": "steam bath, hot water bath"
    },
    {
      "question": "使い立て",
      "answer": "つかいだて",
      "meaning": "causing you trouble"
    },
    {
      "question": "胴乱",
      "answer": "どうらん",
      "meaning": "vasculum, case for botanical specimens, satchel, small leather bag"
    },
    {
      "question": "諸姉",
      "answer": "しょし",
      "meaning": "you (feminine plural), you ladies"
    },
    {
      "question": "銀板写真",
      "answer": "ぎんばんしゃしん",
      "meaning": "daguerreotype, daguerrotype"
    },
    {
      "question": "膠漆",
      "answer": "こうしつ",
      "meaning": "glue and lacquer, great intimacy"
    },
    {
      "question": "中底",
      "answer": "なかぞこ",
      "meaning": "insole, perforated divider in a food steamer"
    },
    {
      "question": "舷灯",
      "answer": "げんとう",
      "meaning": "running lights, sidelight, side light"
    },
    {
      "question": "読誦",
      "answer": "どくじゅ,どくしょう",
      "meaning": "reading aloud, recitation, intoning"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉄板焼",
      "answer": "てっぱんやき",
      "meaning": "teppanyaki (Japanese cooking prepared on a hot steel plate in the center of the table)"
    },
    {
      "question": "馬頭星雲",
      "answer": "ばとうせいうん",
      "meaning": "Horsehead Nebula"
    },
    {
      "question": "架電",
      "answer": "かでん",
      "meaning": "(making a) telephone call, (having a) telephone conversation, calling, dialing"
    },
    {
      "question": "各日",
      "answer": "かくじつ",
      "meaning": "each day"
    },
    {
      "question": "困り抜く",
      "answer": "こまりぬく",
      "meaning": "to be at one's wit's end, to be in great trouble, to be at a loss"
    },
    {
      "question": "立飲み",
      "answer": "たちのみ",
      "meaning": "drinking while standing"
    },
    {
      "question": "舞風",
      "answer": "まいかぜ",
      "meaning": "whirlwind"
    },
    {
      "question": "癖者",
      "answer": "くせもの",
      "meaning": "ruffian, villain, knave, thief, suspicious fellow, peculiar person, idiosyncratic person, stubborn f"
    },
    {
      "question": "探測",
      "answer": "たんそく",
      "meaning": "probing, sounding"
    },
    {
      "question": "公明党",
      "answer": "こうめいとう",
      "meaning": "Komeito (Japanese political party)"
    },
    {
      "question": "引き去る",
      "answer": "ひきさる",
      "meaning": "to retreat, to withdraw, to deduct"
    },
    {
      "question": "自転軸",
      "answer": "じてんじく",
      "meaning": "rotating shaft, axle"
    },
    {
      "question": "比価",
      "answer": "ひか",
      "meaning": "parity"
    },
    {
      "question": "筬",
      "answer": "おさ",
      "meaning": "reed (in a loom), yarn guide"
    },
    {
      "question": "抽象名詞",
      "answer": "ちゅうしょうめいし",
      "meaning": "abstract noun"
    },
    {
      "question": "南十字座",
      "answer": "みなみじゅうじざ",
      "meaning": "Crux (constellation)"
    },
    {
      "question": "京人形",
      "answer": "きょうにんぎょう",
      "meaning": "Kyoto doll"
    },
    {
      "question": "仮名手本",
      "answer": "かなでほん",
      "meaning": "Japanese kana copybook"
    },
    {
      "question": "山巓",
      "answer": "さんてん",
      "meaning": "summit (of a mountain)"
    },
    {
      "question": "珪岩",
      "answer": "けいがん",
      "meaning": "quartzite"
    },
    {
      "question": "目違い",
      "answer": "めちがい",
      "meaning": "error in judgment, error in judgement"
    },
    {
      "question": "運算",
      "answer": "うんざん",
      "meaning": "mathematical operation, calculation"
    },
    {
      "question": "急告",
      "answer": "きゅうこく",
      "meaning": "urgent notice"
    },
    {
      "question": "馬偏",
      "answer": "うまへん",
      "meaning": "kanji 'horse' radical at left"
    },
    {
      "question": "制動機",
      "answer": "せいどうき",
      "meaning": "brake"
    },
    {
      "question": "吊り棚",
      "answer": "つりだな",
      "meaning": "suspended shelf"
    },
    {
      "question": "甲子",
      "answer": "きのえね,かっし,こうし",
      "meaning": "Wood Rat (1st year of the sexagenary cycle, e.g. 1924, 1984, 2044)"
    },
    {
      "question": "不器",
      "answer": "ふき",
      "meaning": "clumsiness, unskillfulness"
    },
    {
      "question": "射倖心",
      "answer": "しゃこうしん",
      "meaning": "passion for gambling, fondness for speculation, speculative spirit"
    },
    {
      "question": "ゴム輪",
      "answer": "ゴムわ",
      "meaning": "rubber tire (tyre)"
    },
    {
      "question": "下歯",
      "answer": "したば",
      "meaning": "lower teeth"
    },
    {
      "question": "文教",
      "answer": "ぶんきょう",
      "meaning": "education, culture"
    },
    {
      "question": "黙許",
      "answer": "もっきょ",
      "meaning": "tacit permission, tacit consent, connivance"
    },
    {
      "question": "継受",
      "answer": "けいじゅ",
      "meaning": "inheritance, taking over (a business, property)"
    },
    {
      "question": "有性",
      "answer": "ゆうせい",
      "meaning": "sexual"
    },
    {
      "question": "糟糠の妻",
      "answer": "そうこうのつま",
      "meaning": "one's devoted wife, wife who has followed one through hard times, wife married in poverty"
    },
    {
      "question": "名菓",
      "answer": "めいか",
      "meaning": "excellent sweet, confection of an established name"
    },
    {
      "question": "軈て",
      "answer": "やがて",
      "meaning": "before long, soon, shortly, almost, nearly, finally, in the end, eventually"
    },
    {
      "question": "世間並",
      "answer": "せけんなみ",
      "meaning": "ordinary (esp. life or behavior), typical, conventional, standard, average"
    },
    {
      "question": "水墨",
      "answer": "すいぼく",
      "meaning": "water and ink, ink painting"
    },
    {
      "question": "地付き",
      "answer": "じつき",
      "meaning": "native"
    },
    {
      "question": "峡間",
      "answer": "きょうかん",
      "meaning": "between the mountains"
    },
    {
      "question": "立原道造",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "小夜時雨",
      "answer": "さよしぐれ",
      "meaning": "light shower on a night in late autumn and early winter"
    },
    {
      "question": "生い先",
      "answer": "おいさき",
      "meaning": "one's future"
    },
    {
      "question": "好い気",
      "answer": "いいき",
      "meaning": "easygoing, optimistic, conceited"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪眼鏡",
      "answer": "ゆきめがね",
      "meaning": "snow goggles"
    },
    {
      "question": "飾り車",
      "answer": "かざりぐるま",
      "meaning": "carriage beautifully decorated with gold, silver, gems, etc., for use by Heian era nobles at festiva"
    },
    {
      "question": "乾飯",
      "answer": "かれい,かれいい,ほしいい",
      "meaning": "dried boiled rice, dried boiled rice used mainly as provisions of samurai troops and travelers (trav"
    },
    {
      "question": "復す",
      "answer": "ふくす",
      "meaning": "to return to normal, to recover, to restore"
    },
    {
      "question": "襲い掛る",
      "answer": "おそいかかる",
      "meaning": "to rush on, to attack, to swoop down on"
    },
    {
      "question": "閾下",
      "answer": "いきか",
      "meaning": "subliminal"
    },
    {
      "question": "嘱目",
      "answer": "しょくもく",
      "meaning": "paying attention to, catching one's eye"
    }
  ]
}
